Damn it! Why? Why me?
Why is this happening to me?
Someone...
Someone help!
One day, a girl with
silver hair and green eyes
saved me from an
attacking monster.
...the best!
She claimed to be a deity of the Cthulhu Mythos, Nyarlathotep.
Feel free to
call me "Nyaruko."
Yasaka
Nyarlathotep
How can I describe her?
You could say she's a bit crazy,
or that there's
something wrong with her.
Sanity Points
I mean, really.
Do I have to take
all that sitting down?
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Now let's become the Adam
and Eve of a new generation.
T-There's a bunch
of them this time!
Don't worry!
I'll take care of this.
Take this! Space CQC
Blasphemous Grenade!
This isn't close-quarters
combat any more.
Oh, man.
How many times do I
have to go through this?
Couldn't you just follow them to
their base and get rid of them all?
You make it sound easy.
It's true that we've been one step behind them until now,
but we're about to
go on the offensive.
Huh?
I'm saying it's finally time.
Time for what?
He waits, dreaming.
Wh-What's going on?
The stars have finally aligned.
R'lyeh shall rise to the surface.
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
uu!
nya!
let's nya!
kokoro nurunuru igyou no kamigami
Strange-looking gods with hearts that go wiggle wiggle
watashi mo anata mo kowagari no monozuki
You and I both love those kinds of scary stories
katachi murumuru ikyouto nigereba
Once the pagans have been scared away
watashi to anata wa entenka de odeeto
We'll go on a date under the blazing sun
tanoshii ne yakeru zo tokeru zo
Isn't this fun? I'll burn! I'll melt!
ikimono janai
Hey, I'm not alive!
mukuro hiyahiya sore demo suki desu
My heart's cold and slimy, but you know I still love you
watashi ga ichiban hoshii no wa naisho yo
What I want most is a total secret
sugata payapaya sore de wa ikimashou
I may not be the best, but let's get going anyway!
watashi ni ichiban niau kana fujouri
What suits me best is total absurdity
kagami ni wa
They won't show up
dan dan dare na no?
Who, Who, Who is that?
utsuranai
in any mirrors
dare nanda? yada yada
Who is it? Oh my
yokubou wa kotoba ni shinakucha
You have to say exactly what you want
uu!
hora
See?
nya!
kiechau deshou
They'll disappear like that
let's nya!
taiyou nanka mabushikutte
The stupid sun is way too bright!
yami no hou ga mugen desu
The darkness is way more free!
doki doki
Thump thump!
taiyou bakka mabushikute
The sun is so very bright!
yami no hou ga
The darkness is way more free!
su
te
ki
Nyaruko!
CAOS CAOS
I wanna CAOS
I wanna chaos
moe yo konton muteki desu
Burn! Anarchy always reigns supreme!
waku waku
So exciting!
CAOS CAOS
una sera CAOS
A night of total chaos!
moeru you na
Feelings that feel like burning!
ki
mo
chi
nyande?!
Why?
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
You know what this means.
The success or failure of our plan
depends entirely on the Crawling Chaos.
No one shall touch the
Crawling Chaos except me.
Good-bye, Nyaruko
What a perfect day for a trip!
Now let's head
toward the Grand Line...
We're not going anywhere.
...and find ourselves a
pile of buried treasure!
We're not finding anything.
We'll break into the
world's most secure prison
and free our brother.
I told you we're
not saving anybody!
What is this smelly thing, anyway?
The R'lyeh express
water taxi, Dagon-kun.
Don't you think he's bellissimo cute?
You have weird taste.
Can you imagine how beautiful his girlfriend, Hydra-chan, is?
I'd rather not.
Dagon-kun will get us
to R'lyeh in no time.
R'lyeh...
That's the city from the
Cthulhu Mythos, isn't it?
What are we going to do there?
But you're the one who told me to go and crush the enemy base!
R'lyeh has an auction house for all sorts of contraband.
We can round them all
up in one fell swoop.
Who are they?
They're headed there too.
They are?
Hiya!
They're all going to R'lyeh?
Look! You can
already see it, Mahiro-san!
That's the universe's
most famous theme park,
operated by Cthulhu
Corporation, Earth R'lyehland!
Yahoo!
Look at this, Mahiro-san!
It's the third-biggest roller coaster in space, Madness Mountain!
Those are the
Leng Plateau Go-Karts!
Look, the Arkham Haunted
House only has a two-hour wait!
Wanna get in line?
Let's get in line!
I got a mask from
the mascot, Innsmouth-kun!
Adigo!
Aren't you here
to stop the auction?
Get to work.
I get the feeling that
you'd be the type of husband
who'd choose work over
his own family, Mahiro-san.
This seems to be the auction house.
You can tell?
Yeah, because my Malign
Deity Radar is going off.
That thing only works
when you want it to.
Oops.
I almost forgot.
I want you to have this.
What is it?
An engagement ring.
I was just kidding!
I didn't mean it!
It's actually like a protective charm.
A charm?
Yes.
We're heading into
the enemy's stronghold.
All I wanted was
for you to be safe.
You should've just said so
in the first place, then.
Okay.
Sigh
Let's go.
Okay.
The building didn't look
this huge from the outside.
The space in here is warped.
Oh. Well, whatever.
Mahiro-san, your tolerance is growing.
Welcome, guests of honor.
I've been waiting
for this moment.
I knew you were the
one behind everything,
Nodens!
All the players are in place.
It's time for the
dark auction to begin.
You seem quite sure of yourself.
Are you sure you
want to do that?
I'm here, you know.
I could kill you and everyone
else here in the blink of an eye.
I anticipated that you'd try to interfere, Nyarlathotep.
She will take care of you.
Cthugha!
Cthugha...
The Living Flame?
Indeed.
They're the arch-nemeses
of us Nyarlathotepians.
On top of that, it's Kuuko.
You know her?
We attended space kindergarten and elementary school together.
We've fought many battles
that words can't describe.
You can beat her, right?
Uh, well...
Hey!
I have some weaknesses
too, you know.
What're we gonna do?
She looks powerful!
Mahiro-san, watch out!
Nyarlathotep?
You shall finish this elsewhere, beyond the gazes of others.
Oh, no! I'm in...
Nodens's Dimension!
This place doubles my opponent's strength and cuts mine in half—wait!
Oh, crap! I left Mahiro-san behind!
If I don't get back to him soon,
they'll take his
virginity before I can!
I will not allow that.
Kuuko.
I will not let you leave this place.
In that case, I'll have to pull out
all the stops against you, evildoer!
My Space CQC Part 5!
My Space CQC Type 100.
Telekinetic mobile batteries.
Every bit as obnoxious
as I remember.
Nyaruko, you cannot run from me.
Lovey-dovey love!
Open fire.
Say that before
you start shooting!
Amusing.
Nyaruko, it looks like you are in a Super-Dimensional Circus.
You're the one who's
forcing me to do this!
Do you remember love?
I don't know what
you're talking about!
I've got you now!
W-What the hell
are you doing?
I thought you could only use two!
People grow every passing day.
You cheater!
Lasers with unlimited ammo
aren't even close-quarters weapons!
From Citizen Bright's
Professional Space CQC...
Wasn't that our textbook?
"Foreword."
"That which you believe is
Space CQC is Space CQC.
However, remember that
others may not agree with you."
You're right!
W-What's going on?!
Kuuko?
What are you doing?
Where do you think
you're putting your hands?
What are you doing?
Nyaruko, we're adults now.
Hold it right there!
I'm going to embrace you.
Y-You mean like, hug me?
I mean the missionary position.
We're going to do
X-rated things.
Like make babies!
How would that
last one even work?!
Nyaruko, I love you.
What?
Now that the nuisances
are out of the way,
let us resume the bidding.
Show our guests
everything you have to offer.
Y-You've got to be kidding me.
I have always loved you.
Even when we
were in kindergarten.
You're not making any sense.
I'm a Nyarlathotepian,
and you're a Cthughan.
We're sworn enemies!
My grandfather once told me,
"A Cthughan may love a Nyarlathotepian."
"That's what it means to live free."
Was that old fart a negotiator in the "City of Amnesia"?
Ye not guilty.
Yes, you are!
H-Hey, that's enough already!
Come with me, Nyaruko,
to the edges of the galaxy.
Stop!
My heart belongs to Mahiro-san!
That boy?
What is he to you?
What is he?
You could say he's bound to me by
the red tentacle of fate, my soulmate.
You love him?
Well, it was love at first sight.
Wait, what are you making me say?
I see.
I'm going to kill him.
I will char his flesh,
melt his bones,
incinerate him until not even ashes remain, and vaporize his very soul.
I will end him.
End him?
I won't let you
lay a finger on him!
Nyaruko?
I haven't even gotten serious yet and revealed my true form.
So, let me show you...
my Space CQC Enhancer!
There is but one reason
you will be defeated today.
One simple reason.
You...
pissed me off!
But why? Don't you realize
how much I love you?
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Welp, that was a pain.
If this thing really is
an engagement ring,
or a piece of paper with
"You just lost the game!" written on it,
I'm going to kick
the crap out of you!
That's...
I have arrived!
It's a PDO officer!
Run before she catches us!
Mahiro-san!
Is it still intact?
Your chastity, that is.
Is that you, Nyarlathotep?
Yes. I'm the chaos that always crawls up to you with a smile,
Nyarlathotep!
I'm going to rescue you now.
Sorry I kept you
waiting, Mahiro-san.
Uh, sure.
You wretch!
What did you do with Cthugha?
I destroyed her.
She was like one of those monsters that
doesn't even last till the opening credits!
You did what?
Seriously?
Man, I thought I'd
finally make some money.
My whole plan is ruined!
Retreat, retreat.
I really screwed this up.
Good job.
You think you can
just walk away?
What do you want
with Mahiro-san, anyway?
You're going to tell
me everything now.
Well, uh...
He's been chosen to be the
protagonist of a new TV drama.
A drama?
It's based on an Earth
comic for young girls.
It's a sparkly love-hate drama about
a pretty-boy bought by a young businessman.
You mean it's gay smut.
I thought I could
make some money
by auctioning off the
role of the protagonist.
I went through all of
that for this stupid crap?
It's not stupid!
I had a lot of good stuff planned, like putting a collar on you
and dragging you
through the park naked!
You would've been
perfect for the part!
What a shame!
Nyarlathotep.
Yes?
Destroy him.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Exterminating Last Bullet!
Well, then.
My work on Earth is done.
I see.
I took care of everyone
that posed a threat to you.
I don't really have a reason
to stay on Earth anymore.
I see.
Mahiro-san?
Nyarlat—I mean, Nyaruko.
Um...
Thanks.
You might have had
your own ulterior motives,
but you still protected me.
We only spent a
short time together,
but thanks for everything.
I'll never forget you.
Nyaruko?
Lo...
Lo?
You're in love!
You're totally in love with me!
I was just being polite.
Don't get ahead of yourself, alien.
I'm glad I was
assigned to protect you.
I had a lot of fun.
Nyaruko.
Stop.
There's no need for
you to look this way.
R'lyeh will soon sink
back into the sea,
and the Milky Way
will continue to rotate.
Our story ends here.
I have my own life,
and you have yours.
I guess... you're right.
Take care, Mahiro-san.
Good-bye.
Good-bye, Nyaruko.
I'm home.
Welcome back, Mahiro-san.
You must've had
a hard day at work.
Would you like to have me first?
Or would you rather have me?
Or perhaps you'd like... me?
All those choices are the same.
And...
what are you still doing here?!
Zigg Mack!
Nyaruko, I thought
you went home!
You disappeared!
The organization pursuing
you may have been defeated,
but other enemies
might crop up.
Our battle has only just begun!
What are you, a weekly
manga that got axed?
Making sure everything is
all right is part of my job.
I'll protect you forever.
Let's sleep in the
same bed from now on.
I want enough children
for an entire soccer team!
Would this be a real life,
"Let's Make Babies! Touch & Direct"?
Mahiro-san?
I like it rough too,
but that's going too far.
Gando Rowa!
shirokujichuu be with you
All day through, I want to be with you
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
watashi ga anata no mae
If I were to appear in front of you
arawareta nara "zutto" nan desu
Then it'll be "forever" that I'm with you
suki toka kirai da toka
"I love you" and "I hate you"
kanjou izen ni zettai desu
It's even more important than feelings like those
nijuuyo jikan ana ga aku hodo
24 hours a day, so much I could burn a hole
anata dake wo mitsumetai
I want to watch only you all the time
uchuuteki kibo no love de I want you
With all my love, as vast as the universe, I want you
soba ni iru yo shirokujichuu
soba ni iru yo  shirokujichuu
I'll be with you all day through
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
hora sunao ni natte love me do
I'll be honest with myself, so love me do
kono chikyuu de randebuu
We'll have on this planet a rendezvous
kibou datte anata to iu
My dreams will always be for you
tokimeki ni deaeta
I found my excitement in you
yakusoku da yo zutto be with you
So I'll promise I'll always be with you
Our life as newlyweds will
start in the next episode.
No, it won't.
The title is "Our—"
Is that supposed to be a
pun on H.P. Lovecraft?
And stop lying in
the episode titles!
The next episode is, "Yasaka
Mahiro just wants to live in peace."
My SAN is plummeting.