Chara-su!
Is everyone shugo-peppy today?
It's time to start Shugo Chara Party!
The next thirty minutes is chock full of shugo-cute anime!
Shugo Chara Egg!
Amulet Spade
Saho Akari
Amulet Heart
Fukumura Mizuki
Amulet Clover
Maeda Irori
Enjoy it from start to finish!
Everyone's hearts:
Unlock!
You're like a dream
yume mitai
It's like I'm dreaming
yume miteru
Whenever I start something new
atarashii koto hajimaru toki wa
I get really excited
sogoku wakuwaku shitetemo
Though I pretend like it's nothing at all
nandemonai you nakao wo shite
I've always been stubborn like that
ijippari yappari
I've always thought it'd be nice
sunao ni naretara
If I could just be honest with myself
iin dakedo natte itsumo omou yo
But it's hard, you know?
muzukashii kedo ne
I'll try working on it bit by bit
chotto zutsu ganbatte miru
It's party time!
party time
hajimaru yo
Someday I'll transform into someone brand new
daremo shiranai jibun ni naru
But for now, I want to forget everything else
ima dake wa subete wasurete
And discover all of the potential in me
ironna watashi sagashite mitai no
It's party time!
party time
hajime you
That brand new me is out there somewhere
daremo shiranai jibun ga iru
But for now, I just want to stay as I am
ima dake wa sukoshi kono mama
And find all of the things I can be
ironna watashi mitsukete mitai no
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Ran's Pressure Points?
"Ran's Pressure Points?"
Hey, people!
Feeling good?!
Today I'm!
Feeling good!
As usual!
Real good!
What's the matter?
You seem down.
We're fine.
You are just too hyper, Ran.
What? That's not true!
Come on, people, get pumped!
Go, Miki, go!
Go, Su, go!
Whoa!
What's the matter?
I'm stuck and I can't move my arm!
You just overdid it.
Just slowly relax it.
Come on, arm, you can do it!
Wait, stop moving!
Hey...
Wouldn't it be good to push
pressure points at a time like this?
Pressure points?
If I press this point, it should instantly release.
Try moving it slowly.
Wow!
She can move it again!
But...
I... can... only... move... slowly...
Oh...
Then how about here?
How do you feel?
I can't stop!
Here?
I'm jit–ter–ry.
This is strange.
Here?
In the end, she returned to how she was.
Maybe it would be best to wait for it to heal naturally.
But I can't stand waiting around!
You can do it, self!
Go, me, go!
Okay then!
In this case, we'll push all her pressure points at once!
Ready, set...
Are you better?
Will she be okay?
I'm fine!
Go, me, go!
Go, Earth, go!
See you again
Shugo Chara Encyclopedia!
Human Edition!
First up is...
Yuiki Yaya
Yuiki Yaya!
Ookiku Naare!
Yaya is the Ace's Chair of Seiyo Academy's Guardians!
Her twintails and big ribbons are lovely!
She loves cute things and sweets, and acts a bit spoiled for a fifth-grader.
Continuing, the second person is...
Mashiro Rima
Mashiro Rima!
Rima is the Guardians' Queen's Chair!
With her long, cascading locks, she's a real beauty! And she loves comedy!
She's a sixth-grader in the same class as Amu-chan.
We'll keep doing these Shugo Chara Encyclopedia introductions each week!
Look forward to it!
Shugo, shugo! Egg Battle!
Today we'll be playing a "touch and answer" character quiz!
There are a bunch of Shugo Chara figures inside this box.
Try to pick out the correct character to solve the quiz, 'kay?
Okay, here's the question:
Who is Tadase's Guardian Character?
I know!
Of course you do!
Then find him!
No, this isn't him.
Nope, not this one.
Or this one.
Nope, not him.
This one's definitely not him.
It's tough to do just by feel.
Shugo-fight, girls!
Oh, Spade, you think you got it?
Ah, the game's almost over!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
You're running out of time!
That's it!
All right, girls, answer together!
Tadase's Guardian Character is Kiseki!
Spade and Clover got it right!
Good for them!
Today's winners are Amulet Spade and Amulet Clover.
Do your best next time, too!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
A New Guardian Character?
"A New Guardian Character?"
I can't wait to meet her.
What is this new Guardian Character like?
Her face is completely white.
And so is her outfit.
She also wears a flowing skirt.
A totally white, flowing skirt, huh?
But there's this one tiny problem.
She won't laugh, no matter what we do.
So we figured we could ask you to give it a shot.
You can count on me!
I'll make her laugh, no matter what!
Ta-da!
Psych!
It's just a teruteru bouzu.
Sorry to trick you!
So your name is Teruteru Bouzu-kun!
Nice to meet you!
You've never heard of a teruteru bouzu?
I think she actually believes us!
Kusukusu, uh...
Bala-Balance!
You're right, she really doesn't laugh.
But we just explained–
All righty then!
Kusukusu, listen...
Just wait, I will make you laugh! I stake my honor on it!
Kusukusu is on fire!
Ultra-spin Bala-Balance!
Hyper-clone Bala-Balance!
Bala-Balance Rainbow Special!
Great Super–
Please forgive us!
This is all our fault!
Please listen! We're begging you!
Don't interrupt me!
I won't go home until she at least smiles, and that's that!
But it's not...
The teruteru bouzu is laughing!
Victory is mine.
Good little children should not play pranks!
We're sorry!
See you again
Coming up next is Shugo Chara Dokki Doki!
Today's episode is titled "But Why!? Rima-senpai!"
It's a story about discovering all new charms to Rima-chan.
Well then... Enjoy!
After the commercial break!
What's really important?
daiji na mono wa naani?
Well, it's white and round
maarukute shirokute
And sunny
howahowa de
And even if they don't know it,
kizukanakute mo
Everyone has one
kokoro no naka ni
In their heart
minna motterunda
The faith I have
shinjiru kimochi ga
In others is what always
senaka wo oshite kureru
Keeps me going
kitto
Guardian Eggs and X Eggs,
shugo tama mo batsu tama mo
Guardian Characters and X Characters,
shugo kyara mo batsu kyara mo
They're all precious things
zenbu daiji da mon ne
So, Open Heart, go!
dakara open heart hora
Everything'll be okay, even if you feel lost,
daijoubu mayotte mo
Because you're not alone
hitori ja nain dakara
We'll always be together
itsudemo issho dakara
And when I think of that, somehow
sou omoeba nandaka
I feel warm and fuzzy inside
genki ga waite kuru
Open Heart, go!
open heart hora
Previous Episode Digest
You can see them smiling, right?
mieru desho waratteru
The eggs are bouncing up and down
hazunderu tamagotachi
Now and forever, I'll be counting on you
korekara mo zuuuutto yoroshiku ne
Hurry up, hurry up!
W–W–Wait, wait, wait, wait!
W–What is it, why?!
Just come with me!
But Why!? Rima-senpai!"
There they go.
Oh well.
It happens all the time.
Here!
What is it?
That's it over there.
Look at all the buds that've sprouted!
It's because of all the seeds we planted before.
Plants sure are amazing.
We just planted them a little while ago and they've already sprouted!
Get bigger!
Get bigger and make pretty flowers!
Amu-senpai, what type of flowers did we plant again?
Oh, um, red ones... I think.
Completely forgotten, haven't you?
Seriously? Even though we were the ones that planted them?
And she's supposed to be a role model for Rikka.
You people are so cruel!
No matter how much of a scatterbrain Amu-chan is, she would never be so heartless!
So many buds have sprouted!
Rima-senpai, what kind of flow–
There are too many; we need to thin them out.
Thin them out?
Pull out the ones that don't look all that healthy.
Stop, please!
Why?
It's necessary.
But, but...
Maybe I'm not understanding, but can't they all grow into flowers?
Why would you pull some out?
I don't get it!
If we let them grow like this, the leaves will overlap,
and they won't be able to absorb the sun's light properly.
If that happens, the flowers won't bloom.
Thinning them out helps them all.
But... But...
Rikka, listen. I know how you feel, but Rima is–
You agree with her?!
Rikka!
What are we going to do with her?
Are you sure about this? I think she misunderstood.
It's fine. Let's continue.
That's so cruel... Pulling them out just because they aren't needed
If that happens, the flowers won't bloom.
That might be true, but still...
Ah, I just don't get it!
Athlete Hiiragi Rikka has stuck the Ultra C!
Wait, now's not the time for that!
Sheesh, I found another one.
Oh, I see.
Come over here.
It's fine, come here.
Here.
You're actually someone's heart's egg.
Did you know?
You're kind of like a tiny little bud.
But you put an X mark on yourself.
A bud, huh?
Maybe you'll be thinned out, too.
You're not needed...
So for the good of everyone...
Ah, wait!
Amu-chan!
An X Egg's here!
Rima!
Right.
It's coming this way!
Ran!
Kusukusu!
My heart:
Unlock!
Character Transformation: Clown Drop!
Character Transformation: Amulet Heart!
Juggling Party!
My juggling clubs!
Rima!
Don't worry about me, get the X Egg!
Heart Speeders!
Heart Rod!
Alright!
Home run!
Here comes the next one!
It dropped!
A fork!
Rima!
Rima-senpai!
I'm sorry, please calm down!
Amu-senpai!
This guy wants to be a baseball player, but he's not good at catching the ball.
He said he's holding everyone back.
I see, so that's why the clubs...
...turned into curve balls.
He transformed them!
Rima-senpai, let's escape!
No, I won't run away.
Why?
Could it be...
Rikka?
Rima-senpai!
The same trick won't work twice!
If you can't catch the ball now,
why not practice until you can?
You want to enjoy playing baseball with everyone, right?
You can do it if you try!
Negative Heart: Lock On!
Open Heart!
Rima-senpai!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Rima-senpai...
You were protecting those flower pots, weren't you?
She felt sorry for the buds that were thinned out, so she replanted them there.
Carefully, one by one...
...she replanted them...
...with all her heart.
Even though her hands got filthy!
Kusukusu!
Every bud has the potential to become a flower.
Don't misunderstand Rima, okay?
She's actually very kind.
I know that now!
But she's not honest with herself!
Rima-senpai, you're super amazing!
I can't drink tea like this.
I need to finish this up so I can go wash my hands.
Rima-senpai, let me help you!
Fine, get over here.
Coming!
It's time for Guardian Egg Fortune-Telling!
Choose one of the four eggs!
Which eggs will be the lucky ones?
Guardian Egg Studying Fortune!
First, for those who chose Dia's egg:
Four Shugoluck Stars! Super Lucky!
You might steal the show in class
by answering a difficult question!
Raise that hand with confidence!
You might steal the show in class by answering a difficult question!
Miki's egg gets three Shugoluck Stars.
Study in your living
room at home!
Your family might
help you out.
Study in your living room at home!
You might do better
if you change the way
you take notes! Think up
a good way of writing!
Ran's egg gets two Shugoluck Stars!
You might do better if you change the way you take notes!
Finally, for those who chose Su's egg:
Um, you get, um... one Shugoluck Star.
Being distracted by worries may
affect your ability to study.
Lucky Item: Puzzle
Being distracted by worries may affect your ability to study.
Your lucky item is a puzzle!
Aim to change your state of mind!
I love Dia!
I'm gonna do my best!
Amulet Dia Audition, Round Two!
Today they get a chance to wow us with their singing!
Give it your all, girls!
Song
Shugo Shugo!
She's so good!
How mature!
Maybe she's nervous.
Minna no Tamago
She's dressed up like Dia! How cute!
Nice rhythm!
They all did their best to show us their characters!
Next time, we'll finally choose our Dia!
Look forward to it!
Yay!
They're all so talented!
Yeah, amazing!
I'm gonna do my best so I don't lose either!
See you next week for more Shugo Chara Party!
Lock On: Open Heart!
Bye-bye!
See you next time!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti
Let's put our hands together for you, yes you
kimi ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Let's put our hands together, that's what I wanna do!
kimi ni hakushu wo okucchae!
Now put your hands together for me, yes me
boku ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Now put your hands together, it's what you should do!
boku ni hakushu wo okucchae!
When I first heard your big dream,
hajimete kiita kimi no ookina yume
It was like I was whisked away
koko ja nai dokoka ni
To another place
tobidasu tte koto nanda ne?
So, I only know a tiny sliver of this world,
so kono chikyuu no honno ichibu shika
But at least you're here to talk to me
mada shiranai tte hanasu kimi ga iru
Hey! When I saw that look, that serious attitude...
nee sono manazashi shinken na kimochi
Before I knew it, my heart
omowazu haato dokidoki
Was all aflutter. Bravo!
ugokidashita yo buraboo!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti