Chara-su!
Everyone, today we're...
Shugo Chara Egg!
Amulet Spade   Akari
Amulet Dia    Nanami
Amulet Heart   Mizuki
Amulet Clover    Irori
...shugo-shugo peppy!
It's time to start Shugo Chara Party!
Let's enjoy it together!
Everyone's hearts:
Unlock!
You're like a dream
yume mitai
It's like I'm dreaming
yume miteru
Whenever I start something new
atarashii koto hajimaru toki wa
I get really excited
sogoku wakuwaku shitetemo
Though I pretend like it's nothing at all
nandemonai you nakao wo shite
I've always been stubborn like that
ijippari yappari
I've always thought it'd be nice
sunao ni naretara
If I could just be honest with myself
iin dakedo natte itsumo omou yo
But it's hard, you know?
muzukashii kedo ne
I'll try working on it bit by bit
chotto zutsu ganbatte miru
It's party time!
party time
hajimaru yo
Someday I'll transform into someone brand new
daremo shiranai jibun ni naru
But for now, I want to forget everything else
ima dake wa subete wasurete
And discover all of the potential in me
ironna watashi sagashite mitai no
It's party time!
party time
hajime you
That brand new me is out there somewhere
daremo shiranai jibun ga iru
But for now, I just want to stay as I am
ima dake wa sukoshi kono mama
And find all of the things I can be
ironna watashi mitsukete mitai no
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Yahoo!
"Yahoo!"
I have done it! I have finally summited this mountain peak!
No more...
Desu.
Pitiful weaklings.
You're just way too into this, Kiseki.
Hmph. It's thanks to my constant drive for perfection.
It echoed off the mountain!
Let's try it ourselves!
Yahoo!
Cool!
Wow!
Hey! How dare you neglect me!
Now, now, calm down.
Why don't you try, Kiseki?
Me? Act like you commoners?
Well... Maybe just this once.
Yahoo!
Dummy!
Dummy! Dummy!
What the heck is this?
Dummy!
Love!
Villainy! So it was you!
What're you gettin' all happy about climbin' such a dinky mountain?
Dinky? This mountain is taller than yours!
"This mountain is taller than yours!"
This one's taller!
"This one's taller!"
You leave me no choice! It's an all-out offensive!
I guess there's no other way.
This mountain is taller than yours!
Damn it! El, say something!
Understood!
Love!
What have you been blabbing, anyway?
El loves the mountains.
So I'm expressing those feelings!
Love!
Victory is ours, yes.
What's this?
Love!
My feelings have gotten through to the mountain!
This is a miracle! The great power of love!
Now everyone, all together:
Love!
See you again
Shugo Character Encyclopedia!
Character Introductions!
First up is...
Souma Kuukai
Souma Kuukai!
Hanbunko no Haato
Kuukai is a former Jack's Chair of the Seiyo Academy Guardians!
He's a bright and energetic young man!
Now that he's graduated to middle school, he's like the older brother the Guardians can rely on.
Continuing with the second person...
Sanjou Kairi
Sanjou Kairi!
Kairi is a former Jack's Chair of the Guardians!
He's a very smart and mature boy.
He transferred schools after confessing to Amu-chan that he liked her.
I wonder what he's doing. I hope he's well!
We'll continue doing these Shugo Chara Encyclopedia introductions every week!
Look forward to it!
Shugo-shugo Open Heart Game!
All right! We're starting a new game today!
We'll do a quick personality quiz to help you understand who you really are!
Your hidden secrets might all be revealed!
Everyone watching at home, you play too!
So, here's the question:
Which Guardian Character would you like to Character Transform with?
Choose between these four!
Eggs, choose which one you'd like to Character Change with!
Spade, have you decided?
Ran!
Dia?
Ran.
Heart?
Miki.
Clover?
Dia.
I see.
Has everyone at home decided?
Now, we'll announce the results!
Which Guardian Character would you like to Character Transform with?
We can find out what kind of boy you'd like to go out with from your answer!
For those who chose Ran, you love sporty boys that are really active!
Am I right?
Um...
Not really.
The people who chose Miki like boys who act mature.
Do you like older guys?
I wonder...
For girls who chose Dia, you like cute guys who look like they belong in a boy band!
Am I right?
Maybe.
And you also have confidence in your own looks!
You think?
No, not at all!
And for those of you watching at home that chose Su...
You like boys that are sweet and will fawn over you!
Okay!
Today we learned that Clover
only cares about people's looks!
That's not true!
She's denying it so passionately!
That's right! What's important is what's inside their heart!
Right!
What about all you viewers at home?
Until the next Shugo-shugo Open Heart game!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Shugo Bomber Part 4
"Shugo Bomber Part 4!"
Egg Warriors! Shugo Bomber!
Shugo Base, Reborn!
Huh? Where'd the Shugo Base go?
Which means...
Shugo Bomber's finally over!
Miki!
Huh?
Dia, what's the matter?
So you're safe, Ran?
Safe?
The Shugo Base was destroyed after the X Egg Empire counterattacked.
No one knows where the
Commissioner and everyone else is.
It's still going on.
At this rate, the world will fall into the hands of evil!
We cannot allow that to happen!
That voice!
From above?!
Commissioner! You were unhurt!
Worry not!
The heart of justice will never lose!
I predicted that this day might come, so I constructed a new Shugo Base!
Shugo Base V2!
It's completely the same!
Look carefully!
V2!
In other words, it stands for version 2.
It's crucial for heroes to
power up sometime during the fight.
I figured that it was about that season.
Uh, if you say so...
Well done making it here, Commissioner.
As well as our Shugo Bomber brothers.
Miki, where have you been?
I am not Miki.
Call me Professor Miki!
Professor Miki is a scientist in the Shugo Bomber science devision!
Et tu, Miki?
Well, I kind of asked her if I could do a scientist role, so...
"Kind of?!" You're totally into it!
Professor Miki has helped Shugo Bomber power up!
Exactly!
Equip the new Shugo Bomber suits!
There's some suspicious antennae sticking out!
Yes! They are the symbol
that shows you've powered up.
You now possess a million
times the power you had before!
Ah, sometimes I even frighten myself.
Power up is completed!
But our days of battle still continue!
Onward, invincible Shugo Bomber!
Miki, you traitor!
To be continued
Coming up next is Shugo Chara Dokki Doki!
Today's episode is "That Sparkling Treasure!"
I wonder what Rikka-chan's treasure is.
What's really important?
daiji na mono wa naani?
Well, it's white and round
maarukute shirokute
And sunny
howahowa de
And even if they don't know it,
kizukanakute mo
Everyone has one
kokoro no naka ni
In their heart
minna motterunda
The faith I have
shinjiru kimochi ga
In others is what always
senaka wo oshite kureru
Keeps me going
kitto
Guardian Eggs and X Eggs,
shugo tama mo batsu tama mo
Guardian Characters and X Characters,
shugo kyara mo batsu kyara mo
They're all precious things
zenbu daiji da mon ne
So, Open Heart, go!
dakara open heart hora
Everything'll be okay, even if you feel lost,
daijoubu mayotte mo
Because you're not alone
hitori ja nain dakara
We'll always be together
itsudemo issho dakara
And when I think of that, somehow
sou omoeba nandaka
I feel warm and fuzzy inside
genki ga waite kuru
Open Heart, go!
open heart hora
Previous Episode Digest
You can see them smiling, right?
mieru desho waratteru
The eggs are bouncing up and down
hazunderu tamagotachi
Now and forever, I'll be counting on you
korekara mo zuuuutto yoroshiku ne
Have you gotten used to school?
I remember all the systems and practices of "school," yes.
I see.
Then, um... Hikaru...
I know it's late, but congratulations on starting school.
It's a fountain pen.
I finally received the order.
This is from the brand with the number one share in the world, isn't it?
Yes, and inside is the highest quality–
But I don't use a fountain pen.
So I don't need it.
I suppose that's true.
That Sparkling Treasure!
You've got to be kidding me!
It's gone! Gone! Gone!
Gone!
Where did it go?!
So, we're going to look for it.
Look for what?
My pendant! It's my treasure.
It's pink and sparkly and shaped like a flower and...
Where could it have gone?!
Is it really something that valuable?
Yeah, 'cause it's...
You look cute, Rikka. Smile for me!
Last year during the school entrance ceremony, I was kind of nervous.
I didn't know if I could make new friends.
Or if the teachers would be scary.
So then...
A present to celebrate you
entering elementary school, Rikka!
Thanks!
Wonderful! It suits you perfectly, Rikka!
I thought it might be a little
too early to give this to you, but...
But just for today, you can dress up like a big kid!
Thanks Dad, Mom!
When I wore it, I felt like everything would be okay.
That's why it's my treasure.
I've worn it ever since I transferred here.
A present from your dad, huh?
It really is something to treasure.
Right!
Okay then, we'll find it for sure!
Yeah!
Thanks!
First thing, Rikka, is for you to tell us exactly where you've been.
We'll start with the classroom, right?
Nope.
Before that...
I went to say hi to the flower beds.
It's not here.
Then I said hi to the baby chicks.
And said hi to the rabbits...
And said hi to the flowers in the Royal Garden...
I have a feeling I went somewhere else, too.
Rikka-chan...
Before you went to class...
...you went all over the place.
Quite a distance you traveled...
But I feel like I also went a bunch of other places.
There's more?
Um... Anyway!
Let's search the classroom!
I guess it's really not here.
Where did you go besides the classroom?
That's it!
Second period was arts and crafts.
Third period was music.
I cooked in the home ec classroom.
I can't find it.
Any other places you remember?
Nope!
I've never been around here before.
Huh? What's that?
This is the planetarium.
Planetarium?
You mean the place where you can see stars?
There was one of those in the school?
Awesome!
Ah, Rikka-chan!
You're not supposed to go in there!
I wanna see the stars!
I think she's lost track of her objective.
Hey!
Amu-senpai!
You're not supposed to be in here.
Ah, um... I was searching for something and just happened in here.
Searching for something?
A present?
Yeah.
So, where should we search next?
You're gonna help me search?
It's something important to you, right?
Senpai!
There's no other places?
I just can't remember.
So when you went to say hi to the flowers and birds...
Did you end up chasing something?
When I saw the flowers in the morning, there was this pretty butterfly.
And I chased it!
That's got to be it!
Good going, Amu-chan!
It seems like you've got Rikka-chan's patterns down to a science!
So after that, what happened?
I ended up in a tree.
You climbed a tree again?!
That's it!
It must have slipped off then!
Something's shining.
Where?
Wait!
Why'd a crow take it?
Crows have an instinct to collect shiny things.
Anyway, we have to go after it!
Right!
Wait!
Ran!
Let's go!
Okay, Amu-chan!
My heart:
Unlock!
Character Transformation: Amulet Heart!
Heart Speeders!
Give back Rikka's treasure!
Please, Mr. Crow!
All right!
Pom-pon Pom Special!
Rikka-chan!
Rikka!
Yay!
Are you okay?
You really overdid it there.
Sorry.
Okay, we've dried your clothes with Remake Honey, so let's get going.
Right!
This is...
It's fake!
There's no silver or platinum.
This metal thing with no value is your treasure?
Well, it's important to me no matter what you say.
That's right.
Things you receive from other people are special, no matter what they are.
Why?
Well...
Because of the feelings put into them, I suppose.
Like "Congratulations!" or "Good luck!"
Someone other than you is thinking about you.
It's pretty amazing, you know?
D–Didn't you say you didn't need it?
It's not like it'll get in my way or anything.
And I might have an opportunity to use it.
Guardian Egg Fortune Telling!
Choose one of the four eggs!
Which egg will be the lucky one?
Guardian Egg Love Fortune!
First, for the people who chose Su's egg...
Four Shugoluck Stars! Super lucky!
Go have fun in a group with your crush!
Go have fun in a group with your crush.
You might get a chance to be alone together!
The people who chose Ran's egg get three Shugoluck Stars.
You'll have a chance to
strike up a conversation
with your crush! Don't
be shy, talk cheerfully
with them.
You'll have a chance to strike up a conversation with your crush!
Be sure to act like a
girl! You might get
your crush to turn
and look at you.
The people who chose Dia's egg get two Shugoluck Stars.
Don't forget to act like a girl!
Finally, for those of you who chose Miki's egg...
Um, you get, um... one Shugoluck Star.
You might be treated coldly by
the person you have a crush on.
Lucky Item: Gloves
You might be treated coldly by the person you have a crush on.
But that just happens once in a while when they're in a bad mood.
Don't let it get to you!
Today was really fun!
See everyone for next week's Shugo Chara Party!
Lock On: Open Heart!
Bye-bye!
See you next time!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti
Let's put our hands together for you, yes you
kimi ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Let's put our hands together, that's what I wanna do!
kimi ni hakushu wo okucchae!
Now put your hands together for me, yes me
boku ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Now put your hands together, it's what you should do!
boku ni hakushu wo okucchae!
When I first heard your big dream,
hajimete kiita kimi no ookina yume
It was like I was whisked away
koko ja nai dokoka ni
To another place
tobidasu tte koto nanda ne?
So, I only know a tiny sliver of this world,
so kono chikyuu no honno ichibu shika
But at least you're here to talk to me
mada shiranai tte hanasu kimi ga iru
Hey! When I saw that look, that serious attitude...
nee sono manazashi shinken na kimochi
Before I knew it, my heart
omowazu haato dokidoki
Was all aflutter. Bravo!
ugokidashita yo buraboo!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti