Chara-su!
Hi! Is everyone shugo-peppy again today?
It's time to start Shugo Chara Party!
Shugo Chara Egg!
Amulet Spade
Saho Akari
Amulet Heart
Fukumura Mizuki
Amulet Clover
Maeda Irori
The next thirty minutes is chock full of shugo-cute anime!
It'll be the most fun you'll have all day!
Everyone's hearts:
Unlock!
You're like a dream
yume mitai
It's like I'm dreaming
yume miteru
Whenever I start something new
atarashii koto hajimaru toki wa
I get really excited
sogoku wakuwaku shitetemo
Though I pretend like it's nothing at all
nandemonai you nakao wo shite
I've always been stubborn like that
ijippari yappari
I've always thought it'd be nice
sunao ni naretara
If I could just be honest with myself
iin dakedo natte itsumo omou yo
But it's hard, you know?
muzukashii kedo ne
I'll try working on it bit by bit
chotto zutsu ganbatte miru
It's party time!
party time
hajimaru yo
Someday I'll transform into someone brand new
daremo shiranai jibun ni naru
But for now, I want to forget everything else
ima dake wa subete wasurete
And discover all of the potential in me
ironna watashi sagashite mitai no
It's party time!
party time
hajime you
That brand new me is out there somewhere
daremo shiranai jibun ga iru
But for now, I just want to stay as I am
ima dake wa sukoshi kono mama
And find all of the things I can be
ironna watashi mitsukete mitai no
Hiyas, my little Eggs!
Which anime's up first on Shugo Chara Party today?
The one starring the Guardian Characters!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Those Guardian Characters sure are...
...shugo-cute!
Yep! And Ran, Miki, and Su are at it again!
Check it out!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Kiseki's Crown
"Kiseki's Crown!"
My... My crown has disappeared!
How could I have allowed my crown to be filched?!
My, my...
So someone stole it?
Yes! I suspect someone must have coveted my glorious, shining crown.
I kind of doubt that.
I certainly am not interested in it.
Now that I look at him, something definitely feels off.
He's barely half a king now.
He looks a bit silly.
I know! Let's make him a new crown!
Ooh, that sounds fun!
I would be pleased to help out!
Gotta make it gorgeous, right?
Gorgeous is great, but it lacks a kingly quality.
Then how about this one?
Way too normal.
It may look normal on the outside, but it has many hidden features.
Like a fan to cool you down.
A back scratcher for those hard to reach places.
And cold beverages for when you're parched!
I–It's too heavy!
And what of a king's dignity?
None of you get it, do you?
A majestic, dignified crown looks something like this!
Splendid! With this new crown on my head, the masses will prostrate themselves before me!
But something's still off.
I've got it! Your western-style outfit doesn't match.
That's true.
All right, people, it's makeover time!
Yeah!
What are you–
C–Cool, isn't it?
Y–Yeah!
D–Desu!
You really think so?
Kiseki-tan!
You dropped your crown back...
Lame-dechu.
You rascals!
Halt! Do not flee!
I can't make it stop!
See you again
Shugo Chara Encyclopedia!
The first Character we'll introduce is...
Rhythm
Rhythm!
Dream-chasing Racer
Rhythm is Nagihiko's Guardian Character, who's the Jack's Chair. He dresses like a rapper.
His "just do it" attitude makes him a pretty impulsive guy.
He was born from something lacking in Nagihiko's overly prudent nature.
He's always so full of energy!
Continuing on, the second Character is...
Temari
Temari!
She's Nadeshiko's Guardian Character, who used to be the Queen's Chair. She wears a long-sleeved kimono.
She's always so ladylike!
But she's pretty scary when she snaps.
Though Amu-chan hasn't realized it yet, Nadeshiko and Nagihiko are actually the same person.
But you all knew that already!
We'll keep doing these Shugo Chara Encyclopedia introductions each week!
Look forward to it!
Shugo, shugo! Egg Battle!
Today we'll play the shugoi "Chopsticks Master!" quiz game!
Once you've solved the quiz, use your chopsticks to transfer the eggs!
When you're done with that, you can answer the question!
Okay, here's the question:
Who was Amu-chan's third Guardian Character to be born?
I know!
Good luck, girls!
Are you good with chopsticks?
Heart's left-handed, huh?
Oh, Spade's got one!
Clover got one, too!
All three of you are doin' great!
Oh no, it slipped!
Go pick it up!
Who will survive this three-person battle?
It's so close!
And now Heart has three finished!
One more to go!
I got it! I'm done!
Okay, Heart, what's the answer?
Su!
Correct! Su was Amu-chan's third Guardian Character to be born!
Today's winner was Amulet Heart!
Do your best next week!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Shugo Bomber Part 2
"Shugo Bomber Part 2!"
Egg Warriors: Shugo Bomber!
The secret to Bomber Robo 421 is now unveiled!
Why are you holding that, Dia?
You know, I can't believe we're actually continuing this.
Bombger!
She's back.
Must we do this, Su?
Do not call me Su! I am the Commissioner!
Look, I understand that you want to help us power-up so we can combat the X Eggs, but...
These outfits are kind of...
So, what's on the agenda today?
Bombger!
What's that?
A catchphrase I created!
By combining the "bomber" in Shugo Bomber with the word "roger" in English, you get "bombger!"
For example: "Move out, Shugo Bomber!"
"Bombger!"
You can use it like that.
That's perfect!
Of course! And I'll gather more research material each week!
Hero
Encyclopedia
All About Heroes
Uh, there is seriously something wrong with you.
To answer your question, today we'll practice using "bombger!"
No way! It's so lame!
I'll never say something like that, ever.
But I've... I've been wracking my brain to help us all.
I'm simply trying to do my very best!
I watched from inside my egg as she built this secret base all by herself.
She only watched?
So she didn't help at all?
Dia!
Commissioner!
Bombger!
Sorry, I guess I went too far.
You've really done a lot for us, I guess.
So will you say "bombger" for me?
Will you say it?!
Okay everyone, all together now!
Bombger!
B–Bombger.
B–Bombger!
And thus, the bonds between the allies were fortified!
But the evil ambitions of the X Egg Empire continue unabated!
Ever vigilant, Shugo Bomber must stand!
Fight, Shugo Bomber!
To Be Continued
There's gonna be more?!
Bombger!
See you again
Coming up next is Shugo Chara!!! Dokki Doki!
Today's episode is titled "Hikaru vs Bunny? The Difficult First Job!"
So it's about Hikaru and a bunny?
And they're going to fight?
What's really important?
daiji na mono wa naani?
Well, it's white and round
maarukute shirokute
And sunny
howahowa de
And even if they don't know it,
kizukanakute mo
Everyone has one
kokoro no naka ni
In their heart
minna motterunda
The faith I have
shinjiru kimochi ga
In others is what always
senaka wo oshite kureru
Keeps me going
kitto
Guardian Eggs and X Eggs,
shugo tama mo batsu tama mo
Guardian Characters and X Characters,
shugo kyara mo batsu kyara mo
They're all precious things
zenbu daiji da mon ne
So, Open Heart, go!
dakara open heart hora
Everything'll be okay, even if you feel lost,
daijoubu mayotte mo
Because you're not alone
hitori ja nain dakara
We'll always be together
itsudemo issho dakara
And when I think of that, somehow
sou omoeba nandaka
I feel warm and fuzzy inside
genki ga waite kuru
Open Heart, go!
open heart hora
Previous Episode Digest
You can see them smiling, right?
mieru desho waratteru
The eggs are bouncing up and down
hazunderu tamagotachi
Now and forever, I'll be counting on you
korekara mo zuuuutto yoroshiku ne
Taking care of animals?
There's a vacancy on the animal committee, so we have to find a replacement.
And you want me to?
This sort of thing is also part of a Guardian's job.
It's like you're hired help.
I guess it seems that way...
But taking care of animals is a fun job.
You think?
Yes.
Although it can be difficult, too.
Hey, what are your favorite animals, Hikaru-kun?
My favorites?
Pork, beef, and poultry. Those are the only ones I've eaten.
E–Eaten,  huh?
Come on, haven't you ever thought dogs and cats were cute?
No.
I'm sure you'll come to think of the animals you'll be looking after as cute.
Hikaru vs Bunny?
The Difficult First Job!
This is the little guy you'll be taking care of.
So cute!
This is...
Phylum Chordata, Subphylum Vertebrata, Class Mammalia.
Order Lagomorpha, Family Leporidae.
You can just call it a rabbit, you know.
First, you've gotta feed it!
Wait... What do rabbits eat?
You don't know?
N–No... It's not like I have one.
Rabbits eat grass and you can also give them pellets.
You should also supplement their diet with vegetables.
Hikaru-kun's so knowledgeable!
Unlike Amu-chan.
Let's try giving it some food!
Don't worry, it's tame.
Are you okay?
Liar.
It's violent.
T–That's not true!
Rabbits are timid, so they're wary of strangers.
It'll get used to you as you earn its trust.
Next is cleaning the cage!
Leave the cleaning to me!
All right.
You there, Red, clean up the droppings.
Blue, give it fresh water.
Why me?!
Yellow, put the rabbit in that cage over there.
You told me to leave it to you guys.
You know, Hikaru-kun...
This is your job.
To hold a rabbit, grab the scruff of its neck,
and hold it close against your stomach.
Wait!
This is annoying.
Taking care of animals isn't fun at all.
It'll happen, little by little.
Just try to find the fun in it as you go.
I finally caught it!
All clean!
The rabbit looks glad, too.
What wrong? Is it hungry?
It wants to play with you, Hikaru-kun!
And it wants you to hold it!
Rabbits need exercise.
If possible, they should be walked daily.
Hey, wait!
Don't go into the flower beds!
Hey, you!
Don't trample the flowers!
Sorry... and thanks.
You're workin' hard, huh?
I'm only doing it because it's part of my job.
You're so not cute!
Working by yourself? That's not fair.
I'm really good with animals!
You have pets?
Pets?
Would those be considered pets?
Wait, are they even alive?
I've got to get back now.
Let's go.
Huh?
It looks kinda sick.
What's the matter?
Rabbits do not eat much, but may occasionally ingest things they should not.
Maybe it ate some of the flowers earlier?
It says its tummy hurts.
What should we do?
I don't believe the flowers are particularly toxic.
With enough rest–
I know!
Let's get medicine from the nurse's office!
Human medicine is no good!
Shall I cook some porridge?
Rabbits can't eat rice!
What about eggnog?
Definitely not!
At times like this...
Ah, that's it!
Rikka-chan?
When I was a little girl...
Whenever I had a bad fever, my mom would stroke my back like this.
And it'd make me feel better.
My mom's warm hand felt so nice.
Hikaru-kun's parents...
...died in an accident.
Porridge might not work, but something soft would be fine.
We'll puree its food so it can drink it.
Yeah! Let's try that!
That's good, it took it!
Yeah.
Keep it up! You're like this bunny's mom now, got it?
Its mother?
Hikaru-sama, it's time to go home.
Please get in.
I'm not going home.
I'm staying here.
Now, we can't have that.
It's time for students to go home.
You have to follow the rules, you know.
But what about my job of taking care of the animals?
I can't let you stay here overnight.
And I've arranged for a vet to look after him.
Don't worry.
Why do people desire and adore these troublesome, annoying things?
Quite the mystery, isn't it?
It takes a lot of work to care for such tiny creatures.
It's irrational.
It is.
But you can't help but fall in love with them.
And those little ones have a strength of their own.
Dogs, cats, rabbits, and even human children.
I think you know that quite well.
So don't fret.
All right!
Hikaru-kun! Rikka!
The rabbit's all better!
Thank heavens!
What is it, Hikaru-kun?
Do you feel okay?
I'm fine... Though I feel a bit strange.
There's this warmth in my chest.
Why is that?
Maybe it's that you've grown to love the rabbit.
It's time for Guardian Egg Fortune-Telling!
Choose one of the four eggs!
Which egg is the lucky one?
Guardian Egg Friendship Fortune!
First, for those who chose Su:
You get four Shugoluck Stars! Super Lucky!
You're going to have a really fun week!
Coordinate accessories with your friends
and you'll be luckier than ever!
Coordinate accessories with your friends and you'll be luckier than ever!
Dia's egg gets three Shugoluck Stars!
You'll get an encouraging
message from a friend!
Don't forget to
check your mail!
You'll get an encouraging message from a friend!
If you play video games
with your friends, you'll
get along better! Beating
games is easy when you
work together!
Ran's egg gets two Shugoluck Stars!
If you play video games with your friends, you'll get along better!
Finally, for those who chose Miki's egg:
Um, you get, um... one Shugoluck Star.
You might accidentally hurt a friend
because of something you say.
Lucky Item: Character Sticker
You might accidentally hurt a friend because of something you say.
Be careful!
Your lucky item is a character sticker!
Apologize before it turns into a disagreement!
Shugo Chara Egg! Amulet Dia Audition Report!
Thank you so much for all your applications to be the fourth member of Shugo Chara Egg!
Look at how many we got from all over Japan!
Next time, we'll fill you all in on the judging process!
Look forward to it, 'kay?
Yay!
I want to meet Dia soon!
I wonder who'll be picked.
Be who you want to be, and do your best!
See you next week for another episode of Shugo Chara Party!
Lock On: Open Heart!
Bye-bye!
See you next time!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti
Let's put our hands together for you, yes you
kimi ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Let's put our hands together, that's what I wanna do!
kimi ni hakushu wo okucchae!
Now put your hands together for me, yes me
boku ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Now put your hands together, it's what you should do!
boku ni hakushu wo okucchae!
When I first heard your big dream,
hajimete kiita kimi no ookina yume
It was like I was whisked away
koko ja nai dokoka ni
To another place
tobidasu tte koto nanda ne?
So, I only know a tiny sliver of this world,
so kono chikyuu no honno ichibu shika
But at least you're here to talk to me
mada shiranai tte hanasu kimi ga iru
Hey! When I saw that look, that serious attitude...
nee sono manazashi shinken na kimochi
Before I knew it, my heart
omowazu haato dokidoki
Was all aflutter. Bravo!
ugokidashita yo buraboo!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti