Chara-su!
Is everyone shugo-peppy today?
It's time to start Shugo Chara Party!
Shugo Chara Egg!
Amulet Spade
Saho Akari
Amulet Heart
Fukumura Mizuki
Amulet Clover
Maeda Irori
The next thirty minutes is chock full of shugo-cute anime!
We hope you enjoy them!
Everyone's hearts:
Unlock!
You're like a dream
yume mitai
It's like I'm dreaming
yume miteru
Whenever I start something new
atarashii koto hajimaru toki wa
I get really excited
sogoku wakuwaku shitetemo
Though I pretend like it's nothing at all
nandemonai you nakao wo shite
I've always been stubborn like that
ijippari yappari
I've always thought it'd be nice
sunao ni naretara
If I could just be honest with myself
iin dakedo natte itsumo omou yo
But it's hard, you know?
muzukashii kedo ne
I'll try working on it bit by bit
chotto zutsu ganbatte miru
It's party time!
party time
hajimaru yo
Someday I'll transform into someone brand new
daremo shiranai jibun ni naru
But for now, I want to forget everything else
ima dake wa subete wasurete
And discover all of the potential in me
ironna watashi sagashite mitai no
It's party time!
party time
hajime you
That brand new me is out there somewhere
daremo shiranai jibun ga iru
But for now, I just want to stay as I am
ima dake wa sukoshi kono mama
And find all of the things I can be
ironna watashi mitsukete mitai no
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Yoru's Pranks
"Yoru's Pranks."
Oh, you showed up-nya!
What did you want of me?
I daresay you have something afoot.
What is this chair?
Just a gift to make up for teasing you all the time-nya.
Yoru, I misjudged you!
It seems you have had a change of heart.
Well, just have a seat-nya.
Indeed. Then, if you don't mind...
Oh! It is soft and cushiony; it makes me feel like I could sit in it forever!
This is indeed a chair fit for a king!
I'm glad you like it-nya.
Well, later-nya!
Yes! You have my thanks!
I must show myself sitting in this chair to the others.
Okay, I shall call someone–
What is this trickery?!
Rubber Glue
Huh? The paint isn't coming out.
Paint
Go, go, go, Shugo Bomber–
Someone put paint on my cleaning cloth!
Paint
I got you all big time-nya!
You knave!
Come back here!
Wait!
If you put it that way...
...I'd better skedaddle-nya!
Come and chase me!
I can feel his presence around here.
We search!
Yeah!
Where is he hiding?
Right here-nya!
Hey you!
Wait!
No! My egg!
That's because you played all those pranks.
Serves you right.
I feel sorry for him. Let's fix it.
Yes, let's.
Rejoice, for we have repaired it!
We spiffed it up a bit, though.
Th–Thank you-nya.
It is good you accept our kindness.
How'd it turn out like this-nya?!
See you again
Shugo Chara Encyclopedia!
Character Introductions!
The first person we'll introduce today is...
Fujisaki Nagihiko
Fujisaki Nagihiko!
Hana Tegami
Nagihiko is the Jack's Chair of the Seiyo Academy Guardians!
He's a beautiful boy with silky long hair!
He's kind, and always gives advice to Amu-chan and the others whenever they are worried about something.
He's also really good at basketball.
Continuing with the second person...
Fujisaki Nadeshiko!
Fujisaki Nadeshiko
Nadeshiko is the former Queen's Chair in the Guardians.
She had gone to study abroad in Europe to further her skills in traditional Japanese dance.
Nadeshiko is actually Nagihiko, but Amu-chan doesn't know this yet.
She thinks Nadeshiko and Nagihiko are twins.
We'll continue doing these Shugo Chara Encyclopedia introductions every week!
Look forward to it!
Shugo Shugo Egg Battle!
Today we're going to announce the results!
Okay, my little eggs, you've done eight Egg Battles up until now.
Good job!
Yay!
We did our best!
And so, I'll announce the overall results!
Okay!
Amulet Clover won the first and last battle...
You got three points!
Yay!
Amulet Spade, who won every touch and feel battle...
You got four points!
And Amulet Heart, the chopsticks wizard south-paw...
You got five points!
Hooray!
Yay!
And so, the grand winner is...
Amulet Heart!
Hooray!
Yay!
In honor of your victory, we present to you a special Shugo Chara Cake!
It looks delicious!
You're so lucky!
We'll start new games next week!
I want some...
Hey, hey! Are you listening?
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
The Ghost of the Royal Garden
"The Ghost of the Royal Garden."
A mysterious hole of horror that appeared at some point in the Royal Garden...
Night after night, from within this hole, can be heard a sobbing voice.
I–I'm scared!
Maybe there's a ghost?
In order to find out, I have gathered you all here.
W–We're going inside?
What if a ghost appears?
Don't be silly. There's no such thing as ghosts.
There is!
I've heard Mr. Ghost's sobbing!
Me, too!
Sob, sob...
A crying voice, as sad and cold as ice itself.
I said there's no such thing as ghosts!
If you want, I'll go exorcise it!
Really?
Sure thing. If it really exists, that is.
And so...
Why am I in front?
You're the one that doesn't believe in ghosts!
If you don't believe in them, then you shouldn't be scared!
Of c–course I'm not scared!
Wait!
Can't you hear something?
I can hear a voice!
Desu!
I–It's just the wind.
There's no such thing as...
I can hear something!
Desu!
It's a crying voice, cold as ice!
Miki, check it out!
Why me?
You said you weren't scared!
It sounds like it's coming from in here.
That's Mr. Ghost's house!
Miki, exorcise it!
Evil spirits, begone!
There's no such thing...
...as ghosts!
A ghost!
What's the matter, everybody?
So it was you, El?
Did you run away from home again?
Il always teases me!
I'm never going home again!
See you again
Coming up next is Shugo Chara Dokki Doki!
This week's episode is "What!? Tadase-kun Has a Crush!?"
Amu-chan is heartbroken?
No way!
It couldn't be!
You can do it, Amu-chan!
What's really important?
daiji na mono wa naani?
Well, it's white and round
maarukute shirokute
And sunny
howahowa de
And even if they don't know it,
kizukanakute mo
Everyone has one
kokoro no naka ni
In their heart
minna motterunda
The faith I have
shinjiru kimochi ga
In others is what always
senaka wo oshite kureru
Keeps me going
kitto
Guardian Eggs and X Eggs,
shugo tama mo batsu tama mo
Guardian Characters and X Characters,
shugo kyara mo batsu kyara mo
They're all precious things
zenbu daiji da mon ne
So, Open Heart, go!
dakara open heart hora
Everything'll be okay, even if you feel lost,
daijoubu mayotte mo
Because you're not alone
hitori ja nain dakara
We'll always be together
itsudemo issho dakara
And when I think of that, somehow
sou omoeba nandaka
I feel warm and fuzzy inside
genki ga waite kuru
Open Heart, go!
open heart hora
Previous Episode Digest
You can see them smiling, right?
mieru desho waratteru
The eggs are bouncing up and down
hazunderu tamagotachi
Now and forever, I'll be counting on you
korekara mo zuuuutto yoroshiku ne
Huh?
It's Tadase-kun and Kuukai.
Well, look at that.
Looks like they're having a
serious discussion about something.
Let's listen in.
Hey, eavesdropping isn't–
Maybe they're talking about love!
Love! This could be a big scoop!
Ah, wait!
They're hopeless.
I'll bring them back.
It's not that I'm interested or anything.
Really.
Dia... You too?
Love?
Ah, I see.
But in the end, it's up to your own feelings.
Yeah...
Let's go.
She's really cute.
When I think about her, I can't sleep at night.
Then take the plunge!
I can't!
You can't just give up before saying anything to her!
If you show her how passionate you are about this, I'm sure she'll say okay!
Maybe...
I'll help you out, too.
Thank you.
You're really the one to talk to
about these things, Souma-kun.
Got that right!
Just leave this kind of advice to me.
Amu-chan!
Get a hold of yourself!
What!? Tadase-kun Has a Crush!?
Stay strong!
Amu-chan, get a grip!
She's acting weird.
Yeah, I wonder what happened.
Who could it be?
Who could what be?
You know who we're talking about.
The cute girl Tadase-kun was talking about.
Wh–Why should I care?
My poor Amu-chan, having her heart broken so young...
Don't, Su!
No matter how obvious it is,
it is just too sad to say it aloud!
That's right!
We have to wait to console her until after Tadase-kun dumps her definitively!
What?! I don't need any of your consoling, thank you very much.
So you don't care if Tadase-kun has another girl he likes?
It's fine!
That's right, see if I care!
Doesn't have anything to do with me!
How brave of you, Amu-chan!
I cannot comprehend her actions.
Yo!
I came over to hang out!
Could you be the former Jack, Kuukai-senpai?
I heard about you from Yaya-senpai!
The upperclassman with all
the free time who always stops by.
Damn you, Yaya!
It's not just 'cause he's free.
He gives us advice on all kinds of things.
That's right!
Like today, I advised Tadase-kun about this cute little thing.
Suppose so...
Amu-chan!
Don't console yourself with food!
I'm not! These snacks are just so tasty!
Amu-chan...
She must be in total shock.
Now that I think about it, I wonder what type of girl it is that Tadase-kun likes.
I know it might...
...not be of any use...
...but we have to find out!
Amu-chan, let's go find out!
Man, these snacks are yummy!
She's out of it.
Yay, snacks!
It's no use. Let's just go ourselves.
Right!
Who is this girl?
She's really cute.
Tadase-kun really has...
...another girl he likes.
What is it, citizens?
Have you come for a visit?
I apologize, but we already have a–
How could you?!
Desu!
Wh–What?
Why are they angry?
Tadase-kun?
Hello?
Bonsoir.
Huh? Who is this?
Always with the cold shoulder...
Have you forgotten my voice already?
Ikuto?!
Correct.
It's been a while-nya!
Are you doing well?
Sure. Well...
Well what?
Tadase dump you or something?
Hit the mark
Seriously?
I–It seems he found a girl he likes or something.
He said she was really cute!
I'd console you if I was there.
Huh?
I'd kiss you, hug you, and everything else.
You blushed just now, didn't you?
What are you saying, you pervert?!
Why did you call me, anyway?
Later.
H–Hey!
What is with him!
Amu-chan!
It's true! There was a girl at Tadase-kun's house!
Enough, I don't understand this at all!
Amu-chan, are you sure
about asking Tadase-kun directly?
Yeah!
It's stupid to just think it over and over!
That's true. There's no point in postponing the sad truth.
We'll throw you a party to
cheer you up when we get home!
I'll bake you a heartbreak cake.
You guys!
Amu-chan!
What are you doing?
You went home yesterday all of a sudden, is something wrong?
Now that it's come to it... I'm scared.
Souma-kun was worried as well.
Uh, um...
Tadase, I sense an X Egg!
Hikaru, go get Amu-senpai and the others!
Why don't you go yourself?
Say what?!
I'm older than you, you know!
Hey!
This is no time to be fighting!
Stand back, you two!
Amu-senpai!
Tadase, Character Transform!
Right!
Us too!
Yeah!
My heart:
Unlock!
Character Transformation: Platinum Royal!
Character Transformation: Amulet Heart!
Holy Crown!
Rikka, what is it saying?
It said it was dumped by the person it likes.
It says it hurts, and it never wants to fall in love again!
I understand!
If you've been dumped by someone, just...
Amu-chan!
Hold it together!
You can do it, Amu-chan!
If you've been dumped...
It really hurts being dumped, doesn't it?
Um, Amu-chan...
This is undignified behavior for the main character.
That's not true!
It's not right to give up on love
just because you were dumped!
Tadase-kun...
Maybe you don't understand
the feelings of the person you like.
And maybe they fell in love with someone else.
But just by seeing them smiling and enjoying themselves, you can feel happiness yourself!
So you mustn't put an X on anyone's feelings of love!
Right, Amu-chan?
Negative Heart: Lock On!
Open Heart!
A puppy?
Yeah. I picked her up the other day.
I can't keep her at my house right now, so I spoke to Souma-kun and he found a foster home for her.
She was so cute, I couldn't go to sleep.
A cute girl?
He couldn't sleep?
So it was a puppy.
Then the girl who came with Kuukai-san to Tadase-kun's house last night was...
Correct.
I am ecstatic that we were able
to find such a kind foster home!
I totally had the wrong idea!
Wrong idea?
Uh, never mind.
I love you, Amu-chan.
Thank you.
Couldn't be better!
Yeah!
Desu!
Everything's great!
You've all been acting funny since last night.
What was it?
Clueless Kiseki wouldn't understand.
That's right.
The heart of a lady is very complicated.
I don't understand at all.
Great!
It's time for Guardian Egg Fortune-Telling!
Choose one of the four eggs!
Which eggs will be the lucky ones?
Guardian Egg Friendship Fortune!
First, for those who chose Ran's egg:
Four Shugoluck Stars! Super lucky!
You might get a present from
a friend that'll cheer you up!
Don't forget to say thank you.
You might get a present from a friend that'll cheer you up!
Don't forget to say thank you!
Miki's egg gets three Shugoluck Stars.
You'll have a chance to
get closer to a person you
thought you didn't like! You
could become close friends.
You might get closer to a person you thought you didn't like.
You might give advice to
a troubled friend. Listen
carefully to their problems!
Su's egg gets two Shugoluck Stars.
You might give advice to a friend.
Finally, for those who chose Dia's egg:
Um, you get, um... one Shugoluck Star.
A promise to play might be canceled. Take
the opportunity to bond with your family.
Lucky Item: Pillow
A promise to play with your friends might be canceled!
Take the opportunity to bond with your family!
Shugo Chara Egg! Amulet Dia Audition Report!
Finally, we've decided on our Amulet Dia!
With over 300 contenders, the girl chosen as Dia is...
This girl!
Chara-su!
Yay!
Dia, congratulations!
I present to everyone, Amulet Dia!
Now, introduce yourself, 'kay?
Okay!
I'm Nanami, Amulet Dia!
Amulet Dia
Tanabe Nanami
I'll do my best at singing and talking!
Let's be friends!
Yay!
You can do it!
Now all four of us are together!
Awesome!
Now, Dia, it's time for your first job!
All right!
All four together now...
Okay!
Stay tuned for next week's Shugo Chara Party!
Lock On: Open Heart!
Bye-bye!
See you next time!
Nice to meet you
Dia will try all kinds of things starting next time!
Cheer her on, 'kay?
C-L-A-P
pa-ti
Let's put our hands together for you, yes you
kimi ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Let's put our hands together, that's what I wanna do!
kimi ni hakushu wo okucchae!
Now put your hands together for me, yes me
boku ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Now put your hands together, it's what you should do!
boku ni hakushu wo okucchae!
When I first heard your big dream,
hajimete kiita kimi no ookina yume
It was like I was whisked away
koko ja nai dokoka ni
To another place
tobidasu tte koto nanda ne?
So, I only know a tiny sliver of this world,
so kono chikyuu no honno ichibu shika
But at least you're here to talk to me
mada shiranai tte hanasu kimi ga iru
Hey! When I saw that look, that serious attitude...
nee sono manazashi shinken na kimochi
Before I knew it, my heart
omowazu haato dokidoki
Was all aflutter. Bravo!
ugokidashita yo buraboo!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti