Chara-su!
Is everyone shugo-peppy again today?
As for us...
Shugo Chara Egg!
Amulet Spade
Saho Akari
Amulet Heart
Fukumura Mizuki
Amulet Clover
Maeda Irori
We're shugo-shugo-peppy!
Any of you kids feeling blue?
If you are, just Character
Change with Shugo Chara Party!
Here we go! Everyone's hearts:
Unlock!
You're like a dream
yume mitai
It's like I'm dreaming
yume miteru
Whenever I start something new
atarashii koto hajimaru toki wa
I get really excited
sogoku wakuwaku shitetemo
Though I pretend like it's nothing at all
nandemonai you nakao wo shite
I've always been stubborn like that
ijippari yappari
I've always thought it'd be nice
sunao ni naretara
If I could just be honest with myself
iin dakedo natte itsumo omou yo
But it's hard, you know?
muzukashii kedo ne
I'll try working on it bit by bit
chotto zutsu ganbatte miru
It's party time!
party time
hajimaru yo
Someday I'll transform into someone brand new
daremo shiranai jibun ni naru
But for now, I want to forget everything else
ima dake wa subete wasurete
And discover all of the potential in me
ironna watashi sagashite mitai no
It's party time!
party time
hajime you
That brand new me is out there somewhere
daremo shiranai jibun ga iru
But for now, I just want to stay as I am
ima dake wa sukoshi kono mama
And find all of the things I can be
ironna watashi mitsukete mitai no
Hiyas, my little Eggs!
Which anime's up first on Shugo Chara Party?
The one starring the Guardian Characters!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
I wonder which Guardian Characters will show up today.
Let's check it out!
Enjoy!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
She Just Can't Stop!
"She Just Can't Stop!"
Morning.
A very good morning to you!
Good morning!
The weather!
Sure is great today!
Something's odd.
Ran, what's the deal?
Would you please stop for a second?
Actually I... can't!
What happened?
Well, it just feels so good to run, I can't stop anymore!
Like when you run down a steep hill, huh?
We don't have time to think about it!
We've got to stop her somehow!
"Perfect Plan to Somehow Stop Ran from Running!"
Or "PSR," for short!
Can the weird acronyms, all right?
Here she comes!
Okay!
Impressive, Ran.
Don't stand there being impressed! Think up a new plan!
"Perfect Plan to Somehow Stop Ran from Running 2."
In short, "PSR2: Anchor's the Way!"
Anchors what?
Here she comes!
Well, it almost worked.
"Perfect Plan to Somehow Stop Ran from Running 3."
In short, "PSR3: Fear the Banana!"
A banana peel!
I can do it! I can do it!
Nope, I can't stop!
So close...
What's the matter-dechu?
Ran can't stop running.
Oh, I see.
In that case...
That's...
Go for it-dechu! You're almost to the goal-dechu!
The goal?
Yay! First place!
She finally stopped.
Victory!
See you again
Shugo Chara Encyclopedia!
The first Character we'll introduce is...
Kusukusu
Kusukusu!
Hanbunko no Haato
Kusukusu is Rima's Guardian Character, who's the Queen's Chair.
Her clown outfit is so adorable!
She loves comedy and has a trademark laugh.
Continuing on, the second Character is...
Yoru
Yoru!
Yoru is Ikuto's Guardian Character. He's a stray cat that loves his freedom!
He's constantly getting into trouble and being scolded by Ikuto-nya!
But he always helps Ikuto when he's in a jam-nya!
We'll keep doing these Shugo Chara Encyclopedia introductions each week!
Look forward to it!
Shugo, shugo! Egg Battle!
Today we'll play "match the answer" with the Character Cubes!
We'll play a Shugo Chara Character song.
If you know who's singing it, arrange that person's face on the cube!
Ready, little Eggs?
Yeah!
Then here's the question: Who do you think is singing this song?
Ah, I know!
Do you know?
Oh? Spade doesn't seem very confident.
Are you okay?
I think I know.
Even if you know who's singing, you have to solve the cube puzzle before you can answer!
I've got three squares done!
You're so close!
The last part's the trickiest!
I'm not so good at those, myself.
Three! I got three again.
Heart and Spade have finished three squares.
That's the way!
How are you doing, Clover?
Keep at it, Clover!
I'm done! I'm done! Here!
Spade, what's the answer?
Rima!
Correct!
That was Rima-chan singing!
Spade, you did it!
Today's winner is Amulet Spade!
Do your best next time!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Place a Crab in the South-Southwest!
"Place a Crab in the South-Southwest!"
A c–crab?!
Oh, it's little.
Now that I look at it, it's cute.
But why is there a crab here?
Is that a daruma?
There's a picture of the moon!
And on the other side is the sun.
What does this all mean?
What is this?
"Place a crab in the south-southwest."
"Place a daruma in the north-northwest."
"A moon in the east, and a sun in the west?"
South-southwest and north-northwest? These are directions, aren't they?
It does look like they were
left in the positions the memo said.
Except the crab moved.
Perhaps this is some sort of code!
A code?
I saw something like this on television yesterday!
That two-hour suspense drama, right?
There were some mysterious lyrics to a nursery rhyme.
And horrifying accidents happened, just like in the song!
And people kept disappearing one after another!
Come on! That kind of stuff couldn't ha–
Miki's missing!
No way! If Miki's gone...
T–That means we're next!
And in the end...
No one will be left!
What's the matter?
Miki!
Those were spells?
Yeah. I read about them in a spellbook and wanted to try them out.
It says that to attract a proud guy, you place a crab in the south-southwest.
And to attract a perpetually cheerful guy, you place a daruma in the north-northwest.
Also, if you draw a moon in the east, your artistic talent will grow.
Plus, if you draw a sun in the
west, you'll become more stylish!
I see!
What are you lot up to?
Kiseki!
W–What are you doing? Cease and desist!
Release me, you fiend! Do you think a lowly crab such as yourself can–
Doesn't look like the spells worked.
I said release me, you scoundrel!
See you again
Coming up next is Shugo Chara!!! Dokki Doki!
Today's episode is titled "Yaya's Enthusiastic Gardening!!"
So Yaya-chan's the main character?
That means we'll see a lot of Pepe-chan, right?
I bet we will-dechu!
I can't wait-dechu!
Watch it-dechu! Watch it-dechu!
After the commercial-dechu!
Babu! Babu! Babu!
What's really important?
daiji na mono wa naani?
Well, it's white and round
maarukute shirokute
And sunny
howahowa de
And even if they don't know it,
kizukanakute mo
Everyone has one
kokoro no naka ni
In their heart
minna motterunda
The faith I have
shinjiru kimochi ga
In others is what always
senaka wo oshite kureru
Keeps me going
kitto
Guardian Eggs and X Eggs,
shugo tama mo batsu tama mo
Guardian Characters and X Characters,
shugo kyara mo batsu kyara mo
They're all precious things
zenbu daiji da mon ne
So, Open Heart, go!
dakara open heart hora
Everything'll be okay, even if you feel lost,
daijoubu mayotte mo
Because you're not alone
hitori ja nain dakara
We'll always be together
itsudemo issho dakara
And when I think of that, somehow
sou omoeba nandaka
I feel warm and fuzzy inside
genki ga waite kuru
Open Heart, go!
open heart hora
Previous Episode Digest
You can see them smiling, right?
mieru desho waratteru
The eggs are bouncing up and down
hazunderu tamagotachi
Now and forever, I'll be counting on you
korekara mo zuuuutto yoroshiku ne
One day, after school...
Wow, how pretty!
Don't you think?
What is so special about an arrangement of flora?
Hikaru-chi, you're always so negative about everything.
So, Yaya-senpai, what's this job we're supposed to help the Guardians with?
Allow me to explain!
It's to look after these flower beds!
That's right!
Wow, sounds fun!
Is that part of a Guardian's job, too?
But of course!
That's right!
Basic, isn't it?
You there, no whining!
Now, let's do this thing!
Yeah!
Yaya's Enthusiastic Gardening!!
You okay, Rikka-tan?
Sorry 'bout that.
What are you doing?!
That's a flower, you know!
But both flowers and grass are plants.
Weeding is about pulling weeds-dechu!
Not the flowers-dechu!
Is that so?
You should have specified.
Just put it back-dechu.
If you say so.
That's right... Gently...
Gently...
Now tell the flowers to grow nicely and quickly.
Talk to them as you water them!
Right!
I'm sorry, but I do not believe that plants can understand human speech.
Sure, whatever. Get back to weeding.
Rikka-tan?
Yaya-senpai! Mr. Ants are making a line!
Rikka-tan! Take this seriously!
"Mr. Ants?" Are you a baby?
Honestly-dechu!
Hey, Hikaru-chi! Don't use water right from the hose!
Yaya's really going at it!
Use the watering can!
Yeah.
She seems different today.
She certainly is not acting like a spoiled child.
Yaya thinks of Rikka and
Hikaru-kun as precious underclassmen.
I guess they draw out her natural wish to be a mentor.
Amu-chi!
Yaya, you sure are working hard.
Don't just stand there watching us, come help!
R–Right!
You've got the hang of it now-dechu.
It's simple once you've learned how.
Watch out, Amu.
For what?
I tried to warn you.
Sorry.
Yaya's really working hard.
She is.
"All the flowers are healthy and look good today."
It sure is rare to see Yaya put in so much effort.
True. It's a bit out of character.
Yep-dechu.
But it's because me and Yaya have taken care of the flower beds ever since we became Guardians-dechu.
Right from planting the seeds.
Hurry up and bloom, flowers!
Pepepepepe Pepe's seed!
And then they sprouted!
They sprouted!
And we spotted a pest!
Extermination will proceed as planned, sir!
Atta girl, Yaya-tan!
We worked on rainy days...
On windy days...
And snowy days, too.
And then, finally...
To sum up, these flower beds are the culmination of our tears-dechu!
All you did was cheer her on though, right?
I see.
So that's why.
You rock, Yaya-senpai!
What a Guardian!
Rikka-tan?
I'm going to take care of the flower beds with all my might, just like you!
Rikka-tan!
All righty!
Let's all do our best!
Now, let's go!
Hikaru! No spacing out! Get to work!
And no slacking either, Amu-chi!
I think she might be a little too gung-ho.
The next day, after school...
I want to become a Guardian
like Yaya-senpai as soon as I can!
But she sure is late.
And Hikaru hasn't shown up, either.
Being by myself makes me feel a bit lonely.
Huh? Where did you come from?
Hey, wanna help me out?
Crap! I totally forgot!
Yaya?
Sorry, I don't have time for you right now!
Yaya-tan fell asleep in class, so she had detention-dechu.
Hey, don't rat me out!
Guess some things never change.
Oh no!
Please stop!
Rikka!
Amu-senpai!
What is this?
What's going on here?
Um, there was this X Egg and–
Amu-chi, look!
I worked so hard to take care of those flowers!
Yaya-tan, let's go-dechu!
Su!
Right!
My heart:
Unlock!
Character Transformation: Dear Baby!
Character Transformation: Amulet Clover!
Here we go!
Go Go Little Duckies!
Duckies!
The duckies disappeared!
Rikka, what's the X Egg saying?
It really wanted to become a magician.
A magician?
It wanted to do magic that would surprise everyone, but it couldn't.
I see. So that's why it made the flowers big.
It wanted to surprise everyone!
Hey, wow!
You could totally become a magician with that!
Boring.
That's just an ordinary magic trick.
Try reading the mood a bit, will ya?
No, Hikaru-kun is right.
You're doing this all wrong!
Messing up those flower beds
will cause people trouble, right?
Magic's supposed to make people happy!
So why are you causing trouble instead?
If you think about how to make people happy, you're sure to come up with some great ideas.
Then you could do magic that'll surprise even Hikaru-kun, who just said he was bored.
Negative heart: Lock On!
Open Heart!
We did it! We did it!
The flower beds...
I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
Don't worry.
Leave it to Amu-chan!
Remake Honey!
Yay! It's back to how it was!
Do your best to take care of
the flower beds tomorrow, okay?
Right!
How about taking care of Yaya, huh?
I'm pooped!
Take care of me! Take care of me!
Babu!
Yaya-tan...
It seems Remake Honey returned Yaya-chan to her old, spoiled baby self...
Someone take care of Yaya!
I need some TLC!
It's time for Guardian Egg Fortune-Telling!
Choose one of the four eggs!
Which egg will be the lucky one?
Guardian Egg Romance Fortune!
First, for those who chose Dia's egg:
Four Shugoluck Stars! Super Lucky!
You're destined to be mega-popular!
Take this chance to confess your love!
Su's egg gets three Shugoluck Stars!
Attack your crush with
honesty! It'll work out!
Be assertive with the person you like!
Miki's egg gets two Shugoluck Stars!
Get a new cell phone
strap and your luck
might improve!
You might get a text from
someone you're interested in.
Get a new cell phone strap and your luck might improve!
Finally, for those who chose Ran's egg:
Um, you get, um... one Shugoluck Star.
The person you like might misunderstand you.
But don't lie! Make an effort to approach them honestly.
Lucky Item: Stuffed Animal
The person you like might misunderstand you.
But don't lie! Always be yourself, okay?
Your lucky item is a stuffed animal!
See you next time on Shugo Chara Party!
Lock On: Open Heart!
Bye-bye!
See you next time!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti
Let's put our hands together for you, yes you
kimi ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Let's put our hands together, that's what I wanna do!
kimi ni hakushu wo okucchae!
Now put your hands together for me, yes me
boku ni hakushu wo okurou okuritai
Now put your hands together, it's what you should do!
boku ni hakushu wo okucchae!
When I first heard your big dream,
hajimete kiita kimi no ookina yume
It was like I was whisked away
koko ja nai dokoka ni
To another place
tobidasu tte koto nanda ne?
So, I only know a tiny sliver of this world,
so kono chikyuu no honno ichibu shika
But at least you're here to talk to me
mada shiranai tte hanasu kimi ga iru
Hey! When I saw that look, that serious attitude...
nee sono manazashi shinken na kimochi
Before I knew it, my heart
omowazu haato dokidoki
Was all aflutter. Bravo!
ugokidashita yo buraboo!
C-L-A-P
pa-ti