Chara-su!
Is everyone shugo-peppy today?
Shugo Chara Egg!
Amulet Spade   Akari
Amulet Dia    Nanami
Amulet Heart   Mizuki
Amulet Clover    Irori
Let's start Shugo Chara Party!
Memorize our dance with us!
Everyone's hearts: Unlock!
My heart: Unlock
watashi no haato anrokku
Open up my heart
kokoro wo hiraite
Face straight ahead, going on!
mae wo muite Going On!
We're going on forever
dokomademo yukou
There's nothing to fear
kowai mono nanka nai
Lately it feels like things have changed a bit
saikin nanka fun'iki kawatta ne tte
And it's kind of nice, you know?
sore tte nanka chotto ureshii ne
No matter who you are, if you don't give up,
akiramenakereba dare datte
You'll fly farther than you did today
kyou yori tooku ni toberu tte
Even if you cry your eyes out and get depressed,
mechakucha naitemo hekondemo
The morning will still come
asa wa kuru kara
Negative Heart: Lock On
negatibu haato rokku on
You'll find the courage
yuuki wo kureru yo
Hold your head high, going on!
kao wo agete Going On!
Continue on to tomorrow
asu he tsuzuiteku
Your heart: Unlock
kimi no haato anrokku
Open up your heart
kokoro wo hiraite
Face straight ahead, going on!
mae wo muite Going On!
We're going on forever
dokomademo yukou
There's nothing to fear
kowai mono nanka nai
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Chin, Ton, Shan
"Chin, Ton, Shan"
Ya fell for it, ya fell for it!
Damn you Il!
Temari, reform Il for us!
Please!
Desu!
Understood.
I shall impart to Il-san the traditions of a model Japanese woman.
Traditional Japanese Woman
Great Plan One
Flower Arrangement
Chin, ton, shan!
First, I will teach you flower arrangement.
As if I'd be caught doing that!
Finished!
Oh, that's Miki for you!
I have also finished!
Aloha!
Nice!
Traditional Japanese Woman
Great Plan Two
Haiku
Chin, ton, shan!
Haiku are formed from five, seven, and five syllables.
They should express a Japanese cha–
R–Ran-san, you go first, please.
'Kay!
Flowers blossoming! Look at the really pretty flowers blossoming!
I may have forgotten to mention this,
but a haiku must contain a seasonal word that represents one of the four seasons.
Like spring or summer?
It seems quite difficult.
Finished!
Ah, it is now spring. Summer and fall both pass by. Now it is winter.
Oh, wow! All four seasons were included!
She did it!
That's a four-pointer!
Amazing, right?
This is easy!
I do request that you cease such tomfoolery from now on, if you please.
Too many syllables.
Traditional Japanese Woman
Great Plan Three
Tea Ceremony
Chin, ton, shan!
Please.
It's sweet and delicious!
Not bad!
Sweet?
Yes! I added milk to make it easier to drink.
Now see here, people. Have you perhaps forgotten the purpose of this exercise?
Purpose?
I'm headin' home.
Wait plea–
My legs are numb!
That's about enough!
Oh, I'm pretty good at that.
Temari, do something!
Chin, ton, shan. Goodbye, traditions of the model Japanese woman.
You didn't include a seasonal word.
See you again
Shugo Chara Encyclopedia, Character Transformations!
The first one for today is...
Black Lynx
Black Lynx!
Aikotoba wa Open Heart
Black Lynx is the form that Ikuto takes when he Character Transforms with Yoru!
His special attack uses the sharp claws on his hand, Slash Claw!
He's got cat ears and a long tail, with a punk outfit!
A wild, sexy black cat character!
Cool, don't you think?
And the second one is...
Samurai Soul
Samurai Soul!
Samurai Soul is the form that Kairi takes when he Character Transforms with Musashi!
His special attack uses two katanas, Inazuma Blade!
He wears an angel's raiment like Ushiwakamaru,
and wields Japanese swords. A samurai character!
Cool, isn't he?
We'll continue these Shugo Character Encyclopedia's each week!
Look forward to it!
Shugo-shugo Dance Lesson!
Let's split up Arigatou ~Ookiku Kansha!~ into four parts and memorize it!
Today it's Lesson 1!
Lesson
First, look at the Eggs' example.
kinou to wa chigau jibun ni
Let's try doing this much together!
Lesson
kinou to wa chigau jibun ni
Spin your hand around...
...and do the "chara-su!" pose!
Make a big heart, and then little heart beats!
Okay? Now, try dancing to the music!
Lesson
kinou to wa chigau jibun ni
Did you do it?
Then, let's look at the next step!
kitto nareru yo hoppu suteppu de janpu
Lesson
(interlude)
Let's try this section together!
Lesson
(interlude)
Shake your hips to the side...
One, two, three!
Add your hands... One, two, three!
Once more... One, two, three!
Point your finger three times... Blow a kiss!
Wag, wag, wag...
Jump, jump! Jump, jump, jump!
Now, try dancing it again to the music!
Lesson
kitto nareru yo hoppu suteppu de janpu
(interlude)
Okay!
Finally, let's try doing the whole lesson at once!
You can do it!
kinou to wa chigau jibun ni
kitto nareru yo hoppu suteppu de janpu
(interlude)
That's all for today.
Try your best next time, too!
Shugo Chara Pucchi Puchi!
Taking an Afternoon Nap!
"Taking an Afternoon Nap!"
What's the matter, Miki?
I'm sort of...
Bored! Bored! Bored!
Is there anything to do?
Something to do?
How about we have a snack?
I'm not hungry.
Then, draw a ske–
Did that already.
That's it! You should take a nap at times like this.
An afternoon nap?
Yeah!
You can get over times like "Bored! Bored! Bored!" by going to sleep!
Then let us go outside!
I can't go to sleep so easily.
It's a pretty butterfly!
What's the matter?
You've got to take a nap!
Sorry, but I'm not sleepy.
It's simple. Just lay down
and close your eyes, and then...
See? You're getting sleepy.
Wait... When I washed my hands before, I feel like I left the tap on.
I've got to check!
Su, what about the afternoon nap?
Oh, right...
You two are hopeless. I'll cheer on your afternoon napping to help!
Yay, yay, Miki, Su! Sleepy, sleepy, Miki, Su!
Deep sleep, deep sleep, Miki, Su!
You're so loud I can't sleep!
It doesn't seem like we can get to sleep.
All right then! Let's refuse to
open our eyes, no matter what!
Even if it's snack time?
Yeah!
Or if it starts to rain?
Right! No matter what!
Got it. If we're that serious about it, we've got to be able to get to sleep.
Desu!
But I'm just not sleepy.
The tap...
Now that I got some exercise, I'm even less sleepy.
But we promised not to open our eyes.
If I open them secretly, they'll get mad at me.
What am I going to do? I can't get to sleep.
What am I going to do?
What am I to do?
See you again
Coming up next is Shugo Chara Dokki Doki!
Today's episode is titled "Hikaru and the Fun Amusement Park!"
Hikaru-kun will ride a roller coaster?
He'd set foot on a merry-go-round?
I can't imagine it!
Not in the slightest!
I'm sure I can be a different person
kinou to wa chigau jibun ni
Than I was yesterday
kitto nareru yo
With a hop, step, and a jump
hoppu suteppu de janpu
Since I met you,
kimi to deatte kara
Every day has been chaotic
mainichi dotabata nanda
Laughing, getting angry,
warattari okottari
Going crazy... It's been tough
abaretari taihen
Since I was able to see you,
kimi to deaeta kara
I've been excited every day
mainichi wakuwaku nanda
Even slipping and falling,
subettari korondari
I've been having fun
sore mo tanoshii
Now that I think about it,
sou ieba
I haven't had a chance to tell you
ima made chanto ienakatta
I have something to say
kotoba ga arunda
Thank you, I'm so grateful!
arigatou ookiku kansha!
I might not be saying it right,
terekusai kedo
But it comes from my heart
kokoro kara omotteru yo
Previous Episode Digest
Thank you for everything!
arigatou zenbu ni kansha!
I can be honest
sunao ni ieru
And say it, thanks to you
sore mo kimi no okage kana
Hikaru and the Fun Amusement Park!
Ah! This is bad! I'm gonna be late!
Hey, out of my way!
Move it!
Hotaru, let's go!
Come on, let's go.
Right!
Hurry up, Hotaru!
Everyone sure is late.
Yeah, they are.
What the heck is that?
It's really popular with us Guardian Characters lately!
Sounds fun!
I'll do it, too!
That was fun!
Hey, didn't you think that was funny, Hikaru?
What was?
"Dadashiko" is funny, right?
I suppose the rhythm is intriguing.
Then try laughing, huh?
Why?
You laugh at strange things, right?
Laughter is nothing more than a release of tension.
I have simply never
experienced such an occasion as of yet.
Will you stop with all the mumbo-jumbo?
You mean you've never laughed out loud?
No.
Well, Hikaru does give off that vibe.
I have to agree.
It's not surprising.
I do not do unnecessary things.
That is all.
On to the next!
I'm tired.
He's a tough one.
I do not do unnecessary things.
But laughing is fun.
Fun?
Right! It's fun because you laugh.
And you laugh because it's fun.
It's fun to laugh?
That is technically laughing, but...
...it's an evil, scary laugh.
That wasn't fun at all.
Yeah, I suppose not.
I believe that if he was truly having fun from the bottom of his heart, Hikaru-san would laugh.
That's it! Hikaru-kun, would you hang out with me this Sunday?
And so, Sunday!
And so, amusement park!
But this amusement park is closed, remember?
We're gonna sneak in again?
How?
Easter purchased this.
We're going to start operations again shortly.
Wow.
That's Easter for you!
You would never guess it worked to put X's on children's hearts just a little while ago!
All right! We're gonna have a ton of fun today!
Since we're together with the owner of the place!
First off, the ferris wheel!
Yeah!
Wow!
I can see the entire park!
I have a lot of fun memories of this place.
So that's why I wanted you to have fun, too.
Understood. I will attempt to enjoy myself to the extent of your expectations.
I think he has the wrong idea.
Hotaru-chan, don't you want to see the view?
Hotaru, what's the matter? Not feeling well?
Y–You see, I...
I–I am afraid of heights!
Even though you're a Guardian Character?
And you can fly?
I am okay about as high as Rikka-chan's height, but...
Any farther and I...
There, there, it'll be okay.
It looks like...
...Hotaru's got an unexpected weak point.
Hotaru, you don't have to force yourself.
N–No, please do not worry yourself about me.
I–I–I am Rikka-chan's...
G–G–Guardian... Guardian Character, after all!
Ah, that was fun!
How about you, Hikaru-kun?
Not particularly.
Then, on to the next challenge!
When did this become a competition?
Are you okay?
I love going fast.
Now, attack from the inside!
Go, Amu-chan!
Not good enough.
Say what?! Then the next
challenge is the house of mirrors!
House of Mirrors
That's a funny face!
You too, Su.
I see. So the mirrors are warped.
Let's take a time out. I need a break.
What? Let's play more!
You're sure full of energy, Rikka-chan.
Now that I think about it, we've forgotten why we came here.
You just won't laugh, will you?
You're not having fun?
No, I'm having a lot of fun.
You both are trying to get me to have fun, right?
So I must try my best to have fun.
Even so, you don't look like you're having fun.
You can't tell?
This is my normal face.
This is my face when I am sullen.
This is my face when I'm having fun.
They're exactly the same.
But lately...
I had thought he'd gotten more expressive lately.
Then perhaps it's subconscious.
It's difficult to consciously express a certain emotion, isn't it?
Then I suppose we just have to make you have a lot of fun to get you to smile.
Then, let's ride those next!
Ikuto...
Okay! Time for spinnin'!
Let's go!
How is this fun?
You see...
You do it like this!
You try it too, Hikaru!
Like this?
Yeah, that's right! Like that!
Wow!
Hey Hikaru, you having fun?
Is this fun? I don't really know anymore.
It's fun for me!
'Cause I'm with you, Hikaru!
That's right.
Playing around in an amusement park with someone is something fun.
I'm having a lot of fun, too!
That was a blast.
I'm dizzy!
I'm still dizzy even though we've gotten off.
Yeah.
My legs are all wobbly.
That is because we spun too much.
Hikaru-kun?
Are you okay?
Hikaru?
You don't mean...
Maybe he hit his head?
Hikaru's broken!
I'm okay!
I don't hurt anywhere.
Then, why?
I can't control myself!
Not being able to move my body like I want to...
I've never thought something like that could happen!
So that's why you're laughing?
Yeah!
You think that's strange?
I think I can understand.
Spin, spin, spin, spin!
Okay! Everyone get dizzy!
I'm so dizzy!
I can't take it!
I'm all wobbly!
Your smile is really something, Hikaru.
I see. So this is a smile?
Hey!
Don't go thinking about it seriously!
Okay.
Then, let's spin again!
Okay, let's go, Hikaru!
Yeah!
Here we go!
Guardian Egg Fortune Telling!
Choose one of the four eggs!
Which egg will be the lucky one?
Guardian Egg Friendship Fortune!
First, for those of you who chose Ran's egg...
Four Shugoluck Stars! Super lucky!
This is a time when people will focus
on you and you'll gain popularity.
Smiles are the key to happiness!
This is a time when people will focus on you and you'll gain popularity!
Dia's egg gets three Shugoluck Stars.
When you feel like you're
communicating well, talk
to lots of people and deepen
your mutual sense of trust.
Try talking a bunch with your friends!
Your friends might
provoke you into
playing a prank. If you
do it, a teacher could
get mad at you.
Miki's egg gets two Shugoluck Stars.
Don't go playing pranks with your friends!
Finally, for those of you who chose Su's egg...
Oh no, how unlucky! Only one Shugoluck Star.
You might anger your friends by not
being straightforward with them.
Lucky Item: Comic Book
You might anger your friends by not being straightforward with them!
Make sure to get your opinion across to them!
Today sure was fun!
See you for the next Shugo Chara Party!
Lock On: Open Heart!
Bye-bye!
See you next time!
Now's the time to make your move
ima tobidasu toki sa
If you start worrying, nothing
mou nayandetemo nannimo
Will begin. A song-on your-lips
hajimaranai yo kuchi-biru-ni wa-uta
Now, what are you waiting for?
saa nanika ga matsu yo
Bang on the door to this world
kono sekai no doa wo tataku
On whose terms? That's right, ours!
kimeru no wa sou bokutachi da!
If all you try to grasp is immediate success,
me no mae no sakusesu dake wo motomete wa
You're sure to become lost in the labyrinth
kitto meiro he to mayoikomu