Stay away! Stay away!
No!
Stop! Stop!
I can't take this anymore!
This is a living hell!
Someone!
Anyone!
Anyone… Save me… from this hell!
Well…
Compared to the office,
that would be heaven.
Oh, no…
I need to sleep, since tomorrow's…
Tomorrow…
I got work again
tomorrow?
Work…
I don't wanna go…
It happened three years ago.
Here.
Starting today, you're assigned
to the Production Department…
All right.
My name is Akira Tendo.
Nice to meet you all!
-Nice to meet you!
-Welcome aboard.
On my first day, I got the impression
that it was a lively company
with a great atmosphere.
Yes! I'm happy to be here!
I landed a job in a production company
and industry I'd dreamed about.
I was full of hopes, dreams, and ambition.
I'm gonna pump out commercials
for all the big players!
Which means
maybe I'll even meet some stars!
Wow… I'm gonna do my best.
All right…
You'll be sitting here.
Yes, sir!
If there's anything you don't understand,
ask Kosugi, the Department Chief.
Nice to meet you!
Yes! I look forward to working with you!
Thank you for your hard work, sir.
I'm sorry!
It's all right.
I wasn't looking where I was going…
No! It's my…
Excuse me!
Here!
Thank you.
Sure…
Nice to meet you.
I'm Saori Ohtori from Accounting.
Looking forward
to working with you, Tendo.
Same… here.
For invoices or if you have any questions,
come ask me anytime.
I sit right through there and to the left.
Got it.
Well, good luck on your first day!
She's so cute…
TORIYA
Cheers!
-Thanks for all your hard work!
-Bottoms up!
Tendo, where did you go to school?
K University!
Wow, that's a good school!
It's not really…
Got a girlfriend?
No, I haven't had any luck…
What? A stud like you? What a shame!
No… I'm not…
You can ditch the tie,
we're not that kind of office.
Thank you.
But this gets me pumped up.
You look athletic, did you play anything?
Yes! I played rugby throughout college.
Rugby?
-That's great!
-Yeah!
Looks like we got a dependable
and valuable asset on our team!
I'll say!
Wow. Miss Ohtori's cute, for sure!
She's totally my type!
All right!
I'll work hard and show results
to make a good impression on her!
About time we got going, right?
Yeah.
Thank you very much for today.
I'm looking forward to--
All right.
Let's get back to the office.
KOSUGI
TAKAHASHI
What's going on?
What is this?
This can't be normal, right?
How much longer till you finish?
-About…
-Ten minutes, okay?
An all-nighter on my first day…
The next morning…
Still in the office.
Good morning!
Morning.
And that evening…
SOLD OUT
I mean, seriously…
When can I go home?
I'm going out to buy dinner.
It doesn't look like
I'll be going home tonight, after all!
Ultimately, I wasn't able
to leave the office and go home
until two days later.
This must be one of those
exploitative corporations.
I'm still sleep-deprived.
How long will I be
away from home this time?
All of a sudden,
I don't want to go to work.
Why am I whining?
This is nothing! Get used to it!
I chose this career!
I worked hard to get it!
Suck it up! Show some backbone!
Don't underestimate us jocks!
Good morning!
Our company has
many employee-friendly policies.
TENDO
Yes, well…
Annual paid vacations, naturally.
But you also get your anniversary day off,
and mental health days.
Never seen anyone use them, though.
We encourage each other
with good-natured competition.
How much unpaid overtime
did you log last month?
One hundred and fifty hours.
Talk to me once you pass 200.
I'm blessed with kind co-workers.
I'll cover dinner.
I might not look it,
but it's my fifth year.
I make more than you.
Thank you…
He just treated me, but Mr. Takahashi's
take home pay is 210,000 yen.
Mr. Kosugi, our team leader…
Quit asking me each and every time!
Why can't you decide
on something like that yourself?!
What?! You made a decision without me?!
Don't go off on your own!
He can be moody.
Get out of here!
But he's so passionate about mentoring
that some employees are moved to tears.
Where do you think you're going, damn it?!
Everyone at the office
is very health conscious.
Talk to me when you start pissing blood.
Another day, another ulcer.
And then, in my second year…
TRASH
When was the last time I took a bath?
Tonight, I'll go home no matter what.
Tendo!
Yes?
Takahashi's out. So you take over.
It's due by the end of the week.
TAKAHASHI
Yes, sir.
YAMAKAWA - TAKAHASHI - SAKAI
Another all-nighter confirmed.
Damn it, useless crap, honestly…
Maybe a missile
will come falling down on me…
Here, Tendo!
You worked through lunch again,
didn't you?
You have to eat.
Miss Ohtori!
Thank you very much!
The one person keeping me sane
at this company…
Miss Ohtori, the one
I'd secretly had a crush on…
-Thank you--
-Ohtori, got a minute?
Yes!
See you, Tendo!
Hang in there.
Miss Ohtori was also…
Sir, not here…
-It's okay! The walls are thick.
-Sir!
…the CEO's mistress.
Sir…
No… Sir…
Why am I still working there?
Should I find another job?
No… Impossible.
Where would I find the time?
If I leave, the team
will have to pick up my slack.
Besides, there are worse companies
than mine in the industry.
Oh, well…
Forget it…
Excuse me…
In my third year…
Like I said,
the managing director promised his
grandkid a role in the online commercial.
I'm sorry but can you rewrite
the scenario and include the kid?
But we've already been
through five revisions…
I see what you're saying!
Fine, then!
There are plenty of other companies
that would…
No, I'm sorry! I'll have it by today.
-You'll do it?
-Yes.
-Of course you will.
Please do that…
Yes…
I already signed the cast and crew
to work on a shoestring budget.
How do I make it up to them?
Why the hell are you slacking off?!
Is this harassment? Is that what this is?!
Are you harassing your superior?!
Quit messing with me!
You idiotic piece of…
This is blocking me.
If this wasn't here…
I wouldn't need
to go back to work tomorrow.
Running a thousand leagues!
According to a witness…
BITE MARKS ON VICTIMS
Long working hours
and bullying from their higher-ups
robs employees of their will to quit,
losing even the ability
to make a simple decision…
I see…
They fall into depression, and in the
worst case, they are driven to suicide.
Is that so? That's really scary.
Wow, exploitative companies seem like
they're hard to work for…
There's one thing that I think of
before I fall asleep.
"Please let me sleep
"and never wake up."
I don't wanna go…
I don't wanna go to work!
I don't…
Quit asking me each and every time!
Get out! Get out!
Go die, you piece of trash!
What?! You made a decision without me?!
Don't go off on your own!
Damn it. I forgot to pay
for my bike space.
I wonder if the building manager is up?
Excuse me.
Damn it, I'm gonna be late for work.
It's about my parking fee.
I'm sorry it's late…
Hey!
Hey… Wait! Wait! Wait!
What is this?
What's going on?!
Zombies?
Zombies?!
I mean, those are zombies, right?
What do I do?
What do I do?!
I mean, if this keeps up
I'm gonna be late for work!
Wait…
So…
Could this…
Does this mean…
Starting today,
I don't have to go to work anymore?
I'm…
…free!
Until yesterday, I saw the world
in monochrome, shrouded in a black cloud.
Blue skies!
Green trees!
Bright red blood!
It's been so long…
I'd forgotten the world
was so full of color!
I'm just so happy
to have a day off from work!
Now then, what to do today?
I was gonna get my motorcycle license
when I had some time off.
I could go to Yakushima.
Or go skydiving…
Or I could start day drinking
and binge movies all day!
I've had a ton a things I've wanted to do!
And now I can do them all, starting today!
I wonder if Miss Ohtori's all right.
Who cares if she's someone's side chick?
I'd rather get eaten by zombies
than regret holding in these feelings…
…I've had for the past three years!
Miss Ohtori, wait for me!
EMERGENCY CONTACT LIST
SAORI OHTORI
This is it!
Damn it, I'm starting to get cold feet!
Is it creepy if a coworker
you've never hung out with
suddenly shows up at your house?
Yeah, it's definitely creepy.
No! This is just a safety check
during an emergency!
It's open?
Miss Ohtori?
I came to check if you're…
Boss…
Sir!
I have something important to tell you.
Do you have a minute?
The long, hard hours at work
have been overwhelming,
and it's made me forget
what living like a human is.
I don't even know why I'm working anymore.
Anyway, it pains me to say this,
but it's time I regain control
over my life.
So, I've made up my mind
to resign as of today!
I know I was inexperienced in many ways,
but you mentored me until today.
For that, I'm very grateful.
I know this is selfish of me…
But please, accept my resignation!
Thank you very much!
-A comeback try!
-Go! Go! Akira!
Miss Ohtori!
From the moment
I saw you on my first day at work…
I've always…
Always, always…
Been completely in love with you!
Goodbye,
my love.
That hits the spot.
Tomorrow, the day after, next week…
I don't have to go to work ever again.
It's like a dream.
We could die today…
Or we could die 60 years from now…
Either way, there's never enough time
to do all the things we want.
In that case, I'm…
I'm gonna…
100 THINGS TO DO
BEFORE BECOMING A ZOMBIE
Next time:
"Bucket List of the Dead."