Where am I?
Is someone there?
Anyone? Help me, please! Help me!
My dear sister, I guess
that means you're conscious again.
How are you doing in there?
Were you dreaming of something pleasant?
MY HAPPY MARRIAGE
EPISODE 6
DETERMINATION AND THUNDER
Can't you drive any faster?
Getting upset right now
won't change anything,
so settle down.
You're acting awfully calm about this.
They might've hurt her, you know.
She's your fiancée,
shouldn't you at least be upset?
Before we arrive,
you're positive she's there?
Yes. Miyo is at the Saimori's.
You were really trying
to get in your beauty rest.
It was taking you
such a long time to wake up
that I was wondering
if your heart had just stopped.
Wh... Why are you doing this?
What is it I did?
Annoying as always.
I had thought you'd be spending
your days working as a servant,
or dying like an animal
on the side of the road.
You must think you're better than us.
Listen, girl.
You will step down as Mr. Kudo's fiancée.
Understood?
You will repeat these exact words to him,
"I reject, and wish to leave
this arranged marriage with you."
I was thinking, the responsibility
of being Mr. Kudo's wife
is too much for you to bear,
my dear sister.
That blue kimono you're wearing
is as beautiful as the summer sky.
Don't you think
it's ill-suited for you though?
Come on. Promise me
that you'll reject these arrangements.
Or else I'll have to alter
this precious, precious kimono.
Since it looks so awful on you,
you would force me
to make it match the person wearing it.
If you have the gall to ask him
to buy you
such an expensive kimono for you,
then rejecting the marriage arrangements
would be a piece of cake, wouldn't it?
When I get engaged to Mr. Kudo,
then you can finally have Koji
all to yourself.
Now then, Sister, tell me...
the next time you see Mr. Kudo,
what will you say?
No...
No?
Please, no...
No!
- That wasn't what I said.
- No!
- You already know what to say.
I wanna hear you say it.
I want to hear those words
exactly from your mouth.
"I do not want this marriage arrangement."
Why?
Why is this happening?
It would be easy to give up
and do what they told me.
But it's the only thing in so long
that I've wanted...
...for myself.
Something wrong?
Did you lose your voice?
You're just as useless
as you've always been, Sister.
No.
Huh?
No, I won't...
What you're asking me, I can't.
How dare you?
You brat...
Mother.
I'll handle this, don't worry.
See, I knew you would look better
as a crumped mess down on the floor.
Listen. Did you forget
what a failure you are?
Not only do you not have Spirit-Sight,
but you never had
any good traits to begin with.
It's an absurd idea
when you think about it.
The embarrassment of our family
is the one that gets to marry Mr. Kudo?
- Hey! Open up!
-Wouldn't you agree
this is the better deal?
Not only do you get to stay
at the Saimori house,
but you also get to have Koji
all to yourself
just like you've always wanted.
I... I want...
I want...
Uh?
...my Lord Kudo...
I am Kiyoka Kudo's fiancée.
He's not yours, now or ever.
You gotta be kidding.
I've had enough of this!
I'm the one who raised you!
All these years of your ingratitude!
And as soon as you get a husband,
you start spewing this nonsense?
You're as wretched as I thought you were!
You will not ruin this!
My life will not be ruined
because a horrible little girl
doesn't know her place.
In the past,
I would've already... apologized to them,
praying for the storm to pass...
That was the life I lived.
It was easier, so I was quiet.
But that's not my life anymore.
I've...
changed.
Changed into someone stronger than I was.
I chose him.
And he chose me!
Hey.
- Huh?
- You should stand back.
What a stubborn little welp you are!
What was that?
What...
What... have you done?
We're going in.
Huh? All right.
What's going on?
Kudo? Wait! Wait a moment! Stop, please!
What is this about?
Mr. Saimori, where's Miyo?
Miyo?
Miyo is done with you.
The Kudo family will not see her again.
How could you? Father, how could you?
Kiyoka Kudo. I didn't expect you
to get here so quickly.
Where are you keeping my fiancée?
Miyo has no interest in marrying you.
She said that she will not return.
I intend to face her myself
and ask if that's what she wants.
You should tell me where she is or move.
I refuse.
If you're not going to listen
to what I say,
then you and I are facing an impasse.
I'll have to use force
if you won't step aside.
Hang on! Please just wait!
Tatsuishi, what is going on?
What's happening?
Once this is over,
you can ask your daughter about it.
The main entrance has been destroyed.
If you allow him to proceed any further,
he'll destroy the entirety of your home.
If you wish to keep a roof over your head,
lend me a hand.
Hmm...
As I expected from the head of the Kudos.
This is pointless.
It's true what they say. You're a monster!
You're in the way.
Now move.
Father's no match for him.
It's like an adult facing an angry child.
That power...
He's known as the strongest gift-user
of our time for a reason!
What was that? That light?
You... You disgust me!
Hurry up and say it already!
"I will reject the marriage arrangements
with the Kudo family."
I won't lie because you say to...
You worthless brat!
I told you. You know exactly
what your place is in this world!
I won't...
I refuse to say that.
My fiancé wants me there!
He knows that I belong...
Miyo...
Storehouse?
Yes.
There's an old storehouse in the back.
They barely use it.
It's unassuming,
so Miyo could be in there.
Show me the way.
Over here.
Stand down now!
My father!
This isn't a safe place to be using fire.
How many more foolish decisions
will he make?
Is... this worth it?
I will not let you marry an Usuba!
If that's how it is...
He was rendered unconscious.
Now let's go.
It didn't need to be this way.
Hurry up and say it already!
Say you'll reject him this instant!
Say it now!
In the past, I would wait,
hoping the next moment
would lead to my last breath.
Every day was such a struggle.
Being alive hurt...
to the point that my heart went numb.
Living was exhausting.
Back then, I believed...
there was no place where I belonged.
I'm glad...
I was wrong.
I want you to stay with me
until death separates us.
I belong somewhere.
I will be by his side.
Hurry up and spit it out!
I will...
never say it.
Say it!
I've decided that...
I will be with him until my final breath.
Is that... Mr. Kudo?
Miyo!
He really... came for me.
Do you see?
Lord Kudo,
I didn't give up this time.
Miyo.
Lord Kudo, are you...
Yes, you're safe now.
You really came all this way for me.
It was worth it to fight.
Thank you all so very... much.
What on earth? What is it now?
But I... No, the house...
No!
How did she get like this?
What did you do?
She didn't bow to you
and you decided to beat her for it?
What did you want from her?
I'm not the one... None of this is my fault.
I just wanted to...
to correct a mistake.
Nothing else happened, that was it.
Mistake?
Sister doesn't possess Spirit-Sight.
She's boney and ragged
and is useless as a servant.
That has to be why she could never be
a good match for the Kudo family,
so it must be a big mistake.
I know I'm the better choice for you!
Mother and Father wouldn't just say
I'm the greatest!
They've told me
that I'm the opposite of my sister.
That I'm superior to her
in every possible way.
Shut your mouth.
That's enough.
I don't want to hear
any more of your putrid drivel.
But... why don't you understand
why you should be with me?
This isn't fair!
Did I not just say
I've heard enough of your horrid nonsense?
I would not and will never marry
an arrogant woman like yourself.
Even if the very heavens demanded it.
Now go!
Why choose her?
How could things have ended like this?
Kaya, we need to evacuate.
I'm right. I know I'm right.
Let go of me! Just go and leave me alone!
Just shut up!
What? How dare you?
Sister was the only one
you ever liked anyway.
You should just go evacuate with her,
so you can forget about me already!
Yes, that's right.
It's just like you said.
The only person
I care about in this world is Miyo!
But the truth is...
that if you die here today,
Miyo will grieve for you,
because that's who she is.
Even though you...
No, we all did this to her.
I just... I can't let you hurt her again.
You're taller than the last time, Miyo.
Mother! It's you!
I am so sorry
for making you endure
everything all alone.
Oh...
Believe in yourself
for the rest of your life.
Believe in that power
- that lives within you.
- Huh?
Believe in...
what power?
What terrible news!
How detestable!
As utterly awful as imaginable!
Tatsuishi was completely useless.
At this rate, Kudo will get ahold
of the Usuba bloodline.
Your Majesty.
It is time.
We must ask your permission for a request.
I beg you. Allow us to achieve
what we've been hoping for all this time.
To put things back where they belong.
A ripple effect will begin soon.
I grant the permission you seek.
However, do not miss this opportunity.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Then we shall proceed.
We will begin the operation as planned.
You must destroy
the accumulation of power no matter what.
Huh?
Uh, Lord Kudo...
Miyo!
Lord Kudo, it's you!
Yes, it's me.
Don't push yourself. Lie down.
I just...
But...
Are you sure you're all right?
I am, but, um...
Lord Kudo, I...
This was all...
I was careless with the amulet.
No need to blame yourself.
None of this... is your fault.
None of this was ever your fault.
Thank you very much, Lord Kudo.
My Lord Kudo!
Miss Miyo!
Miss Yurie.
Miss Miyo! I'm so glad!
- You've finally woken up.
- But...
Miss Yurie, you don't...
You really don't need to cry, okay?
You've no idea
how worried I was about... you, Miss Miyo.
And you're okay now.
I agree.
I'm glad you're home safe.
Yes.