Hey, Touma.
Are you really going to school starting today?
Oh, that's right.
You're going to be home alone from now on.
I didn't say that I'd be lonely or that I don't like being alone; it's not like that!
We need to take the time and actually think about what to do about this.
But, sorry, be home alone for today.
Touma, will you come home as soon as you can?
I guess.
Let's go hang out somewhere once I get back.
OK!
I'll be going then.
Yeah, have a good day.
Well, what are we going to play today?
Huh?
Touma, what about my lunch?
What should I do...
This is a huge crisis I have yet to face...
Shocker...
Yo.
All fired up already, eh?
You sure seem relaxed.
Well yeah...
So much has happened, and my body's tired.
W-What?!
Was yesterday's "boyfriend" game that tiring for you?
Hey, that's not the only factor.
Not the only...
Are you saying... you're doing that kind of thing for other girls, too?!
...You're the only one who would calmly ask me
to do such embarrassing things, okay?!
You think I asked you calmly?!
Even for me, I didn't know what to do...
...and since I couldn't come up with any other solution...
...I swallowed the embarrassment and...
...begged you to do it!
Uhh, yeah, sure, uh huh, it's just like you say.
Hey, wait!
Listen to me seriously!
September 1st.
The first day of the second semester.
But, having lost my memories during summer vacation,
I have the nervous feeling
transfer students have on the first day.
Komoe-sensei?
...Her feet can reach the brakes?
I can drive even if my feet can't reach the brakes!
Gosh!
Sensei doesn't remember raising you in such a bad manner, Kamijyo-chan!
Sensei... that's not a pop quiz, is it?
Sensei wouldn't do something to her own students that she, herself, hated.
A friend requested that I gather some data.
It's a white paper on AIM dispersion field.
What's umm...
"An Involuntary Movement",
in other words, lack of self-consciousness.
Basically, it's when an esper emits
a field of power like the sun emitting light.
Granted, these are so weak that they can't even be measured.
Then, if there was an esper that could detect those,
they can say "Hey! There's a presence of an esper nearby" or something?
Yes!
And further down the line, they might even be able to distinguish the type or magnitude of the power, too.
"Mmm... his Power Level is 70000!"
...something like that,
and basically, there are people who devote their passion to that kind of research.
Thanks for bringing me here every time.
Hey, what's going on?
Allowing a magician to break into this city so easily.
It doesn't matter.
I am tracing the location of the intruder as we speak.
Shelley Cromwell.
She's not a vagrant magician, but a member of the English Purist Church, Necessarius.
If she's taken down without care, then the status quo between the Church and Academy City will be ruptured.
For both "neighbor loving" sides
to be breathing down each other's throats...
Anyway, have me take out Shelley.
If a magician takes out a magician,
then the commotion will be smaller.
There is no need for you to do anything.
Don't tell me... you want to have Kamijyo Touma handle this again?!
It can shorten the time between Plan 2082 and Plan 2377.
Is that the control theory of the Imaginary Number Sector - Five Elements Institution?
For it is a restive horse that could rip apart the entire world,
and it would be best to have a
firm grip of the reins before it's too late.
Huh?
What's up, Kami-yan?
Where's Tsuchimikado?
Yeah, we haven't seen him yet, huh?
Maybe he didn't finish his homework.
Hey, look at me,
I purposely left them on the backburner just so that Komoe-sensei could give me a scolding!
Hey now...
Okay children, time to begin homeroom.
Before the starting ceremony, I have big news for you all.
And wow, we have a new transfer student in our class today.
Oh, it's a girl, by the way.
Congratulations, goons!
Better luck next time, kitties.
Okay, transfer student, come on in!
Index?!
Ah, it's Touma!
This was your "school" after all!
Where did you come from?!
You're not the transfer student!
Come on, get out, get out.
Sister-chan, what are you doing here?
Here.
Use this and get a taxi to go straight home.
And don't follow strangers, okay?
By the way, the real transfer student is me...
...Himegami Aisa.
I'm hungry...
Mmm, I've heard of this.
Coupons that can be exchanged for food come out from them.
Touma makes fun of me and calls me an "antique",
but this is a piece of cake.
Put in the money.
And just press the button.
Huh?
Where's the button?
There's no button!
What should I do?
The money got eaten, too!
Umm...
You need to press the button.
There's no button anywhere.
Well, just touch the monitor.
But I can't touch the people inside the TV.
This TV is linked with the inside, huh?!
No, umm...
Thank you!
What's your name?
I'm Kazakiri Hyouka.
And then, you know?
I called Touma's name,
but not only did he not answer me,
he turned his eyes somewhere else!
Well, school's not a place for outsiders to come.
But, Hyouka, so are you...
I'm a transfer student.
I'm going to become a transfer student, too, then!
Umm...
There's no way I'm going back home like this,
and what's most important is that I need to ask what to do about lunch!
But your attire is too distinctive...
Then, what should I do?
Umm...
If we go to that place, then maybe...
I know it's weird for me to be saying this,
but she's the type that gets into trouble quite easily.
It stretches well, and it's a fabric that gets cleaned very easily.
Wow!
This is what they call "high tech" right?
Damn you, stupid Sister!
Hey Index!
What the hell are you doing in a place like... this...
Sorry, wrong room-
Touma!!!
It's just the opening ceremony today, so I would've been home by noon.
How would I know that?!
This is common sense.
Then, Touma, did you know this?
The direction and standing position of the caster in the formula used...
...during the idol creation ritual of injecting telesma into crucifixes made in England?
Get it wrong just by a little, and it won't function at all.
Do you know that golden ratio, huh?
See, see, this is common sense, eh~
So, Index, who is she?
I'm not sure, but she's my friend.
You're not sure?
I'm not sure, but Hyouka's my friend!
My name is Kazakiri Hyouka.
I'm Kamijyo Touma.
Are you a transfer student?
Y-Yes-
Touma!
Don't be scaring Hyouka here!
Don't worry, Hyouka.
Touma's hot-blooded and indecisive,
and if it involves girls, he's the type that'll dive right into problems for her,
but, he's a good person.
Here, I'll let you hold onto Sphinx.
You could relieve your nervousness by touching a cat, maybe.
Is Sphinx... his name?
What's the matter?
Animals are much more cunning than humans,
so he could probably tell the difference between you and me.
Kamijyo-chan!
You sure got some guts already on the first day of second semester!
Huh, Sensei, shouldn't you be at the ceremony...
Sensei didn't see you at the hall, so she got worried and came looking for you!!!
Yet, Kamijyo-chan, you-
No, umm, I-
Why is it that girls always trickle down to you wherever you are, Kamijyo-chan?!
Do you possess a weird kind of AIM dispersion field?
What the...
Why don't you say something, too, Kazakiri-
Huh?
She had enough and left?
Umm...
Hyouka.
It was wild back there, huh?
I was a bit shocked.
Komoe isn't mad or anything.
You don't have to worry about it too much.
You seem to have some sadness about you.
Touma was mad at me.
He didn't hear anything I said.
He didn't smile at all.
Has Touma started to dislike me?
Friends that are able to fight with each other are the ones that are really close.
Why?
The fact they can fight means they can forgive each other properly afterwards.
It's like you can trust that person to not cut off the relationship even after a fight.
Really?
He's a person who would get angry over something for your sake,
so it'll be fine.
Although he's also a person who would come talk to you calmly even after seeing you naked...
Hey.
Touma!
Let's go eat.
We're not eating at home today?
We're going out after we eat anyway.
Would you mind joining us, Kazakiri?
Yes, join us, Hyouka!
Is that okay?
Let's go, let's go!
Thank you!
Let me go withdraw some cash.
Himegami.
I transfer here, and now you give me this cold reaction?
I'm a girl who goes unnoticed after all, huh?
Ah, no... right!
We're going to hang out somewhere, won't you join us?
...stupid Komoe...
Nothing.
I was asked to run an errand, so I can't go.
That aside, who is she?
Kazakiri Hyouka, I think.
You're sure she's Kazakiri Hyouka, right?
Yeah, Index said so, and she said her name, as well.
You know her?
Kirigaoka Girls' School.
The high school I attended before.
I saw Kazakiri Hyouka's name there too.
Then is she a user of a rare kind of power like you?
I don't know.
Her name always showed up
on the top rankings of test results,
but no one ever saw her in person.
No one even knew which class she was in.
What's up with that?
That's when I got curious and investigated a little.
It was then that I found out.
She's called "Counter Stop".
However, that's not the important part.
Kazakiri Hyouka has been called the key to understanding the Imaginary Number Sector - Five Elements Institution.
The Five Elements Institution?
That thing really exists?
Rumor has it this Institution is the one that controls the administration of Academy City from the shadows.
A special research facility was established just for researching her ability.
So, it is a research center dedicated to discovering the truth of the Imaginary Number Sector - Five Elements Institution.
What is a person like her doing here?
She said she is a transfer student.
I should be the only transfer student.
Be careful.
This must be...
...the famous "Underworld"!
You mean, underground mall.
Underground mall.
Index, is there something you'd like to eat?
Expensive places and places with long lines
are out of the question!
I want somewhere cheap, abundant in amount, delicious in quality, and not too popular!
Yeah, yeah.
What about you, Kazakiri?
Did I do something wrong?
No.
I'm not scared or anything...
You've seen my body already...
No!
Secret tea time with an outsider girl, eh?
If only the elite kids in my class would pull something reckless like that, too...
Gosh, you Anti-Skills have a problem here!
What if this outsider were a dangerous person!
Yeah, yeah.
So, I heard there were two of these outsiders.
I wanted to confirm one thing really badly with you.
Were there really... two of them?
Yes, Yomikawa speaking.
I'm on my way.
Anti-skill work?
Looks like we got a big one.
I'll be out for a bit.
See ya~
I brought you the book you asked for.
Thank you, Himegami-chan.
Komoe-sensei.
Yes?
Is there a student called Kazakiri Hyouka at this school?
There she is.
It's an evacuation order!!
I'd prefer if you wouldn't move at all.
I serve in the law enforcement unit of this city,
Shirai Kuroko of Judgment.
I'm sure you don't need us to tell you the reason we're going to arrest you.
Search halted.
Giving me extra work...
I said not to move.
Don't understand Japanese?
What is this?!
Impossible!
A normal human who's also an esper?
This is not good!
I have to retreat-
I'm not sure what this fuss is about...
...but don't be touching my friends, damn it!!!
It's okay now.
That huge hand was just a diversion.
The fact that you're after this person means...
Yes, it was apparently an intruder.
Oneesama!!!
Hey!
Geez...
Kuroko, it's okay to rely on me more.
Don't think about not causing me trouble.
This is such a rare chance!
Being this close, I can enjoy Oneesama's cleavage as much as I want...
Hold it, Kuroko, that's not what I meant...
Widespread even before the era before Noah's Ark,
using bits of knowledge passed on by the chief of the Grigoris,
now, in a method different from the original...
"In the beginning, there was primal clay."
"God created a form from the clay,
bestowed life upon it, and called it 'Man'."
"This secret was passed to Man through the oral tradition of the fallen angels."
"However, this was a secret too great for Man to handle."
"Thus, the life borne from my hand halts at a decaying mud doll."
Mud-stinking golem, Ellis.
Laugh and decay at my bidding.
Don't make me wait too long, Ellis.
The monster that Shelley Cromwell controls, Ellis.
Being stuck in the underground mall,
we get caught in an intensive battle.
Kazakiri, what's your secret?!
Next time, "Golem".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!