Original Script:曙光字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正大黑_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HC88F8F8F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,134
Style: Second,方正大黑_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HC88F8F8F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,5,10,10,61,134
Style: SGS,Geometr415 Lt BT,70,&H00D8CEBC,&HF0000000,&H3C000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,30,30,10,1
Style: SGScn,汉仪圆叠体简,70,&H00E7B7A5,&HF0000000,&H3C000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,30,30,10,134
Style: OP,DFPHSGothic-W5,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,&H78FFA54A,&H642B2B2B,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,5,22,20,15,128
Style: OPcn,黑体,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,&H78FFA54A,&H642B2B2B,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,5,22,20,15,134
Style: Notes,方正大黑_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HC88F8F8F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,10,10,10,134
Style: ED,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,40,&H002D2DFF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H328E8EFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,1,22,22,20,128
Style: EDcn,华康少女文字W5(P),40,&H002D2DFF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H328E8EFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,9,22,20,20,134
Style: Lyric,DFPHSGothic-W5,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00CC1F11,&H64EF9E98,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,1,22,22,20,128
Style: Lyriccn,黑体,35,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00CC1F11,&H64EF9E98,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,9,22,20,20,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.13,0:02:48.84,Notes,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(500,500)}曙光社字幕组提醒您:  本片来源于互联网 仅供试看  有爱 就要支持原版正版动画
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.13,0:02:48.84,Notes,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(500,500)}翻译：LJDtheGR ldy zwzplayer yanxi  时间：skiller 野田斯盖  后期：Teny
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.13,0:02:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\pos(400,580)\bord3\be1}Triangler
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------------------------------op/ed
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.09,0:01:34.84,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}星をまわせ　世界の真ん中で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.17,0:01:41.10,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}くしゃみすれば　どこかの　森で蝶が乱舞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.36,0:01:48.13,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}キミが守る　ドアの鍵デタラメ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.38,0:01:51.03,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}恥ずかしい物語
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.11,0:01:58.01,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}舐めあっても　ライオンは強い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.27,0:02:04.85,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}生き残りたい　生き残りたい　まだ生きてたくなる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.91,0:02:11.41,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}星座の導きで　今　見つめ合った
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.50,0:02:18.21,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}生き残りたい　途方に暮れて　キラリ枯れてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.22,0:02:28.02,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}本気のカラダ　見せ付けるまで　私　眠らない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.11,0:02:34.66,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}生き残りたい　まだ生きてたい　キミを愛してる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.72,0:02:44.63,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a2\fad(100,100)}本気のココロ　見せ付けるまで　私　眠らない

Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.09,0:01:34.84,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}昂头站在世界正中 群星围绕
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.17,0:01:41.10,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}即使一个小小的喷嚏 也让森林某处的蝴蝶禁不住乱舞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.36,0:01:48.13,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}要保护你 即使门锁上胡乱刻着
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.38,0:01:51.03,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}羞耻的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.11,0:01:58.01,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}相互舔舐伤口 狮子还是最强的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.27,0:02:04.85,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}要存活下去 要存活下去 想想活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.91,0:02:11.41,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}星光的指引下 现在 才能互相凝视
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.50,0:02:18.21,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}想要活下去 即使穷途末路 即使星光黯淡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.22,0:02:28.02,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}认真的我 直到闪耀之前 不会睡去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.11,0:02:34.66,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}想要活下去 一定要活着 要活着爱着你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.72,0:02:44.63,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fad(100,100)}认真的心 直到闪耀之前 不会睡去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------

Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.00,0:22:13.02,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}君は誰とキスをする
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.00,0:22:18.52,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}私　それともあの子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.00,0:22:24.02,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}君は誰とキスをする
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.01,0:22:29.20,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}星を巡るよ純情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.16,0:22:38.46,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}弱虫 泣き虫連れて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.90,0:22:44.00,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}また行くんだと思う私
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.27,0:22:48.88,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}愛するより求めるより
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.65,0:22:55.40,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}疑う方がずっとたやすい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.40,0:22:58.28,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}自分が悔しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.58,0:23:00.53,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}痛いよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.78,0:23:06.03,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}味方だけど　愛してないこと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.18,0:23:10.58,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}守るけど　そばにいれないとか
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.63,0:23:14.03,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}苦い二律背反
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.33,0:23:19.43,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}今すぐ touch me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.73,0:23:23.93,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}運命ならば繋がせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.63,0:23:29.83,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}君は誰とキスをする
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.03,0:23:35.43,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}私　それともあの子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.48,0:23:40.63,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}心揺らす言葉より
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.63,0:23:45.85,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}無責任にだいで限界

Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.00,0:22:13.02,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}你会吻谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.00,0:22:18.52,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}是我 还是她
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.00,0:22:24.02,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}你会吻谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.01,0:22:29.20,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}穿梭在星空的纯真
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.16,0:22:38.46,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}胆小爱哭
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.90,0:22:44.00,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}又想吻你的我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.27,0:22:48.88,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}比起去爱 比起去追求
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.65,0:22:55.40,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}却总是犹犹豫豫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.40,0:22:58.28,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}常常后悔着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.58,0:23:00.53,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}心痛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.78,0:23:06.03,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}仅仅是伙伴 不能成为爱人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.18,0:23:10.58,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}想守护 却无法在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.38,0:23:14.03,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}在矛盾中苦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.33,0:23:19.43,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}就请马上 touch me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.73,0:23:23.93,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}如果这就是命运 请把我们连接在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.63,0:23:29.83,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}你会吻谁
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.03,0:23:35.43,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}是我 还是她
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.48,0:23:40.63,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}不需要若即若离的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.63,0:23:45.85,OPcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an7}只求你不顾一切地将我抱紧


Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------------Dialogue
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.88,0:00:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.34,0:00:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到妈妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.63,0:00:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都因为工作太忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.39,0:00:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才都没有回来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.95,0:00:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你寂寞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.73,0:00:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.60,0:00:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.91,0:00:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个好办法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.36,0:00:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.13,0:03:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.81,0:03:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一天终于到来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.93,0:03:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭借我们的希望的歌姬 李兰华的活跃表现
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.44,0:03:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第7次超长距离Fold获得了巨大的成功
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.15,0:03:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的船队终于得以从Vajra的攻击中解放出来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.02,0:03:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了纪念这次成功 全体与会者一致表决通过的纪念日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.32,0:03:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是今天 将我们引向自由的那首歌Aimo命名的 Aimo纪念日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.48,0:03:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 在这里 在Proto-E大街
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.85,0:03:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格拉斯总统和兰华所在队伍正在驶来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.02,0:03:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正向着街边的人们…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.52,0:03:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.39,0:03:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰华人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.67,0:03:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不要看老头子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.86,0:03:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰华怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正在打听
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.41,0:03:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特地在她的学校进行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.94,0:03:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天下午的演唱会 一定要让她赶上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.14,0:03:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.03,0:04:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 总统先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.80,0:04:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小爱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.20,0:04:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么好笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.32,0:04:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 因为布雷拉先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.79,0:04:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心的话 就到早乙女家来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.11,0:04:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等您哦 阿露特先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.03,0:04:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真高兴 你能回来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.35,0:05:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不是要回来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.04,0:05:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.74,0:05:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管理由是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.32,0:05:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个你曾经发誓不会再回来的家里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.30,0:05:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又相遇了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.11,0:05:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么今天要值班监视
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.28,0:05:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.25,0:05:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁着气势做了Fold航行 相对预定宙域飞过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.50,0:05:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未知星域的探测也是重要的任务
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.16,0:05:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯茜中尉真好啊 得到了休假
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.59,0:05:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是找零
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.27,0:05:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.44,0:05:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尝尝这个超辣热狗 啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.24,0:05:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,11点方向 街角上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.08,0:06:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这个啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.58,0:06:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 真辣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.41,0:06:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.44,0:06:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直笑个不停啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.82,0:06:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 因为第一次看到布雷拉先生会被吓到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.97,0:06:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.64,0:06:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 能够听凭我的任性
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.61,0:06:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过 我会保护你的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.10,0:06:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不会食言的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.01,0:06:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.80,0:06:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.28,0:06:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.28,0:06:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 克兰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.13,0:07:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个姿势太勉强了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.07,0:07:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.18,0:07:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好 我帮你调查 你就按我说的做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.64,0:07:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.34,0:07:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到下午的特技表演前为止啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.24,0:07:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.27,0:07:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.39,0:07:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于行动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.19,0:07:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个优柔寡断的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.13,0:07:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.23,0:07:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还是比那些见到美女就下手的花花公子好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.83,0:07:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也越来越有同感了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.26,0:07:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边走
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.78,0:07:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.06,0:07:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿露特
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.70,0:08:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.19,0:08:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你问我来干什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.55,0:08:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身体状况呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.14,0:08:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你所看的一样我身体非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.10,0:08:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有什么事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.81,0:08:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.63,0:08:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰华自己去找了?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.03,0:08:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.41,0:08:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布雷拉先生也在一起的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.82,0:08:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外兰华最近没什么精神
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.77,0:08:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她稍微放松一下也好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.21,0:08:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小爱是兰华的那个宠物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.48,0:08:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也帮你们一起去找
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.98,0:08:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.62,0:08:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把详细特征告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.87,0:08:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.78,0:08:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢卡 来帮忙一下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.21,0:08:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 七濑 一会儿再见
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.93,0:09:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.67,0:09:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不唱歌了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.25,0:09:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束歌手生涯了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.14,0:09:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在唱歌领域已经做完自己想做的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.88,0:09:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经有些厌倦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.36,0:09:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这次想做别的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.01,0:09:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.11,0:09:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前说过的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.40,0:09:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是靠好运气走到那里的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.64,0:09:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力  努力奋斗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.42,0:09:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才掌握自己命运的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.65,0:09:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有兰华在那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.84,0:09:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的 那都是骗人的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.70,0:09:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候我是在自己骗自己
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.31,0:09:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.84,0:09:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是银河的妖精 雪露·诺姆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.18,0:09:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我是雪露·诺姆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.64,0:10:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是唱歌还是不唱歌 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.72,0:10:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天在美星有兰华的演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.43,0:10:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特技表演时我也会飞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.69,0:10:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也一定要来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.33,0:10:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.76,0:10:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.57,0:10:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过解析Fold水晶的波动特征而作的新型导弹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.07,0:10:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是利用那个「时空吞噬者」技术小型化而成的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.49,0:10:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MDE弹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.70,0:10:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来 暂时又有对Vajra有效的武器了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.65,0:10:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,量产呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.77,0:10:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要花时间
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.43,0:10:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这终究不过是次要的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.51,0:10:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是多年的秘密终于被揭开了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.18,0:10:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰雪和玛欧博士都无法解开的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.52,0:10:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女皇的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.09,0:10:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 那个计划出现误差也没关系的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.11,0:11:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明是为了那个才设置了这个会场的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.38,0:11:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来才是真正的节日
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.27,0:11:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个优秀的演员呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.99,0:11:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是美绪夫人 阿露特的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.31,0:11:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来身体就不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.89,0:11:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在阿露特12岁的时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.28,0:12:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还记得 她经常坐在那边走廊给阿露特梳头
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.90,0:12:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一副和蔼的神情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.10,0:12:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我藏匿在这里 是为了让阿露特回忆起那时候的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.06,0:12:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次让他站在歌舞伎的舞台上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.97,0:12:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这样的话 就真不巧了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.51,0:12:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可派不上用场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.55,0:12:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没有舍弃希望
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.64,0:12:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站上舞台 在人群前展现才艺
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.14,0:12:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是甘美的 无比甘美的毒药!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.20,0:12:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸引观众的目光
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.56,0:12:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煽动他们 诱惑他们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.72,0:12:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那热情 那兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.29,0:12:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,支配一切的全能感!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.31,0:13:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦体验过 可不是那么容易能够遗忘的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.93,0:13:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这你也应该非常了解吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.35,0:13:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然能做到这一步
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.10,0:13:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从距今为止收集的证据看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.24,0:13:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经坏掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.52,0:13:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.77,0:13:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经做好觉悟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.17,0:13:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不在这吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.59,0:13:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该在附近吃着路边的草
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.60,0:13:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 一定 会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.11,0:13:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对不起 痛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.22,0:13:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.36,0:13:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 果然和我想的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布雷拉有点像哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.09,0:13:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你有妹妹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.43,0:14:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许吧 我没有过去的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.23,0:14:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不知道有没有亲人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.50,0:14:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 我和一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.71,0:14:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也记不起过去的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.82,0:14:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的你 为什么会去唱歌 会去当歌手?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.27,0:14:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.24,0:14:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢唱歌 所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.05,0:14:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的你即使在唱歌 看起来也不高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.93,0:14:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为了什么 为了谁而歌唱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.60,0:14:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想传达给大家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.83,0:14:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 你会听吗 我的歌?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.16,0:14:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你便
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.57,0:15:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 以为自己是为了传达给大家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.55,0:15:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直这么认定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.38,0:15:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.79,0:15:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 其实是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.99,0:15:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得去弄明白!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.22,0:15:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.22,0:15:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.47,0:16:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰华今天的表现更出色了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.23,0:16:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我们也不能出错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.18,0:16:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可别落后 卢卡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.56,0:16:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白 你想我和你们在一起飞行了多久啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.96,0:16:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 别一个人偷偷干事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.07,0:16:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是一个团队
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.54,0:16:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.56,0:16:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着啊 雪露
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.74,0:16:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米歇尔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.41,0:16:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.02,0:17:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在 阿露特
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.74,0:17:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要上啦!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.99,0:17:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿露特
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.06,0:17:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 果然 我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.68,0:17:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 请紧抱在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.57,0:17:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到银河的尽头!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.20,0:17:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.40,0:17:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逃避
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.55,0:18:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 雪露怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.59,0:18:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一副活蹦乱跳的样子 让我一下子松了口气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.08,0:18:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反复无常和毒舌都一如既往
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.91,0:18:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是变本加厉了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.75,0:18:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟钝也适可而止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.12,0:18:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该给出答案了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.03,0:18:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么答案啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.80,0:18:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.38,0:18:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是你 应该也察觉到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.57,0:18:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的歌声和刚才的歌声
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.15,0:18:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰华她只是向着你 为了你才唱歌的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.11,0:18:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.27,0:18:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪露也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.85,0:18:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在她正处在很痛苦的时期
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.25,0:18:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 当她知道这一切后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.08,0:18:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个想到的却是你…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.61,0:18:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要对阿露特说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.57,0:19:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.81,0:19:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙她怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.65,0:19:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想被你这种朝三暮四的人在女人的问题上说教
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.02,0:19:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我很懦弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.41,0:19:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类这种 不知道何时就会死去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.10,0:19:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是对我们飞行员来说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.21,0:19:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交往的对手都是些逢场作戏的人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.35,0:19:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去爱或是被爱都是可怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.55,0:19:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你不一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.07,0:19:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪露
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.01,0:19:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就交给你了 阿露特
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.46,0:19:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.32,0:20:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿露特
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.28,0:20:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.32,0:20:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船内有Vajra的幼虫?!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.60,0:20:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样?!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.82,0:21:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.78,0:21:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱昂三岛首席副官
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.96,0:21:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以特别渎职罪 违反保密法以及预谋暴乱罪告发你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.82,0:21:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没想到你在策划政变啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.92,0:21:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这下该结束了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.04,0:21:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾啊 稍微晚了一些呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.78,0:21:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得不错
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.70,0:21:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不知道这样做是好是坏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.53,0:21:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是好事了 大概…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.67,0:21:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都会想对心仪的人表白呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.57,0:22:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿露特 阿露特 阿露特
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.41,0:22:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些话我要对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.52,0:22:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心意 一定要告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.07,0:22:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.88,0:22:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兰华
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.84,0:23:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭到Vajra袭击的Frontier
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.37,0:23:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在悲剧的大幕拉开的时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.51,0:23:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流出的眼泪化作繁星
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.07,0:24:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一集 Diamond Crevasse
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.49,0:24:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镇魂之歌 响彻银河
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.66,0:18:00.03,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}アナタノオト　ドクン　ドクン　ドクン
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.36,0:18:04.37,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}聞こえてくるよ　ドクン　ドクン　ドクン
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.92,0:18:09.11,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}生きてるオト　優しいオト
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.98,0:18:42.90,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}雨が草を濡らすように　涙こぼれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.41,0:20:10.54,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}見詰め合えたら
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.36,0:20:38.16,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}永遠に　守りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.83,0:20:43.20,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}アナタノオト　ドクン　ドクン　ドクン
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.50,0:20:47.96,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}かすかだけれど ドクン　ドクン　ドクン


Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.21,0:05:43.10,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}Baby どうしたい　操縦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.92,0:05:48.39,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}ハンドル　きゅっと握って　もう　スタンバイ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.72,0:05:52.47,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}Want my heart&want my love?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.56,0:05:58.93,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}NO?! んもう！　スウィングしてKISS!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.28,0:06:02.13,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}中途半端なスタイルはNO
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.02,0:06:06.60,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}ブッ飛んじゃってるLOVEならfor me
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.44,0:06:18.91,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}欲したら　　ラララ　possibilities
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.19,0:06:26.96,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}.I don't care $how much fake
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.93,0:06:30.96,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}.ふたつにひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.98,0:06:34.25,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}but　愛なら　して
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.51,0:15:34.74,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}会話などなしに
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.10,0:15:38.57,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}内側に潜って
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.88,0:15:41.99,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}考えが読み取れる
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.46,0:15:44.32,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}不思議な夜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.71,0:15:49.58,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}あなたの名　呪文みたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.93,0:15:52.09,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}無限のリピート
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.79,0:15:56.60,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}憎らしくて手の甲に
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.97,0:15:59.59,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}爪をたててみる
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.31,0:16:00.80,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}キラッ!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.02,0:16:03.98,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}身体ごと透き通り
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.34,0:16:07.67,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}絵のように漂う　uh uh
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.08,0:16:11.41,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}けし粒の生命でも
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.69,0:16:14.78,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}私たち瞬いてる
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.98,0:16:19.41,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}魂に銀河　雪崩れてく
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.42,0:16:22.33,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}流星にまたがって
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.55,0:16:25.96,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}あなたに急上昇　oh oh
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.44,0:16:29.57,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}濃紺の星空に
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.80,0:16:33.08,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}私たち花火みたい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.70,0:16:38.59,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}心が光の矢を放つ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.82,0:16:48.01,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}けし粒の生命でも
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.07,0:16:51.45,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}私たち瞬いてる
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.50,0:16:56.44,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}魂に銀河　雪崩れてく
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.03,0:17:04.68,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\an7}魂に銀河　雪崩れてく

Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.21,0:05:43.10,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}Baby 想做什么？ 操纵这飞机
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.92,0:05:48.39,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}紧紧握住方向盘  已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.72,0:05:52.47,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}想要我的心和我的爱吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.56,0:05:58.93,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}No?! 别这样！ 盘旋着吻我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.28,0:06:02.13,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}不要半途而废
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.02,0:06:06.60,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}爱我的话为我飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.86,0:06:09.18,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}Beautiful! Excuse me!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.44,0:06:18.91,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}想要的话  啦啦啦  有可能哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.19,0:06:26.96,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}我不介意有多少$
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.93,0:06:30.96,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}我们合二为一吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.98,0:06:34.25,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}只要 有爱 就这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.71,0:06:50.78,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}What'bout my star?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.35,0:06:59.39,Lyric,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}How fantastic to be with you. My love!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.51,0:15:34.74,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}已不需要 相互交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.10,0:15:38.57,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}悄悄遛入心的里面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.88,0:15:41.99,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}能够读懂你的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.46,0:15:44.32,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}这不思议的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.71,0:15:49.58,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}你的名字是魔法的咒文
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.93,0:15:52.09,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}无止无尽地REPEAT
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.79,0:15:56.60,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}用指尖用力在手背划下痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.97,0:15:59.59,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}告诉我这是不是梦境
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.31,0:16:00.80,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}闪烁!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.02,0:16:03.98,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}身体渐渐透明
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.34,0:16:07.67,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}像画中那样飘浮而起   uh uh
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.08,0:16:11.41,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}就算飞散成星星点点的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.69,0:16:14.78,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}我们会光芒闪烁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.98,0:16:19.41,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}灵魂跃动起舞 银河般绮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.42,0:16:22.33,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}让我乘着流星
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.55,0:16:25.96,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}向着你直升而去 oh oh
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.44,0:16:29.57,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}今夜星空是一片藏青
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.80,0:16:33.08,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}我们就像那焰火
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.70,0:16:38.59,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}从心中放射出 闪光的轨迹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.82,0:16:48.01,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}就算飞散成星星点点的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.07,0:16:51.45,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}我们会光芒闪烁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.50,0:16:56.44,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\an7}灵魂跃动起舞 银河般绮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.03,0:17:04.68,Lyriccn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\an7}灵魂跃动起舞 银河般绮丽














