[Script Info]
;                                                                          Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
;                                                                          http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-05-03 08:37:21
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0071314D,&H907B7B8E,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFF0,&H0071314D,&H907B7B8E,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: OP-J,Old English Text MT,37,&H00E80074,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP-C,華康少女文字W6,27,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: ED1,ＤＦまるもじ体W3,29,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H009B54DA,&H8060C7E7,-1,0,0,0,80,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,30,30,8,1
Style: ED2,華康少女文字W6,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H009B54DA,&H8060C7E7,0,0,0,0,80,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,30,30,8,1
Style: biaoti,方正粗圆_GBK,33,&H00C1E7EB,&HFFFFFFF0,&H40000000,&H201F3241,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.22,0:21:53.00,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(160,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組製作(bbs.dmguo.com)\N僅供試看,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.07,0:21:58.44,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(160,500)}翻譯:Grubby 校對:迦羅葉夕驀 時間:尤斯蒂婭 雜工:Ichino MKV:神戶アキラ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.06,0:00:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.42,0:00:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 只是暈過去而已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.58,0:00:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人所擁有的負能量太少了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.43,0:00:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這隻驅魂就以量來取勝
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.66,0:00:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.67,0:00:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.48,0:00:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.86,0:00:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放走的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.15,0:02:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺跟之前的驅魂不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.78,0:02:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 這隻驅魂有臉 是LV3吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.96,0:02:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.96,0:02:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能硬上了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.45,0:03:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行動停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.26,0:03:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.95,0:03:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拘留瓶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.08,0:03:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 不愧是白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.88,0:03:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.05,0:03:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放開我！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.36,0:04:02.87,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓不住 抓不住…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.86,0:04:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與我無關哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.29,0:04:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家應該都失去知覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.83,0:04:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 這難道是？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.65,0:04:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是驅魂搞的鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.83,0:04:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅魂利用心靈空隙操控他們
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.29,0:04:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 該怎麼辦才能讓大家復原呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.76,0:04:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.06,0:04:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把驅魂關進拘留瓶就能復原了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.94,0:04:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西 制止他們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.74,0:04:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 我制止住了 快趁現在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.19,0:04:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.09,0:04:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 用手怎麼可能全制止得了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.47,0:04:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用羽衣一口氣全部制止住啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.55,0:05:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 一次性制止那麼多目標我還做不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.07,0:05:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.73,0:05:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅魂 逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.00,0:05:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.64,0:05:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羽衣的複數控制 初級中的初級啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.95,0:05:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.73,0:05:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.00,0:05:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一個人夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.93,0:05:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要你幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.70,0:05:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,單幹的話 還會失敗的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.44,0:05:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟艾露西一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.02,0:05:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已經抓獲5隻驅魂了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.30,0:05:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.73,0:05:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是這話題？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.45,0:06:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直是胡扯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.85,0:06:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信艾露西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.76,0:06:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西是個連羽衣都用不好的吊車尾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.17,0:06:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也看到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.49,0:06:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是我做得更好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.42,0:06:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在學校我明明很優秀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.17,0:06:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將鐮刀授予第203屆首席畢業生以示鼓勵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.26,0:06:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.13,0:06:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐮刀擁有者是我的朋友 我要去跟大家炫耀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.06,0:06:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直是首席
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.03,0:06:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直是大家的榜樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.61,0:06:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的我 會需要艾露西的幫助嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.61,0:07:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一個人就夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.43,0:07:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 站住
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.06,0:07:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西 跟她一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.91,0:07:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 為什麼大神會跟白婭在一起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.95,0:07:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我卻一直很冷淡的說
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.14,0:07:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這其中是有原因的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.01,0:07:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起這些 趕快去幫白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.27,0:07:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正去了也只是拖後腿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.55,0:07:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的啦 白婭很優秀一個人就夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.26,0:07:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少囉嗦跟我來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.30,0:07:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.34,0:07:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要從頭開始找
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.08,0:08:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學校的模擬捕獲 行動模式很顯而易見
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.67,0:08:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實戰 完全沒手冊上寫的那麼簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.68,0:08:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 搭檔也一直決定不下來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.68,0:08:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢業後盡是失敗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.15,0:08:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不該這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.87,0:08:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不該…這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.38,0:08:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.01,0:08:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭肯定會很活躍的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.09,0:09:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.00,0:09:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭可是天才啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.60,0:09:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厲害厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.08,0:09:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神 探測器…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.13,0:09:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然在上面啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.29,0:09:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.92,0:09:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把艾露西帶來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.75,0:09:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅魂在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.53,0:09:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 聽到我說話沒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.09,0:09:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你誰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.39,0:09:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要妨礙我！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.10,0:10:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.15,0:10:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神 白婭…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.27,0:10:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭被驅魂操控了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.01,0:10:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是惡魔 竟然還被抓住心靈間隙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.03,0:10:21.12,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住他 抓住他…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.80,0:10:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神 該怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.19,0:10:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾也自己想想辦法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.86,0:10:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 那個
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.29,0:11:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭與大家都被操控了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.73,0:11:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就首先從驅魂入手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.86,0:11:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 請放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.98,0:11:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神 既要對付白婭和學生們
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.56,0:11:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要捕捉驅魂是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.60,0:11:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西 好好想想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.96,0:11:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在應該對付的只有一人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.35,0:11:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.48,0:11:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭現在很煩惱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.92,0:11:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份心情被驅魂所利用了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.37,0:11:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去填補白婭的心靈空隙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.31,0:11:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 是我啊艾露西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.38,0:12:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 聽到沒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.49,0:12:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好燙好燙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.55,0:12:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.68,0:12:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准接近我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.29,0:12:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准觸摸我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.60,0:12:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 振作點
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.18,0:12:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被驅魂操控 不像是白婭該有的樣子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.69,0:12:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.72,0:12:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說得那麼簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.79,0:13:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.80,0:13:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭不會失敗啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.37,0:13:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為白婭是優等生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.65,0:13:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說得那麼簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.59,0:13:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我為此付出了多少努力去學習
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.20,0:13:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力地 努力地學習啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.16,0:13:27.99,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.24,0:13:29.31,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.22,0:13:31.05,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.18,0:13:32.03,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.33,0:13:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 一點用都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.85,0:13:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使在校學習是多麼地優秀
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.32,0:14:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連捕捉從自己手中逃跑的驅魂都做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.24,0:14:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.50,0:14:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點都不想見艾露西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.92,0:14:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰都不想見
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.67,0:14:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什麼都做不了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.83,0:14:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須拯救她 一定要拯救白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.86,0:14:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我該怎麼做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.94,0:14:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.44,0:14:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 你幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.10,0:14:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.03,0:14:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經無法挽回了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.63,0:14:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎麼做也沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.25,0:14:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經沒救了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.42,0:15:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.79,0:15:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.01,0:15:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.22,0:15:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會沒事啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.31,0:15:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我心中 白婭依然是個厲害的惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.42,0:15:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論是從前 或是未來
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.51,0:15:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧白婭教我羽衣的用法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.19,0:15:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才能像這樣飛翔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.34,0:16:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以白婭為模範 模仿白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.60,0:16:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 不論發生什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.13,0:16:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到死都會深信不疑白婭很厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.11,0:16:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.62,0:16:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.62,0:16:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太失望了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.32,0:16:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然淪落到被艾露西鼓勵
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.86,0:16:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.00,0:16:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是回到了原點呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.37,0:16:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.43,0:17:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像變輕鬆了點
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.52,0:17:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白婭 復原了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.03,0:17:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你操心了 艾露西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.86,0:17:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 利索地解決它吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.85,0:17:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 但是該怎麼抓捕它呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.25,0:17:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼多的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.60,0:17:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用跟剛才相反的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.61,0:17:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來制止人類 這次由艾露西去抓驅魂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.52,0:17:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 由我來？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.96,0:17:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比較熟練
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.55,0:17:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然沒能說出口 其實我…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.40,0:18:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連一隻驅魂都沒抓到過
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.99,0:18:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西 前面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.11,0:18:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羽衣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.95,0:18:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我沒關係哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.72,0:18:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.02,0:18:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西 用羽衣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.97,0:18:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 對
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.20,0:19:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.85,0:19:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾露西 趁現在
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.25,0:19:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有破綻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.62,0:19:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了哦 白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.91,0:20:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收下真的沒關係嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.10,0:20:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是艾露西抓的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.43,0:20:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 這是白婭的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.09,0:20:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是白婭把它趕出心靈間隙的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.48,0:20:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我的首個成果嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.12,0:20:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本想更華麗地抓住的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.82,0:20:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢來 慢慢來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.18,0:20:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.67,0:20:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼連我也被抓住
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.70,0:20:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.52,0:20:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也給你添麻煩了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.31,0:20:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為賠償 跟你握手也行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.57,0:20:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到你還真是個好人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.09,0:20:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒抓住過驅魂的事 一直閉口不說
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.78,0:21:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份人情 總有一天會還的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.69,0:21:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後會有期
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.71,0:21:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說大神 跟白婭悄悄地說了些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.12,0:21:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼 怎樣都行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.92,0:21:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 就我一人被排除在外
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.70,0:21:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.40,0:21:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天被你救了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.85,0:21:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真虧你說服了白婭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.47,0:21:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大神 肚子餓嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.06,0:21:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我請你吃蛋餅炒麵麵包哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.90,0:21:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為都幾點了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.11,0:21:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那就明天
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.80,0:21:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.93,0:21:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要2份蛋餅炒麵麵包
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.79,0:21:59.98,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(650,0)}{\pos(300,400)}FLAG 4.0 地區長 奪回尊嚴
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.86,0:21:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼…還在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.07,0:23:44.99,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs27\1a&HFF&\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HA20000&\bord1\4c&HA20000&\shad0\pos(401,221)}FLAG 5.0\N 好不容易到了 卻是連綿細雨
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.07,0:23:44.99,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs27\1a&HFF&\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HA20000&\bord1\4c&HA20000&\shad0\pos(400,220)}FLAG 5.0\N 好不容易到了 卻是連綿細雨
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.66,0:23:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一說 人類只活用了3成的腦能力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.34,0:23:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換句話說 如果能全都運用到的話
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.41,0:23:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在玩GALGAME時能獲得現在的3倍快感
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.13,0:23:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊我的腦 Fight my brain！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.97,0:23:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥大人 還要玩遊戲嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.20,0:00:56.20,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K30}I {\K30}don't {\K50}wanna {\K20}let {\K20}the {\K40}chance {\K40}slip {\K70}away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.30,0:00:59.40,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K40}Why {\K30}is {\K50}my {\K60}freedom {\K60}taken {\K70}away?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.50,0:01:02.00,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K70}Reason {\K70}as {\K50}against {\K60}emotion
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.10,0:01:07.10,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}I've {\K40}gotta {\K50}deal {\K70}with {\K50}extreme {\K270}frustration
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.20,0:01:10.30,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K30}All {\K40}my {\K30}efforts {\K60}will {\K40}never {\K30}be {\K30}in {\K50}vain
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.50,0:01:13.30,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K60}Endless {\K60}desire,{\K50}like {\K30}a {\K40}haunting {\K40}refrain
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.40,0:01:16.60,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}Such {\K30}a {\K30}pain,{\K30}the {\K60}ideal {\K50}versus {\K40}the {\K60}real
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.90,0:01:19.10,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}There {\K30}is {\K10}a {\K50}way {\K20}to {\K30}change {\K20}the {\K40}world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.20,0:01:20.70,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}Just {\K30}count {\K20}on {\K80}me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.90,0:01:23.90,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}So {\K60}what {\K50}if {\K40}sing {\K50}off-key,{\K30}who {\K50}cares
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.10,0:01:26.20,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K30}Not {\K30}good {\K30}at {\K40}drawing,{\K20}no {\K20}big {\K40}deal
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.30,0:01:30.80,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K15}Let {\K15}me {\K10}go {\K30}for {\K20}my {\K20}one {\K40}true {\K300}belief
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.10,0:01:32.70,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K80}Overcome {\K80}myself
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.10,0:01:32.70,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K80}Overcome {\K80}yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.80,0:01:35.80,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}"A {\K40}whole {\K40}new {\K40}world {\K20}god {\K70}only {\K70}knows"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.10,0:01:38.90,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K80}I'll {\K40}always {\K30}be {\K30}on {\K30}your {\K70}side
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.30,0:01:40.00,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K40}I {\K30}know {\K40}you're {\K60}hurting {\K100}inside
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.00,0:01:42.40,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K40}To {\K20}be {\K20}a {\K80}knight {\K40}to {\K30}be {\K10}a {\K60}light {\K20}for {\K20}you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.50,0:01:43.40,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K15}We'll {\K15}be {\K30}shining {\K30}bright
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.40,0:01:44.90,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}No {\K20}more {\K40}fears {\K20}no {\K20}more {\K30}tears
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.00,0:01:46.10,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K60}Everything {\K20}will {\K15}work {\K15}out
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.30,0:01:48.30,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K30}That's"{\K40}God {\K60}only {\K70}knows"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.60,0:01:50.50,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K40}Don't {\K40}get {\K70}me {\K40}wrong
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.80,0:01:53.10,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K30}This {\K40}in {\K20}not {\K50}real {\K30}love {\K60}but
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.20,0:01:55.70,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}I'll {\K20}do {\K80}anything {\K30}for {\K100}you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.90,0:01:58.80,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K60}Whatever {\K20}happens {\K20}in {\K20}my {\K20}life,{\K20}turn {\K20}the {\K20}page {\K20}and {\K20}come {\K20}of {\K30}age
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.50,0:02:01.80,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K110}(Remenber,{\K70}no {\K20}one {\K40}can {\K30}judge {\K60}me)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:02:02.10,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K30}Every {\K30}end {\K20}leads {\K10}to {\K10}a {\K20}new {\K50}beginning {\K20}of {\K20}the {\K30}next {\K60}stage
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.30,0:02:04.80,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}Try {\K10}to {\K20}make {\K20}my {\K20}life {\K40}complate,{\K30}trust {\K90}myself
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.90,0:02:07.20,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K20}Be {\K40}strong {\K30}and {\K30}do {\K40}my {\K70}best
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.50,0:02:16.20,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1vc(E80074,F152F1,FFFFFF,FB9733)}{\K80}Don't {\K80}look {\K170}back,{\K60}carry {\K480}on
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,OP-J,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.00,0:22:06.36,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}コイはなくてアイよ あなたを思うだけで切ない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.48,0:22:11.49,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}毎日の色が鮮やかに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.59,0:22:27.26,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}いつか会えると占い信じて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.40,0:22:33.21,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}派手なスカーフを胸に飾ってた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.36,0:22:39.22,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}空は青くて 小鳥がさえずる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.50,0:22:45.27,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}何か始りそう そんな予感する
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.41,0:22:51.28,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}昨日の私 もう脱ぎ捨てて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.52,0:22:56.74,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}未知なる世界へ 新しい誕生日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.88,0:23:03.45,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}コイはなくてアイよ 絶対失いたくはないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.56,0:23:08.77,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今までの人と何かが違うDestiny
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.91,0:23:15.52,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}コイはなくてアイよ あなたを思うだけで切ない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.62,0:23:24.70,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}アイシテル I LOVE YOU 心から
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.00,0:22:06.36,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}這是愛而非戀 想到你就會傷感
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.48,0:22:11.49,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}每天都變得五彩繽紛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.59,0:22:27.26,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}迷信說我們能再見的占卜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.40,0:22:33.21,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}胸前點綴上鮮艷的方巾
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.36,0:22:39.22,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}天是那麼藍 小鳥在歌唱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.50,0:22:45.27,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我預感到 將會有新的際遇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.41,0:22:51.28,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}擺脫昨天的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.52,0:22:56.74,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奔向未知的世界 迎來嶄新的生日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.88,0:23:03.45,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}這是愛而非戀 我絕不想失去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.56,0:23:08.77,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}命運不同於曾出現的所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.91,0:23:15.52,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}這是愛而非戀 想到你就會傷感
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.62,0:23:24.70,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我愛你 I LOVE YOU 真心愛你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.98,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,


