Perfect memorization.
Index apparently used 85% of her brain's capacity to memorize 103,000 grimoires.
Since she can only use the remaining 15%, she needs to have her memories erased every year or else she'll die...
...said the magician.
And only three days remain until that limit.
Wait, I was out cold for three days?!
Well then, Kamijyo-chan, Sensei's going out now.
#05 Limit
Midnight
I might be back late,
so take care of the house while I'm away.
Please, don't hurt Touma anymore!!!
There's twelve hours and thirty-eight minutes left until the limit.
We were going to see the effect of the "fetter"
depending on whether you chose to escape or not,
but this exceeds our expectations.
Fetter...
If you don't want us to take away that "toy",
then I suggest you throw away the idea of escaping.
You hear me?
You'll be all right.
If I negotiate with them,
your daily life won't get altered any further.
I won't let them step any further into your life...
...so it's... all-
Index!
It's me.
You know who I am?
Kanzaki... was it?
We don't need to know each other's names.
Is she... is Index there?
Must I wake her?
Good.
Listen as you are.
The limit is tonight at midnight.
We are preparing our schedule to finish everything to match that exact time.
Why are you telling me this?
Now that you've told me,
don't you think I'd resist until the very end?
Don't you need some time for farewells?
This is neither a conversation nor a negotiation.
It's an order.
Bid her farewell before we arrive and leave that room.
All of you are pushing your own incompetence on others...
You guys are magicians, aren't you?
Will magic really not solve anything?
Won't Index be able to find a solution using her 103,000 grimoires?
Of everything, the Church fears
a rebellion from Index the most.
What's that supposed to mean?
There are most likely biases amongst those grimoires,
such as, she is not allowed to learn anything related to Mind Hound.
Then, your own magic can't solve anything?
There is a fear magicians outside of Necessarius would dispel environments created by magic.
There is no way the Church would allow such possibilities to happen.
And most importantly, the act of memorizing grimoires itself signifies the contamination of the brain.
You guys knowingly let Index...
We were only informed afterwards.
Magic... won't solve anything...
What about... us?
Us?
The science side.
We have many methods of scientifically removing people's memories.
We could have a solution you don't have that could remove the 103,000 grimoires from her brain.
And this is Academy City!
There are plenty of espers that can control one's heart.
It's too early to give up all hope!
Are you still going to give up trying or challenging things
and put someone's life at risk?
These are cheap words for persuading your enemy.
If you look at it from our side,
at least we have successfully saved her life.
We do not trust your bet that has nothing to support itself.
Don't you think that this is neither trying nor challenging,
but rather, just, recklessness?
Right.
In the end, there is no place for a truce.
Fine.
Then I'll crush you, arch-rival.
I'll save her and steal all the heroic moments for myself!
If she collapses again, consider it too late.
See you at midnight, then.
There really is little time remaining...
Show us a sensational struggle to the end...
Memory loss.
Loss of memory due to aging is one kind of memory loss,
as well as the loss of memory caused by the stoppage of blood to the brain.
Loss of memory from side effects of halothane, isoflurane, general anesthesia, or benzodiazepine, same thing...
I'm not getting anywhere like this.
Cellphone bill?
Right!
I'll just ask Komoe-sensei to introduce me to
a neurological research or mental ability institute!
What the hell are you doing, Komoe-sensei?!
Looks like I'll just have to call random places...
Next.
Damn it!
Hello?
Perfect memorization?
Yes, I know of it...
But, you need to tell me the symptoms...
Huh?! Magic?
What time of the day do you think it is right now?
It's almost midnight, you know?
Hello?
Hello?!
Gosh!
Index...
Outta the way.
Refer to Moonchild.
We'll have an angel descend and create its temple in this room.
We're going to kill her memories.
W-Wait...
Please wait.
There's 1,800,000 espers in this Academy City...
...and more than one thousand research facilities!
If we go to those places, we might not have to use this last resort!
You guys don't want to use this method either, right?
You're hoping that there's some other way deep inside your heart, right?
Then wait a bit longer!
I'll find a way to resolve this so that everyone is smiling and happy in the end!
Is that all you have to say?
Look at her!
Can you spit out the same words in front of her?
A person who has fought against this all her life...
A patient who can't even open her eyes because of all the pain...
Can you tell her to wait a bit because you want to try some stuff out?
To let doctors whose name and face are unknown... to let them play around with her body...
...and let her waste away with drugs...
...that's not something a human can come up with...
Answer me!
Are you still human?
Or a monster that quit being human?
This is an artifact necessary for removing her memory,
a magic ornament.
Touch it with your right hand,
and that should be enough to dispel its magic.
We're just killing her memories.
She'll still have her life.
But if your trials fail, she will die.
So can you still do it?
In front of her?
Can you still take this away in front of a girl in that much pain?
If you trust your abilities that much, then do it!
You blasted mutant that thinks of yourself as a hero!
My name is Index.
I'd be grateful if you could help me fill up my stomach.
The ritual will begin at 12:15 AM.
We will borrow the powers of Leo to kill her memories.
Understood.
Hey, magician.
How should I say my final goodbye to her?
I don't have a single second to spare for that.
Would you mind just disappearing from here, monster?
Your right hand took out my flames.
I still don't understand the principle behind it,
but I don't want any single thing to influence the ritual.
Why...
Why don't I even have the ability to save one girl in pain?
There's about ten minutes before the start of the ritual, correct?
The night when we swore to erase her memories for the first time,
we wept next to her the entire night.
B-But!
We don't know what this guy's gonna do in his current state!
What if this guy tries to commit a double suicide the second we let our eyes off him?
Don't you think he would've touched the cross already?
It is exactly because we have
confirmed him to still be human
that you wanted to test him, right?
But...
Either way, the ritual won't begin until the time comes.
If he still has regrets,
then there is a danger that we will have obstacles during the ritual, Stiyl.
You have ten minutes!
Okay?
Tou...ma...
Index.
Sorry.
Touma, there seems to be a formation in this room.
Something about a regeneration magic.
Magic... whose?
Those magicians came again, right?
Touma, you need to run!
It's okay now, Index.
Touma!
It's over.
It's all over.
Touma...
Sorry.
I'll become stronger.
I won't ever lose again.
Those people that treat you this way,
I'll kick every one of their butts, that's how strong I'll become...
Wait for me.
This time...
This time, I'll save you all the way.
Okay...
I'll wait...
Damn this!
I can't allow this worst kind of ending, right?
I couldn't do anything in the end.
I couldn't do anything about the 103,000 grimoires that occupy 85% of her brain,
nor could I protect the one-year's worth of memories inside the remaining 15%.
Wait, huh?
85% of her brain is allocated to the 103,000 grimoires.
That is why she can only use 15% of a normal person's brain capacity.
Memory erasure takes place in exact one year periods.
Hold it...
Why can she only live for one year with 15% of her brain?
No, even before that...
...how did Kanzaki get to numbers like 85% or 15%?
Hello?
Ah, that must be your voice, Kamijyo-chan!
You shouldn't be using Sensei's phone without her permission, you know?
Huh, perfect memorization?
Yes, it is a rare case, but that by itself is just a physical condition.
And will one use up 15% of a brain's capacity in one year?
Rather, it's a miserable physical condition where one's brain breaks down around the age of six to seven, right?
It's true that people with perfect memorization can't forget the single smallest thing,
but one's brain definitely won't break down because of that.
A human's brain can store 140 years worth of memories to begin with.
It's impossible for a human brain to break down?
We just don't have one place for memories to begin with.
We have semantic memory,
which governs language and knowledge.
We have procedural memory,
which governs the know-how of your motor functions.
And finally, we have episodal memory,
which governs your memories.
Something like that.
So, there's plenty of them.
Plenty.
So, umm... Sensei.
I don't get what you're saying.
Basically, no matter how much knowledge you force into the brain,
it won't create so much pressure that the brain blows open.
That's impossible, at least, in neurology~
Index's perfect memorization isn't a life-threatening condition.
That would mean that the Church lied to Kanzaki.
Then, why is Index in pain?
The Church messed with Index's brain...
...and made it so that she would die
if her memories weren't killed in one-year periods.
That way, Index, who possesses 103,000 grimoires, would never betray them.
That way, Index's friends will have to swallow their tears and obey them.
But what exactly did the Church do to her?
If you trust your abilities that much, then do it!
You blasted mutant that pretends to be a hero!
I'm not pretending to be a hero.
I will become one!
Huh?
Nothing's happening, which means...
...I'm not touching anything supernatural?
So, is there any place I haven't touched yet?
Don't tell me...
Warning.
Chapter 3, Verse 2.
Confirmed the penetration of seals 1 to 3.
Preparing to regenerate.
Failure.
Auto-regeneration cannot be carried out.
Presently, in order to protect the library of 103,000 grimoires,
prioritizing engaging with the intruder.
Reverse engineering the magic formula that destroyed the barriers, based on the 103,000 grimoires.
Failure.
No applicable spell found.
Forcing the disclosure of the spell's composition and constructing a local weapon against the intruder.
Successfully constructed the most effective weapon against the intruder.
Now initiating local weapon, "St. George's Sanctuary".
Proceeding to destroy intruder.
Next Episode
St. George's Sanctuary...
...has created an infinite amount of distance between me and Index.
But just one more step...
...if I can just take one more step...
I will definitely reach her!
Next time, "Imagine Breaker".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!