I... I...
...killed again, didn't I?
#07 Science Worship
Misawa Cram School
Such misfortune...
To think that a little reference textbook would cost as much as 3,600 yen...
Touma.
What could we have done with 3,600 yen?
Don't say anything.
Hey, To-u-ma.
What could we have done?
All right, all right!
If I had studied every day, I wouldn't have ended up in this-
Hey, what are you looking at?
No...
Normal people don't eat 3,600 yen
worth of ice cream, okay?
Touma!
I didn't let out a single word like
"hot", "unpleasant", or "tired" at all, okay?
Neither have I ever thought of using someone else's money,
and in conclusion, I have never thought about wanting to eat ice cream at all!
All right...
Just say that you want to eat
some ice cream in a store with air conditioning.
Touma, this clothing is a materialization of The Lord's protection.
Never have I ever said that this was uncomfortable, hot,
or wanted to try a "nuts, I can't even tell the difference between summer and winter clothing" experiment!
This very talkative sister and I have known each other for a while, it seems.
There's a reason why I say "it seems".
I don't possess any memories beyond two weeks ago.
And, for another reason, I am keeping this from others.
I especially don't want this sister to find out.
Her tears and her smile were directed at me before I lost my memories.
Touma!
What are you looking away for?
By the way, I am still in training,
so I am forbidden from consuming any luxury foods!
All right, we won't go for it then.
There's no need to force yourself to eat it.
While I am indeed forbidden,
as I am still a sister-in-training,
it would be kind of difficult, kind of not difficult for me to have flawless conduct.
Therefore, there could be a possibility that ice cream might accidentally fall into my mouth, Touma!
A rather interesting negotiation you got going there, Kami-yan.
Who's the lass, by the way?
Huh?
What, what's with your dull reaction?
Your memories got blown away from all this heat?
I'm just kidding, man!
Losing memories is a special privilege that belongs solely to mysterious, wave-emitting girls.
And, who is this miniature girl, really?
Hey, don't tell me it's a trap.
"Her" chest is a bit too flat for a girl.
You guys, there are things you can and can't say...
Even if she has a pedo body-
Touma.
I am a sister affiliated with the English Purist Church.
Repent now, or forever hold your peace.
Shake! Shake!
Three shake drinks!
Sorry, Kami-yan.
Letting you treat us.
So, it was all my treat in the end.
Such misfortune.
Touma, over here!
Oh, you found a place in this crowd-
Suspicious-looking...
Way too suspicious-looking...
Wh-What's the matter?
"S-"
"S-"?
You're sick or something?
Spent all my money on food...
Rock, paper, scissors!
All right!!!
Umm, you said you spent all your money or something?
The 100-yen hamburgers.
I had a lot of coupons for them...
...and so I went ahead and ordered thirty of them...
You got too much of a deal there, dumb girl.
Ah, no, it's not like that!
I... umm...
Frustration meal.
Cost of train ticket home, 600 yen.
And?
Total assets, 500 yen.
What's the connection here?
Spent too much.
No planning.
So... frustration meal...
Can't you borrow the train fee from someone?
That is a great proposal.
Oh, what a lovely lady.
Photo time!
Wh... Why are you staring at me?
Hey, don't look at me as if
you're expecting something from me!
100 yen, too much?
It is.
I will not lend something I will not lend.
Can't even let me borrow a mere 100 yen...
Who's the idiot that doesn't even have 100 yen?!
To be responding with such a frank response to a beautiful shrine girl.
You've grown up, Kami-yan!
Beautiful?
Lend me 100 yen since I'm beautiful.
Shut up! Quiet!
I've been pushed around by some threesome group and have absolutely no economic flexibility!
100 yen.
She's directed it at me!
Why even me?
You took a photo.
What, that cost money?
You want money for that?
Hmm, shrine girls in this city sell their faces, too?
I am not a shrine girl.
No matter who looks at you, they'll say you're a shrine girl.
I am a magician.
Magician?!
What, just "magician"?
Don't just give us something that vague and tell us your specialty, school, magic name, and order name, idiot!
Besides, if you're going to wear this clothing, at least pretend you're an oriental-style astrologist or something!
Then, I'll be that...
Okay, we understand that
this shrine girl is a shrine girl / magician,
so just quiet down for a bit.
Touma! Your attitude is completely different from when you dealt with me!
If that's what she wants to be, then let her be.
When I had to prove that magic was real,
you didn't believe me until you stripped me naked!
That's major, Kami-yan!
Who are these men?
Since when did they...
100 yen more.
Do you know these people?
Cram school teacher.
Cram school... teacher?
But, why does a cram school teacher have to look after a student?
Touma, what's the matter?
It's all because you said I stripped you naked...
What if they find out we're living together?
But...
To think that Kamijyo Touma had such bad friends...
Touma!
Hey, look! Look!
An abandoned cat?
Touma~ Hey~
No!
Touma, I didn't say anything yet!
We cannot have a pet!
Why?
Why can't we take Sphinx home?
We're not allowed to have pets in student dormitories,
so Sphinx can't-
Hey, don't give it a name already!
I DON'T CARE!
WANNA, WANNA, WANNA, WANNA!
No means no!
Look, you scared it away!
It's your fault!
Mine?
Japanese samisens are made with cat skin, you know?
This country does all these terrible things toward cats!
Oh yeah? Your country chases foxes around, too!
Fox hunting is a traditional and prideful-
What's this?
The flow of mana around here is being bundled together.
The attribute is earth.
The color is green.
This formula is a rune?
Hey, Index!
It seems like someone has set up a magic formation around here!
You go home first, Touma!
She tells me to go home, but...
What's this...
You should know what this is.
A rune, it's a rune.
One that removes people.
It's been a while, Kamijyo Touma.
Who is this guy?
Not even a "hi", eh?
Yes, yes, that's how our relationship should be like.
Index...
Don't worry about her.
She found a flow of mana and went to investigate it.
What kind of world was I in?
A daily life where abnormalities like magic surrounded me...
And, what do you want from me?
Quit grinning, else I'm gonna have to butcher ya.
Imagine Breaker...
Yes, yes, that's the face I wanted.
That's how our relationship should be, right?
I don't want you getting all friendly with me just because we fought on the same side once.
What do you want from me?!
A lil' secret talk.
Huh?
Take this.
Do you know of Misawa Cram School, the prep school?
Misawa Cram School?
There's a girl being imprisoned there.
Imprisoned?!
It seems Misawa Cram School has become
a phony religious cult devoted to science worship.
Nevermind what they teach there, the fact is Misawa Cram School has been taken over...
And this time, by a true and authentic magician...
No, an alchemist of the Zurich school, to be precise.
True and authentic?
Yeah, I know it sounds suspicious; I think so, too.
Huh, wait.
Aren't you a bit too perceptive?
Shit.
If he finds out I lost my memories...
What, because I just so happen to be listening attentively, you give me that?
Are you the type of person that likes
his entire conversation to be torn apart?
Whatever.
That the conversation is going smooth isn't a problem either.
The alchemist's name is Aureolus Izzard.
He's been hiding for three years now.
Whatever he's been doing for these three years...
...now, he's back...
For what?
Yes, that's the important part.
His target is the girl imprisoned at Misawa Cram School, Deep Blood.
Deep Blood?
The girl possesses the ability to kill
a certain organism; that is what he is after.
What's that... certain organism?
It's been called many things,
but in simple terms, a vampire.
Vampire?!
Do they really exist?
Not even we, magicians, know the details of that.
But, Deep Blood is, in other words, the "power to kill vampires".
So, we must meet the vampires first.
To do that, don't you think it's a better idea to be in control of Deep Blood?
What are you trying to say, after all this?
I'm in a desperate situation where I have to launch a strike on Misawa Cram School and rescue Deep Blood.
Please don't nod that easily.
You're coming with me, too.
I don't think you have the right to decline.
If you don't agree to me, Index will be taken away from you.
That's the direction we'll be heading in.
The role that Necessarius has given you is
a fetter so that Index doesn't betray them.
However, if you don't listen,
then you'd be practically useless.
You're being serious?
Do as you wish.
You're the one making the choice.
Welcome home!
Hey, Touma.
Hey, Index.
G-Go ahead.
Yeah, actually...
Umm, that stomach is...
Yeah, I might've eaten too much.
Wow, you've grown some splendid ones since the last time I saw you, Index.
I'm a growing girl.
Why you little...
What are you hiding inside your clothes?!
I... I'm not hiding anything!
In the name of Our Father, in Heaven,
there's no way a sister would lie.
So much for your faith.
Get that stray cat out of here already!
Sphinx!
Hey!
Touma, this clothing is called Walking Church.
So what?
And a church will open its arms
without condition to lost sheep.
Therefore, Sphinx, who was lost on the streets,
is now in the protection of the church, Amen.
So, you'd be fine with me putting toilet sand into your sleeves?
Whatever! I've decided that Sphinx will be protected by the church!
Don't decide so easily when you haven't thought it through!
It'll be fine!
You little...
Fine, you can have him.
Ah, Our Father, in Heaven...
...your warm light has finally reached
the heartless, cruel, cold-blooded Touma...
Excuse me...
Ah, Touma, weren't you going to say something to me, too?
Ah, right.
I seem to have dropped my reference book somewhere.
I'm going to go look for it, so could you stay home and watch over the place?
Yeah, sure.
There, there.
Don't let the cat out, okay?
Yeah!
Sphinx, there.
Good boy, good boy.
What are you doing?
I thought I should leave Innocentius here for her protection.
While we're at Misawa Cram School, there's a possibility other magicians might come here and take Index away.
So much trouble...
You... like Index?
Why the hell are you mentioning that all of a sudden?!
Sh-She's a target to be protected, not a target for romance...
So, umm...
I see.
I don't know what I thought of Index
or how I treated her before I lost my memories.
I have no choice but to desperately keep pretending to be "me".
What can I say... such misfortune...
It's like there's two of me.
This is Misawa Cram School?
It doesn't seem suspicious...
Suspicious, it doesn't seem...
However, the building itself is the alchemist's seal, right now.
Is he strong?
Aureolus Izzard...
The descendant of the famous Paracelsus...
What do you know of alchemists?
They can turn lead into gold,
and they can prepare a mixture that gives you immortality?
Yeah, something like that.
But, originally, alchemists had
an ultimate objective in the beginning.
To model everything in this world.
What's that supposed to mean?
If one could bring out whatever he or she imagined in their head into reality,
what do you think would happen?
Like, they can bring out anything?
There's no way we could beat that.
Then, what will you do?
You want to stay here and stand guard?
If you want to help, then confirm
Deep Blood's face and name right now.
Here, to be honest,
I can't tell the difference between oriental faces.
Her name is Himegami Aisa, apparently.
No way...
It seems... unexpectedly normal...
Of course.
On the surface, it's still functioning as a prep school.
Huh, what's... that?
A robot?
Is it broken?
What's the matter?
There's nothing here.
I think it's better if we move on.
Well, it might be a rare sighting for you.
If it's a robot, isn't that something on the science side?
What are you talking about?
This is just a corpse.
Next Episode
The ambition of the alchemist,
hiding on "the inner face of the coin".
The Thirteen Knights that fight against it.
The real objective of the imprisoned Himegami Aisa?
Next time, "Ars Magna".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!