Misaka Mikoto, aka Shocker,
ranked third among espers in the Academy City.
She's another one of my acquaintances from before I lost my memories.
And now, a sister who's a spitting image of her, suddenly appears.
Being taken for a ride by these two, I, Kamijyo Touma...
...had not yet noticed it then...
...noticed the significance of her sister's existence...
#11 Sisters
Why're you running?
Flashing your buttocks so joyfully at me like that...
You leading me on or something?
Now, question.
What am I, the Accelerator...
...doing exactly?
"Reflecting".
Sorry, that's not quite the true nature of my skill.
The answer is "vector change".
Momentum, heat, electric charge...
All kinds of "vectors" can be changed with just the touch of my skin.
I do have it set on "reflect" as default, though.
Now, time for the consolation prize question.
I am now touching the flow of blood.
If I reversed the direction of the flow,
what would happen to a human's body?
A correct answer and you will be given a peaceful... slumber...
Huh?
There, there.
Really, where did she go?
It... can't... be...
Hey.
Hey, you.
We'd like to ask you to come with us to the scene, if it's okay with you.
You think you can do that?
I will.
Hey!
Is something wrong?
The body was supposed to be... here...
Hey.
Okay.
There's nothing here, kid.
Someone... Someone really died here...
What's going on?
What's going on here?
Damn it!
Hey!
How is this possible?
"Forgive me."
"It was my intention to return once I was done with the operation," apologizes MISAKA first.
Huh, wait.
You're Misaka's sister, right?
Damn it, what was all that in the end?
Sorry, I just... thought you were dead all this time...
Thank God... and it looks like you're all right...
"MISAKA did actually die," reports MISAKA.
What... are you carrying?
"For security purposes, I am confirming the 'password' with you," as MISAKA proceeds.
"ZXC741ASD852QWE963," tests MISAKA you.
Wh...at?
"Not being able to decode the password shows that you are not related to the experiment," confirms MISAKA.
The thing inside your bag is...
"Sisters," answers MISAKA.
"I apologize for leaving the black cat behind," says MISAKA.
"However, I could not involve an animal in this unnecessary conflict," explains MISAKA.
"It seems I have given you unnecessary worries from this experiment," apologizes MISAKA.
"However, you need not worry."
"I assume you were the one that called the police."
"Every MISAKA here is MISAKA."
What... is this...
"The MISAKA that you have been in touch with is Serial Number 10032. This MISAKA."
"MISAKA uses the ability to control electricity, and links our brain waves together."
"The other MISAKA simply share MISAKA-10032's memories," explains MISAKA even further.
Who are you?
"Somatic cell clones, mass produced for military use,"
"that use Misaka Mikoto Oneesama, one of only seven Level 5s in the Academy City, as the original model."
"Sisters," answers MISAKA.
What are you doing?
"A simple experiment," answers MISAKA.
"I am not permitted to explain details as it is classified information,"
"but this is not an incident," defends MISAKA.
"I apologize once more for involving you in this experiment," as MISAKA lowers her head.
"Please care for the cat."
Experiment?
Military use?
Why are you wasting your time here?!
"MISAKA's-"
It's okay!
Just come.
Don't tell me...
...she knew about all this?
Itadakimasu!
-masu.
Since Himegami-chan is a guest, start with this.
Now, cook these pieces of meat for Sensei.
But...
Before that, let me tell a scary tale about the Academy City.
Sensei won't be crying just from seven mystery stories.
A component of the char from the yakiniku meat...
It actually leads to cancer.
Th-That kind of actual scary fact doesn't fit summer story telling!
Is this your plan to lower my appetite so that you can monopolize all the meat for yourself, Himegami-chan?
Another guest.
It's probably someone with a circulation notice, but could you go handle him appropriately, Himegami-chan?
In the meantime, Sensei will be cooking some meat and...
...eating up, okay?
I'm star-
Hmm, who was that?
No, nothing was there.
At least... At least feed him... feed Sphinx...
Touma just hasn't come back yet,
so I thought I'd die from starvation.
Don't worry!
It's just one or two more people.
This deluxe yakiniku set,
plentiful in quantity, can handle that.
Meat! Meat! Meat!
Next stop, "Seventh school district -
Tokiwadai Middle School Student Dormitory".
Misaka Mikoto
Room 208.
I see her, then what?
Am I going to ask about the details of a horrifying experiment where people get killed easily?
Yes?
Misaka?
This is Kamijyo.
Ahh... Kamijyo-san, you say?
Ah, sorry! I got the wrong room number.
No, no, don't worry.
I am Oneesama's roommate.
I see.
Yes, indeed.
Wait, where have I heard this voice before?
That's funny, I've heard your voice somewhere before...
AHHHHH!!!
You! You're the guy that rendez-vous-ed with Oneesama yesterday, aren't you?!
What do you need from Oneesama?
It's nothing major, but I-
How rather suspicious of you to be coming all the way here for "nothing major".
If she's not there, then it's okay.
Oneesama has not returned yet.
If you need to see her, I recommend you come in and wait for her.
Room 208.
It's here.
Come in.
The door isn't locked.
Coming in...
So it was you, after all.
Y... You're...
Don't tell me you and Oneesama
committed a mistake afterwards...
No, no, no!
I bet you wouldn't.
Besides, it doesn't seem like you're here to talk about such steamy subjects.
If you're going to wait for Oneesama, then take a seat on that bed.
Wait, that's kind of rude.
I didn't even get permission from her.
Don't worry.
That's my bed.
Then that's Misaka's...
What are you doing on someone else's bed?
What are you, a pervert?
Calling me a pervert is quite hard to ignore.
There are things that people consider
"this should be acceptable" inside their hearts.
You know, like playing the recorder that belongs to a girl you like,
or stealing the person's bike saddle.
I don't do any of that!
Is this the true state of rich girl schools?
Wait, so since you're Misaka's roommate, are you the same school grade as her?
You call her Oneesama, so I thought you were an underclassman.
No, no, I am an underclassman.
I am in a lower school grade, too.
Then, why are...
I had the previous tenant move out, and I moved in.
Legally, of course.
Oneesama has a lot of enemies, too.
Granted, it's the fate of those with power,
but for the person living in the
same room as her to be a traitor,
don't you think that's too painful?
And, you must be the gentleman that has been quarreling with Oneesama frequently, right?
Forgive me if I'm mistaken.
I simply wanted to see the face of the one that has been giving Oneesama support.
Support?
Is she back?
These footsteps...
This isn't good!
It's the dorm supervisor's inspection time!
What should we do?
If they find out that a gentleman is inside a room of Tokiwadai's girls' dormitory...
We're going to teleport outside for a bit, okay?
How come my power doesn't work on you?!
Umm... I'm sure my right hand's the problem...
We have no choice.
Go hide under the bed!
Ow!
Wait, it's impossible!
It's too tight!
Just get in!
It's so cramped in here.
Shirai, it's time for dinner!
Gather in the cafeteria.
Where's Misaka?
Oneesama's at make-up lessons.
Maybe it's taking longer.
I did not hear any reports of this.
If she is going to break curfew, then her roommate will also be deducted one point, okay?
Yes, I understand.
Zipper?
Sisters... this is...
Level 6?!
"From the estimated calculation using Tree Diagram,"
"it has been concluded that only one person can attain the unknown, Level 6."
"By preparing special battlefields,"
"and by fighting according to the scenario,"
"his growth will be stimulated by the battlefield..."
This is wrong.
Where... Where is she?
There's no wind, yet the propellers are turning?
Wind electricity is created from the rotation of the propellers.
Conversely, if electricity is being propagated through them, then the propellers will turn.
Her body generates voltage every second.
That means, if I follow those propellers...
Next Episode
The shocking truth written in the report.
For Misaka, who's shouldering the tragic fate of the Sisters to the point of being crushed, I...
Next time, "Level 6".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!