[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: opch,Kozuka Mincho Pr6N H,30,&H00ffffe8,&H00a00000,&H00a00000,&H80a00000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,10,1
Style: opjp,方正大标宋_GBK,24,&H00ffffff,&H0000ffff,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,3,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,FZZhunYuan-M02,28,&H00ffffff,&H0000ffff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,10,1
Style: opch1,EPSON 太明朝体Ｂ,24,&H00ffffe8,&H00a00000,&H00a00000,&H80a00000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,6,10,10,11,1
Style: opjp2,方正北魏楷书_GBK,24,&H00ffffff,&H0000ffff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,10,10,30,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.14,0:00:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驚爆危機\N FULL METAL PANIC
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.10,0:00:23.40,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}兩人一起尋找逃避之處
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.10,0:00:23.40,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K70}二{\K35}人{\K150}で{\K20}{\K15}逃{\K15}げ{\K25}場{\K25}所{\K80}探{\K30}し{\K150}て
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.50,0:00:30.80,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}在太陽雨中奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.50,0:00:30.80,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K50}走{\K50}っ{\K185}た{\K33}天{\K33}気{\K40}雨{\K70}の{\K180}中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.00,0:00:39.20,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}即使會失去什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.00,0:00:39.20,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K35}た{\K50}と{\K30}え{\K70}ば{\K75}何{\K40}か{\K80}を{\K30}失{\K45}う{\K30}と{\K80}し{\K30}て{\K150}も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.50,0:00:47.30,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}唯有一件事 一定要去保護
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.50,0:00:47.30,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K55}守{\K55}っ{\K85}て{\K30}行{\K40}か{\K30}な{\K180}ぎゃ {\K30}一{\K20}つ{\K30}だ{\K30}け{\K200}は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.20,0:00:55.30,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}誕生於這個世界的意義
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.20,0:00:55.30,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K48}こ{\K48}の{\K28}世{\K45}界{\K95}に{\K50}生{\K28}ま{\K28}れ{\K120}た{\K28}そ{\K28}の{\K45}意{\K30}味{\K70}を
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.80,0:01:01.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}與你一起去尋找
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.80,0:01:01.00,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K80}君{\K30}と{\K30}見{\K30}つ{\K80}け{\K30}に{\K50}行{\K40}こ{\K200}う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.00,0:01:06.30,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}即使擁抱著痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.00,0:01:06.30,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K60}痛{\K45}み{\45}さ{\K45}え{\K50}も{\K20} {\K90}抱{\K30}え{\K30}な{\K30}が{\K180}ら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.30,0:01:13.20,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}一起去迎接新的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.30,0:01:13.20,opch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K80}新{\K35}し{\K35}い{\K40}景{\K140}色 {\K40}迎{\K30}え{\K30}に{\K30}行{\K30}こ{\K250}う

Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.00,0:01:42.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連96式右關節脆弱的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.01,0:01:45.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都能忠實呈現出來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.21,0:01:46.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是Banpre
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.98,0:01:54.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.52,0:02:02.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,#14 習志野在燃燒著嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.83,0:02:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夏天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.46,0:02:05.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大海
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.13,0:02:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.56,0:02:09.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盛夏的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.10,0:02:11.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盛夏的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.80,0:02:14.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盛夏的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.57,0:02:16.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,(歡迎來到習志野)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.94,0:02:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,(陸上自衛隊駐紮地祭典)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.61,0:02:26.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盛夏的回憶，為什麼會變成這樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.88,0:02:28.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是至少都是千葉嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.92,0:02:29.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.72,0:02:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本來應該是去\N九十九里的海水浴場耶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.15,0:02:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,旅館住宿耶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.19,0:02:33.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,白色沙灘耶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.92,0:02:34.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,月球沙漠耶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.86,0:02:36.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有駱駝耶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.43,0:02:39.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會場的警備，似乎沒什麼問題
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.20,0:02:41.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要再玩了，快點過來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.40,0:02:43.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那傢伙嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.53,0:02:44.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然都是那傢伙害的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.23,0:02:47.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳這麼討厭的話\N不要來就好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.00,0:02:49.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對啊對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.01,0:02:51.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在相良答應風間的邀請時
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.91,0:02:53.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳提出抗議就好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.41,0:02:55.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都已經是高中生了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.81,0:02:59.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還耍性子\N破壞團體行動是不好的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.82,0:03:04.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說不定比去海水浴場還要刺激喔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.59,0:03:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像是超英俊的BS駕駛員過來搭訕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.52,0:03:08.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,“要不要跟我一起去坐BS？”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.92,0:03:11.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果被他這樣邀請的話\N我該怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.69,0:03:14.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那應該是叫作AS吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.53,0:03:19.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年一定要洗刷\N在駐紮地祭典所留下的污名
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.64,0:03:23.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓那些送來愚蠢挑戰書\N自稱“赤龍”的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.64,0:03:27.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,練馬的混蛋傢伙們\N見識一下什麼叫作地獄
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.04,0:03:29.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,期待諸位的表現
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.81,0:03:30.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.21,0:03:32.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開始搭乘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.75,0:03:33.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.76,0:03:42.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要來盤炒麵啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.76,0:03:45.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要買包\N習志野的名產落花生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.46,0:03:47.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不剝殼花生一堆200元喔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.13,0:03:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來喔來喔，這是最高級的\N練馬蘿蔔喔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.27,0:03:52.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來啊，小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.77,0:03:53.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,試吃看看嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.40,0:03:58.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,強襲機兵的比賽就要開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.54,0:04:00.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家要來看喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.14,0:04:02.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇，好土
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.38,0:04:03.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不是紙箱嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.21,0:04:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的機兵是很帥的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.28,0:04:08.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正今年也會輸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.52,0:04:10.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.32,0:04:14.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唉，竟然連小學生都瞧不起他們
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.42,0:04:16.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡的AS部隊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.19,0:04:18.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超級弱的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.06,0:04:20.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是裝備有什麼問題嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.36,0:04:24.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N裝備是陸上自衛隊最頂尖的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.30,0:04:25.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為他們是空降部隊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.63,0:04:27.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼為什麼會很弱？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.34,0:04:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是因為只有裝備好而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.51,0:04:32.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.51,0:04:35.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.71,0:04:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就是相良嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.08,0:04:41.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是，我是相良士官
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.72,0:04:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不，初次見面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.02,0:04:47.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是風間信太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.49,0:04:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在這裡擔任事務官
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.79,0:04:54.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二是第一次\N帶朋友來參觀這裡的祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.46,0:04:56.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要說多餘的話啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.37,0:04:58.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為這孩子個性這個樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.20,0:04:59.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身為父親實在有點擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.87,0:05:01.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸，不要再說了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.60,0:05:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就請盡情的玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.77,0:05:05.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是，事務官大人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.84,0:05:09.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在真是罕見
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.35,0:05:11.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,簡直就像軍人般\N禮儀端正的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.85,0:05:20.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是靈巧呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.82,0:05:23.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，應該叫他不要加青海苔的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.73,0:05:25.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是黏在牙齒上的話\N就不會有人來搭訕了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.50,0:05:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小要，妳要不要吃？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.83,0:05:30.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.03,0:05:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們是從哪裡來的？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.54,0:05:36.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊…我們是從千川來的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.44,0:05:38.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是巧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.74,0:05:40.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是從練馬來的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.74,0:05:42.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,離千川很近呢\N這傢伙是誰？好怪的太陽眼鏡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.75,0:05:45.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不，其實根本就是同一個城市嘛\N他是在玩COSPLAY嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.25,0:05:46.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,方便的話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.38,0:05:47.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要跟我一起去駕駛AS？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.05,0:05:48.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.49,0:05:53.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓妳體驗一下\N練馬赤龍的優異之處
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.42,0:05:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,練馬蘿蔔？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.92,0:05:55.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不對
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.99,0:05:57.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是練馬赤龍
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.73,0:05:58.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤色的龍
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.06,0:06:00.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.10,0:06:01.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.10,0:06:02.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好想坐坐看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.37,0:06:05.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫赤城龍之介
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.77,0:06:06.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.94,0:06:10.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很討厭AS
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.41,0:06:12.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也很討厭\N對那種東西很熱衷的笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.98,0:06:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.38,0:06:16.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會很細心親切的指導…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.85,0:06:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多謝好意
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.02,0:06:21.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生氣的表情真是可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.48,0:06:23.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.62,0:06:24.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搭乘時間到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.12,0:06:25.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.09,0:06:28.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我先告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.99,0:06:31.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,氣死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.29,0:06:33.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼不是找我而是找小要？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.63,0:06:36.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此，我就去找小要報仇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.50,0:06:38.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼會變成那樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.48,0:06:48.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家怎麼這麼陰沉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.74,0:06:49.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發生什麼事了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.85,0:06:50.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,囉嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.98,0:06:53.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接著
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.05,0:06:57.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開始進行今天的駐紮地祭典\N最主要的活動項目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.42,0:06:59.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,習志野強襲機兵中隊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.79,0:07:04.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對抗練馬強襲機兵中隊的\N競技比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.49,0:07:06.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,選手入場
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.40,0:07:10.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤城
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.57,0:07:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年我們一定會贏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.47,0:07:14.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼，說什麼大話
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.50,0:07:17.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們只會成為練馬赤龍的餌食
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.11,0:07:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.87,0:07:20.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,練馬蘿蔔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.24,0:07:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,絕不原諒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.38,0:07:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻嘿咻
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.65,0:07:33.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼，一擊就解決你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.16,0:07:35.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,右手握力出力最大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.29,0:07:37.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,右手握力出力最大，OK
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.56,0:07:38.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.77,0:07:45.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔，練馬隊今年也很強
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.44,0:07:49.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,應該是說習志野太弱了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.51,0:07:50.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不是說了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.97,0:07:52.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他們很弱的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.14,0:07:55.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年也很弱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.35,0:07:57.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,習志野緊纏不放
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.48,0:07:59.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年撐到最後一棒定勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.32,0:08:04.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最後衝刺了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.42,0:08:06.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有辦法跑得更快了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.46,0:08:07.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.02,0:08:09.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,解除限制器
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.22,0:08:10.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,解除
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.36,0:08:14.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔，有技巧的一擊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.06,0:08:16.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是練馬獲勝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.50,0:08:19.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,練馬太卑鄙了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.64,0:08:20.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風間
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.18,0:08:32.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對手是兩人操縱的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.82,0:08:34.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在同步上會出現些微的差異
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.02,0:08:36.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屆時就是反擊的機會
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.89,0:08:38.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這邊不也是兩人操縱嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.15,0:08:40.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,戰略B
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.16,0:08:41.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,準備
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.12,0:08:42.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,B，了解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.66,0:08:46.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隊…隊長，要來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.80,0:08:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤龍的切球
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.40,0:08:54.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.07,0:08:56.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是假動作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.24,0:08:58.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前進
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.54,0:09:00.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.78,0:09:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.11,0:09:07.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又來了，不要用卑鄙的招式！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.22,0:09:10.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切都結束了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.86,0:09:15.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.96,0:09:18.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有架所屬不明的AS\N朝這裡接近中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.33,0:09:19.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是習志野的AS嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.80,0:09:20.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.10,0:09:21.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這架AS
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.06,0:09:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,移動速度是一般的3倍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.60,0:09:25.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.47,0:09:31.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.77,0:09:32.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.11,0:09:33.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相良呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.85,0:09:37.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,該不會…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.78,0:09:40.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽得到嗎？練馬蘿蔔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.85,0:09:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是練馬赤龍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.35,0:09:45.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說這是競技比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.49,0:09:46.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,並不是戰爭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.82,0:09:48.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要耍那種卑劣的手段
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.72,0:09:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼，有種就給我出來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.03,0:09:56.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那的確是很俐落的殺球
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.13,0:10:00.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混帳，你是什麼人？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.74,0:10:08.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,AS駕駛員不需要名字是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.54,0:10:09.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.45,0:10:11.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一決勝負吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.68,0:10:12.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.12,0:10:23.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宗介，你在幹什麼啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.86,0:10:26.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我的身份會被看穿？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.20,0:10:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會做這種事的人只有你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.43,0:10:34.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是競技比賽最重要的\N就是公平公正的精神…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.90,0:10:36.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.84,0:10:38.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是不應該來的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.04,0:10:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把我的愉快海水浴還來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.54,0:10:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.25,0:10:45.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,GS裡面很熱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.05,0:10:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳說的是groupsounds啦\N(昭和40年代流行樂團)
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.62,0:10:50.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種笑話沒人聽得懂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.85,0:10:51.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下，瑞樹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.99,0:10:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳在做什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.29,0:10:56.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,與其跟這種小孩子\N你要不要跟我一起去坐GS啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.16,0:10:58.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然穿著布偶裝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.53,0:11:00.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過說不定裡面的人很帥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.96,0:11:03.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把這種東西脫下來\N讓我看看你的臉好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.67,0:11:08.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳這樣會給AS駕駛帶來困擾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.50,0:11:09.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.60,0:11:10.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.71,0:11:12.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.51,0:11:17.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她叫小要是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.75,0:11:19.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.75,0:11:21.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.02,0:11:23.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.79,0:11:26.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…根據協議的結果
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.32,0:11:29.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的桌球比賽\N因為中途有人闖入搗亂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.42,0:11:30.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此判定為平手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.66,0:11:34.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.80,0:11:39.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到在我們習志野隊裡\N竟然有你這種技術高超的AS駕駛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.80,0:11:40.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然說這個實在不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.04,0:11:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想拜託你一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.85,0:11:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.31,0:11:52.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們已經沒有退路了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.35,0:11:54.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事…事務官大人？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.02,0:11:57.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小菅，你這個人也真壞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.25,0:12:00.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然瞞著我，藏著這種秘密武器
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.03,0:12:04.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.09,0:12:06.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無論如何都得贏過練馬才行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.70,0:12:08.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻煩你擔任中隊的指揮官
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.93,0:12:11.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什麼啊，爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.44,0:12:14.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風間
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.77,0:12:16.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你會這樣子向人低頭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.84,0:12:18.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因為爸爸你是事務官，對不對？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.14,0:12:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為你駕駛AS的技術很爛\N只能當事務官
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.88,0:12:26.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以只能這樣低頭求人，對不對？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.28,0:12:29.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.55,0:12:31.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一點天份也沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.72,0:12:36.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我為什麼\N會開始看AS FAN嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.36,0:12:38.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我想確認
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.29,0:12:42.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,確認一下AS的操縱\N真的有這麼難嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.90,0:12:46.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼爸爸沒有辦法駕駛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.77,0:12:49.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好希望你能駕駛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.11,0:12:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好想向人炫耀\N我的爸爸是AS駕駛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.34,0:12:57.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.71,0:12:59.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最討厭爸爸了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.22,0:13:04.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.95,0:13:05.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.42,0:13:08.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了一件很重要的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.49,0:13:13.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,戰場的後方支援\N是非常重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.33,0:13:17.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有這些支援\N前線的士兵就無法發揮實力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.57,0:13:22.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而指揮這些支援\N便是事務官最重要的任務
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.91,0:13:27.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就讓我們來把練馬蘿蔔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.74,0:13:29.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,磨成蘿蔔泥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.01,0:13:33.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.35,0:13:41.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你跟秘密武器的男朋友\N吵架了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.29,0:13:43.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種人才不是我的男朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.26,0:13:45.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說我也有機會了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.60,0:13:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要一起向他挑戰這場勝負？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.40,0:13:52.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從他的身上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.57,0:13:54.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我只跟他對戰過一次
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.44,0:13:58.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是卻能感受到一股\N熟練AS駕駛員所散發出的霸氣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.91,0:14:01.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果跟妳一起\N我就不覺得會輸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.08,0:14:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不，一定能贏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.71,0:14:08.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳不覺得現在正是跟我一起\N坐AS的絕佳時機嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.22,0:14:09.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.69,0:14:11.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贏得了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.65,0:14:12.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.09,0:14:15.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我從來沒有讓淑女後悔過
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.16,0:14:17.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我答應你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.99,0:14:19.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓大家久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.16,0:14:21.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,終於到了最終決戰的騎馬戰
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.76,0:14:23.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這項比賽採特別點數制
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.83,0:14:25.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贏的一方就是冠軍
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.90,0:14:29.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都到哪裡去了？\N哇！衝啊衝啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.67,0:14:30.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.34,0:14:32.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油，BS駕駛員
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.91,0:14:35.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的來歷…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.38,0:14:37.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我現在姑且先不過問
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.15,0:14:38.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盡全力上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.85,0:14:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.32,0:14:43.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然讓外行人的風間父子\N參加了比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.39,0:14:45.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果輸的話，他們一定會被怪罪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.69,0:14:46.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以絕對要贏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.32,0:14:49.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外行人那種無法預期的攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.62,0:14:51.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有時會帶給敵人意外的傷害
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.83,0:14:52.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定贏得了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.86,0:14:55.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好臭喔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.00,0:14:57.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳很快就不會去在意的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.50,0:15:00.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像在上體育課一樣動就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.94,0:15:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的我來幫妳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.64,0:15:05.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請不要碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.37,0:15:06.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,終於到了最終項目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.78,0:15:08.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騎馬戰即將開打
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.04,0:15:10.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,(爸爸，工作加油 父親節 信二)
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.55,0:15:13.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前也有過那麼一段\N可愛的時期
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.45,0:15:16.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是最近
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.62,0:15:19.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那對父子好像處得不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.56,0:15:23.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之前好像也發生過\N像剛才一樣的爭吵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.23,0:15:26.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當時事務官好像弄壞了\N他最珍惜的模型…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.76,0:15:29.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,風間機的團隊精神是最差的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.16,0:15:32.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,團隊精神是在戰鬥中建立的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.33,0:15:34.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不試試看是不知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.77,0:15:35.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,預備
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.44,0:15:42.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我要…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.44,0:15:44.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸，我來操縱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.61,0:15:45.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.75,0:15:46.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼可能…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.35,0:15:50.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幫手先生叫我用這個
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.89,0:15:54.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎麼做？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.66,0:15:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎麼做？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.13,0:15:58.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.36,0:16:01.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想像成在揍可恨男人似的\N揮拳就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.43,0:16:02.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.66,0:16:04.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.67,0:16:07.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二，防禦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.11,0:16:13.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這套OS好厲害喔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.34,0:16:14.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被擋住了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.48,0:16:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係，妳很有天份
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.51,0:16:17.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.65,0:16:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.81,0:16:19.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就再來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.05,0:16:24.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那架隊長機
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.35,0:16:26.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟以往的動作完全不同
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.52,0:16:29.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小要，那傢伙一定坐在那上面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.59,0:16:31.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎，混帳傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.09,0:16:33.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那架隊長機可不能輕視
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.23,0:16:35.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,技術相當好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.60,0:16:36.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.03,0:16:39.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得揮拳的時機\N好像跟以往不同
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.30,0:16:41.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,C班，D班
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.84,0:16:44.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,由側面援護B班風間機
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.74,0:16:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,C班了解
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.14,0:16:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,D班了解
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.51,0:16:48.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們要怎麼辦？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.34,0:16:51.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是這次作戰的重點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.75,0:16:53.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要拿下隊長機
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.35,0:16:54.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就有勝算
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.08,0:16:57.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像越來越有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.15,0:16:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.35,0:17:00.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.26,0:17:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住…住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.76,0:17:03.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.36,0:17:06.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始做掉敵方隊長機
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.16,0:17:08.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,B班，C班
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.56,0:17:09.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,準備做上次那招
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.57,0:17:12.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.50,0:17:15.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤色三連星的紅色氣流攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.47,0:17:16.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.17,0:17:19.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把AS當跳板？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.81,0:17:23.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,DOWN BY LOW
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.95,0:17:24.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,DOWN BY LOW
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.15,0:17:31.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每年都是被那招打敗的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.59,0:17:32.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種重量…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.19,0:17:36.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,時機、飛翔能力\N還有果斷的行動力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.32,0:17:37.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太完美了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.56,0:17:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,覺得好爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.33,0:17:41.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒敵人會更爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是不要把身體靠過來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.53,0:17:47.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸，右腳彎得太慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.37,0:17:50.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你這麼說我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.94,0:17:52.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請退後
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.21,0:17:53.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡交給我們
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.44,0:17:54.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.51,0:17:56.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不能丟下你們
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.38,0:18:00.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事務官也是日夜都在戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.72,0:18:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟諸位同樣都是隊員
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.95,0:18:07.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,習志野隊面臨危機
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.92,0:18:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年仍會面臨粉碎的命運嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.13,0:18:12.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事務官大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.09,0:18:13.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之後就拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.83,0:18:16.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓他們見識一下\N習志野空降的氣魄…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.73,0:18:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.03,0:18:21.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是個笨拙的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.20,0:18:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連個模型也修不好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.57,0:18:27.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是，我絕不能就此退下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.71,0:18:28.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.38,0:18:31.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你願意跟我…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.21,0:18:32.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起戰鬥嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.12,0:18:35.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.15,0:18:37.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我願意
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.35,0:18:40.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好，去贏得勝利吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.29,0:18:43.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,通告殘存的各機
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.32,0:18:45.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始將練馬蘿蔔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.59,0:18:46.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,磨成蘿蔔泥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.90,0:18:47.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.46,0:18:49.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全軍前進
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.76,0:18:51.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開始反擊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.70,0:18:52.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.57,0:18:55.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二，左反擊拳準備
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.07,0:18:57.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,左反擊拳，了解
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.04,0:18:59.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.31,0:19:02.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發…發生什麼事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.78,0:19:03.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說過了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.31,0:19:06.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,團隊精神是在戰鬥中建立的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.02,0:19:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.12,0:19:09.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這邊一直被打敗耶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.15,0:19:11.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎麼回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.22,0:19:13.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,習志野的猛攻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.49,0:19:15.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,練馬一個個的被擊敗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.36,0:19:17.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,展開勢均力敵的對決
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.59,0:19:19.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之，打下隊長機
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.59,0:19:21.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各班準備好了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.30,0:19:21.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.80,0:19:25.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要再來一次蘿蔔跳躍是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.13,0:19:26.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是紅色氣流攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.67,0:19:30.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,過來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.81,0:19:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,DOWN BY LOW會來不及
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.44,0:19:35.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行，來不及
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.75,0:19:40.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,96式的右關節很脆弱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.82,0:19:43.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信二，瞄準右邊的關節
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.05,0:19:45.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,了…了解
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.16,0:19:50.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手腕斷了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.53,0:19:51.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.66,0:19:52.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是現在
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.69,0:19:53.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.10,0:19:55.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看招
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.30,0:19:57.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年一定要贏給你們看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.13,0:19:58.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正拳
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.47,0:20:01.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勝負已分
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.97,0:20:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,習志野隊以些許差距贏得勝利
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.38,0:20:10.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,簡直像在作夢似的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.18,0:20:11.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.35,0:20:15.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不，只不過是習志野空降部隊\N發揮了實力罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.18,0:20:17.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.19,0:20:19.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.09,0:20:20.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.26,0:20:27.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,離我遠一點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.90,0:20:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比賽已經結束了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.27,0:20:31.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不想承認
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.53,0:20:34.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為年輕所犯下的過錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.34,0:20:36.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,煩死了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.04,0:20:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸的工作是很重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.55,0:20:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次了解到了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.32,0:20:48.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你，相良
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.92,0:20:52.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能夠贏都是因為\N有你跟大家的幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.86,0:20:55.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贏的人不是我們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.72,0:20:58.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是習志野空降師團與
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.59,0:21:00.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事務官大人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.33,0:21:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,BS駕駛員…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.90,0:21:06.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.60,0:21:11.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的盛夏回憶在哪裡？

Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.64,0:21:23.74,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}在\N心\N中\N綻\N開\N著\N一\N朵\N小\N花
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.64,0:21:23.74,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K100}心\N{\K140}に{\K50}\N{\K70}小\N{\K50}さ\N{\K90}な{\K40}\N{\K40}花\N{\K100}が\N{\K40}咲\N{\K75}い\N{\K35}て\N{\K200}る
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.24,0:21:35.39,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}你\N給\N我\N的\N那\N朵\N不\N會\N枯\N萎\N的\N花
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.24,0:21:35.39,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K80}君\N{\K40}か\N{\K120}ら{\K40}\N{\K40}も\N{\K30}ら\N{\K30}っ\N{\K120}た{\K50}\N{\K20}枯\N{\K20}れ\N{\K100}な\N{\K30}い\N{\K100}花\N{\K150}が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.44,0:21:42.44,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}讓\N我\N不\N再\N畏\N懼\N相\N信\N他\N人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.44,0:21:42.44,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K50}信\N{\K35}じ\N{\K45}る\N{\K35}こ\N{\K70}と\N{\K80}も\N{\K35}恐\N{\K30}が\N{\K30}ら\N{\K50}な\N{\K40}い\N{\K40}く\N{\K20}ら\N{\K30}い
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.44,0:21:49.24,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}因\N此\N變\N得\N更\N堅\N強
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.44,0:21:49.24,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K50}強\N{\K100}く\N{\K30}な\N{\K80}れ\N{\K35}た\N{\K25}か\N{\K50}ら\N{\K100}。\N{\K100}。\N{\K100}。
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.89,0:21:55.54,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}能\N與\N你\N相\N遇\N\N真\N的\N很\N高\N興
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.89,0:21:55.54,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K70}君\N{\K35}に\N{\K35}会\N{\K35}え\N{\K90}て{\K20}\N{\K70}嬉\N{\K30}し\N{\K40}か\N{\K30}っ\N{\K90}た
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.54,0:22:02.14,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}能\N與\N你\N牽\N手\N\N是\N我\N的\N驕\N傲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.54,0:22:02.14,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K50}つ\N{\K40}な\N{\K40}い\N{\K40}だ\N{\K20}手\N{\K100}が\N{\K90}誇\N{\K25}り\N{\K50}だ\N{\K30}っ\N{\K160}た
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.14,0:22:08.84,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}即\N使\N現\N在\N各\N自\N仰\N望\N著\N不\N同\N的\N天\N空
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.14,0:22:08.84,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K60}今\N{\K60}は{\K30}\N{\K50}別\N{\K50}々\N{\K40}の\N{\K130}空{\K30}\N{\K20}見\N{\K20}上\N{\K20}げ\N{\K30}て\N{\K30}い\N{\K20}て\N{\K100}も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.84,0:22:17.24,opjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(017,010)}你\N看\N\N我\N一\N個\N人\N仍\N能\N向\N前\N邁\N進
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.84,0:22:17.24,opch1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3a&H7F&}{\1c&HE3E38F&}{\1a&H00&}{\K20}ほ\N{\K150}ら{\K50}\N{\K70}歩\N{\K30}け\N{\K100}る{\K20}\N{\K70}一\N{\K80}人\N{\K30}で\N{\K200}も

Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.99,0:22:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宗介要出差？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.15,0:22:32.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.82,0:22:34.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去一個叫作“阿富汗”的國家
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.22,0:22:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去做什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.19,0:22:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暗殺任務
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.39,0:22:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.99,0:22:38.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.16,0:22:42.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一回FULL METAL PANIC\N「在故鄉飛舞的風．前篇」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.03,0:22:44.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要平安回來喔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.43,0:22:45.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,運氣好的話
