Damn it. Magic again!
Blasted Vampires!
Bash them before they use magic--
Argh!
Flame, oh, flame.
Ice, oh, ice.
I have a message.
Laperico's army have been defeated.
We, the Komari Corps, are
the undisputed victors!
Take that, lowly brutes.
Let's celebrate victory as
we drink the blood of the beasts!
Don't get carried away.
It's still not a clear victory.
You never know if
the enemy has a secret weapon.
You're celebrating already?
How pathetic you are.
Be ashamed of yourselves.
This war is
the Mulnite's Empire
We must not be defeated.
Isn't that right?
Her Excellency Terakomari.
Yes, Kaostel is right.
Listen, everybody!
I am the one and only
Terakomari Gandesblood!
3rd year professional shut-in.
THE VEXATIONS OF
A SHUT-IN VAMPIRE PRINCESS
#1: SHUT-IN VAMPIRE, OUT AND ABOUT
I've always thought the world
is an unreasonable place.
15 years ago,
I was born
a highly respected aristocrat,
part of the Gandesblood family.
For 1000 years, the Gandesblood family
has been a prestigious house
of Mulnite Commanders.
And so, there were expectations of me,
that I tried to meet,
but I failed.
Every possible talent, I lacked.
Number one, I cannot use magic.
Number two, I suck at physical activities.
Number three, I am short.
The reason I struggle with
these three issues
is obvious.
I am a vampire, but I can't drink blood.
They say I have to do it or I won't grow,
but I just can't.
Why not, you ask?
I can't stand anything about blood.
With all that said, my life has been
nothing but bitter memories.
In a society
where power is everything…
I swore to be
a righteous and peaceful vampire,
so I decided to become a shut-in.
It's so itchy!
Huh?
The Mulnite national emblem?
Why?
Good morning, Lady Terakomari.
Who the hell are you?
Why are you in my room?
I'm late in introducing myself.
My name is Villhaze.
I belong to the Mulnite Imperial Army,
as a Junior Third Class
Special Lieutenant.
As of today, I will be
Miss Terakomari's personal maid.
Even so…
Pardon my directness,
but your room is a bit of a mess.
What do you want? Is it money?
Please do not be so frightened.
I am an ally of the Lady Terakomari.
Hey. Villhaze or whatever,
wait here for a minute.
We have no time for that.
We must depart for the Court right away.
Get off me! I have to pee!
This is not the time to urinate.
Please listen to me.
Do you want me to pee myself?
Listen while you pee.
Isn't that perverse?
We're in a hurry, so please obide.
No! You'll just kidnap me!
Because I am a one-in-a-million beauty!
You're saying that yourself?
Let her go, Vill.
Oh! Komari!
Are you hurt?
It hurts. I'm dying.
More importantly, Dad!
What the hell is this girl?
This is Vill,
your new personal maid.
I don't need a maid.
Especially such a scary one…
Even so,
this was the Empress' decision.
The Emperess? What do you mean?
Let me explain that to you.
Lady Terakomari.
Do you know the Crimson Sky Seven?
What's with that, out of the blue…
No, I know, but…
The Crimson Sky Commanders
lead the Mulnite Army.
Those seven are
the fiercest of all vampires.
You have now become one of them.
Huh?
The other day,
I asked if you would start working soon.
And you said,
If I could be an empress,
I wouldn't mind working.
I was so moved!
So I said to Her Majesty,
'Let Komari take over the throne!'
Are you insane?
I did my best for you.
The Majesty was furious,
but I insisted that you are
an absolute genius
and a one-in-a-million beauty!
Then her Majesty said it was funny.
It ain't funny!
So Her Majesty made a contract with you,
and appointed you
to the Seven Crimson Skies.
I don't remember
signing anything like that.
She snuck in last night.
Who did?
Her Majesty.
Huh?
While Milady was sleeping,
you kissed, then signed it.
WHAT?!
Oh, oh, oh!
Well done, Komari!
You're as sweet as ever!
I'm happy to see you, my dear!
I'm honored, but…
Your Majesty…
You're very close.
Ah, I want to touch your boobs!
Can I please?
Your Majesty, please, don't be silly.
She will cry.
I'm just joking!
I am the type to value your feelings!
I won't touch them until you're ready.
Didn't you kiss me?
That is hilarious!
Politeness doesn't suit you.
I'll have you treat me
like an old friend.
I ain't never had a single friend.
Well.
Terakomari Gandesblood.
The reason I summoned you here.
'Things to know
as a Crimson Commander!'
'Explanation Segment! Whew whoo!'
What is that picture?
The Seven have
only one condition they must meet.
They must wage
and win a war every three months.
If they win 100 wars,
one can become
a candidate to be the next monarch!
That's way too hard though.
But if you keep getting defeated…
I'll get sacked?
Yep, you'll explode and lose your head.
You've got to be joking! Give me a chance!
Do not worry.
You'll have the 500 men
in the Seventh Corps under you.
Though all of them are the kind to
try to kill you if they think you're weak.
They're no better than the enemy then!
I'll feel so unsafe!
They're vampires,
so all of them are
as power-hungry as the next.
Komari….
You're actually weak, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm super weak!
Dying hurts like hell, right?
It hurts more than
stubbing your little toe!
You don't want to die?
Nobody wants to die!
Then we'll keep it a secret.
No matter what,
you must act strong in front of your men.
Your maid there will help you with that.
Let me help you, Milady.
I'll make sure the men overestimate you.
This all worries me.
You won't undermine me, will you?
Of course not.
Because I love Milady
more than anything else.
That's definitely a lie.
We literally just met.
It suits you well, Lady Komari.
You think so?
Well, I am
a one-in-a-million beauty after all!
I guess everything suits me!
It's great. It's super cute.
When we get back,
let's do a Lady Komari Fashion show!
Absolutely not.
Come on, Lady Komari.
Your new subordinates are waiting.
Right…
This definitely weighs more
than a million tons.
There's no way that's true.
Any normal vampire can open it.
Too bad I'm an abnormal weakling!
Do your best, Milady.
You…! Don't just stand there.
Help me!
Oh, it open--
I'll kill you,
Honorable High Commander!
Lady Komari, are you okay?
I-I -I-I…
I'm-I'm-I'm….
There, there. Good girl.
What do I do?
They probably found out I'm super weak.
Don't worry, Madam.
You happened to beat the insolent rebel.
Vill, that…
- He is dead
- He's dead!?
Oh my God, how'd this happen…
Should we put flowers?
A fool like him you can just spit at.
We'd better get going.
Your men await.
They welcomed me with mutiny.
Can I really make it back
alive?
Your Excellency, I am impressed.
With one single blow, you killed
THE REMAINS OF JOHAN
Johan Herders,
despite how bloodthirsty he was!
Pffh!
I can take out someone like him
with just my little finger.
No way…
-Wow.
-The new Commander is something.
By the way, as a child
Lady Komari murdered
a hundred vampires with her pinky.
If she decides to get serious,
she can kill all of you in five seconds.
Don't say that stuff!
Anyone can tell those are lies.
Quit the thumbs-up.
Your additions were not nice!
Ahem.
Anyway, how about I introduce myself?
Of course, Milady!
The Seventh Unit's… No.
The Komari Corps members are
sincerely looking forward
to your self-introduction!
Everyone!
I am the new Crimson Sky Commander
Terakomari Gandesblood!
Now that I am your commander,
you are done with
the sweet and…
Lady Komari's nerves made her halt.
How was it? Cute right?
No, come on! Support me properly!
You are done with the sweet and easy life!
Never again!
From now on, it's war every day!
Bloodshed will be constant!
It is a daily carnage!
But rest assured.
You guys just shut up and follow me!
Don't you dare think of
silly things like succession!
All you must do is follow
Terakomari Gandesblood
as beautiful, smart, and strong as I am!
I promise you!
Do as I say and wage war,
and you can enjoy
endless days of pleasure!
Our first enemies
the Kingdom of Laperico is led by monkeys!
It is a piece of cake!
We must do more than win!
Let the world know!
That I
Terakomari Gandesblood
will be the the ruler of the world!
Urgent report!
Lieutenant Bilius
took out the enemy general!
Our army has won!
Had I gone onto the battlefield
I could've shredded him
in all but three seconds.
Three seconds?
No, that's wrong!
One second! Just one!
Each one of them killed in a second!
Whoa!!
Komarin! Komarin!
Well done, everybody!
But not all our enemies are beasts!
The Ji-Liu's Gera-Alka and the Blue Jade!
They shall know my power!
And then there's, um…
Divine Paradise and Immortal Haven.
Right!
Divine Paradise and Immortal Haven!
We'll beat them to pulps!
That's right!
You all just follow the powerful me!
Be honest and obedient at all times!
Never rebel! Don't even think about it!
You'll just trust and shield me!
Come, conquer, dear soldiers!
There is glory
in the vivid color of blood.
Komarin! Komarin!
How did this happen?
May I have a moment?
I am Melca Tiano from Six Nation News.
Lady Terakomari Gandesblood,
May I please have an interview?
Okay, okay! Ask whatever you want.
But first,
can you step back a little?
Thank you!
How did you become
a Commander of the Crimson skies?
What's your relationship with the Empress?
What's your favorite food?
Did you really kill a hundred vampires
with just your pinky?
Do you have a lover?
When was your first kiss?
Step back!
The strong do not speak with words.
I reckon that's a problem for you,
so I'll offer you a few words.
What I will do
is a simple conquest!
I, Terakomari Gandesblood,
will wipe out the commanders
of the other five nations
and spread the glory of Mulnite
throughout the world!
Got it?
Amazing.
By the way,
my favorite food is Omelette rice!
That's all!
Ah… this is a Crimson Sky Seven.
An amazing vampire!
I thank the gods
that I live in
the same time as Her Excellency.
Please look this way! Amazing!
She's weird.
Been a while since I last died…
Dying really is tough.
In this world
there is no such thing
as a war of life and death.
The six nations of this world
each possesses
a supreme divine tool
with infinite magical power.
They're "Magic Cores."
And within the range of the Magic Core,
no matter how deep the wound,
or how brutal the manner of death,
after some time, you will recover fully.
With that being said,
the place I stand now is the Core Region.
It's a special area where
the six Magic Cores overlap,
and wars between nations
primarily take place here.
How do you like it, Lady Komari?
This is what we call
an entertainment war.
How can it be
such absurdity exists?
Good morning, Lady Komari.
What are you doing here?
Why are you naked?
Put some clothes on!
Lady Komari, please see today's paper.
Yesterdays pictures are in there.
Seriously?
You want me to read right now?
'The new Crimson Sky Commander
will turn the world into omelettes.'
'I love omelette rice.
I will wipe out
the Commanders of the other nations,
and like one carelessly pours ketchup,
I'll gut them like
an inside-out omelette.'
This is nothing but fake news!
This will definitely provoke the others.
It will.
Looking at that,
that chimpanzee from yesterday
will never be forgiven.
I will put her through
absolute humiliation
for making criminal threats
in a national newspaper.
No!
Don't worry Madam.
I will protect your virtues.
I trust you the least!
Milady, your schedule for today…
I can't hear you!
I'm taking today off!
If you intend to stay
under the covers forever,
I have an idea.
If you come even one step closer…
I'll start wailing.
The Strawberry Milk Equation.
'I wanted a love like strawberry milk.
Sweet and mellow.
Not a single sting to tease the tongue,
but warm and gentle to the end.
a love like a sunny spot.'
Stop it!
I found it in your trash bin.
I didn't expect to find a romance novel.
If you continue playing hooky,
I will distribute this to the court.
With your name on it.
Huh?
Are you listening?
I'll do whatever you say.
Just, please.
Don't tell it to anyone.
Do not worry.
I would never do that.
Th-thank you, Vill.
You smell amazing!
The real thing is
so much better than a pillow!
I want to be embraced by
this strawberry milk scent
and ascend to Heaven!
I've never been so repulsed!
I'm so tired…
I don't remember the last time
I talked that much with someone.
Resist just a little, won't you?
Stop…
It hurts…
No…
I'll never allow that.
#2: REBELLION