Good, you came!
Terakomari.
Vill!
Oh my, no need to get upset.
She isn't dead yet.
I will kill her eventually though.
Give me back Vill!
Come now, there's no need to rush.
We finally have
this chance to talk in private.
So, Terakomari.
Do you have any idea
how much pain I've been through
since that day?
That day? When was that?
Three years ago today.
I'm talking about the day
I tried to take that pendant of yours.
You must become strong.
Stronger than anyone else.
#4 CRIMSON RESENTMENT
Yes, father.
My father's teachings were simple.
The Bluenights are
a family of politicians.
In a vampire society
where force reigns supreme,
the fact is that weak
politicians are picked on and eaten.
The person over there who has come
all the way from Divine Paradise,
is Mr. Amatsu.
Starting today,
he will give you lessons in fighting.
Do not bring us shame.
My name is Kakumei Amatsu.
Nice to meet you.
N-Nice to meet--
Ah!
Your father hopes that
you have special powers within you.
Special... powers?
It's a supernatural ability
called "Rekkaku Liberation."
Rekkaku Liberation.
A special ability that deviates
from all the laws of this world.
It is said that
once used,
it has the power to pierce
the Earth and move stars.
The likelihood that a person has
this ability innately is extremely low.
However, our research has revealed
that if you undergo special training,
you can acquire this power.
What is the special training?
Cultivating a spirit of resilience
in the face of adversity
It seems that the state of one's mind is
deeply related to the Rekkaku Liberation.
And the quickest way to train your mind
is to threaten your life!
This is called a Sacred Article.
It is an item that can cause damage
which cannot be healed by Magic Cores.
By enduring
the pain of a wound that won't heal,
the mind can be trained.
Please train me, Mr. Amatsu.
It's already been one month
since Mr. Amatsu arrived!
Why can't you use
the Rekkaku Liberation yet!?
The Gandesbloods will be laughing at us!
With such a mess of an heir!
Damn it!
You are a complete failure compared to
the daughter of the Gandesbloods!
F-Father...
Hey, you hear about the kid
in the class next door?
They say she can use magic
that others can't!
Are you talking about advanced magic?
That is cool, but...
No, no. Not that, it was retsu...
Rekkaku?
Rekkaku Liberation!?
Oh yeah, that's it!
Can you tell me everything
you heard about her?
Whatever, hurry up and show me.
Please drink my blood.
Huh?
My Rekkaku Liberation allows me to see
the future of those who drink my blood.
Pandora Poison.
If it's about what's going to happen today,
my accuracy rate is 100%.
Oh?
I see your future.
What can you see?
This is...
Umm.
What is it?
Stop holding back and tell me!
Okay.
You are a pitiful person.
Huh!?
This one is no good, she's broken.
-It's no fun if she doesn't react.
-Should we kill her then?
Shall I blow your head off!?
Stop...
Stop it!
Ms. Gandesblood!
This is, umm...
Gandesblood!?
This brat
is the daughter of the Gandesbloods!?
We've come this far and now I'm sure.
It seems you do not have the
ability to evoke the Rekkaku Liberation.
That's not to say you don't show promise.
You have other talents
that anyone would be envious of.
What should I do then?
Act freely, my dear.
Admire the things you love
and kill the things you hate.
Is there someone you'd like to kill?
In that case,
do whatever it takes to kill them.
Come on, if you want this to stop
use your Rekkaku Liberation or something!
Let's see you put up a fight!
I pity you.
Huh, what was that?
I didn't hear you.
I pity you.
Is there something troubling you?
In order to force
Terakomari's spirit to submit to me,
I thoroughly investigated
her lineage and history.
I learned that the pendant was
a keepsake of Terakomari's mother.
Hey, you mind if I borrow
that pendant?
After that I can't seem
to remember what happened.
Afterwards I learned that
I died after Terakomari evoked
her Rekkaku Liberation.
My life changed forever that day.
Your goddamn father
falsely accused my family
of treason and deported them.
Kicked out of the academy,
kicked out of the country,
my family was separated
and we had nowhere to go.
I finally ended up
part of the terrorist organization,
The Inverted Moons.
While you were enjoying
the elegant life of a shut-in,
I was experiencing my fill of malice
that the world has to offer.
There has been an unchanging conviction
in my heart for the past three years.
I will exact my revenge.
A conviction to kill you.
That is all.
Oh, so she is actually similar to me.
Someone who is lost,
cannot live in the moment
and can't escape from the trauma
of what happened three years ago.
What are you doing Terakomari!?
You! Why are you here?
It doesn't matter!
You need to run away!
She's crazy and she has a Sacred Article!
Just look at this wound on my stomach,
it hurts and it isn't healing.
I see.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm going to help, you stay right there.
Don't... don't be stupid.
I was helping her
so that we could kill you.
Despite that y--
Eh!?
Shut up you noisy gnat.
I'm about to fight
Terakomari to the death.
I'm sorry. If you die now
then you'll be safe by the time you revive.
A Magic Stone?
Well done, Terakomari.
I see you've actually
come prepared to fight.
Come now, how long will you be
hiding like a rat!? Come out and play!
You precious little
maid is going to get killed!
Okay, next is--
What are you doing?
It's no fun
if you die so quickly you know.
Vill!
Hmm? You can still stand?
Well done.
I won't lose!
You have more guts than I thought.
Where would you like to be shot next?
Your chest? Your stomach?
Or right in the face?
It'll be fun to ruin a beauty that comes
around only once in ten billion years.
You're wrong.
Huh?
It's not ten billion years.
It's a hundred million.
Your attempt at humility disgusts me.
I'm ten billion times
more disgusted with you!
Oho? A special attack!?
I think you've lost your mind!
Explode! Magic Stones!
What a petty attempt.
Shock Wave!
Get crushed! Millicent!
I did it.
Vill, are you okay!?
Vill!
You've done such a good job,
Terakomari!
Oh, little miss Terakomari
where do you think you're going!?
If you think you can kill me
with such a low-grade magic stone,
you're sadly mistaken.
Does it hurt? It hurts a lot doesn't it?
Just look at all the blood you're losing.
S-Stop...
I'm not stopping you idiot!
You're three years too late to kill me.
Weaklings like you
are meant to be killed
like the insects you are
like you never existed in the first place.
Crying? I knew it,
you're a real worthless piece of trash.
You think crying will save you?
I'm telling you,
the world is not that easy.
Even if you cry
nobody is coming to save you.
You'll only ever be
able to rely on yourself.
Shut up! Shut up!
Don't get smart with me!
How about you just use
your Rekkaku Liberation now?
I don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about!
You really do seem to know nothing.
Didn't you come here thinking you could
beat me because of your Rekkaku Liberation?
I came for Vill--
I came all this way to save Vill.
I've always been short,
no physical talents,
unable to use any magic
and in general a bad vampire.
Coming here was really scary.
My legs were trembling and I thought of
turning back multiple times.
But
I can't stand to run away anymore!
I'm weak, I know that well enough.
But I have to try.
For the people who care about me.
I know I have to do my best!
I can't take this.
I really can't stand this. Alright then,
I'll just kill the maid first.
No, stop!
Watch closely Terakomari!
Your precious maid is
about to reduced to a heap of meat!
I won't let you lay a hand on Vill!
Shut up you vexing brat!
I can- I can still fight.
I said shut up!
There's no way...
There's no way
I'm leaving here without Vill!
Acting all righteous
but you're a simple shut-in!
I'm not a shut-in!
I'm going to defeat you
and turn over a new leaf!
If you think you can do it, then do it!!
So is this how I die?
Without being able to defeat
Millicent or save Vill?
As a helpless little shut-in?
That's, not what I want.
Lady Komari.
You are the strongest
and kindest person in the world.
But you lack confidence and always
end up with that anxious look on your face.
V-Vill.
So you're still alive!?
Forgive me Lady Komari.
I'm ready to receive
any punishment for you.
Lady Komari.
You will not lose.
Oh, this is so exciting!
Hurry up and show me, Terakomari.
The supreme Rekkaku Liberation,
unprecedented in the history of the Empire.
The full power of
"The Solitary Crimson Sky."
I'm killing you.
What is that!?
-Is this the Rekkaku Liber--
-I'm killing you.
What happened!?
Her magical power has suddenly grown!
That's right, just like back then.
This brat.
She drank my blood.
-Millicent.
-Eh?
You really are a pitiful person.
Wha?
You shitty little brat!
Your Excellency!
We're sorry Your Excellency!
Even against your orders we want to be of aid!
That's special grade magic,
"Annihilating Flame!"
Please run, Your Excellency!
I will destroy you!
♪ Running through this fate with you ♪
That was too intense YO!
Whoa!
Y-You!
You... you've gotta be....
You've gotta be kidding!?
It's all over.
That's right.
Just die, Terakomari!
Ah... Oh....
It seems that the state of one's mind is
deeply related to the Rekkaku Liberation.
I know I have to try my best
for the people who care about me!
Ah, so that's why.
Prepare yourself.
The one who was weak
was me after all.
If only I had taken a different approach
I would have had a different future.
With this,
I give you peace.
Lady Komari.
Are you awake?
Vill!
Are you okay--
Owowowowow!
Please stay still.
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
Vill, is this Heaven?
No, this is reality.
You won, Lady Komari.
Huh? What did I win at?
The first time Komari evoked
the Rekkaku Liberation, she was three.
At dinner, she drank blood
for the first time,
and killed all of us who were in the room.
Immediately after that we hypnotized Komari
so that she would hate blood.
I don't want her to have a hard time.
If she doesn't remember the Rekkaku Liberation,
it's best to leave it that way.
Come on, what did I beat?
The past.
The past?
The Mulnite Empire detains
the woman from the “Inverted Moon.”
Someone came to help, I guess.
By the way, what will you do now?
Eh?
Everything from
three years ago is wrapped up.
-There's no need for you to stay my maid--
-No way!
Do you mean to say you're done with me?
No that's not--
I'll have no choice but to become a thief,
break in and steal your panties!
At least steal something valuable!
If you say that again, I'll really fire you!
Alright, alright.
You'll be my maid from now on too.
So always stay by my side okay?
I'm relying on you, Vill.
Huh? Was that a proposal!?
How could you possibly think that!?
#5 SAKUNA MEMOIR AND THE RED CRIMSON SKIES