I, Kamijo Touma,
came in contact with a homeless shrine maiden, who, *quote* calls herself a magician *end quote*.
Together with another magician called Style, I headed to where this shrine maiden was being held captive...
...and what I saw there was...
This is just a corpse.
koko ni ikiru sono wake mo
Be it the reason I live here,
kono basho de deau subete mo
or be it everything I encountered here,
tatoe chigau sekai demo
even if it were a different world,
doko ni itemo kono omoi wa yuruganai
no matter where I am, this feeling won't be swayed.
mune wo chikuri to sasu itami
The pain from the heart getting pierced,
sore mo warau shiawase na mono tachi e
that should be directed at those bystanders jeering at you.
se wo mukeyuku
Turn your back on them.
touzen no kurushimi wo unmei ga sasou
Fate beckons the obvious suffering.
furuedasu ashi ga oboeteru
The trembling feet remember,
kakushin ni
a certain now.
yume dake ja mamorenai
Illusions alone are not enough to protect
tayoranai chikara
such an unreliable power.
ima kono te de shirukara
I will now see for myself with these hands.
mayowanai
No more hesitation.
Ars Magna
The Alchemy of Gold
A corpse?!
He's probably from the Thirteen Knights of the Roman Catholic Church.
From the looks of this, they were probably completely annihilated.
Why?
We're on a battlefield.
What's so surprising about a corpse or two lying around?
Why isn't anyone shocked or panicking?
Megumi, long day, huh?
What was that just now?
The difference between the "outerside" and the "innerside".
These students are inhabitants of the outerside of the coin;
they won't be able to notice us enemies from outside that are on the innerside of the coin right now.
Neither can we, in any way, interfere with their actions.
Don't even try it.
Without destroying the core of the magic, you won't be able to dispel this seal.
I'm sure the core is somewhere outside, though.
Looks like I have one more reason to fight now.
Hey, couldn't we have taken the elevator?
We're on the innerside of the coin,
so we won't be able to press buttons that are on the outerside of the coin.
So, what about phones?
Huh?
Ah, you know, I was wondering if I could call from the innerside of the coin to the outerside of the coin.
See for yourself, then.
I'll do that.
Ah, th-this is Index Libro-
I mean, this is Kamijo speaking!
Um, yes.
What, is this the first time you've answered a phone?
Ahhh-
Ah, this is Touma's voice.
And Touma, for you to be using something as exaggerated, excessive, cumbersome,
and unfriendly as a phone, what's wrong?
No, nothing.
Ah, there were two lasagnas in the refrigerator,
was that-
Did you eat them?!
Ah, there was pudding in the refrigerator-
...What... Did you...
...Did you eat it?!
You ate it, didn't you?!
You ate it, right?!
Oh, well.
As long as I can reach you by phone.
I'm hanging up.
Ah, right, right.
I heard that your life is shortened a day for every minute you speak on the phone.
Wh-What?
Nothing.
I just thought you might be too relaxed.
I said we were on a battlefield,
yet you're chatting nonchalantly with a girl.
It's like, I don't care if you die because of your conceitedness,
and in fact, I'd be jumping for joy,
but heck, just don't drag me down because that's problematic.
You jealous?
Don't get it wrong.
She's not a target of romance.
You should be well aware of that.
Until now, her body was one that would die unless her memories were erased in one year periods.
Many people were in the position you're in right now.
To become her father, her sibling, her friend, her teacher...
Many people wished to become different roles for her.
You have succeeded in what I failed to do in the past.
That's all.
That's the only difference between you and me.
That's right.
The one that saved Index isn't me, right now.
The one that Index desires is...
...me, before I lost my memories...
And that was so mean!
Yeah, for real.
This is the first time I've seen the science religion,
but this seems pretty normal.
I'd think they have a portrait of the religion's founder framed somewhere.
It does seem pretty safe...
Shit...
Don't be stupid,
because there's no way people on the outerside of the coin can see people like us on the innerside of the coin.
The wings of the seraph shine brightly.
The bright light is a pure white color that reveals sins.
The pure white color is the mark of purity.
The mark is the result of one's actions.
One's actions represent the future.
The future is time.
Time is uniform.
Auto-warning, eh?
Uniformity is all.
These students that were supposed to be on the outerside of the coin...
All is created by the past.
The past is the cause.
...have been put on the innerside of the coin.
There is but one cause.
One is sin.
Sins are humans.
Humans fear, and fear is guilt.
Guilt rests within oneself.
If there is something one despises within,
the wings of the seraph will reveal your sins,
and force it from within you.
Okay, Imagine Breaker.
You're up!
H-Hey!
Geez...
Hey, don't run away!
Your right hand was able
to fend off a Dragon Breath attack!
So you must be nuts to be showing your back right now!
I don't want to hear that from someone using me as a shield!
There's just too many of them!
One right hand won't be able to cover them all!
But, damn!
That may be a replica, but to be able to reproduce Gregorio's Choir...
What's that Gregorio whatever?!
Originally, it was a grand magic spell that employed 3,333 monks in a cathedral and gathered their prayers.
Then, there's no way we can beat that head on!
No, Gregorio's Choir requires the simultaneous control of a large amount of people or else it won't work.
If we can destroy whatever's synchronizing them...
Now, I do have a secret plan.
Then use it already!
Oh yeah?
What the hell are you doing?!
Bad luck, scarecrow.
The flame punishes sins.
Purgatory governs the flames.
Purgatory was created to burn sinners,
as the only violence God recognizes.
Violence is the acknowledgment of death.
Acknowledgement is recognition.
Stop it!
Recognition rests within you.
Don't you see that your own body is in trouble?!
Within refers to the world.
Connect your inner self with the outside world.
What the...
What is this...
But man...
That alchemist is messed up...
The one cutting a path through enemies should be oneself, not others...
Naturally, using Gregorio Replica would definitely direct you to the core no matter where it was hidden.
Inevitably, there were two intruders to begin with, but...
Evidently, your familiar has been devoured by Gregorio Replica?
Unfortunately for you, that one's much tougher than you think.
And?
What do you intend on doing by luring me here?
Alchemist, Aureolus-Izzard.
Treatment suffices.
But...
Her skin was torn open and her capillaries injured.
Had her arteries been cut, it would be worse.
You're not a doctor, and...
I am much more informed about
the flow of blood than other people.
Assist me.
Ah, wai-
Do not panic.
That is rude to the victim.
Hey, Sphynx.
Where did Touma go?
Ah, there was pudding in the refrigerator-
...What... Did you...
...Did you eat it?!
You ate it, didn't you?!
You ate it, right?!
Oh, well.
Something's weird.
There's no way Touma would just say
"oh, well" when someone eats his pudding.
Rune marks!
Done for now.
You're... pretty skilled...
Are you a certain famous doctor without a license?
Not a doctor.
But then...
I'm a magician.
Umm, which part shows that you're a magician?
I have this.
This.
A magic wand.
That's just a police club!
New material.
Quit joking!
We need to call an ambulance.
Good idea.
Don't sound as if you're not a part of this.
You need to go home, too.
That is, stop being held here, so that we can go out.
I have my own objective.
An objective that does not involve escaping from here,
but to achieve something that I can only accomplish while here.
No.
It's more accurate to say that without the alchemist, the objective would be impossible.
But, a friend wouldn't hold someone, okay?
That was before Aureolus took over.
I do not sense the necessity of going out.
Going out without caution will just attract "that".
Then, you're saying you've been hiding here all this time just because you don't want to be noticed by vampires.
Vampires.
Do you know what kind of an organism they're like?
Nothing is different.
Nothing is different between them and us.
They can laugh, and act for the sake of others.
That's what they are.
My blood attracts them with its nice smell.
I attract them, gather them, and kill them.
There is no motive.
I just kill them without exception.
Academy City is a place that governs power,
so I thought they would know the secret behind this.
If the secret is known, then the method to remove it might be available...
But the secret isn't known.
I don't want to kill anymore.
I have decided that if I had to kill anyone, I would kill myself.
Let me ask you one thing.
If you don't want to attract vampires,
then why were you spending all your money on food outside?
Simple.
Aureolus needs me because he wants a vampire sample.
If I stay inside the seal, then I can't attract vampires.
But...
Isn't that the opposite of your objective?
Aureolus promised me...
...that he wouldn't hurt the vampire.
Aureolus said...
...that there's someone he wants to save...
...that he needed the powers of a vampire.
That's why the pact was made.
To use this power not to kill,
but to save.
That's wrong.
If he really were the kind of person you speak of,
then I couldn't let him commit any more wrongs.
If I let this happen, then it'll really end up being an irreversible mistake.
Necessarily, what about me leads you to say that this will be irreversible?
He's...
Composedly, it does not matter.
I shall come for you right away.
Naturally, you have questions I need not answer.
You...
You shall not approach me any further.
H-How come...
Disappointingly, you bore me, young man.
Fade away-
Wait!
Y-You idiot!
Deep Blood has enough power to kill vampires.
That means...
And so at the very end, you ended up leaning on Deep Blood, relying on it, and prayed.
What's the difference between you and me, then?
That's not true!
This person doesn't know the significance of Deep Blood.
He came here to rescue someone that he met today and barely knows.
Aureolus-Izzard, what is your objective?
Is satisfying yourself by killing civilians your objective?
If that kind of meaningless act is your objective,
then I shall quit.
I have the right of choosing to bite
my own tongue to end my own life.
Necessarily, there is no time to waste in a place like this.
Young man, do not worry.
I won't kill you.
Forget everything that happened here!
Here, huh?
Where the mana that was being supplied to
the runes near Touma's room is completely cut off.
Where am I?
That you're here means we're still in Japan.
I think I'm forgetting something important...
...am I right?
Well, it's probably something that doesn't need to be remembered.
You sure?
Forget everything that happened here!
Let me teach you a charm that will erase your doubts.
Oriental charms are Kanzaki's specialty.
I'll ask her.
Just close your eyes and put your tongue out.
Here's a souvenir for having the balls to use me as a bait and escaping yourself!
There's a seal set up to prevent enemy intruders from escaping.
Hmm, it has been a while.
Who are you?
You don't remember me?
Naturally, you wouldn't happen to recall the name, Aureolus-Izzard?
No, perhaps that should be a fortunate occurrence.
Sleep.
Hey, these guys were the ones at the entrance-
The remnants of the Thirteen Knights, huh?
Commence attack!
Gregorio Choir.
The true choir of Gregorio.
But, didn't you say a lot of people were required for this Gregorio whatever?
Those 3,333 monks are probably sending their prayers right now from St. Peter's Basilica.
Revelation 8:7 -
"When the first angel blew his trumpet, hail and fire were mixed with blood and thrown to the earth"
What the hell are they trying to do?
Holy magic bombardment.
Bombardment?
Himegami and other students are still inside!
It's gonna collapse!
It's rising again?
Ars Magna.
Ars Magna?
That is our enemy's,
Aureolus-Izzard's true power.
Sphynx?!
Don't tell me...
...this is Index's...
nee kikoeru
Hey, can you hear it?
kioku wo samayotteru
Memories are wandering around.
nee kokoro wo shinjite
Hey, trust the heart
ikiteyukereba
as long as we live.
ikirusekai ga tatoe
Even if the world
chigatta toshite mo
we live in is different,
mamoritai mono ga arunara
as long as there's something to protect...
sashi dashita chikara wa dare no tame ni
For whom do you reach out your right hand?
toki hanatsu itsukusen no mana
The thousands of mana that you release...
sono shigusa ga
Your actions...
sono manazashi ga
Your gaze...
kokoro wo shimetsukeru
They tighten my heart...
tebanasanai
I won't let go of you.
The varied clashes surrounding Index.
The moment the alchemist who rebels against destiny shows his fangs,
roars will resonate inside the Misawa Cram School.
Next time, "Deep Blood".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!