Oowarai Beach
Touma!
Tou~ma!
Right now, I am away from Academy City, spending time at the beach with Index.
Obviously, this wasn't voluntary on my part.
Get out of this city right away?
It seems like the higher-ups are getting cranky about this.
At this rate... Kamijo-chan,
you'll be in a dangerous situation,
so until the dust settles...
...is what a couple of higher-ups are thinking...
Oh, and the place you'll be going to is... let's see...
Ah, here.
Seems like a nice place.
Oowarai Hot Springs - Beach Season is here
I'm going!
I'm going with you, Touma!
This will be the first time I go to the beach!
"No" means no!
Besides, you're an illegal alien who doesn't even have a valid ID!
Even if you try to tag along,
I bet you'll get stopped at the city limit!
Go ahead.
How in the world did he just let us go without a second look?!
...but yeah, just like that,
we ended up here for some odd reason.
And I just get a bad feeling from the name of the place they chose.
Note: "Oowarai" means big laugh/joke/jeer
Tou~ma!
I found a cute hat, and I'm going to give it to you as a present.
S-Sure...
Here you go.
Beware - Large Jellyfish Outbreak
Owww!!!
toaru nichijou wa parallel world ikusen mo no jikan ni
A certain daily life becomes thousands of parallel worlds, of different times.
onaji mono nado nai masterpiece de orinasu jikuu e
Let's fly to a dimension created by the one and only unique masterpiece.
kakinagutte hakushi no scenario ni pen saki ga kooru
Without much scribbling, the pen's movements freeze on the blank scenario sheet.
originality mezase douse kono michi wo yuku no dakara
Aim for originality, for that's the road that'll be taken away.
shinjite tooku made
Believe in it, far and beyond
kakenukete
Sprint!
kanjiru daichi kette
Feel it, kick this earth
daichi wo kette
and kick off the ground!
nanika no tame ni kogare ikiteru kanshoku wa kitto
The sensation of living for a reason will certainly
dare ni mo makenai chikara ni naru
Become a power that won't lose to anyone.
shiawase tte tabun kono shunkan onore ga shiru
This moment is probably when one realizes what happiness is...
kono kandou wo atarashii page ni kizamu
And uses that emotion to carve out a new page!
It's only my thing,
"highest masterpiece!"  ho
Angel Fall
Quite a misfortune you experienced so soon after your arrival...
This year's jellyfish season came quite early though.
And thanks to that, we have no guests.
I'm sorry, Touma.
It was really the first time I've seen a jellyfish.
Well then.
I will come back to retrieve the first-aid kit later.
Ah, th-thank you.
Excuse me.
We just got a call from your party-
-that they'd be arriving late.
That they'll arrive tomorrow morning-
And I thought we were going to see them soon!
Touma's-
Okay.
Thanks for the message.
Excuse me.
I'm so disappointed!
Yes, I was supposed to meet them here.
Kamijo Touya and Kamijo Shiina.
My parents, that is.
Touma.
Let's go take a bath.
Since I don't see them that often, Komoe-sensei seems to be taking care of me more than normal.
And it seems a cousin I grew up with is coming, too.
Hey Touma.
Yeah?
What kind of people are your parents?
What kind? Umm...
I'm really looking forward to seeing your parents.
Hey, Touma, are you listening?!
I am.
You'll find out tomorrow, won't you?
You're being a meanie again!
How much could it hurt to tell me now?!
And you're always, always so cold, so cruel, so blunt,
so rude, so brusque, so indifferent,
so unregretful, so hard to grasp-
Yeah, I'll find out tomorrow.
I lost my memories, so I obviously don't remember how my parents are,
what kind of people they were, or what kind of son I was.
Will I be able to act naturally before them?
The red-hot Hitotsui Hajime-san!
Good evening!
As such, I'm uncharacteristically nervous right now.
Heck, will they find out I lost my memories?
Well, there's no point worrying about it.
The fun will start tomorrow.
Yeah?
Are you awake, sir?
Your party just called now-
-that they will arrive soon-
Oh, okay!
Touma!
You look good.
Anything different?
And you, Dad?
That's right, I wanted to hand you something.
I went to India on my last business trip.
This is a souvenir, a local deity called something...
Thanks...
What's the matter?
It's as if you're meeting me for the first time.
Eh, ah-
Ah, let me get your bag.
Take Mom's and Otohime-chan's, as well.
I'm sure they'll be here soon.
Wait here.
This person is my father.
Sorry about our arrival.
We were supposed to get here last night.
You know, we just moved,
so we don't know where things are.
Move?
I told you, remember?
We went over this on the phone last month.
Ah, yeah.
I see.
I won't ever be able to see the home I was born in.
Oh, well...
Onii~chan!
Oh, there she is.
That's my cousin-
Onii~chan!
Ahh, Oniichan! I wanted to see you so badly!
Hey, Touma-oniichan!
Take me to the sea later! The sea!
C'mon, please?
Just hold it!
What, Oniichan?
Not "what"!
What are you doing here?!
And what's with your disgusting sister acting?
Sister or Sister-in-law,
that is the issue, eh?
What~
Dad!
Why did you bring someone like her here?!
Heck, since when did you know her?
What do you mean "someone like"?
What do you mean "since when did I know her"?
She's your cousin, Otohime-chan.
No, yo, cut it out!
That's bad.
My back-
They're touching my back-
My, my.
Touma-san, is being hugged by Otohime-chan embarrassing because you haven't experienced it in some time?
What the hell do you think you're doing here?
My, my.
Touma-san, is-
Weren't you sleeping like a pig in the room just now?!
Changing your clothing and teleporting, who are you, Shirai Kuroko?
And! What's with your obvious madam-like, señora-like way of speech?!
Watch your mouth, Touma.
What's with you?
Talking like that to your mother.
I said, what's with you talking that rudely to your mother.
Dad, are you saying...
...that this girl, who looks like she'd get kicked out of a R-15 movie...
...is my mother?
My, my.
Touma-san, are you saying your mom appears younger than her age?
And that this electrifying shocker of a girl...
...is my cousin?
What do you mean, shocker?
They are your mother and Otohime-chan, without a doubt.
What's wrong with you, Touma?
What's wrong? EVERYTHING!!!
What is this surprise?
Where's the "You've been punked" sign?!
Playing around with the tender soul of a young man like this!
What kind of grudge do you guys have against me?!
W-Wait, calm down, Touma.
See, look at this.
The swimsuit girl drawn on this pen.
Flip it and-
Good-bye!
W-Wait, Touma!
Where are you going in the middle of our conversation?
Wait, Oniichan!
Touma-san?
Toying with me like this...
I never thought my dad would be like that.
Welcome...
We have been waiting for you.
Please... come in...
Please take care of us.
What's wrong, Touma?
Y-You're part of this, too, Misaka sister?
Since when were you hiding here?!
...huh?
Ah, please don't mind him.
He's a bit emotional since we haven't seen each other in a while.
Thank you for staying here at our resort.
I will take you to your rooms.
Come, come. This way.
Oh, your friend is awake now it seems.
Ah, good morning, Touma.
Let's go eat breakfast already.
AHHHHHHHHHHHHH---
Onii~chan!
Right now,
I am at the beach with a Misaka Mikoto that's wearing a school swimsuit and pretending to be a sister character.
Obviously, this wasn't voluntary on my part.
What the hell?!
PLACEHOLDER
I can't breathe!
You're going to play a part in this, too?!
Wait, calm down, Touma!
Sir, please calm down.
In times like these, just take a dip and cool your head, Oniichan.
We'll come over afterwards, okay?
Such misfortune...
But how long is this comedy act going to last?
It's no longer at the level of
"You've been punked!" anymore.
Cooled your head a bit now, Touma?
I don't know what you're worrying about, but...
Here, I'll give you this.
It's a souvenir I got on my business trip to Russia.
See?
Fun, isn't it?
No, not at all.
My, my.
Touma-san, Dad's taste doesn't work on you, huh?
Y-Y-You... that-
Mom!
That looks perfect on you.
It was a great idea for me to have gotten you that.
You were the one who bought this swimsuit?!
Is this your taste, as well?!
Yeah.
If you go around the world on business trips,
you start to see that Japanese women need to be refined a bit-
What are you doing to me so suddenly, Touma?
I am certain now...
...that my father is a failure of a person...
...that he is just a damn lolicon pervert!
Oh, there she comes.
Your friend-
Tou~ma!
Touma!
Oniichan, what's wrong with you?
Touma-san!
Shut up!
Next in the news.
With the political scandal that has shaken up the White House,
the President will be holding a press conference to explain the situation.
What's the doc doing?
Komori reporting from Washington, D.C.
With the suspicions surrounding the Office this time,
it will be interesting to see what stance the President takes
and what will be said-
What are you doing, Sensei?!
Hey, I can't see, you know?
The President has arrived.
She is showing a calm, nonchalant face.
Yes, we can!
What is Shirai Kuroko doing...
Hold it...
This is way too ridiculous no matter how you look at it.
This is too well planned for a surprise trick.
Besides, there's no point in crossing the ocean just to do this trick.
Assuming it's not a prank...
Thank you!
Then, take this hill road in front of you and go straight-
Shana-tan, moe...
This person's uber annoying.
Drop the loser.
What the...
What exactly is going on here?
Oniichan!
Now, now...
See?
This was a photo from New Year's last year.
Do you remember me now, Touma-oniichan?
Are you okay?
You're really weird today, Oniichan.
So, what are you saying?
The girl in this picture is my cousin-
Yup, me!
Tatsugami Otohime!
She can't tell that her own appearance is different in this picture?
What's going on?
It's as if everyone's inside and outside are "inside out".
And they don't realize it themselves.
Why...
Kamijo Touma knows.
He knows from experience.
Even if it's not in my memories,
he knows that people that show up in these crazy cosplays are usually his acquaintances.
And thus, in these situations,
the attitude I should take is-
Hey, long time no-
-see...
Question no. 1 - Are you the spellcaster?
Asking question no. 1 again.
Are you the spellcaster?
Please wait.
It is rash to say that this young man is the suspect.
Hmph, glad we made it in time.
Tsuchimikado!
And he actually sees me properly as Tsuchimikado Motoharu.
Yes.
But the fact that he can properly recognize you must mean...
No, no, Neechin.
Do you see any traces of that on Kami-yan's body at all?
We must consider him the same as us; that he was able to escape the spell.
I am a magician from the English Purist Church, Necessarius,
Kanzaki Kaori.
I came here for the same reason as you.
To determine the origin of this distortion.
However, it is unreasonable to conclude that this young man is the caster.
I am a magician from the Russian Orthodox Church, Annihilatus,
Misha Croitsef.
Wow, to be able to see a magician of Annihilatus here!
Question no. 1 - What evidence do you have to say that this man isn't the caster?
Question no. 2 - If not this man, who is the caster?
Wait, I can't tell what's going on here!
Heck, what is Tsuchimikado doing here?!
This young man is not a magician, but an esper.
And his level is-
Are you guys just going to ignore the fact that I was almost killed?
Just gonna ignore me?
How disagreeable.
Your rudeness and vulgar attitude...
It appears you haven't grown at all...
This person is my acquaintance, as well?
Good thing I played dumb.
At least tell me what's going on here, okay?
How about it, Kanzaki?
Very well.
It's best to let all concerned members know what's going on,
else we cannot move forward.
Concerned member?
Me?
Currently, a certain magic spell is spreading around the entire world.
The structure and formula of the magic is unknown.
For convenience purposes, we are calling this magic "Angel Fall".
Angel Fall?
Do you know of the Tree of Sephiroth?
Shall I say it's a graph that ranks the spiritual classes...
...of the Supreme One, angels, and humans.
Normally, there is no way a human can attain the rank of an angel.
And the other way around certainly is impossible, as well.
In other words, all classes are full.
However, when an angel falls to the human class-
Time out!
Time out for a bit!
Having a hard time understanding, as expected?
Ah, but... angels? This is too much.
You should've experienced, firsthand, the effects of this spell, Kami-yan.
Effects?
Basically, the switching of appearances.
The emergence of this messed up world.
From the distortion caused by the fall of an angel,
the "appearance" and "content" of
the human world has been completely messed up.
And now, the musical chair game is all about first come, first served.
"Appearance" will quickly take the place of "content".
As a result...
Then, the fact that everyone's appearance is being switched around is...
While we don't know by whom and
for what purpose this magic was cast,
the important thing is the person in the middle of this distortion...
...and that is you, Kami-yan...
You are the number one suspect in the Angel Fall incident.
You escaped the effects of the magic,
and from the viewpoint of the magicians who are trying to stop the effects from spreading,
you are one who will be targeted.
But even so, it is hard to conclude
the true suspect is Kamijo Touma.
One, he does not possess any magical knowledge.
Two, we cannot see any trace of the "load"
typically seen on espers who have used magic.
Rebuttal no. 1 - This man has not been affected by the magic.
But hey, he's got the Imagine Breaker that can nullify any kind of illusion in this world with his right hand.
Oh, I see.
That's why...
Tsuchimikado, how do you know that?!
Number value: 40, 9, 30, 7.
Sum of 86.
Corresponding to "O' water,
become a serpent and strike like a sword"...
Correct.
I acknowledge this explanation as evidence for clearing him from suspicion.
Young man, I apologize here for pointing
my blade at you for the wrong reason.
Well then.
Even if you no longer have any suspicion on you,
it is a fact that Angel Fall is centered around you.
There is a high probability that the caster is near Kami-yan.
It is hard to imagine that a single caster is responsible for a spell of this scale.
There must be a ritual location that has a barrier or a magical seal deployed.
We'd need to destroy the ritual location...
...or defeat the caster himself.
There are only two ways to stop an Angel Fall.
Hold it, now.
What are you, Tsuchimikado?!
Why are you on this side of the world?
How do you know about my right hand?
Answer me, Tsuchimikado!
C'mon, Kami-yan.
I'm also a member of Necessarius.
nee kikoeru
Hey, can you hear it?
kioku wo samayotteru
Memories are wandering around.
nee kokoro wo shinjite
Hey, trust the heart
ikiteyukereba
as long as we live.
ikirusekai ga tatoe
Even if the world
chigatta toshite mo
we live in is different,
mamoritai mono ga arunara
as long as there's something to protect...
sashi dashita chikara wa dare no tame ni
For whom do you reach out your right hand?
toki hanatsu itsukusen no mana
The thousands of mana that you release...
sono shigusa ga
Your actions...
sono manazashi ga
Your gaze...
kokoro wo shimetsukeru
They tighten my heart...
tebanasanai
I won't let go of you.
Searching for the caster that started Angel Fall,
Tsuchimikado and I headed for Dad's place.
The horrible finding we made there was...
Next time, "Kamijo Touya".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!