A Certain Magical Index
A certain daily life becomes thousands of parallel worlds, of different times.
toaru nichijou wa parallel world ikusen mo no jikan ni
Let's fly to a dimension created by the one and only unique masterpiece.
onaji mono nado nai masterpiece de orinasu jikuu e
Without much scribbling, the pen's movements freeze on the blank scenario sheet.
kakinagutte hakushi no scenario ni pen saki ga kooru
Aim for originality, for that's the road that'll be taken away.
originality mezase douse kono michi wo yuku no dakara
Believe in it, far and beyond
shinjite tooku made
Sprint!
kakenukete
Feel it, kick this earth
kanjiru daichi kette
and kick off the ground!
daichi wo kette
The sensation of living for a reason will certainly
nanika no tame ni kogare ikiteru kanshoku wa kitto
Become a power that won't lose to anyone.
dare ni mo makenai chikara ni naru
This moment is probably when one realizes what happiness is...
shiawase tte tabun kono shunkan onore ga shiru
And uses that emotion to carve out a new page!
kono kandou wo atarashii page ni kizamu
It's only my thing,
"highest masterpiece!"  ho
Counter Stop
Unknown Entity
AIM Dispersion Field
for Dummies
Neither the nonchalant present, nor the unforeseeable future
nanigenai ima mo mada minu ashita de sae mo
Know of the firm resolve within my heart.
yuzurenai omoi dake wa mune ni himeteru
Fighting my way past the coincidental laughs,
guuzen to warau koe kakiwake
and arriving on the other side, believing in myself.
tadoritsuku mukou gawa jibun wo shinjiteru
They are always remembered, the wishes I want granted,
omoidesareru koto wa kanaetai negai wa itsumo
One more time, one more time, as I kept challenging.
mou ichido mou ichido dake to idomitsuzuketeta
Just a bit more
sukoshi dake
The memories that were lost, I will get them back,
nakushita omoi wa sou katachi wo kaetetemo kitto
Even if they change, until the day comes, I will keep searching.
torimodosu sono hi ga kuru made sagashi tsuzuketeku
Just a bit more, one more time
sukoshi dake mou ichido