A Certain Magical Index
Be it the reason I live here,
koko ni ikiru sono wake mo
or be it everything I encountered here,
kono basho de deau subete mo
even if it were a different world,
tatoe chigau sekai demo
no matter where I am, this feeling won't be swayed.
doko ni itemo kono omoi wa yuruganai
The pain from the heart getting pierced,
mune wo chikuri to sasu itami
that should be directed at those bystanders jeering at you.
sore mo warau shiawase na mono tachi e
Turn your back on them.
se wo mukeyuku
Fate beckons the obvious suffering.
touzen no kurushimi wo unmei ga sasou
The trembling feet remember,
furuedasu ashi ga oboeteru
a certain now.
kakushin ni
Illusions alone are not enough to protect
yume dake ja mamorenai
such an unreliable power.
tayoranai chikara
I will now see for myself with these hands.
ima kono te de shirukara
No more hesitation.
mayowanai
Sisters
Shirai
Misaka
Call
Cancel
Hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoeru
Memories are wandering around.
kioku wo samayotteru
Hey, trust the heart
nee kokoro wo shinjite
as long as we live.
ikiteyukereba
Even if the world
ikirusekai ga tatoe
we live in is different,
chigatta toshite mo
as long as there's something to protect...
mamoritai mono ga arunara
For whom do you reach out your right hand?
sashi dashita chikara wa dare no tame ni
The thousands of mana that you release...
toki hanatsu itsukusen no mana
Your actions...
sono shigusa ga
Your gaze...
sono manazashi ga
They tighten my heart...
kokoro wo shimetsukeru
I won't let go of you.
tebanasanai