If Academy City's strongest Level 5...
...loses pathetically to its weakest Level 0...
...then perhaps...
...this outrageous experiment will be suspended.
Although it's not as easy as I'm making it sound,
it's something worth attempting.
Right, Misaka?
koko ni ikiru sono wake mo
Be it the reason I live here,
kono basho de deau subete mo
or be it everything I encountered here,
tatoe chigau sekai demo
even if it were a different world,
doko ni itemo kono omoi wa yuruganai
no matter where I am, this feeling won't be swayed.
mune wo chikuri to sasu itami
The pain from the heart getting pierced,
sore mo warau shiawase na mono tachi e
that should be directed at those bystanders jeering at you.
se wo mukeyuku
Turn your back on them.
touzen no kurushimi wo unmei ga sasou
Fate beckons the obvious suffering.
furuedasu ashi ga oboeteru
The trembling feet remember,
kakushin ni
a certain now.
yume dake ja mamorenai
Illusions alone are not enough to protect
tayoranai chikara
such an unreliable power.
ima kono te de shirukara
I will now see for myself with these hands.
mayowanai
No more hesitation.
Weakest
Strongest
(Strongest) VS (Weakest)
Looks like it was wheat flour inside.
You've heard of "dust explosions" at least, right?
Good grief.
Didn't I just learn my lesson?
I'd feel it too with this lack of oxygen.
Damn, I thought I was gonna die.
Rejoice, for you could be the first in the world, 'ya know?
You pushed me to a near-death situation.
Try as hard as you want, but you won't get a step near me.
And even if you did get near me,
what could you possibly do to me?
I can control any vector I come in touch with.
The second I come in touch with you,
I'll blow up every single one of your veins and organs inside your body, okay?
You got that processed in your brain yet?
But, okay,
the fact you are standing and breathing before me,
Accelerator, is somewhat of a miracle.
Asking for more is a bit of a luxury, don't you think?
So, lie down and rest already!!!
Damn you!!!
Okay...
This is interesting, damn.
Good, this is perfect.
You got my blood jumping for joy now.
You little...
My right hand's power is working.
Damn...
Damn this...
What the hell... is happening...
So, you've never lost, huh?
You defeat all your enemies in one shot.
You deflect all attacks away.
People like you wouldn't know how to street fight.
Don't get too cocky, thug!
What?!
Even they... do their best in fulfilling their lives...
They do their best... living all they can...
...and these people who lived all they could...
...why do they have to end up being food for the likes of you?
Lived all they could, you say?
Do their best in living all they can, you say?
What is that bullshit?
Kill him.
What? What? What's this?
In the end, you're just all talk and powerless.
C'mon, I'll take care of you with one more hit,
so try your best coming out of the loser's bracket, eh?
Compress... Compress...
Compress air.
Compress... Good, I've come up with something fun!
What's the matter? Where did your bravado disappear to?
I need you to play along with me somewhat
or else this debt won't be settled.
Accelerator!
Freeze.
...Don't...
...Don't... Misaka...
Sorry.
You wished for nothing to be lost,
for everyone to be smiling,
for everyone to be able to make it back safely.
But that's not possible.
So... sorry...
I know this is selfish of me,
but even so...
...even so, I... I want you to live on...
DON'T!!!
Plasma?
He controlled the direction of the winds,
gathered them into one spot,
and created plasma?!
There's nothing my power can do against something like this...
If I could control the winds, as well...
But, that kind of power's...
Wind?
I'm quite sure that the plasma was formed by compressing nearby winds together.
Accelerator's calculating the flow of wind to control the plasma.
If so...
Please, wake up.
I need you to do something for me.
No, this is something only you can do.
I know this is asking for too much.
But, please, just wake up this one time!
Just listen to my wish this one time!
I probably won't be able to save everyone...
...no matter how hard I try... I won't...
...so... so please...
...so please... I need your power to protect... his dream!!!
"I do not understand the meaning of your words,"
"but for some reason, they resonated very powerfully," comments MISAKA with utmost honesty.
I miscalculated the winds?
What? What's happening?
There shouldn't be any mistake in my calculations.
This irregular pattern of movement can't be natural wind no matter how you look at it.
It can't be...
Wait, I've heard of this.
I remember that if you direct a certain special kind of electromagnetic wave at the motor of a power generator,
that'll make it start spinning...
You bitch...
I'll kill 'ya...
You think I'd let you?
Don't get too conceited, low class.
You're way too weak for me.
Perfect vision can only be measured as 2.0 - same idea.
The levels in this city only go up to 5,
which is why I'm reluctantly staying in this position.
Don't... touch...
Don't... touch them...
You're really something, 'ya know?
You're really... the best!!!
Grit your teeth well, "strongest" one.
My "weakest" attack...
...might shake you up a little!!!
Huh?
Mi-Mi-Mi-Mi-Misaka-san?!
Why am I experiencing such a happy event?
I don't remember raising any flags like this at all.
"To inform you properly, let it be known you were the one who came grabbing me,"  recites MISAKA.
N-No, it's not true!
You're saying I'm so sexually deprived that even under anesthesia,
my hand went for a girl's breasts on its own?
That's so not true!!!
"All you did was grab MISAKA's hands," adds MISAKA.
"Moving your hand to this location was MISAKA's will,"
"so you are not at any fault," answers MISAKA.
"MISAKA was simply using the electric flow in your body..."
"...to calculate your heartbeat and brainwaves," replies MISAKA.
Wait, so my hand is touching them right now?
I can't feel anything because of the anesthesia though.
Nor can I move a finger.
Such... Such misfortune!!!
"I did not detect any irregularities in your brain's speech center though," suggests MISAKA with a bit of anxiety.
Well, looks like we both made it back somehow.
"Regarding that," replies MISAKA,
"MISAKA isn't able to return to the same world you are in yet," answers MISAKA honestly.
Wait... they're still performing the experiments?
"No, that is not it."
"The experiment, following Accelerator's defeat,
is going to be suspended," explains MISAKA cordially.
"MISAKA's problem is an issue with MISAKA's body," explains MISAKA.
Body?
"Yes."
"MISAKA's body is a clone body created from Oneesama's cells to begin with,"
"and with the addition of many kinds of chemicals, this led to accelerated growth," explains MISAKA.
"Thus, the duration of an already shortened lifespan
of a clone is shortened even more."
"Do you understand?" asks MISAKA.
"That is why MISAKA will be staying at a research facility to adjust MISAKA's body..."
"Are you listening?" as MISAKA stares at you.
Adjust?
"Yes."
"By adjusting the hormones that expedite the body's growth..."
"...and the speed of cell segmentation, a certain amount of lifespan may be recoverable," answers MISAKA.
"Well then."
Hey, wait!
Adjusting... will that cure you?
"Don't worry."
"MISAKA will see you soon," declares MISAKA.
Well, looks like there's nothing serious.
But you sure have an affection for this room.
Rest well for the time being.
See you later then.
Thanks, Doc.
Ah, you up?
It's you, Misaka?
Afterwards, what did-
Here, a gift for the sick.
Ahh...
I just picked some expensive looking ones from the basement of the department store.
I'm sure these cookies are delicious to a certain extent.
Home-made cookies are the best, you know?
What kind of character are you hoping I'd be?
You know?
The clumsy character that tries clumsily hard and makes some crumbled cookies.
You don't get it, huh?
I said, what kind of character are you hoping I'd be?
Stop!
Really, stop!
Gosh!
Ah, that's right.
Your sister came by early this morning.
I see...
I'll be going now.
Hey...
If you hadn't given them your DNA map,
then the sisters would've never been born.
Even though that experiment was wrong in many ways,
the fact that they were born... was, I think, something you should be proud of...
But more than 10,000 Sisters have died because of me...
Even so...
I'm sure they don't hate you.
Had they never been born, they wouldn't have been able to experience happiness or sadness.
So, it's okay for you to smile.
Those sisters that you wanted to protect so much...
...aren't people that satisfy themselves by forcing their own wounds and pains on to others, right?
See ya.
Touma, got something to say?
Umm...
Good morning?
Wait, wait!
They said my injuries this time are pretty serious and stuff.
Heck, shouldn't you show some worry for the master of the house?
I was worried!
I was worried for you.
Sorry.
Touma, you put all the burden on yourself this time,
and this time, and this time, right?
If you don't consult us a bit,
then I might really need to lecture you.
Oh well, digging too much into this wouldn't do any good.
So, what did you fight for, in the end, Touma?
For myself, I bet.
nee kikoeru
Hey, can you hear it?
kioku wo samayotteru
Memories are wandering around.
nee kokoro wo shinjite
Hey, trust the heart
ikiteyukereba
as long as we live.
ikirusekai ga tatoe
Even if the world
chigatta toshite mo
we live in is different,
mamoritai mono ga arunara
as long as there's something to protect...
sashi dashita chikara wa dare no tame ni
For whom do you reach out your right hand?
toki hanatsu itsukusen no mana
The thousands of mana that you release...
sono shigusa ga
Your actions...
sono manazashi ga
Your gaze...
kokoro wo shimetsukeru
They tighten my heart...
tebanasanai
I won't let go of you.
A touching reunion with my parents by the summer sea,
or at least, that was the original plan...
But with the appearance of a dangerous magic spell, now we're in a panic?
This person is... my mother?
Next time, "Angel Fall".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!