[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 720
PlayResY: 396
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: EDC,方正黑体_GBK,24,&H0031a6db,&Hff00ffff,&H00efefef,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,2,15,15,13,134
Style: title,華康娃娃體(P),35,&H0031a6db,&Hf0000000,&H00efefef,&H001f1f1f,-1,0,0,0,100,100,4,0.00,1,4,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPJ,DFMaruGothic-Md,21,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,15,15,13,128
Style: EDJ,DFHeiMedium-UN,21,&H0031a6db,&Hff00ffff,&H00efefef,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,15,15,13,128
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00ffffff,&H005955fd,&H00000000,&H00ffffff,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,10,12,134
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,12,134
Style: OPC,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00ffffff,&H006367ef,&H002d2ed4,&H50222222,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,15,15,11,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.87,0:00:07.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.32,0:00:08.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.96,0:00:27.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長請讓開一下  你妨礙到我工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.87,0:00:29.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.16,0:00:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那給我錢吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.92,0:00:34.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要我動就給我錢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.86,0:00:36.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.62,0:00:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零食吃光了  幫我丟掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.34,0:00:43.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.54,0:00:53.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代  聖代
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.78,0:00:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.88,0:01:00.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鳥遊  冷靜點
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.10,0:01:02.17,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想緊緊抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.10,0:01:02.17,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.23,0:01:02.92,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.23,0:01:02.92,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.02,0:01:04.11,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想緊緊咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.02,0:01:04.11,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.15,0:01:04.77,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.15,0:01:04.77,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.89,0:01:06.02,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想嚇唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.89,0:01:06.02,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.07,0:01:08.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}現在還是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.07,0:01:08.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.22,0:01:11.01,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.22,0:01:11.01,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.69,0:01:27.51,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.69,0:01:27.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}平常心が大事です
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.66,0:01:28.58,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.66,0:01:28.58,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.62,0:01:31.46,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抑制住急躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.62,0:01:31.46,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}はやる心を抑えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.58,0:01:32.41,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.58,0:01:32.41,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモンモンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.45,0:01:35.37,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}做個平常人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.45,0:01:35.37,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}常識人になりましょう！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.47,0:01:36.31,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.47,0:01:36.31,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.41,0:01:39.63,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}難應付的人也會親密起來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.41,0:01:39.63,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ヤバイ人ならすぐなれる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.89,0:01:43.91,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}兩人蔚藍的Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.89,0:01:43.91,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}青い二人のヘブン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.00,0:01:46.72,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}變成小狗的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.00,0:01:46.72,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}子犬になる夢は
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.95,0:01:47.67,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}稀奇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.95,0:01:47.67,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}レア
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:54.57,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}愉快燦爛地投影在腦海中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:54.57,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}ユカイ特盛りの脳トレースして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.61,0:01:57.24,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在天空盤旋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.61,0:01:57.24,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}空を　駆け回りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.70,0:02:01.84,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}在搖曳思念下的果實
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.70,0:02:01.84,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}揺れる想いの下の　果肉には
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.94,0:02:05.36,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}充滿戀愛的甜美
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.94,0:02:05.36,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}恋の美味しさだけ　ふくらんで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.41,0:02:09.63,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}如果有製作美味菜譜的野心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.41,0:02:09.63,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}凄いメニューを作ると　野望なら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.75,0:02:13.65,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}那就用心培育果實吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.75,0:02:13.65,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}まっとうに　フルーツ　はぐくみましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.31,0:02:15.45,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想緊緊抱住你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.31,0:02:15.45,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}抱きしめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.56,0:02:16.23,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pa
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.56,0:02:16.23,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.27,0:02:17.36,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想緊緊咬住你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.27,0:02:17.36,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}かみみめたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.45,0:02:17.95,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}mon mon
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.45,0:02:17.95,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}モンモン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.07,0:02:19.27,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}好想嚇唬一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.07,0:02:19.27,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}おどかしたいんだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.38,0:02:21.18,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}現在還是先忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.38,0:02:21.18,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}今は我慢しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.22,0:02:21.84,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.22,0:02:21.84,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.94,0:02:22.92,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}努力修行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.94,0:02:22.92,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}修行しよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.02,0:02:23.69,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}pan pan pan
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.02,0:02:23.69,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}パンパンパン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.75,0:02:25.07,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}拿出幹勁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.75,0:02:25.07,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}気合いしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.20,0:02:27.97,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.20,0:02:27.97,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be3}COOLISH WALK…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.16,0:02:35.99,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(235,270)\fs25}「瓦古娜利亞的巨大胃袋」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.93,0:02:34.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好了  羞鳥遊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.81,0:02:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐好歹也是個店長
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.73,0:02:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.21,0:02:43.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來的人生  你也會和年長的人接觸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.67,0:02:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須要尊重他們哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.99,0:02:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝姐姐樣子的前輩好可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.81,0:02:51.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要尊敬年長的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.93,0:02:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鳥遊好像從進店打工開始就和杏子姐關係搞得不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.60,0:02:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.36,0:03:00.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你問為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.10,0:03:02.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.72,0:03:04.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好煩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.24,0:03:06.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒臭味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.48,0:03:09.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.41,0:03:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半老徐娘什麼的都一樣啦  讓我今後和店長搞好關係什麼的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.93,0:03:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是再多瞭解一點店長的話  說不定就會喜歡上她的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.45,0:03:22.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要聽聽嗎  關於混混時代的店長的限制級武勇傳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.01,0:03:24.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不想聽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.15,0:03:27.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有什麼共同點呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.51,0:03:32.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有什麼相似點的話  說不定能成為變親密的契機
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.29,0:03:35.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此  共同點嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.16,0:03:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生肖一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.53,0:03:40.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要大我12歲啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.74,0:03:43.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有其他的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.49,0:03:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他會吸引小鳥遊的地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.47,0:03:49.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.15,0:03:52.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那回到基礎問題  先報上三圍什麼的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.02,0:03:53.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相馬！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.79,0:03:55.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要命了嗎！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.54,0:03:58.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開玩笑的開玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.16,0:04:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.80,0:04:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們希望他們可以搞好關係
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.13,0:04:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啦  我完全誤以為是想性騷擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.53,0:04:09.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們懂的  快把刀收起來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.70,0:04:13.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代姐  請把杏子姐的優點告訴我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.46,0:04:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  我會一五一十詳細說明的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.26,0:04:20.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油  會說很久的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.54,0:04:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啦  說很久什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.05,0:04:24.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有短短的六小時左右喲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.96,0:04:26.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.96,0:04:29.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也請你們聽聽山田的優點  差不多十個小時…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.77,0:04:31.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不想聽  幹活去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.72,0:04:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過分
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.05,0:04:38.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進行得不是很順利呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.35,0:04:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那請前輩告訴我店長的優點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.32,0:04:48.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很…很強！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.92,0:04:51.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很強…還有其他的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.93,0:04:52.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高大
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.24,0:04:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是優點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.15,0:04:57.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鳥遊  不要責備她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.53,0:04:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那店長的優點是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.66,0:05:03.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健…健康？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.45,0:05:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這答案太過普通了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.84,0:05:11.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是也有其他的優點的  好了快搞好關係吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.41,0:05:13.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不是想不到她的優點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.62,0:05:16.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了前輩  我知道了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.62,0:05:17.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.67,0:05:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.71,0:05:19.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了小鳥遊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.53,0:05:22.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又在逗種島了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.86,0:05:27.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從根本來說是店長的錯  讓這麼小的孩子為你操心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.60,0:05:33.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要每次都讓打工的說你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.90,0:05:35.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要隨便吃店裡的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.82,0:05:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明有這麼多的說
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.53,0:05:39.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吃的是客人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.08,0:05:41.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家庭餐館不就是吃的地方嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.05,0:05:43.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我說了 可以吃的是客人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.97,0:05:46.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在工作  所以也算是客人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.83,0:05:50.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  客人會乖乖付錢的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.15,0:05:53.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤君…這點小事就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.10,0:06:01.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不夠的份  記得要買上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.78,0:06:09.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤…莫非他  討厭我？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.55,0:06:12.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長現在才發覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.61,0:06:17.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔細想想  他好像針對我的態度特別差
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.97,0:06:18.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做什麼惹到他了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.28,0:06:24.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他才沒有討厭你  佐藤君他很清楚杏子姐的優點
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.70,0:06:26.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在和他說的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.85,0:06:28.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是主要原因
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.58,0:06:36.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來領班一直很照顧店長呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.03,0:06:38.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從以前開始就這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.45,0:06:42.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  八千代以外的人  也都是比自己小的小鬼比較容易親近
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.62,0:06:46.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶木刀的小鬼  擅長特攻的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.37,0:06:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎…哎…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.55,0:06:50.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐  我做好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.06,0:06:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長和領班果然是不會有結果的關係呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.98,0:07:01.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好  她們兩人都很幸福不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.57,0:07:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太狡猾了  店長不工作隨便吃也都不會被罵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.68,0:07:09.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田也想被這樣寵著
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.82,0:07:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤先生  今天請寵一下山田吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.99,0:07:16.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開什麼玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.28,0:07:20.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田也希望能像店長一樣被寵著
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.56,0:07:21.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去幹活
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.10,0:07:28.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤  砂糖  明明叫砂糖卻不像砂糖那樣甜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.10,0:07:28.82,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}註：佐藤和砂糖的假名都是さとう  音調發音不同而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.52,0:07:30.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.76,0:07:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煩死了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.78,0:07:39.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.22,0:07:45.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代姐八千代姐請寵一下山田
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.30,0:07:49.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  現在在給杏子姐做第二杯聖代呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.71,0:07:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.74,0:07:56.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嚇死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.81,0:07:59.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天請寵寵山田我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.45,0:08:02.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寵你？怎麼寵？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.15,0:08:04.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像相馬先生那樣鼓勵我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.94,0:08:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有鼓勵你嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.03,0:08:11.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是總是只有相馬先生鼓勵我 山田我偶爾也想讓別人鼓勵
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.30,0:08:16.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 山田小姐總是和相馬先生在一起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.51,0:08:18.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田我喜歡相馬先生哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.94,0:08:20.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.48,0:08:21.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開心？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.55,0:08:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他很淵博嘛 願意陪我聊納豆
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.59,0:08:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.67,0:08:28.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2315根
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.61,0:08:31.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能在瞬間告訴我海膽刺的根數
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.79,0:08:34.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田超期待的說
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.00,0:08:37.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海膽刺…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.55,0:08:50.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他還能寵山田的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.54,0:08:52.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  小葵你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.60,0:09:00.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在山田心裡  種島是比山田小的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.59,0:09:05.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊  沒人寵你所以覺得寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.94,0:09:08.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有店長被寵著  真是太不公平了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.75,0:09:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那麼為了得到大家表揚  來學習下聖代的製作方法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.21,0:09:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能得到表揚?  山田要加油
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.68,0:09:19.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來  只要按順序疊加上去就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.46,0:09:21.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能擠好生奶油…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.30,0:09:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真前衛…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.71,0:09:30.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田不會氣餒的  為了讓全世界都寵著我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.79,0:09:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  就是這種氣勢啊  小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.55,0:09:34.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.33,0:09:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.47,0:09:40.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通往世界的道路真是坎坷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.76,0:09:42.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.73,0:09:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒完成的  可能會不好吃的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.57,0:09:52.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩飯都比這好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.78,0:09:56.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會吃的  失敗的作品我會幫你吃掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.99,0:09:57.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,練習吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.46,0:09:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.90,0:10:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代姐  杏子姐吃了我的聖代失敗品
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.50,0:10:12.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.38,0:10:19.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著默默地吃著聖代的店長  總覺得好想養一隻狗狗了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.61,0:10:20.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗狗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.77,0:10:24.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田有幹勁了  我會加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.17,0:10:26.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.79,0:10:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有人會把所有的材料都用光了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.57,0:10:37.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤先生辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.14,0:10:41.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然山田也是問題  但店長就不能像樣點嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.18,0:10:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說都不聽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.81,0:10:47.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次都有轟袒護她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.81,0:10:50.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是在吃卻根本不工作
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.78,0:10:53.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不工作卻和轟關係很好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.15,0:10:57.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長要是不在的話  轟絕對會從了佐藤…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.54,0:11:01.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們倆…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.06,0:11:08.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之店長這樣很頭疼呢  雖然對前廳來說只是不工作而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.70,0:11:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廚房可是有實際損失的  只要有吃的她就會吃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.61,0:11:15.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說別光讓我去說她啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.40,0:11:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也去勸勸那個大胃王不要再吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.66,0:11:23.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  我雖然沒有特別討厭店長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.23,0:11:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很喜歡女人困擾的表情  就去試試吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.19,0:11:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抖S
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.34,0:11:33.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之先讓她體會一下什麼叫食材有限吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.97,0:11:36.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長  商量個事可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.01,0:11:42.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  我把食材的進貨數量搞錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.43,0:11:44.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個月各種食材緊張
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.23,0:11:47.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請一定不要再吃店裡的東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.06,0:11:51.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是亂吃的話  這店就會倒閉  大家就回老家了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.86,0:11:54.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.93,0:12:03.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是口胡的  但是至少會有點效果的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.24,0:12:07.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒閉…回老家…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.38,0:12:17.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半老徐娘什麼的果然不是我的菜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.72,0:12:19.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少身材也要像前輩那樣的還好說
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.64,0:12:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.56,0:12:49.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡的是這種生物呀！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.18,0:12:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羞鳥遊綁了個小女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.43,0:12:56.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快報警！快報警!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.93,0:12:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  她是迷路了  迷路了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.33,0:13:00.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷路了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.80,0:13:02.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在附近找了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.63,0:13:03.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但沒找到她父母
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.19,0:13:06.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放小孩子一個人在外面感覺不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.99,0:13:08.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且快下雨了的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.39,0:13:11.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就盡全力帶進店裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.60,0:13:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不是綁來的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.92,0:13:17.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鳥遊帶著小孩子  總覺得有犯罪的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.63,0:13:19.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼連佐藤都說這種話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.42,0:13:23.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是因為太可愛了才綁來的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.36,0:13:24.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快還回去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.28,0:13:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.56,0:13:28.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算太可愛到實再忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.17,0:13:30.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會招待到家裡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.64,0:13:33.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了不吃壞牙齒  給她適度的點心和飲料
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.19,0:13:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了保護視力  每天看電視不超過一小時
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.33,0:13:41.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有為了不讓父母生氣  5點前讓她回家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.55,0:13:43.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想太周全了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.67,0:13:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.24,0:13:51.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之先把這貼到店裡和員工出入口吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.60,0:13:52.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前輩好偉大
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.63,0:13:58.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好…好可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.09,0:14:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們倆雖然不知道在搞什麼  快點去工作
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.13,0:14:05.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.18,0:14:09.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那杏子姐  迷路的小孩子就交給你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.39,0:14:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她欺負你就喊救命
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.02,0:14:14.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去工作
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.92,0:14:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓您久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.55,0:14:44.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您點的餐這樣都上齊了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.48,0:15:18.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…  羞鳥遊說這個要給迷路小孩吃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.55,0:15:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐想吃掉迷路小孩!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.71,0:15:26.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店裡人請客的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.18,0:15:28.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客氣  快吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.19,0:15:35.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下輪到外來的迷路小孩被寵著了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.24,0:15:43.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波  伊波  大家光寵著迷路小孩了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.62,0:15:45.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田好不甘心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.59,0:15:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎?那是因為她迷路了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.39,0:15:50.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩子又做不了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.33,0:15:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不保護好的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.79,0:15:54.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣  山田我也是什麼都做不了的說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.09,0:15:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還好意思理直氣壯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.50,0:16:02.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田要去說服小鳥遊叫他更寵我一點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.72,0:16:05.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊波要一起去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.06,0:16:07.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.48,0:16:08.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就看著吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.29,0:16:23.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失敗了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.02,0:16:24.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖  不哭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.49,0:16:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好沒跟著去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.44,0:16:56.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷路小孩的事問了一圈店裡的客人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.27,0:16:58.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似沒人知道她
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.17,0:17:01.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就確定不是店裡客人的小孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.47,0:17:02.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.08,0:17:04.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說怎麼辦  小鳥遊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.45,0:17:09.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法了  我來養育她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.86,0:17:13.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的  反正我家有個妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.13,0:17:16.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼沒關係啊  冷靜點
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.24,0:17:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多可以報警了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.63,0:17:22.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…對了  迷路小孩的事有頭緒了沒？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.84,0:17:23.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別過來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.25,0:17:25.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩子會被教壞的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.65,0:17:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過份
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.04,0:18:46.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.59,0:18:56.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.94,0:19:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意外地相處得很好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.98,0:19:14.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有吃迷路小孩的蛋糕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.41,0:19:18.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得良心有點過意不去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.85,0:19:20.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真巧了  我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.01,0:19:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杏子姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.28,0:19:25.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須吃的那份一直以來都是靠著店裡的說
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.23,0:19:29.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤  這下應該滿足了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.92,0:19:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算把責任推給我一個人嗎  你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.66,0:19:36.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很擔心店長  但得盡快找到迷路小孩的媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.23,0:19:38.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個不用擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.63,0:19:42.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.19,0:19:46.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.84,0:19:50.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有什麼媽媽說「這種時候給別人看一下」的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.14,0:19:59.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對於經常迷路的孩子來說  一般都會帶著父母的聯繫方式
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.54,0:20:01.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你一開始就說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.44,0:20:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相馬好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.56,0:20:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  相馬好厲害…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.68,0:20:09.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這感謝好像很不情願似地
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.04,0:20:13.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太感謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.53,0:20:17.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這孩子一不注意就不知道跑哪兒去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.80,0:20:20.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用不用  很高興能幫上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.14,0:20:22.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.55,0:20:35.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想領回我家養育的說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.12,0:20:39.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各種意義上對那孩子的成長有害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.41,0:20:42.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說店長人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.53,0:20:44.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.74,0:20:45.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.27,0:20:49.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.71,0:20:52.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是用快要過期的廢棄食材做的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.71,0:20:55.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算吃了也不會影響店裡的庫存
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.34,0:20:59.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死在那邊精疲力盡的樣子太煩人了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.71,0:21:00.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.43,0:21:02.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.43,0:21:06.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有…這種閃亮亮的效果也很煩人  別這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.63,0:21:19.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤很擅長做料理呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.60,0:21:21.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是按照食譜上的做而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.79,0:21:25.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像討厭我的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.86,0:21:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對給自己食物的人一般都會喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.02,0:21:30.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我也喜歡佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.33,0:21:32.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這還真是榮幸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.08,0:21:35.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八千代之後第二喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.16,0:21:37.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨你便
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.08,0:21:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果還是給她吃了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.42,0:21:58.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.22,0:22:01.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說可以吃就全吃光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.86,0:22:04.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不可以吃就完全不吃
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.60,0:22:07.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做對事  真的很累人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.42,0:22:09.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無所謂了  隨她去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.65,0:22:13.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了她那年齡  性格基本定型已經改不掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.13,0:22:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為身邊多數為年長者的人來說
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.35,0:22:20.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總結一個對付外表像大人  內心卻還是小孩子的人的訣竅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.80,0:22:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己變成熟點
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.81,0:22:27.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺悟到這種程度的話  一開始就說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.69,0:22:29.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鳥遊不也生氣了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.33,0:22:34.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.10,0:22:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一盤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.15,0:23:02.09,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}チラリと洩れる目論見は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.15,0:23:02.09,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}不經意間流露出的意圖
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.41,0:23:05.70,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}上目づかいなり
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.41,0:23:05.70,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}是曖昧的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.50,0:23:09.32,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}スキマに忍び込みたいと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.50,0:23:09.32,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}想要見縫插針
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.65,0:23:12.37,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}タギってるけど
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.65,0:23:12.37,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}內心卻激動不已
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.57,0:23:16.12,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつものように
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.57,0:23:16.12,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}一起來裝作
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.26,0:23:19.72,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}きどっていしまょ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.26,0:23:19.72,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}和以往一樣的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.90,0:23:23.49,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}その距離もまた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.90,0:23:23.49,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}這份距離也
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.61,0:23:26.85,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いけてるんです
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.61,0:23:26.85,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}感覺還不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.97,0:23:28.92,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LOVE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.97,0:23:28.92,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LOVE&PEACE
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.96,0:23:30.96,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LIFE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.96,0:23:30.96,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}LIFE&PEACE！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.12,0:23:34.61,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}飛び道具は　胸に秘め
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.12,0:23:34.61,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}把愛之矢  藏在心裡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.73,0:23:38.89,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつか大事な　日を待とう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.73,0:23:38.89,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}等待著重要的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.23,0:23:41.56,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}夢の地図なら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.23,0:23:41.56,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}到達夢想的地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.73,0:23:45.50,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}瞳の奥に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.73,0:23:45.50,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}就在你眼中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.66,0:23:49.13,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}秘密兵器は　二人のため
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.66,0:23:49.13,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}秘密兵器是兩個人的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.25,0:23:53.45,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}いつも磨いて　備えよう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.25,0:23:53.45,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}隨時打磨好  以備不時之需
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.71,0:23:56.05,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}本気の恋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.71,0:23:56.05,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}真正的愛戀
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.23,0:23:59.75,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}それは突然
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.23,0:23:59.75,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}是突然之間
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.89,0:24:04.70,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}花が咲く
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.89,0:24:04.70,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be3}開花結果
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.92,0:24:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上班第一天
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.35,0:24:18.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不小心看到社長糗事的我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.43,0:24:20.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像坐上了社長的寶座一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.12,0:24:23.05,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(360,320)}第六道菜\N「就任、解任、已經不能忍啦」
