This is not the first time
you are living July 22nd.
You must have repeated the day many times.
In other words, you are a time traveler.
Yes.
I see, but the one who told you my name
was probably not me.
Did you meet my brother?
Next up, we have a report
from Kinokawa City.
Let's hear about delicious
Wakayama treats for the summer.
Please tell us all about that--
KOBA MART
YOMOGIMOCHI
It's time, Ryunosuke.
THIRD LOOP
JULY 24 (TUESDAY)
Very interesting. It could even be
the plot of my next novel.
It's so confusing.
It went right over my head.
This book is proof that you believe me.
Swamp Man is a true story.
The Swamp Man in this story
is exactly like the shadows…
and the protagonist has
the same name as you.
Fourteen years ago, I met a shadow
on this island. It killed my family.
That's the reason why I believe you.
But… That's…
I won't say anything more.
It would reveal who I am.
If I told you and you were copied,
a shadow could learn who I really am.
Shadows go after the family.
Since Hizuru returned to this island,
they'll be after her too.
Fa-Family.
Is that why Ushio, Mio, and I
were targeted? Wait…
What about Alain?
Don't worry, I already took care
of Alain's shadow.
His shadow will
no longer be able to return.
It's just like chickenpox.
You develop an immunity.
If your shadow is killed,
you'll never get shadow sickness again.
So if you kill your own shadow,
you can't be copied again.
Yes. That's why I got immunity.
My shadow won't exist. You can trust me.
But Ms. Nagumo, you have no immunity.
Why did you risk coming back?
I can't tell you that, either. However…
I came to save you, that's for sure.
Although you might not want
to trust me too much.
No, I…
What is your plan?
We have 54 hours until everyone is killed
at the summer festival.
That four-armed shadow…
It seemed to control
all the other shadows.
My sister Mio is in danger.
Will you help me defeat Mio's shadow?
Your notes said Mio's shadow will appear
at Bistro Kofune at 9 p.m. tonight.
Yes.
Fine. But I need to handle
one thing before that.
The Kobayakawa family, right?
You're bound to fail.
What?
I saw Shiori's shadow
on the grounds on the 24th.
You're saying that I will fail
to kill Shiori today.
Yes. So let me come with you.
It is my enemy too.
Even if we fail again, I can find out why.
Okay. However, I will be
the only one who will enter the house.
KOBA MART
What is she doing?
She's been listening to something.
She doesn't have any memories
of being Hizuru.
Roger that. Sis.
The famous Arakawa peaches
grown here in Momoyama,
loved by people all across Japan,
are in season now!
Hi, Hizuru!
Hey, did I catch you at dinner…
I mean, excuse me.
I had some gifts from Tokyo to give you.
Oh! You shouldn't have!
Let her in.
Oh, come in.
Thank you.
This is my husband Tatsuo
and my daughter Shiori.
Hello, make yourself comfortable.
I hope I'm not interrupting, Asako.
Can I open my luggage here?
Of course.
Hizuru, why don't you stay for dinner?
We have so much catching up to do.
I was wondering…
What is it?
Does Ms. Nagumo have a split personality?
No thanks, I won't stay long.
The shadow itself is flat,
so a body blow will not hurt it.
Mama?
It is merely the eyes of the body
that is looking at me.
If they knew I could kill them,
they would be cautious and avoid me.
So it's best to kill them both
at the same time.
Asako!
I only reeled in one.
Split personality? Why do you say that?
She asked if I met her brother.
That has to mean…
Well, you aren't too far off,
but that's not it.
Can she really handle this alone?
We wait here.
Ryunosuke has the power to battle shadows.
Ryunosuke?
Yes. Ryunosuke's a tough one.
Let me be clear.
I don't get your loop or whatever.
But if you go inside,
it might change the reason
to let Shiori's shadow escape.
Ryunosuke is trying to find
the cause of the failure.
Listen up. She trusts you.
You said she's not dying today.
If that was a lie, I'll never forgive you.
Yes.
Ms. Nagumo was certainly strong.
It was Ryunosuke.
Mr. Nezu, can you tell me about Ryunosuke?
I guess it wouldn't take much to find out.
Hizuru had a twin younger brother.
His name was Ryunosuke.
He was found dead
in Mount Takanosu 14 years ago.
I heard Hizuru scream, so I ran over.
It was a hideous sight.
Papa! Mama!
This can't be real… Why? Why kill them?
He was eaten.
Chunks of his body were bitten off.
People thought it was wild dogs.
Hizuru claimed that it was murder.
Along with those bite wounds,
he had strangulation marks.
I missed.
No, I felt a hit.
But no one believed Hizuru.
The body was cremated that same day.
Mr. Nezu, that's like Ushio's…
Yeah, wasn't it similar?
All this could be related.
There are monsters on this island.
I want to kill every single shadow
on this island…
even if it costs me my life.
Can you say the same, Shinpei?
Yes.
You're dangerous. You know how to kill us.
Is that traitor on your side?
I see you could follow
Mama and Papa's movements…
and you move quicker than shadows.
Are you really human?
Copy me and create my shadow,
and then you ask it.
So smug. Fine, I'll do that.
After I kill you.
You old hag! How dare you stab yourself
just to hurt me!
Did I not strike deep enough?
Strange, that first hammer strike
should've been fatal.
Something is different about that shadow.
Sorry, Sis, I hurt your body.
So it went to the third floor.
It's exactly like Sis said.
It's from her.
CHANGE TO PLAN B
Plan B.
Now it's our turn. Here.
Let's see how serious you are about this.
BEDROOM 2 (KIDS' ROOM)
NORTH BALCONY
Third floor, north side window.
DIARY
SHIORI KOBAYAKAWA
It's useless.
After you release the light to copy,
you cannot move for a few seconds.
I guess it takes quite an effort
to scan information on one human.
Do you think I'll waste those few seconds?
The moment you try to copy me,
I'll kill you.
It'll be for sure this time.
No fun.
Bye-bye.
It's Plan B.
The third shot…
Bring it!
Running away? Get over here!
Damn it!
Shinpei!
No… Stop…
You… Did you do it?
Get off me, you scum.
Did you kill Ushio?
Ow!
That's enough. Let it go, Shinpei.
It can't move an inch anymore.
One or two won't do it.
We nail it down in three spots.
Then the shadow gets stuck in place.
In other words, you can capture it.
Capture?
That was your intention from the start?
Yeah.
I didn't know!
Well, I didn't tell you.
I didn't expect you to be helpful.
This is huge that we captured Shiori.
It will change the future.
Once the body is pinned down,
I guess the shadow can't escape.
This is a new discovery, Shinpei.
Thanks to you, we didn't lose it.
If it were just the two of us,
we would have failed.
You've got some guts for a youngin'.
Good job.
What's so funny?
This shadow is different from the others.
I chose Plan B to examine it.
Different?
First, let's get it to answer
Shinpei's question.
Did you kill Ushio Kofune
and create her shadow?
Oh. Big Sis Ushio, huh.
Yes. I killed her.
I strangled her to death.
Killed her… Why? Why kill Ushio?
You kill people and take their places.
What do you want?
It's the end.
It'll be done after this summer.
We're going home.
Our whole family is going home.
What? What are you talking about?
Don't be so afraid.
You misunderstand me, Shinpei.
My human self was killed by a shadow,
but the shadow made a perfect copy
of my body, mind, and memories.
So I am Shiori Kobayakawa.
I was just born again.
Don't lie! You're not Shiori!
You killed Shiori and her family!
I wish you'd become a shadow soon too.
Come with us.
Become my big brother, will you?
Enough. Talking to a shadow
for too long can confuse you.
D-Damn it!
It was a tough one.
How did you kill Asako
and Tatsuo's shadows?
The usual way with one strike
using the hammer.
If we strike a blow to a fair percentage
of the flat shadow, it is fatal.
We don't have enough samples
to prove my sister's theory.
It was saying strange things
about its family going home.
Copies acting like the same humans?
It said it was reborn.
How is a perfect copy different
from the original person?
That was a theme in Swamp Man.
Right, Ryunosuke?
What do you think?
I told him about the split personality.
Is that right? Nice to meet you.
I'm Ryunosuke Minakata.
I was Hizuru Minakata's brother.
So, are you the author of your novels?
Oh, no, it's my sister.
I'm not a good writer.
I come out when she's in an interview,
or when she has to be social.
You've read her books, haven't you?
Well, actually…
He's a nerd. A total Nagumo nerd.
Is that right?
That wasn't in the recorder.
I guess she was embarrassed…
What are you doing?
Don't get the facts messed up.
I am not embarrassed,
and I am not hiding anything.
I just leave out unnecessary information…
Ms. Nagumo, your nose is bleeding!
You okay?
I'm not okay. You have no vocabulary.
Does letting down her hair
bring her back to Hizuru?
Don't let the words and the appearance
of shadows affect you, Shinpei Ajiro.
They might appear as a friend
or a family member, but don't hesitate.
Contemplate about
the sameness of copies and originals
after we're finished with everything.
It was too late for the Kobayakawas.
However, there is still time for you.
Can you really kill Mio's shadow?
We'll wait outside until it's time.
Let's exchange numbers.
Tell me if something unexpected happens.
Act the same as you did before
and assess the situation.
You are an observer.
Yes.
I'm home!
Sorry for being late, Mio…
Welcome home, Shinpei.
N-No way.
What is with this onion?
It's making me cry so much!
I can't see anything!
What? Are you cooking?
Isn't it obvious? I wanted to
stir-fry some onions and chicken.
Oh, be careful!
This is strange.
Mio never cooked in the past loops.
Why?
You didn't look too well in the morning,
so I thought I'd make something for you.
I see. Thanks.
But leave the rest to me.
I don't want to see you cut yourself.
Don't worry. I feel fine.
I'll go wash my face!
Thank goodness, Mio isn't a shadow…
and I can still make curry with this.
She can be so cute.
What am I thinking? Nothing can change.
The way I acted already changed
Mio's behavior tonight.
I'll make curry,
and everything will be the same.
Well, aside from Ms. Nagumo and Mr. Nezu
waiting outside, armed and ready,
that's different…
but besides killing the shadows,
I need to do exactly the same things.
Any changes will affect the others
to change too. It's all connected.
The future I've seen becomes useless.
Hey, Mio. That was a loud rumble.
Are you really that…
hungry?
Yes.
Translated by James Burns