MISSION 57
"IT'S JUST A SNOWMAN."
When a person has extreme social anxiety,
they struggle to communicate with others.
Bear in mind,
they only struggle to form connections.
It doesn't mean they don't want to.
RUSTLE RUSTLE
DEAD
EXCITEMENT
SNOW!
LET'S GO PLAY!
PUSH
SHIVER
HUGE
CRUMBLE
HELP ME
-NAJIMI MADE IT.
-STARTLE
FINISHED!
FROWN
SMILE
Yummy!
Komi! We brought some for you too!
You know, I found a weird rock
the other day…
Oh!
MISSION 58
"IT'S JUST A SNOWBALL FIGHT."
Who wants to have a snowball fight?
Yeah!
So many people came!
The rules are simple!
If a snowball hits you
and breaks, you're dead!
Hit!
If it doesn't break, you're safe!
Safe.
FIELD
The teams will be like this!
HIGH SCHOOL TEAM
NAJIMI, TADANO, AGARI, YAMAI, YADANO
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TEAM
SHIOTA, MICHISATO, SAIKO, OKI, KOMI
Why is Komi on the elementary school team?
It's to keep the numbers even! Ha-ha.
-I feel like there's something more…
-HAVING FUN
We won't lose to some high schoolers!
Yeah!
Huh?
-What's up with her…
-She doesn't speak at all!
-She's scary!
-She's messing with our vibe.
GLOOM
I-I hope she's okay.
We're starting!
BOFF
Oki!
Itsuya Oki. Dead.
Ha-ha! Don't underestimate high schoolers!
Hey lady! You still have that snowball?
TREMBLE
-CAN I REALLY THROW THIS?
-IT MIGHT HURT.
What's she doing?
BOFF
Sacchi!
Chii Saiko. Dead.
They're strong.
-Those two are especially good.
-NAJIMI, YAMAI: STRONG
Everyone else is average.
We have three people left.
We have to cooperate!
Lady, just throw the snowball!
TREMBLE
TOO SCARED SO SHE THREW WEAKLY.
She's useless!
-BOFF
-Micchi!
Micchi! Are you okay? Micchi!
Sho…
It's alright. Don't speak!
Sho… Live…
LAURA MICHISATO
DEAD
-SPLAT
-JIGGLE
TADANO HITOHITO, AGARI HIMIKO
DEAD
A-Alright!
BOFF
SHOTA SHIOTA
DEAD
So we've… lost…
In the end, we couldn't beat the adults.
-H-Hey. Look!
-Hm?
Since when was there only one enemy left?
Just seconds before.
No!
They were aiming at Komi,
so Yamai killed them.
I did it for you, Komi.
I killed Najimi and Yadano.
Okay?
W-Whoa!
The elementary school team won.
ELEMENTARY SCHOOLER RELATIONSHIP CHART
LIKE - MORE THAN FRIENDS - LIKE
MISSION 59
"IT'S JUST THE END OF THE YEAR."
THE KOMI FAMILY HOME
Mother! Hello!
Thank you for another year.
Please keep us in your care
for the year to come.
-Yay!
-POKE POKE
Oh my!
Shuko, you're here!
Ryoko!
-Déjà vu.
-Your hair looks great!
Thanks!
-I haven't seen you since summer holidays!
-Yeah!
My first summer break since I turned 17!
Hey now.
What? Is that Shoko?
You get prettier and prettier
every time I see you.
Déjà vu.
And Shosuke. You're handsomer than ever!
Shosuke!
COUSIN: AKIRA
DASH
BOO
THUD THUD
And then Ms. Aoyama stopped
the potter's wheel…
DIDN'T THINK SHE'D BE SO SURPRISED.
THUD THUD
Wow! But I suppose I would do the same.
Don't fall!
They get along well.
They've started having fun.
The emotional distance
between them has shrunk.
S-Shoko!
Hanafuda!
Let's play Hanafuda!
SUDDEN DESPAIR
Oh. Akira always cries when she's happy.
We'll play Koi-koi.
The simplest rules. Okay?
Shoko, do you know how to play?
SHAKES HEAD
I'll explain.
The ones with a ribbon are slips.
Ten dregs are worth one point.
And one extra point
for each dreg after that…
Oh Grandma, do you want to play too?
I'll play too.
-Alright, Grandma and I will show you how.
-SHOCKED BY GRANDMA.
Shoko, you can watch.
We'll play six rounds.
With Cup Cherry and Cup Moon.
One point is a hundred yen.
Winnings go to your New Year's gift money.
But if you lose,
I'll take it out of your gift money.
I'll let you deal, Akira.
Yeah?
YUIKO VS AKIRA
This is how the Grandma Yuiko vs. Akira
Hanafuda Battle began.
First up, Akira.
She uses the Cherry Dreg to pick up
the Cherry Curtain from the field.
A sensible move.
She drew…
Pine with Red Slip.
There's no Pine in the field.
Yuiko is next. She chooses…
Pampas Moon.
-Her opponent takes a Bright card.
-BRIGHT: VALUABLE, 5 IN TOTAL
But in Akira's hand, there's already…
-The Chrysanthemum Cup card.
-CUP & CHERRY BRIGHT: 5 POINTS
A fearless smile.
But there still isn't
a Chrysanthemum card in the field.
Akira collects the Peony and Butterfly.
The card from the deck,
is Plum and Bush Warbler.
She takes the Plum and Red Slip
AKIRA'S HAND
A good start!
A very good start!
And then…
There! The Chrysanthemum card!
She plays the Chrysanthemum Cup.
She already got a combo!
Cup Cherry for 5 points.
It's enough to call the game.
But Akira chose…
Koi-koi.
…to continue playing!
Akira decided she could still squeeze
more out of her grandmother.
Gambler's intuition!
Here's an explanation of the rules!
After making a combo, the player
can choose to stop or keep going.
Koi-koi!
Koi-koi means, "I can still make combos!
I'll make more money!"
A declaration of intent.
I'll take Paulownia and Phoenix.
-Now I've got Three Brights.
-3 BRIGHTS: 6 POINTS
I'm done.
Defeat! A sudden defeat!
Akira was too confident. She didn't watch
which cards her opponent took.
Typical pride.
I let my guard down. But that's not all.
What's amazing is Grandma's power!
The best hand, Three Brights!
Five hands to go. This'll be interesting.
Akira lost by 34 points.
New years gift money, minus 3,400 yen.
Shoko, do you want to play?
…ko…
Shoko…
Avenge me!
Right.
SHUFFLE SHUFFLE
If you can get even one point,
I'll cancel Akira's losses.
-Shoko!
-ELATED
Her aura says she has no choice.
Now, Komi vs. Grandma Yuiko.
Their Hanafuda Koi-koi competition began.
Komi first.
Just try to collect cards
with fancy pictures.
_No, Shoko. That is a fancy card but…
-It's the Rain Bright!
-3 BRIGHTS - RAIN BRIGHT
It takes away one point from the Brights!
You should have taken the Cherry Curtain!
Sho…
No talking!
Shoko, you got the Four Rain Brights.
Want to call koi-koi?
-Four Brights with Rain? Wow, Shoko!
-FOUR BRIGHTS WITH RAIN: 8 POINTS
But Grandma only needs one more slip
to make a combo!
You should call it!
Will you do it? Koi-koi.
NOD
DOESN'T REALLY GET IT.
No, Shoko! You'll never win that way!
If you lose after calling koi-koi
you get double points taken off!
Shoko!
-Shoko, you got Five Brights.
-5 BRIGHTS: 15 POINTS BEST, POSSIBLE COMBO
Hmph. You win.
S-Shoko!
SHINE
Komi was surrounded by a bright halo.
MISSION 60
"IT'S JUST NEW YEAR'S."
Happy New Year.
Let's go to the shrine.
BORROWED IT FROM GRANDMA
It looks very nice on you.
Look, look!
-My dad bought it for me!
-YAY!
What a wonderful gift.
-I've still got it, haven't I?
-SPARKLE
Mother?
That's convenient.
BOW TWICE
CLAP TWICE
Shoko.
Did your wish from last year come true?
Is that so.
Then, you've got to give thanks.
BOW ONCE
Let's say hello at the shrine office.
G-God has come to Earth!
-Everyone started their year well.
-SHRINE VISITORS
Pardon me.
Oh, Yuiko. Excellent timing!
-One of my staff is out with a cold.
-HEAD PRIEST (63)
We're very busy. What should I do, Yuiko?
Oh.
It'll be a good experience. Go on.
Thank you very much!
Noko, here's our temporary replacement.
Show her how to do it, okay?
Alright!
Okay, come over here.
Basically we add up
the prices of the charms.
Just look at this chart
and take the money.
Are you cold? Use this heater.
I'm used to it, so don't worry.
-It's Komi!
-NOTE: INAKA HAS A SECRET
M-My secret! She knows
I'm a country bumpkin now!
-I-I'll be persecuted!
-PLEASE DON'T THROW POTATOES AT ME
-I can't go to school!
-BUMPKIN! HICK!
If she says, "Inaka?", I'll just say
"Must be my doppelganger."
That's cool! I'll go with that.
HER SOCIAL ANXIETY
PREVENTS HER FROM ASKING
Could it be…
she didn't notice?
What a relief.
As long as she doesn't know.
I'll just stay quiet.
I'll get through this
by not showing my face.
But why is Komi in my little town?
Isn't she a city girl?
-But Komi surely…
-EFFICIENT
I'm sure she can do any job
with speed and efficiency.
Of course. She's Komi after all.
A lucky arrow, a big paper amulet,
safe birth, and traffic safety.
Two big and one small daruma.
Komi?!
-TREMBLING
-I have to help her!
But if I talk to her,
she might figure out my secret!
AMULET PRICE LIST
It's okay.
You can write it down.
Alright?
TOTAL: 6,000 YEN
Oh, okay.
Why did she write it down?
Well done!
Thanks for the help!
Some other girls
are coming in for their shift now.
Thanks.
Work is done.
And I'm done too!
THANK YOU FOR TODAY, INAKA.
S-She did figure it out!
ALSO, HAPPY NEW YEAR.
LET'S HAVE A GREAT YEAR.
And the same to you.
Best wishes for the new year.
BONUS SCENE
-AFTER THE SNOWBALL FIGHT
-High school lady, you're pretty cool!
The silent killer!
A single flower
blooming on the battlefield!
JERK! TWITCH!
Komi had always wanted to do that
"humble scratch" move. (It didn't work.)
She still doesn't say a word.
-So awesome!
-A cool beauty!
I want to be a lady like her
when I grow up!
Me too!
-I don't think you can.
-Heh.
-81 more friends until she reaches 100.
-81 TO GO
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka