この先に　何があるんだろう
在这前方 有着什么呢
いつからか　考えなくなった
不知从何时开始 我停止了思考
考え方
就连如何思考
それすら忘れてしまったのかも
或许也都忘记了
変わらない
一成不变
自分だけの世界が　毎日が　続いていく
独自一人的世界 日复一日地持续着
でも　寂しくはない
可是 我不觉得孤单
どうってことないんだ
没有什么大不了的
2539天 没有收到信息
避难所
I could never find the right way to tell you.
我永远无法找到合适的方式告诉你
Have you noticed I've been gone?
你可曾注意到我已离开？
Cause I left behind the home that you made me.
因为我离开了你为我建造的家
But I will carry it along.
即便如此 我也会独自将其传承下去
It's a long way forward.
前路漫漫
So trust in me.
所以请相信我
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me.
我会给予他们庇护 就像你给我的那样
And I know, I'm not alone.
我知道 我并不是孤单一人
You'll be watching over us.
你会一直守望着我们
Until you're gone.
直到你消逝之时
When I'm older I'll be silent beside you.
当我老去之时 我会默默地回到你身旁
I know words won't be enough.
我知道言辞有所局限
And they won't need to know our names or our faces.
他们不需要知道我们的名字和面容
But they will carry on for us.
但他们会为了我们继续传承下去
It's a long way forward.
前路漫漫
So trust in me.
所以请相信我
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me.
我会给予他们庇护 就像你给我的那样
And I know, I'm not alone.
我知道 我并不是孤单一人
You'll be watching over us.
你会一直守望着我们
Until you're gone.
直到你消逝之时
2578天 没有收到信息
东京现状
“未来号”卫星拍摄的影像
It's a long way forward.
前路漫漫
So trust in me.
所以请相信我
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me.
我会给予他们庇护 就像你给我的那样
And I know, I'm not alone.
我知道 我并不是孤单一人
You'll be watching over us.
你会一直守望着我们
Until…
直到...
思い出が悲しいことだったとしても
即使这些回忆让我悲伤
致凛
来自：爸爸
你出生后 时间就已所剩无几
在妈妈离世之后 我不知对你倾注了多少的爱呢
但是你的微笑让爸爸备受鼓舞呀(^_^)
其实要是能一起走就好了 但没能做到
希望你能忘记一切继续前行 你一定可以做到的
当你感受到孤独时 就会想起这一切吧
我相信你会变得坚强起来 读到这封信
本想和你一起创造更多回忆的 抱歉了
也许你小时候不懂 但如今你一定能理解吧
让我再一次重复那天说过的话
信じて進んでいくんだ
也可以凭着信念 向前迈进
寂しさを知ってしまって
即使知晓了我的孤独
くじけそうになっても
几近绝望
あなたのおかげで　思い出して　強くなれるんだ
但多亏了你 我才回想起一切 并变得坚强
ひとりじゃないって　あなたのおかげで
多亏了你 我才发现自己并不是孤身一人
ありがとう
谢谢
本字幕由 SweetSub & LoliHouse 联合制作 仅供动画爱好者学习交流使用 禁止用于任何盈利或商业用途
翻  译    Shimo  Sena星奏
校  对    boday  tastySugar
时  轴    Sion诗音
压  制    VCB-Studio