The dreams embraced by a single life
are boundless beyond even the stars.
The dreams that we foster over time
are waiting for the moment
when we come upon them.
The words we exchange
make our hearts tremble,
and a chance meeting
could change the future.
People, no matter who they are,
as they pursue their dreams,
have the courage to travel new paths.
As we leave behind a living
testament of our journey,
the Galaxy Railways on which
we travel continue ever on.
Don't get sloppy!
Do you want to get killed!?
Sorry!
There is a flower that blooms
within a person's heart.
A flower, tinged by memories,
and bearing the scent of
an unforgettable someone...
"Yearning"
Of the eleven smugglers,
seven have been taken to the prison car,
and the four wounded ones
have been taken to the medical car.
Mission accomplished.
We're returning to Destiny.
- Roger!
Just a minute...
Are you guys hungry?
W- well... yes, actually...
In that case,
let's have some of those famous train
station box lunches here before we go.
Big One will depart in 30 minutes.
But Captain Yuuki...
Bulge, go buy enough for all of us.
Okay.
I can't let you make any private
calls from Big One, after all.
Captain...
Mm-mm, that's okay.
Never mind me, are you unhurt?
Really? That's great.
Don't worry, really.
As long as you're safe, that's enough.
Happy birthday, Catalina.
Here. Thank you.
I'll give you your present
some other time.
Thank you, Bulge. Just hearing
your voice is present enough.
See you then.
Captain?
I'm glad that you like it.
It's a little drab in here,
so I tried to dress it up.
Oh, yeah... Not bad.
Huh? What's that?
It's a request to take some leave
from the base. Can I get you to sign it?
I see.
That's unusual, huh?
The captain spacing off like that...
That must have reminded him
of a woman from long ago.
You mean, a Modesty woman?
Want to bet on it?
Sure. 10,000 says
it's a woman from long ago.
Hey, now...
Louis, I thought you
just barely took some leave.
Louis-san has taken leave a total of
three times. However, in a woman's case...
Say no more. So, what kind of trouble
are you going to make on your leave?
I'm not going to make any trouble.
I'm just doing some shopping,
reading, and cleaning my room.
I'd also like to watch my dramas and
the sports broadcasts that I've recorded.
I'd also like to go learn to dance.
That would take a year to do,
if it were me.
But why don't any of you take any leave?
Even if I did,
there's nothing that I would do.
Besides, once you get to our ranks,
it just doesn't feel right
to take any leave.
Especially when you have a captain
who has only taken a single day's leave
ever since he joined up.
That's not good for you.
This is a right allowed for
by the rules that you deserve to take.
Interstellar Express No. 134
appears to be stalled
in the Melbiunous Zone of
the 6th Ulysses Star System.
Sirius Platoon, please hurry
to their assistance at once.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
Thank you, always.
So, about what we discussed,
we'll be counting on you.
Right. I'll think up a menu.
What you already have will be fine.
But it's such a special occasion.
That's pretty fast
for a commuter train.
Yeah, and I don't
recognize the whistle, either.
This is Yuuki.
I've finished delivering 45 passengers
to the Corneila Royal Hotel.
This is Bruce. I've finished my
third run to the Hotel Garden Palace.
90 passengers delivered.
Copy. Once the
replacement train arrives,
you are to take care of seeing off
the passengers you just delivered.
Copy...
Don't sound so tortured, guys.
This is part of the job.
Captain?
It couldn't have been.
It must be that flower.
Is something the matter, Captain?
Oh, sorry, it's nothing.
It doesn't look like anyone's here.
There's a shop that's open
across the way.
No!
Why not?
Because this shop is so charming.
It's okay. It says
"Be back soon" right there.
And how soon is soon?
Look, I'm going.
Welcome!
Good afternoon!
H- hi there...
I'm sorry about that.
I'll open up right now.
You see? Soon, wasn't it?
For crying out loud,
the captain sure is tough on us.
You're so right. That's why he
can't hold onto any girlfriends.
This is the kind of place
where you'd want a drink.
Hey...
The captain?
Huh? Captan Yuuki!
Bulge, what's the matter?
What's the matter? Captain, I had
no idea you were that kind of person!
And here, in such a conspicuous place!
Captain, I've misjudged you.
The Procyon rail distortion accident?
You mean the worst mishap
in Galaxy Railways' history?
That's right.
This girl is the lone
survivor of that accident.
Every once in a while,
she comes to see me like this.
Today, I came to tell him
that I graduated.
Is that right? I'm sorry for
my indecorous misunderstanding.
Please don't worry about it.
I don't mind.
I saw the news reports
about that accident.
That must have been
when you were still...
I was ten at the time.
Is that so?
And that little girl grew up
to be such a pretty...
So even you are capable of complimenting
a girl to her face, eh Bulge?
W- well, I... I was just...
No, no, coming from you,
it was well done.
Come on, please don't
make fun of me, Captain!
As you can see, he may
be a social basket case,
but as a platoon member,
he's very capable.
He's conscientious in his work,
so ignoring orders and charging
headlong into a situation...
or openly challenging someone of
a senior rank, like his captain...
...is something he would never do, is it?
C- Captain...
Whoops, that's right.
I just remembered, I have an important
matter to take care of at Headquarters.
Forgive me, but I have to head back.
Congratulations on graduating.
Thank you very much.
C- Captain...
Bulge-san, why did you
decide to join the SDF?
Yeah...
Ever since I was a child, I had
been somewhat awestruck by it,
but it's probably because of something
that happened this one time
that I seriously set my heart on joining.
What one time?
The accident you were involved in.
Here there was this terrible scene, where
no one was expected to have survived,
and an SDF platoon member
rescued this little girl,
even while suffering
injuries to himself.
The image of it all just shook me up.
Is that right?
Actually, it was only recently that
I found out that it was Captain Yuuki.
I lost my parents and brother that day.
But that accident did serve
to steer me toward my life's work.
Your life's work?
Is it some kind of profession
in the medical field?
Does that mean you've
just graduated from?
No, that's not it.
I was unable to recover
from the shock of the accident,
and had become anorexic.
And then Yuuki-san... I mean,
Captain Yuuki-san said this to me:
Right now, what do you think your
Mama and Papa up in Heaven want most?
It's for you to eat the
food that's in front of you.
At first, no matter what I ate,
it was as if I was chewing on sand.
But little by little, I began
to consider it as tasty.
And then, I started to think,
my father, mother, brother,
and all the other people
who died in that accident
probably would have liked to go on living,
to eat many other delicious things.
So I became a chef. Strange, isn't it?
No, it isn't strange at all.
And today, you came to tell
that to the captain?
Would you like me to tell him?
That's okay.
Um...
Yes?
I- if it's okay with you...
could I ask you... to see me again?
Delicious!
I'm so happy!
Say, can I have one of those?
Ah, hey! That's bad manners.
Say, Yuuki-kun, how come
you're always so uptight?
I- I'm not uptight!
This isn't the first time
you've ever had dinner with a girl
in a place like this, is it?
Ahem...
Are you, by any chance,
Yuuki Wataru-san's?
Yes, I am his son.
I knew it.
Did you know my father?
Is that right?
You're gallantly following in
your father's footsteps, aren't you?
Oh, no, I'm still not even a captain.
Oh, boy! Listen to you, Yuuki!
Um, who is the captain now?
Here.
Thank you for your service.
This is my treat.
Thanks.
Is that so?
Schwanheld Bulge...
I'm so glad you're safe.
But there's no guarantee
you'll be safe next time.
It will be okay.
Besides, not all of my duties
come with danger attached to them.
Forgive me. I know that, but still...
Catalina...
Say, there's this shop that
I've wanted to take you to.
Then let's go right now.
I'm so happy.
Don't pick up!
No, we might be scrambling.
And here we are, finally together...
I'm sorry.
Thanks for the drink.
Say, Honey, Catalina-chan says she needs
to discuss the menu she's catering for us.
She's a meticulous girl, isn't she?
There's something I want to give you.
I'm on Tabito now. I'm on my way there.
The train on Track 1 bound for
Kleznard is about to arrive.
Passengers boarding are asked to
please wait behind the white line.
Catalina...
Is your family doing well?
Yeah. I'm shocked at how much
the children are growing.
But you only had half a day. You have
to feel sorry doing this to them.
Oh, they'll understand someday.
What about you? If this
hadn't come up, you'd be...
It can't be helped.
But I think she'll understand.
It's a luckless job.
Yes it is.
Looks like I win the bet.
I won the bet. I'm the one who
said it was a woman from his past.
Nope, I win.
How come?
Because she's not a woman
from his past.
Heh, you bastard.
Dad won't ever be!
I've got a one-day pass. No matter what
may happen in this universe,
I will make sure I see you.
I know that you are
coming to say goodbye.
I, too, understand
that you never know
when you might meet with the
same fate that Captain Yuuki did.
I know that you do not want me
to go through the same sorrow
that I did in my youth
when I lost my family,
and that this is surely your
way of showing kindness to me.
I proposed to her.
With me, she will be able
to realize her modest dream.
I can always be at her side,
to nestle with.
Her dream...
May you have every happiness.
Welcome.
She sure was pretty, huh?
A Modesty woman.
Give it up, Yuuki-kun.
She's waiting for someone else.
Someone who?
I don't know, but there's
someone out there in the universe
that she used to love a lot,
that's for sure.
How would you know that, Louis?
I can tell.
So, when we get back, I'm on leave.
Captain, please see to it that you
take some leave sometime, too.
Otherwise,
I understand it makes it more difficult
for David and Bruce to take any.
- Hey...
- That goes for me, too.
Don't worry about taking time off.
It's a right that you deserve.
- R- right.
Maybe I should take some leave...
The flower that grows in a
person's heart never withers.
That single flower will bloom forever,
nourished by thousands
of touching memories.
How many nights have
I spent alone since then?
Constantly having dreams of the hope
that you are, as I lightly sleep.
The smiles and tears that
you gave to me and me alone
come to mind every time
I get disheartened,
and I set forth again toward the morrow.
The joyful light of
the galaxy beckons me
to that beloved person within my heart.
No matter how far apart we are,
my memories will never fade.
My heart wishes always
to be at your side.
I came across this elderly woman
on Planet Arbent.
H- hold on! I'm not Makoto, I tell you!
Next time on Tales of the
Galaxy Railways, Episode 12: "Twilight"
We're going to encounter
something at the next station.