The dreams embraced by a single life
are boundless beyond even the stars.
The dreams that we foster over time
are waiting for the moment
when we come upon them.
The words we exchange
make our hearts tremble,
and a chance meeting
could change the future.
People, no matter who they are,
as they pursue their dreams,
have the courage to travel new paths.
As we leave behind a living
testament of our journey,
the Galaxy Railways on which
we travel continue ever on.
What is this?
Use it.
A gun that doesn't work is
worse than a security blanket.
Understood. I will carry it.
But I will not use it.
The time when you will have to use it
will come, in order for you to survive.
That is the law of the universe.
The stations that the Galaxy Railways
stop at are not only located on planets.
There are railway junctions that
float out in the middle of the cosmos.
People switch trains here, and decide
which paths they will take to continue on.
Thus they become turning points.
A prison train is arriving
at the special trains platform.
"Turning Point"
A party?
That's right.
A Sirius Platoon mixer party.
--Cool!
--Sounds like fun.
I recently won a somewhat
considerable bet.
Some high-class wine will
be arriving this weekend,
and I'll be furnishing that.
Thank you so much!
As for me...
You're coming, right? Then it's settled.
Hey...
Captain Bulge,
you'll be coming too, right?
The captain can't very well miss this.
Right, right.
I suppose not.
This will be nice for a change. I may
not be able to cover the whole thing,
but I'll pick up the tab.
Are you sure?
Captain, that's what I like about you!
Aw, and here I was going
to drink on the sly...
That means the funding will be okay.
I'll add some caviar and
mozzarella cheese to snack on.
Yuki, you'll be coming too,
of course, right? ...Huh?
She said she was going to the medical car.
I guess she's standing
us up again this time.
Yuki has never been one to
show up for off-duty gatherings.
I'm starting to wonder if
Yuki-chan dislikes all of us.
Hey, now, don't take that too seriously.
Oh, yeah, sure...
Find an escape pod.
Got it!
Four prisoners appear to have escaped
from the prison train
stopped at Junction Alpha 32.
Report on the current situation.
Currently, they are inside the junction,
fleeing toward Passageway A25.
Emergency alert status.
Lock down Junction Alpha 32 at once.
Roger.
Yes, come in.
Yuuki-san, are you not feeling well?
Uh, that's not why I'm here.
I was just...
Is it about work? Or maybe
your personal relationships?
Please do not worry,
I will keep your secrets.
You came for counseling, didn't you?
Are there currently any SDF trains
en route to that area?
Big One is on her way home
from Ariadne Junction.
Please, do not laugh.
Since there is nothing wrong
with your physical condition,
I thought that surely...
I'm sorry. It's just that there
was something I was concerned about.
All of that party talk earlier...
Ah. Please be sure to enjoy yourself.
Um, is it somehow uncomfortable
for you to be around us?
No.
Well then, come! You've never
been to a party before, right?
It will be fun, having
all of your friends around.
I am of the understanding
that "friend" is a word
used to describe relationships
that humans have with each other.
I am just a medical sexaroid,
so it does not apply to me.
Well, that's just--
What is that terrible smell?
Acetic acid, I think...
This is awful.
Is the smell coming from this guy?
No doubt about it.
Please do not touch his blood.
Antilian blood has a unique composition,
and when it comes in contact with
the air, it starts to oxidize.
It happens more rapidly
the longer it is exposed,
and by and by, it becomes a strong acid.
I've applied a neutralizer.
We'll be okay now.
Nice work.
I'm going to go over our strategy now.
There are four prisoners who have escaped.
We believe that one of them has
stolen an SDF member's gun
and is carrying it with them.
Two of the prisoners are co-conspirators.
The other two acted on their own.
Since they are not acquaintances,
we believe that they have split up
and are escaping in
three different directions.
What's the matter, Liza?
I- I'm all right.
We don't have time to dawdle around.
Hurry up!
I know.
All of them are criminals who are
in prison for committing murder.
There's no telling what they will do.
Acting alone would be dangerous.
We'll search for them in teams of two.
Yuki, this time, you'll have
to join us in the search.
Acknowledged.
David and Louis, Manabu and Yuki,
me and Bruce is how we'll conduct this.
That is all.
--Acknowledged!
You might have to use your gun
on this case. Be ready for that.
Of course, I mean the gun that works.
Good luck to you.
He went through there?
Probably.
Here we go...
This is Yuuki.
There's nothing unusual in Block A.25.
Moving to Block B.18.
Copy that. There's no telling where
the enemy will be coming from.
Don't let your guard down.
Roger.
We've found one! Let's go!
We've come across one of them.
He's fleeing through the
industrial corridor towards Block F.9.
We're in pursuit.
Halt!
We can't catch up to him!
That's all right.
No matter how strong your legs may be,
I doubt you can get down that way.
Get your hands up!
We've got one of them captured.
Copy.
In the dark, I'm home free!
The dark may be your specialty,
but you can't make a clean escape
if you don't know your way!
We've captured another one.
There's two of them left, huh?
Yuuki-san!
Those are oxidized skin cells.
There's some over here, too.
The trail of blood continues...
It looks like the criminals are fleeing
after having had Antilian blood
spilled on them.
If we don't hurry,
it will be too late for them.
All right, let's hurry.
Liza! Get up! We're getting out of here!
Are you okay?
The trail of blood has stopped.
Watch out! This way!
They could be right nearby.
They've got a gun.
Looks like they arrested
the bleeding and got away.
But they won't stop the hemorrhaging.
They'll be leaving another
trail of blood before long.
They're trying to conceal the trail
of blood in this darkness, are they?
There isn't any time.
We have to find them quickly.
Stop! They could be hiding in the dark.
Damn! There they are.
It's no use trying to escape! Don't add
anything else to your list of crimes!
Even if we do nothing,
they'll still send us to Alcarz!
No matter what we do now, it doesn't
get any more serious than that!
You'll be surrounded in mere moments!
There's no way you can escape!
Let's go!
We found the two of them, and made contact.
They're in Block C.48.
We'll head there immediately.
All right!
At this rate, her whole body
will be eaten away.
If I don't tend to her soon,
her life will be in danger.
Listen to me! If you keep this up,
she's going to die!
Die...?
Throw down your weapon and surrender!
There's still time!
You expect us to fall for that trick?
Believe me! She's come in
contact with Antilian blood!
This is ridiculous!
You get it, right? Now, hurry
and lay down your weapon!
There's no time to spare!
Throw down your gun to save her!
All right, we're coming
over there now to treat her.
Damn it, I missed!
Liza, we're getting out of here, now.
Get up.
Leo, help me...
There's no time left. I'm going alone.
Yuki! You can't! It's too dangerous for
you to go over to the criminals alone!
I will be all right.
Even if they attack me,
I will not feel pain.
If I am destroyed, you will be provided
with a replacement sexaroid.
I won't make any trouble for the platoon.
You dimwit! What do you
take yourself for!?
I am the medical sexaroid
assigned to the Sirius Platoon.
No! You're our friend!
I'm telling you,
I can't just watch a friend of mine
walk into danger like this!
Friend...? I am a medical sexaroid.
I was built to help people.
When I see someone in pain
before my eyes,
I cannot just stand by and watch.
Please, let me go treat her.
Help me... I don't want to die...
There's a medical expert on her way over!
That's all right, isn't it? Don't shoot!
Very well. Send the woman over alone.
It's okay now. I will treat you at once.
Stand up nice and slow.
I'm going to treat her first.
I'll give you plenty of time later.
Get up!
Yuki! Let Yuki go!
Don't move!
Lose the gun, and get
an escape pod ready!
Don't do anything foolish!
Like I said, it can't
get any worse for us!
If you don't treat her right away,
she's going to die!
Are you going to drop it or not!?
Yuuki-san!
The other one, too.
Please! I don't want to die!
Leo, let that woman go!
Hurry! She has to tend to me!
Help me, Leo!
Please, Leo...!
How could you do that!?
She would have died anyway
if I'd left her alone.
It's better for her that
I put her down easy, right?
She would have lived
if she had been treated!
"If" is right.
You... planned this from the start...!
And what if I did?
W- why, you...!
Now, get rid of the gun and
get your hands up! Or else...
You mustn't, Yuuki-san!
Do not concern yourself about me!
Please, carry out your duty!
Yuuki-san!
Would you hurry it up!?
Yuuki-san! Why...?
All right... now then, you're next!
Die!
Why, you...!
Yuki!
Yuuki-kun!
Are you all right!?
Yuki!
Are you okay, Yuki?
David, lend me a hand here!
Stay with us!
Can you get up?
Yes...
Any regrets?
No.
Thank you very much.
Let's go, Yuuki.
Right!
Once again, you've carved out
your own destiny... for yourself.
Hey, you nervous about something?
Thank you very much.
You're not worried that this is
going to be a stag party, are you?
Sorry I'm late.
You're looking absolutely adorable today!
Eh? I guess clothes
really do make the man.
Geez, how rude!
And yet, even as you're saying so,
you're feasting your eyes on Louis-chan!
N- not at all...!
I'm sorry I'm late,
but I had to file a report.
I'm resuming my duties as of today.
I hope you'll accept my regards.
All right! That makes
tonight's party a mixer,
as well as a celebration
of Yuki's recovery!
When we hold on to stubborn beliefs,
it sometimes creates
barriers for ourselves.
However, once we come in contact
with what lies on the other side of
those barriers, that's when we realize...
The barriers were only
there within ourselves.
Come on in!
How many nights have I
spent alone since then?
Constantly having dreams of the hope
that you are, as I lightly sleep.
The smiles and tears that
you gave to me and me alone
come to mind every time
I get disheartened,
and I set forth again toward the morrow.
The joyful light of the galaxy beckons me
to that beloved person within my heart.
No matter how far apart we are,
my memories will never fade.
My heart wishes always
to be at your side.
"Next Episode Preview"
The Modesty flowers sway
on the planet Cornelia.
Is that you, Catarina?
Next time on Tales of the
Galaxy Railways, Episode 11:
"Yearning"
We're going to encounter
something at the next station.