The universe,
stretching out without bound...
It is a an epic poem
of miracles and eternity,
woven by the chains of life.
Each of the countless lives that fill
the galaxy are not of themselves eternal.
For all living things, life is
something that you only get one of.
It's how you have lived, and who
you have passed your dreams down to.
Jose... Silver... Schneider...
Captain Murase...
Guys, we managed to protect it! We...
Yuuki-san...
Manabu, we protected Destiny,
and the Galaxy Railways.
I've identified giant spatial distortions
1000 spacekilos behind the combat zone!
They're dimension holes!
What!?
You... Why are you all?
People inherit the
irreplaceable hopes of others,
as they risk their
own irreplaceable lives.
"Far-Reaching Hope"
New craft confirmed.
Enemy ships numbering around 200.
What!?
Just a moment!
What is it!?
There's a forced signal coming in
on all communications circuits!
My name is Foresis.
I will say this once. Renounce your
control over Planet Destiny,
and surrender your
home station to us at once.
I will not say it again.
This is your final notice.
Captain!
Listen up.
You've all performed well up to now.
I'm proud of you.
David...
Bruce...
Yuki...
Louis...
Yuuki Manabu...
Captain...
Captain, I am not leaving Big One.
Captain,
don't keep us at a distance.
If you do this,
we won't be able to face
the folks of Vega Platoon.
Captain...
Understood.
Here.
Thanks.
Everyone listen to me.
We are the Space Defense Force.
There is no way we can hand over
the Galaxy Railways to the invaders.
We, along with Big One,
are going to overcome this crisis
with all of our strength,
and protect the Galaxy Railways.
Entrust me with your lives.
That is all.
Magnetic barrier output normal.
Boiler pressure normal.
Foresis-sama, sure enough, they
have analyzed the Cosmo Matrix.
Please cease your attack!
At this rate, we are going to
suffer serious casualties as well!
Foresis-sama!
Be silent, Treele.
B- but...
Why do you defy me?
I am disappointed in you
and your sister, you worms!
I do not need you to think.
- Take her to mental reconstruction.
- Yes!
Crush the piece of lint.
The giant battleship
has increased speed.
Drawing to within 800 spacekilos.
Captain, let's withdraw.
What?
Against something that huge, I don't
think random fire is going to work.
Let's buy some time, find its
weak point, and then attack.
We won't destroy it,
but we will stop it in its tracks,
and then negotiate again.
Manabu...
Captain...
you think so? I guess
that is the only way, huh?
Yuki, begin searching.
Right!
Roger! Big One changing course!
This is the core...
Big One!
Captain... David... Yuki... Yuuki-kun...
Big One has altered course.
you saved us, Manabu.
Akatsuki-san...
As it happens, we've got
kind of a problem here...
The makeshift bypass device got
blown out in that last all-out attack.
Then we can't fire right now.
We'll make sure it's fixed... in time...
Akatsuki-san!
Chief!
I don't have enough capacity
to analyze the data.
The search subject is too large.
Akatsuki-san!
I'm all right. Don't worry.
Old-timer...
Akatsuki-san, instructions, please!
Such an eyesore.
Prepare to attack!
Utilize all systems to search for
the giant battleship's weak point.
Hurry and come up
with a firing solution!
Julia!
- Captain Julia!
Looks like we're on.
Connect the blue cable directly.
Don't forget the pulse cycle
for the encoder.
Right!
Avoid damage to the
main guns at any cost!
Roger!
Identified the giant battleship's main
power source, and five backup systems.
Three large-scale propulsion devices,
and two auxiliary systems.
Projecting areas believed
to be crew quarter areas,
which will not be targets of our attack.
The red blinking areas
are the energy control systems.
If we can target these effectively,
we can halt their attack without
actually destroying the whole battleship.
Calculate the optimum attack points
and firing sequence.
Roger.
Transmit the data to Big One
as soon as possible!
Do you know the location
of their command center?
We're unable to search them.
They've discovered us!
It looks like they've raised a shield.
That was pretty skillful.
Akatsuki-san...
Unfortunately, this is
the best that we can do.
How long can we fire?
One shot.
Bring Big One around.
Roger.
The small enemy craft
is coming toward us.
Miserable flea.
Where do we aim our one shot?
We'll have to aim for their
heart at point-blank range.
Either wallop them, or be invaded, huh?
Receiving position of the power core,
and firing trajectory data!
It's coming from the giant battleship!
That voice...
Big One, can you hear me?
This is Louis Fort Drake.
- Louis!
- Image coming up.
Louis!
I'll explain later.
Please accept this data.
This is the command center
of the giant battleship.
I believe the commander
will be in there.
That's all I can do on my own.
Can you come aboard,
and attempt direct negotiations?
Louis, well done.
I was trained how to do
searches in Spica Platoon.
Are you safe there?
Change of strategy!
- Roger!
Um, how is Yuuki-kun?
Yuki, I've carried Akatsuki-san
to the medical car. See to him.
Right.
Manabu!
Yuuki-kun...
Louis!
Yuuki-kun!
Louis, how?
Yuuki-kun, I'm alive.
Louis! Behind you!
Louis!
Louis-san!
Louis!!
Enemy fighters approaching!
We're going to commence the final defensive
action of the Galaxy Railways now.
Ready the Space Eagles for launch!
Prepare to intercept!
- Roger!
Yuuki-kun...
Louis... why?
Treele!
Treele...
Why didn't you escape?
I want to put a stop to this fight.
That's not possible.
Why not?
Like I told you, we can't go back now.
Why not? Why not?
Why does everyone have to
spill their blood like this!?
so many of your comrades have died!
Even Leafle!
There's no way your heart
can't be aching, Treele!
After all, you are
Leafle's older sister!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Manabu, don't be late.
- Copy!
- All fighters, launch!
Big One is now heading
toward the large battleship.
Commander, Spica Platoon,
thank you for the information.
Big One...
Matrix energy at maximum.
Commence intercept!
Pressurize cylinder RPMs to maximum!
Compression injector reading 2800!
Pressure valves half-open!
Energy output at maximum!
Rotate main guns!
Target the enemy ship! Fire!
You miserable insects!
Big One is unarmed! Don't let
them get a single shot on us!
Copy!
So they've come, have they?
David!
I'm all right!
I can still fly.
You two go on ahead!
But...
That's an order!
Captain!
I will watch over Big One.
David, Manabu, get going!
Is everyone... okay?
We are all right. Everyone is safe.
Is that so?
I sure botched that one up.
David...
I'm fine. Hurry and get going.
But...
Let me take care of this.
I promise, I'll catch up.
Don't make that face. Trust me.
Want to bet on it?
Sure. Get going!
Manabu...
I am your absolute ruler.
Eliminate those useless beings!
Prepare to return fire!
There are more and more
of them gathering.
Yuuki-kun!
Louis!
Yuuki-kun...
You're Yuuki?
Who is this?
Treele. She's Leafle's sister.
She saved me.
Thank you.
Why?
You guys are different from the evil
people we were told that you were.
We are the same as you.
We have souls, too.
Souls?
Leafle...
Where is Manabu... and everyone else?
What is going on!?
That last attack hit the power reactor...
Listen to what I have to say, Foresis!
This is no place for
worms like you to enter.
Why are you after the Galaxy Railways!?
Do not come any closer!
Why!?
Yuuki-kun!
Foresis-sama, please stop!
These people are...!
Silence!
Treele!
The Galaxy Railways that you have
extended throughout the universe...
...and the space tracks that you have
endlessly laid out, like nerve fibers...
they are beginning to create
interference throughout our universe.
The Galaxy... Railways are...
Yuuki-kun!
The Galaxy Railways must be eliminated!
That is the only way
by which our Master says the balance
of the universe can be preserved!
No!!
Manabu...
Manabu... Manabu!
Bruce...
You'll be okay, Manabu.
Like I said, I won't
let anyone take you away.
Yuuki-kun!
Yuuki-kun...
I'm all right... Louis...
We've all been watching over it...
together...
Father... Big Brother Mamoru...
Bruce... my friends...
we've all been watching over it...
If there is another universe,
then the Galaxy Railways will go on,
forever connecting
people's hearts and hopes...
It is the infinite bond that ties...
all the lives in the universe together!
Yuuki-kun!
The Guardian of Fate, our Master,
is the one who presides over all things.
I am the Envoy of Fate!
You are not...
You are not!
Fate is something you should
be able to change by yourself.
Fate is something you
carve out for yourself!
Enough!
Yuuki-kun!
Manabu!
Why, you... Treele!
Foresis-sama...
Treele...
I'm glad I did it.
Go on, Yuuki, Louis.
Go where the others are.
Thank you.
Come with us.
No. I am going with my comrades.
We're going back to Alfort's universe
to inform everyone.
Let's meet again, for sure.
I promise.
Yuuki-kun!
Go on, Louis!
N- no way!
You'll be killed too, at this rate...
you at least have to live!
No! Absolutely not!
Louis!
I don't want a future without you in it!
Thanks.
Looks like I win the bet.
Let's go. All of us.
- Roger.
Yuki!
Everyone!
Over here!
Big One... Everybody...
Shutaro, what's the matter?
You've grown up, Manabu.
Father...
Big Brother!
Big Brother, why are you crying?
I saw them... the people
I've wanted to see again.
Big Brother, are you SDF!?
Yeah.
When I grow up,
I want to ride on Big One!
Here!
It's yours!
Big Brother, thanks!
The Galaxy Railways.
It is the fascination of young boys.
They are the trains that run
with the boundless hopes and dreams
of the young people...
... that set out in search of the endless
possibilities of this vast universe.
When you are feeling dejected,
if you look up into the skies,
you are sure to see it.
Big One, move out!
The light of the Galaxy Railways,
as it travels to faraway places,
carrying on the eternal life and undying
hopes of those who have gone before,
carries with it the multitude
of emotions of the youth
that are each making their own journeys.