The dreams embraced by a single life
are boundless beyond even the stars.
The dreams that we foster over time
are waiting for the moment
when we come upon them.
The words we exchange
make our hearts tremble,
and a chance meeting
could change the future.
People, no matter who they are,
as they pursue their dreams,
have the courage to travel new paths.
As we leave behind a living
testament of our journey,
the Galaxy Railways on which
we travel continue ever on.
That was pathetic! Are you through?
No.
Those of you who can't put up with
this level of field drill, go home now!
This is not the SDF! This is
the Space Panzer Grenadiers... SPG!
Restart the drill!
- Roger!
Mankind continually runs
down this road called life.
Occasionally, a person has to
choose which road they should take.
"Choices"
Undergo training?
You mean... me?
Yeah.
It's so the units can
understand each other better,
and strengthen their relations.
That's what the company line is, anyhow.
The real purpose is to retrain
new recruits. Brace yourself.
Sure...
Schnader, from my unit, and Ai
from Spica Platoon are also being sent,
so you can all go through
the wringer together...
...with the most elite force
in the universe,
the Space Panzer Grenadiers.
The SPG...
The outfit my brother was in, huh?
Now then...
There's one more important matter
I called you here to discuss.
Important matter?
Yuuki-kun is being poached?
Are you serious?
The information is reliable.
This is still just between us,
but if they acknowledge him
during this upcoming training,
they say he'll be bumped up to the SPG.
Right now, Yuuki is probably getting
word of this from Captain Murase.
From Captain Murase?
Come to think of it,
Captain Johansson of the SPG
was one of Captain Murase's
upperclassmen in training school.
It sounds like they're serious.
They say that Yuuki-san has drawn
the SPG's attention for some time, now.
Isn't that amazing? To join
the SPG because they want you?
Yuuki-kun isn't leaving!
I- I mean, isn't strange, seeing as
how my grades were higher than his?
There's no way our reckless, stubborn,
obtuse Yuuki-kun could join the SPG!
Am I right?
That's up to him to decide.
He's the one who can make
the decisions about his own life.
Not us.
Captain...
Yeah, I heard from Murase
that they're talking about that.
There's no rush. You can always give them
your answer during the training.
This is a big deal for you. For us, too.
Captain...
But I want you to keep this in mind...
The desire to protect the peace
and security of others will be the same,
no matter where you are.
I'm sure Captain Yuuki must
have said the same thing.
Father...
All right!
Damn it!
Enemy craft approaching
from the left at 8 o'clock.
Escape track is as indicated.
Enemy craft also approaching
from the right!
There are four of them... no, six!
Please hold on,
our escape track will be...
There are even more enemy craft now!
We can't go there!
Stay away!
Damn...
Were you planning to
catch up to it on foot?
What are you doing?
It's time you were in bed.
Sleeping is also part of
your duties. Remember that.
R- right!
Um...
What is it?
I heard from Captain Murase
about the SPG and me... and...
Is it because I am
the son of Yuuki Wataru,
and the brother of Yuuki Mamoru?
You've even got the exact
same determination that he had.
He also gritted his teeth
and endured through my training.
Someone with as much nerve as he had...
I'd never seen anyone
like Yuuki Mamoru before.
Brother...
I still think about him now, sometimes.
What if he were still alive?
Why did you join the SDF? Was it
just out of the awe of it all?
That's what it was at first.
But now, it's different.
I want to protect everyone's happiness.
That's all.
Wanting to maintain people's security,
and defend peace will be the same,
no matter where you are.
Whether you're in the SDF, or in the SPG.
What the SPG needs right now
is the strength of youth.
The ardent zeal of the young.
Like Yuuki Mamoru had...
and like you have.
We're waiting for you, Yuuki Manabu.
For crying out loud...
this platoon sure is rough on us, huh?
I can't even get one date in like this.
You have to find someone first.
Then you can complain about it.
Listen, one trip into the city, and I...
Yeah, I know, I know.
Hi, hi! Such hard workers.
Yo, Old Lady Kinuko! I'll take my usual.
You bet.
Thank you.
And, for you,
this, right?
It's so sweet! Too sweet!
This is just the thing after work.
Huh, Manabu?
Oh, yeah...
All we've lost is Manabu-chan,
and yet it seems so empty...
Okay then, let's bet on
whether he comes back or not.
I'll bet 500 ables that he comes back.
Then, so will I.
Ah, you know it, huh, Old Lady Kinuko?
Bruce, which way are you betting?
In that case, I'll bet
that he joins the SPG.
It's okay. I'm sure he will come back.
Yuuki-san is a member of
Sirius Platoon. He is our friend.
No.
If going over to the SPG is
what is best for Yuuki-kun,
then we can't say that sort of thing
and make him second-guess.
We have to send him off with a smile.
Louis-san...
I tell you, practical training
in a magnetic storm like this...
the SPG are really sticking it to us.
Once this is over, our training is done.
Let's do our best, Yuuki-san.
Yeah. Sure.
This is the lifeboat.
We have arrived on No. 650.
We're now going to rescue
the passengers and lead them out.
666, copy.
After speedily rescuing the passengers,
please restart No. 650's engine,
and get out of the magnetic storm.
Please stay calm, and keep
moving without panicking.
Quickly.
Please follow our instructions.
Wanting to maintain people's security,
and defend peace will be the same,
no matter where you are.
Whether you're in the SDF, or in the SPG.
I'll worry about it after the drill.
Please hurry!
Please move quickly!
Come, this way! Quickly!
Everything will be all right!
These guys are pretty good, huh?
That's the last of the passengers.
Roger. I'll get the
dinghy ready to launch.
All we have to do now
is restart the engine.
Yeah. I'll go do that.
Be careful.
Detecting an anomaly
in the magnetic storm!
The energy is climbing at a sharp rate!
Damn it!
Are you okay!?
Yuuki-san is still aboard No. 650!
Yuuki!
Crewman Yuuki, come in! Crewman Yuuki!
It's no use!
Communication lines are down!
Our sensors are all blacked out!
We can't ascertain the status of No. 650!
666 is going to move in now
to rescue No. 650.
What's going on?
Main engine has been damaged!
Output has dropped by 30%!
Switch to the auxiliary engine.
No. 650 is lost!
We've lost sight of her!
Yuuki...
Widen the search area to G Area!
Don't overlook any readings,
no matter how small!
- Roger!
Do your best, whatever the situation!
That is our duty!
What happened here?
Adrift in the storm?
This is Yuuki. 666, please come in!
666, please come in!
What should I do? What should I?
It's like I always tell you.
Keep calm. Then you'll be
able to use correct judgment.
The song of the engine.
The engine is still running!
Hang in there, Yuuki-san.
Let's bet on it, Manabu.
500 ables says it will turn out fine.
How about it? Are you in?
All right...
Is this hopeless?
Steady on, Yuuki-kun.
Okay then...
Six hours have passed since the accident.
We still cannot be sure
of No. 650's location.
Yuuki-san...
You've got to be kidding me!
He's definitely alive!
He's Yuuki Manabu, of the SDF!
It couldn't be!
Is that?
Yes!
Mission... accomplished.
Yuuki did great! He got out of
that situation all by himself!
I hate to admit it, but he's
a shoe-in for the SPG now!
Easy...
What?
You win the bet, Bruce.
Yeah.
Yuuki-san...
Everyone, smile! Smile!
We have to send him off with a smile.
For crying out loud,
what is he thinking?
He?
Yuuki. Yuuki Manabu.
He turned down joining the SPG!
Would you tell me what your reasons are?
I still want to learn
some more with Sirius Platoon.
Besides...
Besides?
My desire to maintain people's security,
and defend peace will be the same,
no matter where I am.
Whether I'm in the SPG,
or in the SDF.
Manabu said that?
That rascal!
You've got to be kidding!
How could he say such a grown-up thing!?
I'm the one who had the better grades!
Louis-san...
Yuuki-kun really had everyone worried.
I'm not going to be satisfied...
until he is really taken to task...
Yeah, you're right. He leaves for just
a little while, and gets all cocky on us.
If we're going to rail on him,
that's my job.
Please go easy on him.
Yeah, you can count on us!
People continue to run along.
Even when they don't know
what waits for them ahead,
people continue to run along.
Together with their friends,
and with faith in their futures.
I'm back!
How many nights have
I spent alone since then?
Constantly having dreams of the hope
that you are, as I lightly sleep.
The smiles and tears
that you gave to me and me alone
come to mind every time
I get disheartened,
and I set forth again toward the morrow.
The joyful light of the galaxy beckons me
to that beloved person within my heart.
No matter how far apart we are,
my memories will never fade.
My heart wishes always
to be at your side.
"Next Time"
A distress signal from Planet Coulomb.
What we came across in
that melancholy city was...
Next time on Tales of the
Galaxy Railways, Episode 21: "Rebellion"
We're going to encounter
something at the next station.