The clock says 2 in the morning.
I'm in my single apartment.
Alone with a high school boy
who is a friend in a game.
And my temperature is 37.8 degrees.
LV. 11 - There's Something I Want to Talk  About
I slept like a log last night.
Sorry for not noticing at all.
Can you last with all these for a week?
Uwooogh
You're a goddess, Momo!
I mean, your fever always tends
to get so heavy every time.
You lack fundamental stamina too much.
You should do some training
Give me the stuff
that needs chilling
You lack fundamental stamina too much.
Give me the stuff
that needs chilling
Yes
Give me the stuff
that needs chilling
Yes
Have you visited a doctor?
Yeah. Yamada brought me to a clinic
that was still open at night.
I'll be going there again tomorrow.
Wow... You even
brought meat!
Huh?
Well... Yamada came
to check up on me yesterday.
Say what?
Have you two started going out
while I wasn't looking?
No way, we're still friends.
He really is a nice guy.
Wh-What? So...
I can just tell her after she recovers.
Mercy
Anyway, that should do for now.
I'll be on my way now.
Thanks. I'll get your money,
so wait here.
"Is there a guy who'd go that far
for a girl he doesn't even love?"
That's what I think,
but I don't know bits
about Yamada's personality.
Akane's hurdles in romance
seems to get higher too
thanks to her heartbreak.
Stare
Well, not that I don't
understand, but...
I've put
a lot inside!
Yep
I'll be going now.
Let me know ASAP if you need anything.
Yeah.
Also, timing is important in romance.
Oh, yeah... Right.
Glad you understand.
See ya.
You Have a Message from Akito Yamada
Thank you so much for today, how are you holding up?
Sorry i just saw your message, I'm fine
All green
for now...
I should thank him properly
after I get better.
What would work for him?
Akito Yamada
Are you okay?!
I can log in this weekend!
Let's play together
once you get better!
I'm so lonely!
Blush
Runa...
By the way,
did Runa log in yesterday in the end?
I told her we'd be greeting the new girl,
but I've never even met with her.
I'm sick of studying too,
so let's log in for a bit.
While Runa and Yamada aren't around,
maybe Rurihime
and Mister Kamota will be?
I want to grind together with them.
Akane Has Logged In
I haven't ground so much these days,
so let's do that all day long!
Akane Has Logged In
Oh, it's Akane!
It's the new girl I heard about!
This is our new member, Tsubaki!
Nice to meet you! I'm Akane!
I'm a Lv. 55 Paladin!
I'm Tsubaki.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a beginner who just started playing.
We were just about to do
some map scouting with Tsubaki now.
Since you're here,
want to farm together?
I'm in!
Huh? But...
I still don't know how to get around
in this game, so I'll just be dead weight...
You can learn from Akane
how to play as a paladin.
So you're a paladin too, Tsubaki?
Is there really a lot of sorcerers here, after all?
That's
right
This guild's full of
magic users with high FP...
Huh...
Also, everyone has higher DEF stats than me...
I sometimes wonder
why I picked this class.
Huh...
I mean, it's written that it's
the recommended class for beginners.
But I think paladins can
be strong at higher levels.
Did the
Homework
It's said that one of the strongest classes
Did the
Homework
to solo endgame bosses is paladin.
Did the
Homework
It's worth grinding, so I like it.
Did the
Homework
Well, to each
their own way
She's really a nice girl!
But I heard the movement's so hard...
Don't worry! Leave it to me!
I need to show her my good sides!
I need to make sure
not to hinder everyone.
Mom! I can't find my donuts!
Let's go, then.
Have you checked your gear?
Yes.
Yes, I have.
The sky's so beautiful!
I love the game's sky graphics so much!
It might be my favourite thing in FOS!
What do you think, guys?
I'm kind of busy now!
They Don't Have Time to Enjoy the Sky
Strike!
Shield! Shield!
Hey, stop having a peaceful time
and help us out, will you!
This is one tough enemy!
It'll be over in a microsecond if I join in.
It's not that strong a boss,
so break a leg!
You're kidding me!
Thing's got too much HP, it's literally four bars!
Normal Enemy
It's so interesting seeing your damage
counts lose to the boss' Natural Healing!
Rurihime Has Gathered 2x Paladin's Hates!
Here it comes.
Dang it!
Strike! Strike!
But...
Natural Healing
For real...
This is unproductive as it is!
Thanks to the GM's Healing Magic,
we're not out of the loop, but...
My willpower's starting to get close to zero!
If you play it a bit smart,
the current you can beat the boss easy.
Huh?
Oh, right! I got it!
Maybe we need to spam the skill buttons?
Is that what it means
by playing it smart?!
What... But I've been spamming a lot of buttons...
Let's do the button spam strat till drop!
One, two!
Ratatatatatatatatatatata
The Guild Master,
Aware of Why the Chat Went Silent
Annoyed
They must be spamming
them keys like crazy.
Need a hint?
Wait.
I think I got it now.
I couldn't
get it!
For real?
Maybe...
Don't say it just yet.
Okay!
Give me the hint
Feels Like 500 Million Years Have Passed
RIP my fingers.
The Boss Went Back Home Due to Time Limit
Same...
But we could drain the HP
in the second half, right?
It's like there was a timing
that made it easier to attack.
Yeah! When it spread its wings!
Maybe we should attack efficiently
when that happens?
Let's spam some skills
when that happens!
Why don't we check our skills' effects?
Right, let's recheck our gear too!
They're already getting along.
My armour got so tattered, so I'll take a rest
I'll log out, then! See you two again!
Okay! Thanks for today!
My armour got so tattered, so I'll take a rest
I'll log out, then! See you two again!
Okay! Thanks for today!
I'll fix your armour, so lend it to me, Tsubaki
My armour got so tattered, so I'll take a rest
I'll log out, then! See you two again!
Okay! Thanks for today!
I'll fix your armour, so lend it to me, Tsubaki
Thank you for today, Akane
I'll take it off now
Akane from the same guild...
That must mean that girl.
Delete
You Have a Friend Request from Akane
Accept
She was easy to talk with...
You still up?
Yes
Akane
Hello?
Yes.
Huh?
Super Evil Demetal?
What's that?
The monster that spawns
at the first fields of the first city.
The one with long, four HP bars.
Oh, you mean the random spawn boss?
Yeah! Rurihime also said that!
The first city...
Have you ever beaten it, Yamada?
I've never faced such a boss in that rank.
I see. I thought there
might be a walkthrough.
Well... Maybe you'd be able to move
if there's a gimmick or something.
Super Evil Demetal
Gimmick...
Maybe there's a period
when it's invincible,
Super Evil Demetal
a pattern or something.
Yep! There was that!
What do I do in that situation?
Oh, buff? I see!
Buff=Status Up
Might be better than
random button spam
Do you think you'll like our guild?
Currently Fixing The Armour
with Sewing Skill
Yes?
Currently Fixing The Armour
with Sewing Skill
Akane was pretty easy to talk with, right?
Currently Fixing The Armour
with Sewing Skill
Uh, yes...
Everyone is so kind,
I'm so relieved.
So much that I actually feel sorry.
Why?
I was never interested
in this game in the first place.
I joined this guild out of a selfish reason...
And yet, now...
I'm starting to lose sight
of what I wanted to do.
Y-You okay?!
So dark
I'll lend you my ears if you want!
I don't have anything
to talk about
I just kept on looking.
Just like that,
I kept being covered in fear.
It's nothing.
I just didn't have the courage,
and couldn't move...
You don't have
anything to talk about?
Didn't have
the courage?
You don't have
anything to talk about?
Didn't have
the courage?
Couldn't move?
Err, I don't really get it, but...
Why don't you try making a move, then?
It's done
If you have something you want to do,
then why not try doing it?
It's done
Courage and motivation won't
come to you if you just sit around.
You gotta move yourself!
If you want to change something, that is!
So...
Oh, shoot. It's already this late.
Sorry, I kept blabbering all the time.
You must be tired, right?
Yes. My hand got too tired,
I switched to Bluetooth.
Brutally honest, aren't you?
So what was your business, again?
Oh...
Well, rather than business...
I just wanted to hear your voice.
That's all. See you!
Akane
M-My hands...
Phone
...are trembling.
Oh, Momo? Thanks for earlier.
You okay?
Well...
There's something I want to talk about.
I'll holler at you again
Got it, I'll be waiting
About tomorrow's meeting,
There's a cafe I want to go to, so let's meet up there, okay?
See You at 11!
Momo
This is the place?
So Cute
So there's a cafe this cute, huh?
So, about the thing I wanted to
ask you over the phone...
I, uh...
Why do you think I got dumped?
I'll take your orders.
I'll have chunky soufflé
pancakes and iced tea.
Just give her a glass of water.
You're so meanie!
I'll have the same thing!
Two pancakes and iced tea, coming.
Akane, I'm disappointed in you.
But why?!
About Time!
There's something I want to talk about.
For real?! Wait, let's meet up
and tell me in person!
About Time!
I'll listen to you wholeheartedly!
As I waited for your cold
to go away silently for one week,
I couldn't get in the mood,
so I could only join three mixers...
And yet when I heard your story...
You had to come out with something
that goes beyond the imagination.
I'm disappointed.
Nonsense
Isn't three times in a week like,
already full power enough?
Gah!
I thought I could hear
a sweet romance story here!
Gah!
Now, now...
Hear me out till the end, will you?
There's been something
on my mind these days...
In a... rather romantic way.
In order for me to move on too...
I want to fix my super bad flaws...
I might actually have a bad habit
that I'm just not aware of!
I won't know anything
about that myself!
What's with that weird thought?
Like, I won't be able to date anyone with it...
I might have a critical flaw,
so I got scared...
You don't really have any.
Regret...
If I'm gonna regret it later,
even if I have to put myself to shame,
Regret...
I should've asked the reason
why Takuma dumped me back then...
You can't
do that...
Well, that's...
You can't
do that...
Welcome!
You can't
do that...
Oh?
- U-Um, Sir?
- I thought I saw a cute girl,
- but it's you, Momo!
- U-Um, Sir?
Geh!
Oh, what a coincidence!
- Um, your seats...
- Wh-Who're they?
- Oh, don't mind us!
- The guys in my mixer two days ago!
- We'd love to show you
- They were so forceful
- your seats over here...
- and touched me a lot, so I bailed.
Just what kind of people
you go to mixers with?
It's my acquaintance's acquaintances...
Can we share a table?
No way, no way!
Oh, hello to the friend too.
What to drink now?
Really sorry about this!
I'll do something about them,
so just ignore them!
Isn't it a bit forceful of you?
Momo's not feeling comfortable.
Right? We really are a handful, eh?
Momo, you didn't pay the bill
the other day, right?
Huh? I gave the money
to the organiser, though?
Huh? I didn't know anything about it.
Have you checked with the person?
Oh, who cares about the bill?
Let's have fun together!
At this rate,
they're gonna sit here for a while...
Momo, you smell so good!
I can't! You're too close!
Hey!
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your chunky soufflé
pancakes and iced tea.
Huh?
Oh? It was for four, again?
E-Eita...
Sasaki, actually...
Oh, my.
Oh, we're friends with them.
Don't mind us.
Wow, Eita! Help Us!
Yay!
I'm sorry, Sir, but you're troubling
Kyah
the other customers,
so let me take you to another table.
We'll be fine here.
We are really sorry,
but you're really troubling
the other customers,
so please move to another table.
Well, we...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thanks, Eita.
Fancy seeing you here!
That was surprising!
I didn't notice you at all!
I noticed you, though.
What? You should've said hi!
It'd be more fun if I kept quiet.
A friend of hers?
U-Um... Sorry for causing trouble to the cafe.
Not at all.
Whew, that was surprising.
Good thing Eita was here.
He was really hot.
Eita is also in the same guild as me.
Aww!
Huh?! Him too?!
Yeah! He's the guild master!
That game you're playing
has more hope than any mixer...
I Wonder...
I suddenly feel empty now...
Momo, about earlier...
Good work today.
Keep Things Tidy
Good work! Oh, you got a minute, Sasaki?
Huh? No.
Keep Things Tidy
After all, I'm already off my shift.
I'm not talking about work.
We're going for a karaoke with the guys
from the noon shift. Want to tag along?
You did save my bacon too earlier,
so it's on me.
I have a cute sister
waiting for me home, so no.
Geh
What a siscon.
How rude.
I just have too much affection for her,
so I'm a siscon.
So you admit it?
Sasaki
Thanks for today.
Um, Eita!
Oh, you two are still here?
What are you doing?
There's nothing here.
We were waiting for you.
Awwie
Oh, you were waiting for a star's exit?
Huh? Now that's a mysterious personality.
Awwie
There's something I want to talk about.
Is that okay?
Let's go, then.
Have you checked your gear?
Yes.
Yes!
I need to show her my good sides!
Her gear...
Staring at Her Gear
Wait, is your gear
a bit different than mine?
Huh?
It's so cool!
N-Not at all...
You can obtain that
if you do the main quests
Hey, how do you obtain these?
You just have to clear
the starter quests...
Yeah, and then?
If anything,
Akane with maxed out default gear,
is probably the rarest breed of all.
Nice
Default Equipment
Maxed Out
GPU Maxed Out
HP Maxed Out!