Yes?
Guess who it is?
KYAH
Yeah, it's you, Eita.
Were you busy?
I made some adjustments for the sens.
SENS: MOUSE SENSITIVITY
Free much, are ya?
Oh, right. You're coming
to our place today, right?
For Runa's home tutor.
Oh, so the schedule is unchanged?
Hm? Is it?
Anyway, bring me the manga
I mentioned the other day, okay?
I wanna read it.
Sure.
Yay! You're the best, Yamada!
All right, see you.
Okay!
Sure. Saturday next week, right?
Sounds good!
I get to play with Runa!
I'm so happy!
OCTOBER 3, SAT
MY LOVE STORY WITH YAMADA AT LV 999
Well, well...
I never expected the person
behind Rurihime...
...to be an actual woman,
and a cute one.
Based on my past experiences,
I was 100% sure that you'd be a man,
and of course,
I was prepared to love him,
but your being a real woman
really took me aback.
Looks like I was still
shallow in my predictions.
Err... Like I already said so many times,
I'm not Rurihime...
Still, I never dreamed of meeting
Rurihime unmasked in person.
Since I heard that a player
named Rurihime was also in FOS,
I'd been pursuing them
from the previous game,
but I didn't think I'd be noticed...
Not only cute, but you're also touted
as a fast ranker in every game,
RUNA SASAKI: I STILL HAVE SOMETHING TO DO,
and with that reason,
SO I'LL BE A LITTLE LATE.
I THINK MY MMO FRIEND WILL BE THERE TOO,
it makes me proud as a fan.
SO ENJOY A CUP TOGETHER FOR NOW.
SORRY -RUNA
it makes me proud as a fan.
And then, it got realised
in this way today...
If you'd like, I was wondering
if I could join your guild...
Sorry! Need to wash my hands!
Roger.
LV. 05 - MIND SHARING THE DETAILS?
What's happening here?
Runa's not coming...
And a stranger was in
the meeting place instead...
Lady Rurihime?
You're Lady Rurihime, right?
Lady Rurihime...
He thinks I'm Rurihime,
and he's not listening to me at all.
Coming!
Welcome, Yamada!
Hello.
As handsome as always, aren't you?
Runa's always cooped up in her room,
playing games all day.
Can she really enroll
at your school like this?
Runa! Mr. Yamada's here for you!
Yamada!
Hi.
I'll leave her in your care, then.
'Kay.
Be sure to study properly, okay?
I will!
I've already solved the question
in the textbook as you said!
Here!
PRAISE ME
Runa...
Don't you have an appointment today?
Wh-Why do you ask?
Nah, it's okay if you don't.
AKANE
I don't have any appointments...
RUNA SASAKI
She's not picking up...
What do I do now...
I'm all alone with a stranger...
Um, Lady Rurihime?
Excuse me,
but are you Lady Rurihime?
This is the women's room...
Are you serious?
Lady Rurihime, are you okay?
My stomach kind of hurts...
Anyway, this is the women's room...
Oh, I thought so!
Umm...
You're taking too long,
- This is...
- so I thought you might've fainted...
Hey! This is the women's room, mind you!
Lady Rurihime...
Could you open the door for me?
Could you please?
Lady Rurihime...
It's not something important.
Besides, she's probably
on her way home now.
So you stood her up?
I didn't.
I had an MMO friend go there instead.
An MMO friend?
He seemed to be
a die-hard fan of Bro's avatar.
When I invited him using Bro's account,
he was super excited.
Where are you going, Yamada?
Where are you supposed to meet up?
Why?
Why, you ask?
It's too dangerous for her.
I'll go check on her.
What about my tutor?!
I'll be back soon.
Do the textbook questions for now.
Wait!
Wow, that was something.
I BROUGHT SOME SNACKS
I thought this was an automatic door.
Eita...
What's up?
MY LOVE STORY WITH YAMADA AT LV 999
Wow... She really sent a message
from my account.
Now that's evil...
Where's the meeting place?
Uhh...
Oh, it's pretty close.
I guess it's about
fifteen minutes by car from here.
Why...?
Runa.
Runa! What are we playing today?
Why can't we stay like this?
Akane's been kidnapped
by a seriously antisocial person?!
Is that true?!
Aka-Aka-Aka-Aka...
Akaneeeee...
I think I might've exaggerated it.
Akane!
Thanks for the ride, Mr. Kamota!
Mr. Kamota, you shoud've taken
a right at that intersection.
ROAD SAFETY CHARM
Mr. Kamota, we're off-course.
When you see Akane,
you'd better apologise to her.
I won't!
Cut it out already.
That's why you're hated even at school.
I don't care.
I have 300 friends online.
Akane! What do we do, Yamada?!
Mr. Kamota, eyes on the road, please.
Everyone just keep shouting her name...
So stupid.
Besides, who said you could let her join
the guild without my permission?
Now...
IT'S MY GUILD...
If old-timers continue
to push out newcomers like that,
the game's content
will just become stale.
Have some tolerance, will you?
What the heck?
That girl...
She was trying to be nice to you, right?
Saturday next week, right?
Sounds good to me.
All right, let's spread out
and look for her!
Akane! Akane!
Mr. Kamota, you're heavy.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Where is she?!
There she is.
That was quick!
Pretty observant, eh!
But...
She's looking so strange...
Aka...
Akane!!
Aka-Aka-Aka-Aka...
Aka-Aka-Aka-Aka...!
Huh?
Akane! Thank goodness you're okay!
Mr. Kamota!
You'll be fine now!
Leave it to the adult from here!
Who are you?
My name is Takezo Kamota,
the representative
for Kamota Strawberry Farm!
I have a friend in the attorney business!
I won't yield to any violence or threats!
Let's settle this at the courtroom!
You okay, Akane?
Eita? Yamada, too?
Why are you here?
Runa said she invited a stranger here,
so we came here out of worries.
What's up with your legs?
This is...
Pardon me, it was on me.
I spooked her at the woman's room...
Mind sharing the details?
You're too close.
Out of fear that Lady Rurihime
might have fainted in the bathroom,
I meant to give her some medicine...
Lady Rurihime?
Can't you open the door?
Then...
Excuse me, here.
ANALGESIC
Ah...
Lady Rurihime?
INTENSE PAIN
ANALGESIC
That's what happened.
After she was excessively startled,
she hit the toilet bowl at her shin.
IT STILL FREAKIN' HURTS NOW
Anyone would've been startled after that!
That's strange...
When a woman coops up
in the toilet looking unwell,
my mother taught me to silently
give analgesic pills to her...
You shouldn't have acted
with that local knowledge.
For starters, don't enter the women's room!
You are extremely rude.
How are you related
to Lady Rurihime?
I don't want to tell you.
I don't care anymore...
Yo!
So you came here
because you're worried about me?
Thanks.
Well... I'm sorry.
Why are you apologising?
I mean... had I told you
that I'd be tutoring Runa...
So you're Runa's home tutor?
Yes.
Oh, I see!
That's why Runa couldn't make it!
That's...
So that's the reason, huh!
Runa?
Runa!
Oh...
Ouuchh!!
Are you hurt?!
Huh?
Sorry...
Runa.
Come.
I'm gonna scold you.
I won't help you.
That was something
really dangerous you've done.
Please reflect on this.
Come on.
O-Ow, ow, owww!
Akane?
My stomach suddenly hurts...
Huh? Not your leg?
Huh? Uh, well...
The pain went up to my stomach...
What?
Why don't you use
the analgesic I gave you?
You don't talk to Akane!
He's still here...
UGH...
No way... That won't work...
It has to be a first-class analgesic,
prescribed by a pharmacist,
or else it won't work...
First-class what?
About 500 metres from the station,
you'll find a drug store on the right.
Ah, okay. I'll go there now.
I'll go!
Please rub my stomach...
Oh, it'd be worrying
if only you go there,
so have Yamada
and Mr. Kamota go with you.
Also, you go home now.
Runa, what's your level?
Huh?
Oh, sorry. I mean in-game.
Uh, I maxed-out two already,
and now I'm just casually grinding...
Huh?! So we can't do hunting together...
My level is still low...
We can't go together
with that much level gap, right?
I was once rejected by Yamada, too.
Hunting together?
Your level is way below me, so I can't.
I don't wanna deal
with the EXP penalty.
I don't really mind.
I have a low-level avatar too.
Let's go hunting together next time, then!
My job is a Paladin,
and you...
Why are you talking to me so normally?!
Don't you find it strange
for me to stand you up?!
Huh? Err...
I stood you up on purpose!
I thought it'd be better this way!
I hate you, after all!
I wanted you to leave the guild!
I thought you'd start hating MMO
if I sent a weirdo to you...
I thought it was strange, but then...
I SEE...
Are you hurt?!
I guess I'll leave
the scolding to your brother.
I'm here to get along with you.
Everyone is just so nice to me,
and I've been thinking
that I'm glad I joined this guild.
But, they're your precious friends, right?
So that's why I want to ask you
to let me in the circle too!
As your friend!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry for pranking you!
Girls in their teens
are so complicated...
MEDICINE
To think she'd hate Akane this much...
I already give up...
She was so cute and honest
when she was little...
What do I do now...
Welcome back!
MEDICINE
Akane! Is your stomach feeling better now?
Huh? Oh, yes, I'm feeling better now!
Maybe it's because
Runa rubbed it for me?
That was rough.
Huh?
You'd been looking forward to this,
but then she set you up.
Ah...
Well, I guess I should've left...
...when I met that stranger.
While it pissed me off a bit,
too bad I couldn't play
with her normally.
But, yeah, just you see.
While I suck at romance,
I'm pretty good
at getting along with girls.
So, I'm sure I'll get along better with her,
eventually.
As one would expect
from Lady Rurihime.
You are indeed
HE'S STILL HERE?
the kind muse as rumoured.
Please date me on the assumption
that we'll get married!
Please go home!