Yamada? What's wrong?
Your hair hit my eyeball...
What?! Sorry!
Are you okay?
Did it get in your eye?
Let me see. Which eye?
I'm... okay.
Sorry, Yamada!
You apologise too, Runa!
S-Sorry...
I'm sowwy...
I'll put my hair up.
Um... I'll go back home for a bit.
Huh?!
Need to grab the needed tools for this.
But...
I'll be back soon.
Won't you get tired going back and forth?
I'd feel bad...
Don't worry.
It's close by.
Ugly
Idiot
I don't mind being bullied...
Ugly
Idiot
As long as you're here, it's fine, Akito.
Even if we become adults,
let's stay together.
We can't know for sure.
Do You Want to  Feel  at Ease?
Welcome.
Would you like a bag for that?
Yes, please.
I see you always buy this, Sir.
This tea brand taste good, right?
Ah, yes...
I also like this one.
Thank you for your patronage!
Um...
I-If I may,
could you tell me your name?
The uniform you're always wearing is
from Tosei Academy, right?
I'm actually an alumnus there.
I've been wanting to talk to you...
Sorry, but I'm busy now.
Of course you are...
I'm sorry...
Why is she looking like that?
I'm in a hurry...
What am I supposed to
talk about with a store clerk?
You've always been like that, huh...
I don't know.
I'm not fond of girls.
Maybe I'm better off
not approaching them.
I'm back.
No one's here...
Yamada
Naptime After Lunch
They're sleeping so peacefully...
I'll just fix this in silence.
That was close.
Sorry. I'll put my hair up.
Yamada
Riiiing
Yamada!
Why are you here?!
Wait, what?!
I'm your fan!
Oh, yeah... I remember seeing him...
Why are you here?!
Well, stuff...
What do you mean by "stuff"?!
Fill me in, will you?!
What a drag...
Don't tell me Akane's really...
Let me introduce you
to my new boyfriend...
No, I'm not.
I guess not, huh...
After thinking about it,
it was obviously a farce led by Akane...
She's an open book, after all.
Besides, I always check
all your SNS every second!
All normal! No females detected!
All business as usual!
I won't have any weird ideas
about this, so rest assured.
Oh, right.
You see,
I wanted to return something,
so I came here.
We don't meet at all on campus,
and I don't have any means
to contact her either.
With every lunch box and plate
she gave me alongside the food,
I never bothered to return
every single one of them,
so it just kind of piled up...
There's like five of these boxes,
so I'd feel bad if I didn't return them...
Lunch Box Tower
Isn't that just too many?
But well, I'm sure she doesn't
want to see me again now,
and when I thought of cleaning up
and seeing these, I thought of this as well.
I've made you lunch!
Is she doing well?
I got so worried...
If I see her smile,
I can feel at ease too.
She's... probably doing well.
Do you... want to see it for yourself?
Do you want to feel
at ease by seeing her?
I...
I'll just go home.
Sorry for being so self-centred.
Please don't tell Akane that I came visit.
Just tell her that these boxes
just appeared out of the blue somehow!
I'm counting on you!
I'll be rooting for you too
in your next tourney!
Stare
Uhh...
Since when have you been there?
Um... Lunch boxes...
...have appeared...
It's Obviously a Bust, But He's Fulfilling His Promise
There's no way they suddenly
appeared out of nowhere!
It's funny when you say it
with a straight face!
Thanks for handling these.
Um, I'll return this to you.
Wait, come to think of it,
my hair's down again!
Yes, I took it off.
Huh?
I took it off while you were sleeping.
Is that so...
Yes. I'm sorry.
But why?
You didn't have to...
I don't know.
I just felt like I had to...
Why, I wonder?
Wh-What does he mean...?
It's Eita.
Hello.
Yes.
So can I tell you the missing parts now?
Oh, hang on.
I'll write it down.
Hmm...
What was that?
Akane Kinoshita
Miss Akane Kinoshita, right?
Do you have a time preference?
As long as I don't have any classes,
anytime is fine.
Oh, now that's reassuring.
Your university's close by too,
so it's easy to commute here.
Yes!
We're quite a busy store,
so we'd like you to work as much as possible,
but is that okay with you?
Yes! I'll do my best!
Broke
A part-time job at a convenience store?
You actually applied?
Just for a short time.
It's the one close to our college.
You know, the one along the road,
and the manager's got long hair.
Oh, that one?
Let me know if your shifts have been set.
I'll drop by.
Oh, please do!
But why a part-time job?
You got your broken PC fixed, right?
That's right, but Eita...
I mean, a guild member exchanged
my PC parts for free, so...
It's quite pricey
when you buy them, I guess.
I can't just take them all for free,
so I'll just ask them
about that in-game today.
You're actually asking them in-game?
Yep.
Well, they saved your bacon,
so of course you'd want to pay them back.
Momo!
Oh, they're calling me.
All right, I'll continue my mixer now.
Let's talk again sometime.
Okay!
Momo, you took your
sweet time in the restroom.
The guys are waiting for you.
Sorry, got a call from a friend.
A friend?
Akane said she's starting a part-time job.
Oh, Kinoshita.
By the way, I've never seen her
in any of our mixers these days.
She's busy with her MMO now,
just let her be.
All right!
I'll definitely find my prince today!
Momo Maeda
The mixer's done! I failed in finding a prince again today!
Oh, my...
The men up to her standard
are hard to come by...
Just Finished Bath
Currently Wearing Cotton Pack
If you give up,
it's game over.
But, is there such a thing as finding
the ideal person in the first meeting...
...in this life, I wonder?
Akane Has Logged In
Oh!
Hey, Rurihime!
Akane!
Long time no see!
Hello, hello!
The Type to Come Back to Her Senses
It's Eita...
The Honest Type
The Type to Come Back to Her Senses
What were you doing?
Just having a meeting
with the submaster now.
Huh?! Submaster?!
Submaster: Guildmaster's Sub
Where?
I've never met them!
Over there!
Huh?
Right there!
So small! The submaster's so small!
He's of the Micronest race.
They become so small
when not in combat!
It's more like a joke race,
but they can get strong
depending on how to grind.
Right, takezo?
He becomes a
giant in combat
Akane, hello!
I'm Takezo Kamota.
My avatar name is my name,
in alphabet.
Huh?! Mr. Kamota?!
It's takezo here.
Oh, right. Sorry.
takezo rarely gets out of the dungeons,
so it's also rare
to see him in the guild room!
He's so cute, but I can't see him
if I pan out the camera even for a bit.
I feel you!
Oh, right.
There's something I want to ask you.
What's that?
About the total fee
for fixing my PC parts the other day...
How much did it cost?
Not Telling!
Rurihime
Huh? But why?
Not Telling!
Rurihime
It's all old hand-me-down parts, so don't sweat it
But I can't have it.
What should I do, takezo?
I can see where you two are coming from,
so this is difficult...
Why don't we make a compromise,
and have Akane join us
as well in our plan earlier?
Oh, that sounds nice!
Plan?
Oh, shoot! It's Yamada!
Huh?! No way!
Wanna say hi to him?
But what should we talk about?
Uhh... stuff about game?
Oh, what was that, again?
FP-something...
Oh, someone's approaching him.
Yo.
Hey.
Taking out the trash?
That looks heavy.
The girls are always on to you, huh...
If you signed up for the beauty pageant,
you'd win in an instant.
Isn't it a waste to reject it again today?
But the committee don't seem
to have given up yet.
They asked me to convince you.
If you get yourself a girlfriend,
there'll be a lot of girls crying, I bet.
It'll be chaos in the school.
Your point?
Nothing.
You free today?
Wanna play a game after school?
Sure
Yamada!
Your phone's been ringing here!
Thanks.
Huh?
What's up with that earlier?
You could've replied with more feeling to it.
Like this...
"Thank you!"
- Or something.
- It was Eita who said "always", huh...
- Or maybe, "Thanks, my kittens!"
Also...
The vibrations were so loud
against the desk, so...
World History in Details
I put a towel over it.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Tsubaki.
I saw your match yesterday online.
Your aim was sloppy,
and your reaction slow.
You got rusty or what?
You were always
slacking off in that MMO,
so you got bad at FPS now, right?
The server used yesterday
was from abroad,
so it was lagging...
Stop blaming the connection.
Yes.
Our guild Chocolate Rabbit will be going to the Tosei Academy school festival which will be open
soon to the public! Regarding this, I want to ask Yamada to get some tickets for the guild
members here are the members joining:
Guild Breaking News
Eita Sasaki, Runa Sasaki, Takezo Kamota,
and our sponsor, Akane Kinoshita
Sponsor?
Eita Sasaki, Runa Sasaki, Takezo Kamota,
and our sponsor, Akane Kinoshita
You're playing FOS, right?
Yes.
Is it fun?
Wh-What is this?
An external GPU dock.
G-What?
It's bigger than the PC...
Please don't remove it when playing the game.
At all?
Yes.
At all...
But it feels faster than before.
It's even smoother now.
How? Did you also fix this?
You're so amazing, Yamada.
All I did was exchange the parts.
Most of the parts
were leftovers from Eita.
Alongside the faster GPU,
I think it also got faster from exchanging
the last-gen CPU, doubling the memory,
and also swapping the HDD with an SSD.
I don't really get it, but...
So the insides are mostly different now?
Well, yeah.
Thanks, Yamada.
You've really saved my bacon.
No problem.
He really is a god...
A Few Days Later
Today, as a private welcome
back party event for Akane,
the three of us will be
on a dungeon guide tour!
Let's go!
The Third Guy
P-Please take care of me!
No need to be so tense.
With your level now,
I'm sure you can tackle it today,
so don't worry.
We'll support you
with everything we have.
Mr. Kamota's so nice
both in-game and IRL...
His avatar also has
the Mr. Kamota aura,
I think I like it.
All right, guys! Let's go now!
Off to the dungeon!
Yeah!
All right! I'll have to do my best
to contribute at least a bit!
GPU
Huh?
Huuuuuuuuuh?!
The gap is something else...
A real demon god...