Sorry, Akane.
There's someone else I like.
Hmm... Well...
I'd been wondering why he was
so cold to me these days...
This Is Why I've Had Enough with Gamer Boys!!
Your BF was taken by someone else
from an MMO game?!
Now that's a scoop! Wow!
My main ma'am Momo,
you're ringing my ears.
Anyway...
The game was something you guys
played together on PC, right?
Yep...
Wow... Something like that can
even happen in a game, huh...
Akane.
You should play this game, too.
Wow, what's this?
It's the new MMO!
I thought he was a bit of a gamer,
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Ah, okay.
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Ah, okay.
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Ah, okay.
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Takuma Furukawa
Oh, i forgot to mention this,
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
but I never expected him to cheat
with another girl from that game...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Ah, okay.
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
But about the equipment I lent you...
Could you give it back to the shared storage??
It's rare stuff, so sorry!
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
Not to mention,
this was the last thing he sent me...
Ah, okay.
Gosh, now this sucks.
I'm at a loss of words.
It was a good call
you broke up with him.
I'm sure you're still feeling
disappointed now, though...
But I've got a lecture this afternoon,
so I'm going now.
Stop feeling gloomy forever
and come to class, okay?
You'll keep feeling blue
if you shut yourself in.
Well, yeah...
It's not like I'll die if I got dumped,
so my life still continues,
and I can't skip college too much.
I want to work part-time too.
Did he get the equipment
I gave him back?
Notice
A Server Maintenance Will Be
Performed from 21 September at 14:00.
"New Quest Update!" Campaign Will Start!!
Maintenance Notice
Notice
A Server Maintenance Will Be
Performed from 21 September at 14:00.
"New Quest Update!" Campaign Will Start!!
Maintenance Notice
I was never into games...
Name
Character Select
Paladin
Iron Hammer
Iron Shield
Traveler's Uniform
Job
Name
Character Select
Paladin
Iron Hammer
Iron Shield
Traveler's Uniform
Job
But I thought I'd play this game
Name
Character Select
Paladin
Iron Hammer
Iron Shield
Traveler's Uniform
Job
if we could enjoy it together...
Name
Character Select
Paladin
Iron Hammer
Iron Shield
Traveler's Uniform
Job
Oh, he even unfriended me...
Wow, that's pretty thorough of him.
Anyway, if we were gonna break up,
Annoyed
I shouldn't have whaled at all.
I bought a costume for 3,000 yen, dang it.
Equipment
I only have the character
I ground for nothing now...
Attack
Spell
Defence
Special Skill
Item
Equipment
I only have the character
I ground for nothing now...
Attack
Spell
Defence
Special Skill
Item
Hunting Filled with Wrath
Equipment
Attack
Spell
Defence
Special Skill
Item
Hunting Filled with Wrath
Strike! Strike! Strike!
Power...
...Strike!
Um...
Huh? Who's this guy
with a noh mask-like face?
I think I've seen him somewhere...
Yamada
Oh, it's a fellow guild member, Yamada.
Morning, Yamada! :)
Hello
Are you hunting too??
Morning, Yamada! :)
Hello
Are you hunting too??
Yes
Oh, I forgot he was this kind of guy.
He left a bit of a bad impression
on me for being unsocial.
Morning, Yamada! :)
Are you hunting too??
Hello
Yes
Morning, Yamada! :)
Are you hunting too??
Hello
Yes
Besides, what took him two minutes
to reply with "hello" and "yes"?
Morning, Yamada! :)
Are you hunting too??
Hello
Yes
Morning, Yamada! :)
Are you hunting too??
Hello
Yes
You looking for the Prophet's Stone?
Morning, Yamada! :)
Are you hunting too??
Hello
Yes
You looking for the Prophet's Stone?
What's that?
Hello
Are you hunting too??
Yes
You looking for the Prophet's Stone?
Morning, Yamada! :)
What's that?
Are you hunting too??
Yes
You looking for the Prophet's Stone?
Hello
The rare item that the monsters here drop for a 0.01% chance
What's that?
Not to mention, he sounds like
someone whose mental has shut down.
No, I'm not.
I just got dumped by my BF yesterday and got
so pissed, so I was just hunting to vent.
Also, listen to this! He cheated on me
because of this game, too!
It's just the worst!
Two Minutes Later
Oh, really...
Also, listen to this!
Oh, really?
He cheated on me
because of this game, too!
It's just the worst!
He cheated on me
because of this game, too!
It's just the worst!
Anyway, if you're not looking for the rare item,
Oh, really?
could you give this hunting ground to me?
So you don't want to
converse with me, eh?
Not a chance!
I got here first, so you should refrain
from asking such a thing since you came later.
I heard it's the manners in a hunting ground.
Polite Words with Enough Anger
I may not be interested at all,
but I'll use this hunting ground to vent.
Just go find the rare item
on another channel.
I will never give you this place!
I may not be interested at all,
Just go find the rare item on another channel.
I will never give you this place!
but I'll use this hunting ground to vent.
Just go find the rare item on another channel.
I may not be interested at all,
but I'll use this hunting ground to vent.
I will never give you this place!
Oh, no! I ranted to the stranger
Yamada out of anger...
Well, yeah...
I guess...
Yamada
I'm not interested
I hate you, Yamada!
I'll just log out after you're gone!
This is why I've had enough
with gamer boys!!
You Will Also Receive a Pin Code For the Prophet's Stone (Purple)
1st Anniversary Event Will Be Held
More Details over Here!
Visitors Will Be Rewarded with a Special Limited Avatar
You Will Also Receive a Pin Code For the Prophet's Stone (Purple)
1st Anniversary Event Will Be Held
More Details over Here!
Visitors Will Be Rewarded with a Special Limited Avatar
An event?
You Will Also Receive a Pin Code For the Prophet's Stone (Purple)
1st Anniversary Event Will Be Held
More Details over Here!
Visitors Will Be Rewarded with a Special Limited Avatar
Visitors will be rewarded
You Will Also Receive a Pin Code For the Prophet's Stone (Purple)
1st Anniversary Event Will Be Held
More Details over Here!
Visitors Will Be Rewarded with a Special Limited Avatar
with an avatar and special reward...
You Will Also Receive a Pin Code For the Prophet's Stone (Purple)
1st Anniversary Event Will Be Held
More Details over Here!
Visitors Will Be Rewarded with a Special Limited Avatar
Wow, it's pretty close, too...
Akane, let's be together forever.
Yeah!
Sorry...
I have someone else I like...
in that game...
She said she likes me too...
I'm really sorry...
He must already be going out
with her anyway...
Will they be going there together?
Dang...
Like hell I'd let it end
with him dumping me!
Akane!
You're finally here!
You back on your feet already?
Momo.
Hey, Momo, would you tag along with me
to buy some clothes and shoes?
Hm? You going somewhere?
I'm going to an event.
He might be coming there too.
I'll make him regret dumping me,
who has become the utmost beauty now.
Wow, she's not back on her feet at all!
It couldn't be that game's event, could it?
Of course it is that game's event.
He'll most likely go there.
Now that's tough.
Whatever you say.
Wow...
- Please make me cuter!
- I'll definitely make him regret...
- Okay!
- ...choosing a girl in a game over me!
- Please make me thinner!
- I'll definitely make him regret dumping me!
- Okay!
Thank you for coming to Forest
of Savor Autumn Fest today!
The PIN code given to you
at the entrance...
...will expire by the end of December!
Original Exhibiton
and Sale
This is surprisingly quite grand...
...will expire by the end of December!
And there's a lot of people
here too than I expected...
Hang on... Could it be that I...
I'm actually gonna go
bankrupt this month?
Still, everyone here plays
the same game as me, huh...
There's a lot more men here
for some reason...
But it just feels so strange.
What kind of character
is everyone running?
Takuma!
Takuma...
Ta...
Let's go to the front?
Sure.
W-Wait!
What happened?
Oww...
A girl just tripped?
This is just too dumb...
I want to disappear...
I just... want to cry now...
You okay?
Wow! A hot dude!
Yes, I'm okay!
Did I hit you, by chance?
Yes...
I'm sorry!
I was so deep in my thoughts...
I just had a bad day...
...and couldn't see around me...
Oh, really?
I'm sorry, it's nothing.
Huh...
Well... I'm not interested.
Huh? Hang on...
I thought I'd heard that before...
I'm not interested
Yamada?
Are you the Afro Yamada?
Who are you?
My Love Story with
Yamada at Lv999
Who are you?
Umm... Err...
Huh?
Now that's a shallow reaction...
But he's really got that déjà vu feeling
of the Afro Yamada, or is it just me?
There can't be such coincidence, can there?
And he's looking at me so suspiciously...
So he's not that Yamada?!
I'm sorry...
Huh?!
Takuma, and his new girlfriend...
Why are you here...?
T-Takuma! Wow, fancy seeing you here!
If it isn't you, Yamada!
Huh?
Whoa! You're Yamada, aren't you?!
Who?
You don't know?
He's a really famous pro gamer!
Oh, that's amazing!
He really is!
Hey, are you playing FOS too, Yamada?
I'm a big fan of yours!
I always watch your live streams!
So cool!
Wowzer!!
Are you famous?
Well... locally.
Fancy seeing you here, Takuma!
Are you on a date too?
Oh, it's you, Akane.
You're here?
I was always here!
What are you doing here?
I also play that game,
so it won't be strange if I come, right?
Huh?
By yourself?
Like hell!
Let me introduce you
to my new boyfriend...
No, I'm not.
I beg you... Could you please
take pity on me and play along?
Are you for real?
Just consider it
as an act of helping someone...
Huh...
Let me give you this ticket
I got from being a visitor.
You can have this...
Visitor's Benefit for the 1st Anniversary Event
The Prophet's Stone
For real? This is the PIN code
for the Prophet's Stone, you know?
A super rare enhancing stone, you know?
So that's what it is...
I am...
He's my boyfriend!
For real...?
I've always followed him for three months,
yet he never followed back or responded...
I always
replied on
his tweets
too...
I always
replied on
his tweets
too...
This is frustrating!
Takuma!
I won!
This is a bit different from what I imagined,
but he's frustrated!
This is frustrating...
Takuma, cheer up.
Eri...
Takuma.
Takuma!
Robbed
Izakaya Botta
Welcome!
Man... How do I describe this feeling...
It's just like I won the match,
but lost the game...
You didn't even win the match, did you?
Or something like that.
You must be that Afro Yamada, right?
This annoying feeling...
Huh... Anyway, can I go home now?
Yes, you are...
Come on, don't be a prude!
I don't wanna be alone!
That girl...
She was really pretty...
Who?
Takuma's girlfriend.
Who's Takuma?
My ex-boyfriend!
I told you on chat, didn't I?!
So you're that lame paladin...
The one hogging
the hunting ground...
You just realised now?
Isn't it great already that I noticed?
Welcome!
Actually...
I meant to show my beautiful side
to make him regret today...
I never meant...
to see that happening before me...
Um...
If you're gonna keep me here for long,
It's starting to
taste like water...
can I get a refill?
It's starting to
taste like water...
Suit yourself.
With pleasure!
I'm starting to relax now.
Anyway, Takuma mentioned this earlier,
but what's a pro gamer?
Someone who plays games
and takes sponsors, I guess.
Sponsors? No way.
Give me cola
With pleasure
It's true.
So, you also get paid to play FOS?
I just play that as a side hobby.
I main FPS games.
What's that?
FPS: Short for First-Person Shooter. A Shooting Game With a First-Person Perspective
Oh, forget it.
Aren't you being so cold, Yamada?
You're definitely not popular
with girls, I bet.
I'm not.
I've never had a girlfriend either.
Huh? You're kidding me!
But you said that I'm not popular.
Well, yeah, I did...
But there's no way you're not popular
with girls with such face.
Humblebragging
much?!
I'm not interested in romance,
it's kind of unknown to me.
What a waste of a handsome face...
It's more fun to play games.
Well... It's not always a smooth sail
on the ship of romance too...
I, for instance,
was cheated on through a game...
That's a tragedy.
Tragedy, huh...
Oh, shoot... I want to cry...
Need to wash my hands.
Oh... My shirt's all dirty...
I guess it was because I tripped earlier.
Whoa... even my foot's got scraped.
I shouldn't have gone there...
If I'm going to feel like this...
Huh?
Th-That guy...
He actually went back home?
I can see him do that...
He looked like he wanted to go home so bad...
I wanna go home...
Not that it matters to me...
I forced him to tag along, too.
I'm going to be all alone
from here on anyway...
You okay?
What's up with your face?
Yama... Yamaya...
Anyway, could you sit down for a bit?
What's that?
A band-aid.
Shoot, it stuck on my fingers.
I'll just apply it like this.
You bought it for me?
The blood on your foot
was bugging me.
But you actually went and bought it?
Well... I also drank
three glasses of cola, too.
Yamada!
Izakaya Botta
Just order to your heart's content!
No, I'm going back now...
Izakaya Botta
Let's drink our fill tonight!
U-Um...
Izakaya Botta
We'll order again here!
With pleasure!
So, Tani's going to watch our surroundings,
we can just focus on the front.
Maybe we can get our K/D higher.
She Got Hungover
My head hurts...
The next map won't score that much...
Wait, I keep hearing someone talking...
I'm telling you,
no face cam for me.
Who's that?
You're so persistent.
Sorry, gonna go AFK for a bit.
I'll be back soon.
Samurai
Yamato Nadeshiko
Extreme Twintail
Hmm...
Samurai
Yamato Nadeshiko
Tonkotsu
F2P hairs aren't that cute, huh...
Obtained from Flower Field Gacha
(The Dreaming Flower Girly)
Obtained from the Moon Night Gacha
(Fairy Twintail)
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
Obtained from Flower Field Gacha
(The Dreaming Flower Girly)
Obtained from the Moon Night Gacha
(Fairy Twintail)
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
But the cute ones are mostly from gacha...
Obtained from Flower Field Gacha
(The Dreaming Flower Girly)
Obtained from the Moon Night Gacha
(Fairy Twintail)
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
Obtained from Flower Field Gacha
(The Dreaming Flower Girly)
Obtained from the Moon Night Gacha
(Fairy Twintail)
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
No way I'd get them...
Obtained from the Moon Night Gacha
(Fairy Twintail)
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
No way I'd get them...
Obtained from the Moon Night Gacha
(Fairy Twintail)
No way I'd get them...
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
No way I'd get them...
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
Obtained from the by the Lake Gacha
(Swaying Inward Curl)
Obtained from the Tower of Stars Gacha
(Dango Gorgeous Girl)
Recommended for Beginners!
There are also hairstyles with fixed price...
While it's not as cute as the gacha ones,
these are cuter than the default one.
Recommended for Beginners!
I see... So I can just get it first
and develop her uniqueness moderately.
So I bought the cutest one
on the fixed price hairstyles!
Akane Has Logged In
So I bought the cutest one
on the fixed price hairstyles!
Everyone thinks of the same thing...