Welcome!
Care for some freshly fried chicken?
Please touch your phone over there.
You Can Play Once for
a Purchase over 700 Yen!
Here you go, Sir!
You Can Play Once for
a Purchase over 700 Yen!
You're eligible for our lottery campaign!
Please pick one.
So...
- You're going to shop tomorrow? You are, right?
The Convo in FOS Last Night
- The reason you insisted me to go was this...?
- You should come to my store!
The Convo in FOS Last Night
- There's something to look forward to!
- Come on, you're on
That eating habit is
really bad for you
- your way home from school, too.
That eating habit is
really bad for you
- your way home from school, too.
The one near my room is
also doing this
That eating habit is
really bad for you
The one near my room is
also doing this
You'll be buying food as well
as you walk home, right?
That eating habit is
really bad for you
The one near my room is
also doing this
Well, yeah.
Been a while since we saw each other
at the festival. Is Runa well?
Yes. She seems to be doing well in her study.
You Got a Cup Ramen!
I see.
She sometimes calls me,
but we rarely meet offline.
Oh, is he your friend, Akane?
Part-Time Comrade
Mrs. Shinohara (Housewife)
Mrs. Shinohara.
Part-Time Comrade
Mrs. Shinohara (Housewife)
He looks so cool.
He is! We met in a video game.
He's got a pretty face,
just like an actor.
It makes my heart skip a beat.
I'll excuse me...
I'll be done in a sec,
so let's go home together!
He's waiting so patiently outside.
Is he your boyfriend?
No, he's not.
He doesn't seem to be
too fond of girls, so he's not.
Oh, what a waste.
He heh
But you do like him, don't you, Akane?
I mean, you desperately tried to stop him.
Uh... I'm not sure.
This is so fun!
Gosh!
The way you reply is so like a pure maiden!
This is so fun!
Sure, compared to when we first met,
I'm not interested
I feel like he's opened up a lot to me now...
What a drag...
I wanna go home
I'm not interested
Kinoshita
I do think that he really is...
Hello.
...a nice guy.
Thanks for waiting!
Even if we're just connected through a game,
it makes me happy
that we can get along through that.
But that also includes Eita and Runa, right?
It's a Big Disaster for  the  Guild!!
I didn't ask you to come for the lottery.
Actually, I made you lunch as a thank you
for helping me, so I wanted to give it to you.
A thank you?
For my PC.
I couldn't really say
thank you during the festival.
I don't really mind.
I've finally escaped my broke status recently,
so expect great stuff inside the box.
I don't know why,
but I can't see him as a candidate
for my boyfriend...
Feels like I'm not allowed to...
Shoot, I just sneezed in front of
a third year about to take his exam.
Caught a cold?
I dunno.
Where's my mask?
Found it yet?
Found it.
I hope it doesn't get worse.
Your cold, I mean.
Yeah...
Thanks.
The distant look...
Don't you think guys who are unaware
that they're nice are scary?
Go on.
When I let my guard down,
I might fall under the illusion,
that he might actually fall for me,
but he's not really into it at all.
It's just a scary trap,
with him exercising his kindness to me.
There's only one thing I want to confirm...
How can you claim that he can't fall for you?
Still learning
nail arts
Also, can I make this a bit extravagant?
Still learning
nail arts
The theme will be the night butterfly.
Still learning
nail arts
Please don't. They'll scold me at work.
While you don't mention the subject,
you must be talking about Yamada, right?
Ohh
Yep.
Weren't you happy after he called you
a flower on a high peak?
That shouldn't have a deeper meaning too...
That's why it's scary...
If a younger handsome man said
something like that as a trick or something,
I'd have struck him straight away.
Night Butterfly
I don't know what makes you so fidgety.
What do
you think?
Night Butterfly
I don't know what makes you so fidgety.
What do
you think?
Nope
Night Butterfly
What do
you think?
Nope
I'm not fidgety...
Really? It seems to me
that you're most fidgety these days.
You always talk about Yamada so happily,
probing your own feelings.
You never tell what you
want to do at all right?
If you don't tell,
I won't be able to comment.
Touche, Ma'am...
So the butterfly...
That's still a no.
Runa Sasaki
Oh, it's Runa.
Oh, I remember her.
The Lolita middle schooler.
Yep.
Hello?
Akane, can we meet right now?!
It's a big disaster for the guild!
Runa!
Thanks for waiting?
Is it okay for you to be
outside at this hour?
It's getting darker.
I came here by taxi, so I'm good.
I'll be going home by taxi too.
That's great, then.
Anyway, I actually met with...
Wait, did you read my message?!
Well, yeah, I did.
So we have a new member in our guild.
Another stranger woman
has joined the guild...
Unbelievable! The guild was meant
to be for our circle only!
I like you now though, Akane!
- She's so exclusive...
- It'll be a completely different guild
after I come back from the entrance exam!
Also, I hate women!
They'll hate me straight away!
Must be because
I'm cute?!
I'm looking forward to it, though.
Grrrrrrr
I hope she's just a girl new to MMO.
Oh, I brought hot chocolate with me, want a can?
Grrrrrrr
This one's a
limited edition
Oh, I brought hot chocolate with me, want a can?
This one's a
limited edition
So nonchalant!
Top Secret
No Peeking
With that being said,
Top Secret
No Peeking
I've come up with plans to drive her away.
Top Secret
No Peeking
Hey!
The newbie must be anxious,
so we must greet her warmly, okay?
Besides, maybe we can get along
with her if we get to know her.
Just like the two of us.
When you think that you get to know someone
who you normally won't meet in real life...
Isn't it exciting?
That's why I hate it!
I bet you'll get along fast with that girl!
Then, you'll start hanging out with
her more than with me, right?!
That's not true.
We haven't even met yet...
That's definitely true!
What...
We could just get along well together...
I hate odd numbers!
There'll be an extra!
Let's get along together, okay?
Okay?
I'll just let it
pass with a sip...
It feels like having a girlfriend
I'll just let it
pass with a sip...
who's easily jealous.
Well, I knew it all along, though.
You're that kind of person, after all.
Even my brother...
He said our new member
is brought in by Yamada,
so I better greet her properly.
Yamada did?
I'll have the chocolate
She's his classmate.
Originally, she's an FPS gamer girl, apparently.
She said she could use
an MMO as a distraction.
They seem to be good friends too.
When I asked
who she is on the phone...
Tell me!
She's just a normal girl.
Yamada wouldn't tell much.
He said if I bully her like I did you,
he'd be real mad...
I haven't done
anything, though...
A girl on good terms with Yamada...
I haven't done
anything, though...
I didn't expect Yamada
to actually invite a girl.
Huh? Well, yeah.
Anyway, I've thought of a good idea!
Give me your phone!
Yamada
What are you doing?
Inputting Yamada's number to your phone.
You call him yourself, Akane!
He seems to be wary of me,
but I bet he'll tell you!
If I know what kind of girl she is,
I'll feel at ease!
Akito Yamada
Techno Solutions
Kawai Cram School
Japanese Restaurant Nagomu
So, I heard they started
dating just like that.
For real?
Didn't they say they're both
not suited for each other?
But still, they're a man and a woman.
Even though it's impossible,
they might actually hook up
over the most trivial reasons.
So dating someone can start
from a trivial reason?
Hello, Class Rep.
Hello, Okamata, Yamada.
Hey.
Anyway, it's kind of funny for you
to mumble on you own while coming here.
Huh? I was asking you two, though.
Sorry about that
Dating, huh? Well...
You're really gonna ask that to us?
History of Life without a GF = As the Age Shows
Hobby = Game
I suppose not.
Oh, right. Thanks for the invitation, Yamada.
And for talking with the master about me.
Sure.
What's that?
A game.
Oh, FOS?
I've just started playing,
then I heard that it'd give me
the upper hand to join a strong guild.
So I asked Yamada to let me join his.
Can i eat
the hamburger?
You're a closet gamer, after all.
Can i eat
the hamburger?
You're a closet gamer, after all.
The class is
about to start
You're a closet gamer, after all.
The class is
about to start
I'm not really trying to hide it...
I just can't talk about it with other girls,
since they talk a lot about romance.
Sho ywou're intwested in womance stooff?
Not really...
So you've devoted your life to gaming?
Not gonna pick that up?
It's vibrating
like crazy
I don't know this number.
Incoming
Class's about to start too.
You Have 1 Missed Call
Oh, they hung up.
You've been getting a lot of calls, huh?
Maybe it's a confession from a stranger woman?
There shouldn't
be anything like
that normally
You could actually get one if you...
Yamada...
He's not really fond of
romance stuff, am I right?
So loud...
That was shocking...
Well, yes...
Right.
I'm famished!
Great Scott... I'm dying...
Didn't you eat a hamburger just now?
I want a hamburger...
Again?
I'll also buy potatoes next...
Huh? Hey, are you listening?
I'm on the phone.
Oh, you're calling
the unknown number earlier?
If she's a girl with a cute voice,
let me talk to her!
Gonna ignore me?
Akito Yamada
Incoming
Coming.
Hello?
Sorry about earlier...
Yamada?
It's me, Akane!
Akane?
It really is a girl.
Huh? How'd you get my number?
Heheheh
Right.
Sorry for suddenly calling you.
I met Runa earlier in the evening.
You okay?
Yeah... Anyway,
there's something I want to ask you,
but I'm about to go to work now.
Welcome!
But you've already worked today...
The manager couldn't seem
to contact the night shifter, so...
I got called suddenly...
Isn't there any other stand-ins?
Nope, I don't think so.
My apartment's near,
so I can be summoned pretty quick.
I see.
Yamada, you...
Yes?
His voice sounds quiet on the phone.
It's nothing.
View the Moon
Eat the Burger
Mangetsu Burger
View the Moon
Eat the Burger
Mangetsu Burger
Okamoto Is Buying Food
Was she the one with you
at the festival?
Wow
I'm surprised you could tell.
I heard you call her name.
Wow
She's in the same guild in FOS.
I'm sure you'll eventually meet her too.
I see.
You seem to be good
friends in real life too.
Well, right.
Our master's my senior
from the neighbourhood.
I can't remember... her face.
What kind of person?
Huh? Our master?
No, that Akane person.
Akane...
My ex-boyfriend!
Did I just cross the line overnight?!
Yamara!
She always
looks weird...
Yamada!
I don't really know.
Could it be...
...that you like her?
Sorry, Akane!
The night shift guy's out of reach,
and I alone can't run the store!
You should've just fired
that quitter already!
It's really a bother
R-Right...
But I can't really hate
It's really a bother
the guy with the guitar!
Oh, I'll treat you something as an apology.
What about tomorrow night?
I know a good place...
Not going!
I'll just eat in my apartment
I'm feeling cold,
so I was hoping to go to bed soon...
Momo
Call History
Akito Yamada
Momo
It feels strange seeing
Yamada's name in my call history.
All right, time to work.
You never tell what you
want to do at all right?
Akane!
Coming!
Oh, shoot!
Would You Like to Log in to Aria 5 Server?
You Have Received an Invitation to the Guild Chocolate Rabbit from Rurihime. Would You Like to Accept?
I don't have any regrets,
but I think just now...
Sorry, Akane.
There's something I actually regret.
Incoming
Akane
Oh, it's Akane.
I'm tired already
Can I pick it up?
Go ahead?
Akane, what's up?
I'm having my tutor session now.
Runa...
Geh! What's with your voice?!
You sound
like a zombie!
A cold?
So you can't play tonight?
Is that so...
No, it's okay. It is what it is.
Get well soon.
Akane said she caught a cold.
We promised to play
FOS together tonight...
She sounded like dying earlier.
Will she be okay?
I hope it's nothing serious.
Cooling Patch
Pafron Gold A
My throat burns like hell,
I can't drink water...
I gotta drink my medicine...
It's Pretty Serious
Wait, I gotta eat something first...
I haven't eaten anything since yesterday...
Break time...
A Little Rest
I'm beat...
Also, now out of all days...
Koyanagi Clinic
Off during Weekends and Holidays
I feel so...
Calling
Momo
- The number you are calling cannot be reached...
Calling
Momo
- ...unlucky.
- The number you are calling cannot be reached...
But...
Weep as I may,
no one's coming to save me.
If I don't move,
I'll only face death.
Need to eat something.
Maybe porridge or something?
Gotta buy something...
I got no rice left...
I'll just spread the cold, so no bus...
Oh, yeah. The bike.
All right, my thoughts are still running.
Please give me some energy
to survive the night...
I can't ride a bike...
Like, it's so out of question...
I feel hot...
Why didn't I just order online?
How come I didn't realise?
Right, I could just order online.
Running thoughts.
Before that...
I need to fix the bikes...
Then I'll go back to my room...
What was I supposed to do, again...?
My head hurts...
Akane.
What... I'm seeing someone
who looks like Yamada...
But, there's no way
he's in my apartment...
Can you hear me?
A dream?
Oh, boy...
He's finally in my dream now...
Sorry, Yamada.
Sorry for seeing such
a convenient dream.
Butterfly, butterfly...
Land on me!
The night butterfly, Momoko Maeda.
Today, I will meet
the destined prince of mine...?!
Glasses Girl
Soothing Girl
The Night Butterfly
Suffered Total Defeat
Excuse me! I want a refill!
Akane
Get me a strong gin.
Momo's not picking up...