Psychic Beast!
She's been hypnotized
into opening the door!
-Hold it off, Raiga.
-On it.
-Edgar, the walls!
-Roger that.
Rayloca sladseld.
Magic sealers!
Kuroki can't use magic
until we take them down!
If we lose track of them, it's over!
Get them!
I'll leave this to you.
-Wow.
It's not looking good, Uncle.
You're right about that.
Without magical enhancements,
I score two or three in gym class.
I'm basically a useless log.
Two or three out of what?
The teachers saw his efforts
and spared him the lowest grade.
Things sure change, Edgar.
We're no longer those crybabies
in need of his cuddles.
The man's got a scary face,
but we trained to be strong like him.
That's--
-They're talking about you!
-What?
They really admire you!
Huh? What? Really?
His strength is unmatched.
Oh, cut it out--
Gigant hunter Doldor Rexdor!
Sorry, wrong guy.
I'm so sorry, Uncle.
I need to go use the restroom.
You two keep watching.
Also, we can't let Kuroki
outperform us again.
You got that right.
Kuroki is a great fighter too.
He's a bit odd though.
Uncle!
Hey, Uncle! They're praising you--
Enough!
Watch without me!
-Uncle!
-I'm so sorry, Uncle.
UNCLE:
YOU'RE FINE THE WAY YOU ARE
GET HOME
SOLD CHEAPER THAN A SCOURING PAD
He won't come out.
Will he be okay?
I believe in him.
He'll get through it.
You're right.
So let's believe in him and keep watching!
Hurry, start it. What happens next?
You…
Let's see, wind, fire and ice.
Let's go with this order.
DEAD?
-Uncle!
-He's alive!
Good one.
-Uncle!
-That's gotta hurt!
He's fine.
Who was behind the attack?
-That was Elf.
-Uncle.
Are you better already?
Of course I am.
That was Elf's newest weapon.
The scabbard she left in a hurry to grab.
Wait, the scabbard?
Heavy projectile mode.
How useful.
Glasses! Ponytail!
The scabbard is cool, but why the glasses?
They're an ancient magical relic too.
Not that way, orc face. Over there.
Dummy.
I said this way. He ran off!
-Perhaps because she's royalty…
-Don't run.
-…she hunts humans for sport.
-Crap, I lost you!
-Elf is being unkind.
-You sneaky little--
-So, what's the deal with those birds?
-Don't do this to me.
Being able to block magic
is quite a power.
They told me this later.
Those birds' breath
contains magical properties
that inhibit the spirits' activities.
Wow, so that's how it works.
Suits the fantasy setting.
No. The spirits are more like,
"Smelly birds! Don't put us to work."
I see.
They have halitosis.
Regsuuid zaldohna.
The spirits are saying,
"It's still stinky! Nope, not gonna work!"
Those birds have
a terrible case of halitosis.
Spirits are pretty stubborn.
After that, I joined Alicia
and the others.
No!
Everyone's hypnotized!
-Alicia.
-Kuroki!
You got burned!
Lord, grant us healing light!
Thanks.
Can't your wand undo the hypnotism?
Not possible!
The wand may be powerful, but divine magic
is for healing the body and spirit!
It's ineffective against overwhelming
brute force. I said so!
There's no activation button on it?
Elf's sword has a special function.
There's no button.
What if we twist this part?
What?
Kuroki, what are you--
This light-- It's harmless.
Looks like it, yeah.
Is this the wand's area of effectiveness?
Alicia, try to undo the hypnotism again.
Okay, I'll try.
It's just, this magic--
It cures altered states by synching
my tranquil mind with the targets'.
What? I can't hear you.
Please don't stare at me so closely.
Oh, sorry.
You can't cast magic like this.
Oh, Lord.
Let the hearts of those
who wander in darkness
become one with mine.
What was I doing?
Hypnotized…
We did it, Kuroki!
Alicia!
Ashura Steel Fist!
That's my skill!
-Alicia!
-Are you hurt?
Huh? What did I…
Uncle. What just happened?
The wand enhanced Alicia's spell
and gave her additional powers.
Alicia can now use the abilities
of her synched allies.
Something about divine powers
boosts skills even more.
No way.
She's turning into a real hero.
You won't get away.
This is bad. Flaming Hell Beasts!
We're outnumbered.
They're easy to trap.
They charge headfirst.
Good grief. Finally.
Rayloca mivald bagl hild.
The spirit of water here
is boiling with rage.
Brace yourselves.
Bagluuid.
What?
Great.
We did it!
I can't thank you enough.
-That was incredible, great hero!
-It was nothing.
-Train from the basics again.
-Yeah.
Mister!
Sorry I got scared of you earlier.
It really was nothing--
I patched up the holes in the walls
with a barrier for now.
Make sure the baths look good.
An impressive open view.
A "have a drink while watching the sunset"
package will make us rich!
Fantastic! We'll be filthy rich!
Man, this barrier is crazy strong.
How'd you manage to cast
something this powerful?
I put up a huge barrier once.
That experience came in handy.
Yes! Finally, a competitive edge
to our outdated and boring inn!
That's terrible, Lenia.
That's what you think about our inn!
You're not wrong, Lenia.
And that's a wrap for this incident.
It all worked out in the end. I'm glad.
Wait. I thought you got in trouble
for erasing memories.
Oh, right.
After the battle, I went for another soak.
-Skip it.
Oh, okay.
Hello.
I forgot to tell you I was coming in.
The beasts burned down the fencing
separating the men's and women's springs.
Back to fast-forwarding.
-Don't!
STRIKING WATER SERPENTS
Kuroki.
I'm covered.
Oh, good.
What, you thought I'd join you naked?
It's a hot spring, so yeah.
No way.
Icuras cuora.
-That was fast!
-Uncle?
No, I wasn't looking at anything dirty…
I know. Your memory must've flashed back.
No one in real life suffers nosebleeds
after seeing a dirty image.
Thanks. I was caught off guard.
The memory I erased
was about seeing Alicia's naked body.
Sorry. You didn't want to see that.
What? Well…
Yeah, I know.
You wouldn't be interested
in a young girl like me.
Are you that young? I'm 20.
Are you, now. What?
We're the same age?
You're not in your thirties?
I only just turned 20.
When's your birthday?
I was an August baby.
I was born in November.
I'm older?
Alicia is older than Uncle.
I'm with her.
I wouldn't believe it either.
But I may have been born in another month.
What do you mean?
I can't remember anything
from before I turned nine.
Kuroki, can you project my memory?
-August, 11 years ago.
-Yeah.
Icuras elran.
My first memories are
of seeing blood and a carriage.
I was getting taken away
in a carriage by goblins.
I was saved by knights from the village
Edgar and Raiga are from.
Maybe because I hit my head,
I can't recall anything from before then.
WE LOVE YOU
HAPPY 10TH BIRTHDAY
All I had was this piece of paper.
We never found my family.
They were most likely
killed by the goblins.
I was named Alicia by the priestess
in charge of Edelcia's outskirts.
They took me in and raised me.
And here we are now.
So my birthday may not be in August.
Alicia, are memories important to you?
Huh? Of course they are.
Since I can't recall any of my childhood,
I've treasured all my experiences since!
I erased your memory. Twice.
Huh? Are you trying to be funny?
I can cast icuras cuora.
It's a memory obliteration spell.
Memory
obliteration.
Why? I--
Kuroki, which of my memories
did you erase?
Be warned, you'll get nosebleeds.
Nosebleeds?
The first memory I erased
was when we won against
the goblin horde on Mount Dordo.
The second time was when we attacked
the Labyrinth of Depths via the back door.
So the goblin mission,
becoming a crusader,
earning my title as a hero--
That was all you, Kuroki. Not me.
I'm nothing special.
At the Sealed City, you fixed the barrier
and didn't tell a soul!
These are all actions of a legendary hero!
You saw me do that?
You can disclose the truth.
I'll go somewhere far away.
What are you saying? I don't understand.
It was I who undid that barrier.
Why would you do such a thing?
It was out of curiosity.
Kuroki,
you wouldn't risk people's lives
without a sound reason.
I come from a different world.
I'm from Japan Bahamal.
Murayama came from the same place.
You're from there too?
My goal is to go back to my world.
That's why
I slammed my strongest offensive magic
against the thick barrier wall.
I was looking for clues in the time warp
caused by the impact.
I ended up only shattering that barrier.
You wanted to do what Psychic Beast did.
You tried to create a tunnel
between your world and ours.
In essence, yes.
You erased only those two memories, right?
Yeah. No more.
Don't ever cast this spell again!
On yourself or others!
It's for survival's sake.
If I need to, I'll use it.
Kuroki!
I don't want to forget you!
And I don't want you to forget me!
All right.
I won't use the memory obliteration spell
on you ever again.
That's not enough.
I won't erase my memories of you either.
Happy now?
It's a promise, got that?
Okay.
Great.
Let's shake on it.
Oh, but--
What is it now?
This explains why you were scribbling
and mumbling just now.
Again? Did I erase another memory?
What was it?
It's nothing. Just my nake--
I'll recall it. Show me what you did.
It wasn't a big deal. It's fine!
No! We made a promise.
I won't erase any of my memories of you.
-It was only a glance.
-Glance? What did I get a glance of?
Oh, well, fine.
Can you keep your eyes closed?
Huh? All right.
What?
Unbelievable.
She shot through this barrier!
Kuroki!
He's younger than me.
Beasts attacked, Alicia grew furious
and Elf tried to hunt me down.
More like Hell Springs
than Purgatory Springs. Good heavens.
What do I call him?
Tenma? Or do I keep calling him Kuroki?
I wonder if Uncle's got screws loose
from getting rid of too many memories.
I know.
Uncle, go easy on erasing your memories.
Yeah. Earlier, you erased one again
in the bathroom.
-No, I didn't.
-What?
But you looked oddly refreshed.
You're misunderstanding.
That wasn't magic.
It was a technique
for killing my emotions.
Say what?
Theoretically speaking,
even if you go through hell,
nothing can bother you
if you don't feel the pain.
That's what I was doing.
I killed off my feelings
before things took a toll.
You'll have many chances to do the same
when you hit middle age,
so take the time to practice
while you're young.
No, thanks. Right, Takafumi?
He's right. If I don't feel a thing…
Good.
-Good. It's working.
-Stop!
The Great Recession.
-Good start.
-Lost 20 years.
-Now, empty your heart even more.
-I've had my fair share of troubles.
It's a handy skill.
Takafumi, stop!
No matter what happens to me from now on…
-Stop! Don't do this!
-…I think I can overcome it…
-Come back to us, Takafumi!
-…with this skill.
Subtitle translation by:
Megumi Hunter