-I want to eat a crepe!
-Wasn't that maid cute?
Yeah! Do you want to go again?
Oh, wow!
1-1 MAID CAFE ITAN
-Welcome back, Master!
-Welcome back.
Komi!
Help over here!
Maid Cafe Itan
now has a fifteen-minute wait!
-THIS IS TADANO.
-Najimi's planning something devious.
Right this way! Welcome home, Master!
Step right up! Best deal in town!
Master! Right this way!
Hello young masters!
We have many maids to choose from!
How about it? Just a drink! Well?
Thank you very much!
Get your discount tickets!
Have fun with our fabulous maids!
We have lots of special services!
Hey kid,
want the experience of a lifetime?
A cool grand will get you everything!
And a little something on the house!
We have cold towels!
It was hot outside, wasn't it?
Has Najimi done this before?
60-MINUTE WAIT
Where are the towels?
-Take an order here!
-Okay!
We could do more.
More what?
Komi!
Go out the classroom,
walk about a hundred meters and come back!
This pancake is…
Oh…
5 MINUTES LATER
Ah.
More customers?
It's the Komi Snowball Method!
When Maid Komi walks,
she naturally draws people towards her.
Alright. That'll up our turnover rate.
Yes Maid Boss!
What's with this marketing genius…
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look over there!
-Nooo!
-Games with a maid!
-300 tan per game!
-LOOK OVER THERE!
Take a photo with a maid! 500 tan.
Walk with a maid!
30 minutes for 1,000 tan.
-Oh!
-Whoa!
And now!
Get slapped by a maid, 2,000 tan per slap!
Woo-hoo!
-Tadano! Look at this!
-STEREOTYPICAL NEW MONEY
My business is a roaring success!
Next is hand reflexology for 4,000.
Touch a thigh for 5,000. Let's go for it!
Yes, Owner!
I just can't stop smiling!
-Osana.
-Yes.
-One strike.
-Yes ma'am.
After that, they offered refunds
over the PA system.
Okay!
Now we'll advertise the maid cafe
the legal way!
This worries me.
It'll be fine!
Komi, you're tired, right?
Let's go see the other events!
Our maid outfits will be
great advertising!
Oh.
This too is a gigantic
Komi Snowball Method.
-Nobody's noticed.
-REPENTING
Look at that sign on your chest.
WELCOME TO ITAN FESTIVAL
SPIN SPIN
Komi drill!
1-4 SCARY HAUNTED HOUSE
Oh! It's a haunted house!
Let's go in!
NOD
-NOT A FAN OF SCARY THINGS
-You don't have to if you don't want to.
-Group of three coming!
-Huh?
It's pretty dark!
What's going to happen?
STARTLE
BEWARE OF BEARS
-STARTLE
-Bears?
-KONNYAKU
-SPLAT
It's just a block of konnyaku.
Here they come.
-Let's do this!
-SCARER: SHIZUKA ODOKA
Oh.
Aah! It's Komi!
What should I do?
She's the god of our school!
Is it really okay to scare Itan's icon?
I don't want Komi to hate me.
But… But scaring people is my job.
I'm not even that scary.
Komi might not even be satisfied.
Alright, I'll scare her!
I can do it!
-Now! Right now!
-KOMI AND THE GANG HAVE LEFT
EXIT
Wow, that was fun!
Um, are you alright?
Oh, they're doing Rooftop Confessions!
Let's go see!
-WHAT IS "ROOFTOP CONFESSIONS"?
-Huh? You've never heard of it?
Students go on the roof
and yell secrets or confessions of love.
Watanabe! I love you!
I don't love you back!
-I NEVER KNEW.
-You've never heard of it?
Huh.
Let's try it!
Here we go again.
There's still more to come
on Rooftop Confessions!
The next confessor is…
DECIDES TO WATCH FOR NOW
From Class 1-1!
Ren Yamai!
Oh! It's Yamai!
Yamai!
Today, I will…
confess…
my love to someone special!
Who is it?
Komi from Class 1-1! I love you!
With marriage in mind,
please go out with me!
SQUEE!
ROOFTOP CONFESSIONS
Oh Komi, shy as always!
Well then!
Next is the person
who cleanly ignored that confession!
It's Komi from Class 1-1!
Go on and promote the maid cafe!
Here we go!
Get ready for something shocking!
-She's not coming.
-Huh? Not coming?
-What's happening?
-Wait! Just believe!
-POP!
-A MAID! KOMI! AHHHH!
KOMI OUR GOD
Hey! Komi's going to say something!
-Listen to the voice of our god!
-Quiet!
QUIET TIME
Meow…
-Meow?
-TRIED TO SAY "MAID."
M-Meow…
A cat?
-And she's dressed like a maid.
-Komi…
-Cat…
-Maid…
Komi…
Komi's a cat maid?
YEAH!
Let's go see!
ABOUT TO FAINT FROM NERVES
ROOFTOP CONFESSIONS
That was great, Komi!
Our advertising plan was a huge success!
Don't push Komi too hard.
Making embarrassing memories
is what culture festivals are all about!
You're evil.
Was it fun?
Where to next?
Oh! Najimi.
We're in the meditation club.
-We're doing a demo.
-MONK WHACKS AWAY EVIL
WHACK
Your teacher said
we should make you do it.
Huh?
-Hang on! Wait!
-Demo for one!
Wait! Wait!
-REPENTING
-PRAYER HANDS
-WHACK
-AHHH
-Wow!
-So pretty!
So beautiful!
Hm? What's wrong?
-PEOPLE ARE STARING MORE THAN USUAL
-Ah, I suppose so.
You're wearing such a cute outfit.
FIDGET
EMBARASSED
-SLAP
-Ow!
W-What was that?
It's amazing how you can be
so perceptive and yet so dense.
Huh?
Since we're here,
why don't you walk around with us, Komi?
Us?
Huh? Kaede was just here…
-Hm? Oh, there she is.
-OTORI GOES AT HER OWN PACE.
Why is she in there?
There are so many fun things to do!
Yeah!
Well, let's go!
Yeah.
ITAN FESTIVAL
AKA KOMI FESTIVAL
SCHOOL-WIDE ULTRA QUIZ
HOT-BLOODED! STRIKE-OUT ZONE!
ESCAPE GAME - SURVIVE AND GET ICE CREAM
TIME REMAINING:
ART CLUB - CARICATURES
WE WILL DRAW YOU
-NO! I'M NOT WORTHY TO DRAW HER!
-STARTLE
MANGA RESEARCH CLUB
ART EXHIBITION AND FAN FICTION FOR SALE
I wonder how the class rankings are going?
Oh, now that you mention it.
There was a ranking.
It was so fun, I forgot.
In the courtyard…
it seems like a band is playing.
Oh cool! Let's go see.
H-Heavy metal?
Will Komi be alright?
Um, this band is pretty cool, hey?
Why is my heart beating like this?
This brings an end to the
Itan High School Culture Festival events.
All students, please gather in the gym.
Do you want to hear
who won the grand prize?
Yeah!
The coveted grand prize winner
of the 23rd Itan Culture Festival is…
Class 1-1 Maid Cafe Itan!
Yay!
Or it would have been.
But due to a student's
inappropriate profiteering,
the grand prize has been withdrawn.
Yeah, but.
We all prepared together,
eating rice balls,
working hard towards the grand prize.
We had fun, right?
Don't gloss over it!
Too bad we couldn't get the grand prize.
Huh?
-BUT IT WAS FUN.
-HEART SQUEEZE
What?!
That reaction's totally different
from what I got!
In the end, they're smiling together.
What a great class! 200 degrees!
Now what you've been waiting for!
The Itan Post-Festival Dance Party!
Enjoy a night of sophistication,
moving to our soulful tunes.
There is a buffet as well,
so help yourself.
Komi, will you da--
-Komi, dance wi--
-Shall we dance?
Don't cross me!
Don't worry about them.
-WANTS TO JOIN IN.
-Komi's fired up.
-BUT SHY ABOUT BEING WATCHED.
-Now she's cooled down.
Why is she looking at me?
Huh? What? Should I ask her to dance?
But…
I'm sure she's not interested
in dancing with me.
Right?
Do…
Do you… want to dance?
-Komi?
-Dancing?
-NEITHER CAN DANCE
-Who's that girl with her?
I guess we should hold hands…
Pardon me.
Are we…
-Are you dancing?
-Augh!
Let me join in!
Huh?
No way! Komi's dancing!
MAID CAFE ITAN WAS A HUGE SUCCESS!
MISSION 43
"IT'S JUST THE AFTER-PARTY."
A party to celebrate
the success of Maid Cafe Itan!
Is everyone here?
Count off!
-One!
-Two!
-Three!
-Four!
I'll count the rest.
Onward! To the land of karaoke!
-Yeah!
-So much energy.
KARAOKE
Komi, is this your first time at karaoke?
-I WENT WITH MY FAMILY ONCE.
-Huh? Did you sing?
ONLY MY MOM SINGS.
Everyone tell me your drink order!
We all have to get one,
so say what you want!
-Cola.
-Me too.
I'll have ginger ale.
Corn soup.
-Hot lemon tea.
-Oolong tea.
-Me too.
-Cafe au lait.
-Melon soda.
-Ah.
Oh, hello? Twelve colas please!
Hey!
Okay, everyone enter your songs!
-Uh, I don't know many songs.
-Alright, let's sing!
Um, uh…
-GETTING SCARED NOW THAT SHE HAS TO SING.
-You don't have to force yourself to sing.
What are you talking about?
In here, everyone has to sing a song.
If you don't hurry,
I'll fill the queue with my songs!
Take your time.
INTERLUDE 24 SECONDS
Hey!
CHOSE A SONG BUT ISN'T SURE
IF IT'S THE BEST CHOICE.
Ultra knee!
Hiii!
QUEUE
SENDING - SENT!
-Is everybody having fun?
-Cut it out, Najimi!
-I'm next!
-Get out!
KOMI QUEUED A SONG,
BUT SHE'S NOT SURE IF SHE CAN SING.
I'm next! Turn on the scoring system!
I dedicate this song to Komi.
This is how I feel.
Listen, Komi!
I…
CALCULATING…
PLEASE WAIT
-TA-DA!
-Alright!
98 POINTS
NATIONAL AVERAGE: 76.05 POINTS
-Komi was so moved that she's shaking!
-NERVOUS BECAUSE HER SONG IS UP SOON.
I'm so happy! I love her!
Next is my turn.
Heh. The time has come.
I'll take care of this.
In preparation for this day,
I learned the theme, "Endless World end"
from the hit anime,
The Lost Absolute Realm
including all the speaking parts!
My perfection will make you shiver!
I…
I nailed it.
Good one!
The reaction's not great…
Wasn't that from some anime?
-I knew my ally would understand!
-TADANO'S HAVING FLASHBACKS
-Goosebumps, right?
-SUPER NERVOUS
"NATSUI IRO"
LIME
That high, high…
"THE BEAR IN THE FOREST"
NURSERY RHYME
The other da-a-ay
"367 DAYS"
"MOTTEKE! MIKO FUKU"
FROM LOVELY STAR
Is it too squishy?
And then, finally.
KOMI'S TURN
Komi!
"HIKARE INOCHI"
MISSED HER TIMING
AH
-I can hear it!
-AUDITORY HALLUCINATION
The song you can only hear
if your heart is pure!
CALCULATING…
0 POINTS
-ABOUT TO CRY
-Huh? The machine must be broken!
What's this? I'll call the company!
"FIXED-POINT OBSERVATION"
I'm next.
PRELUDE 15 SECONDS
3 p.m. on the roof
I installed a fixed-point camera
Nobody's listening…
It… It hurts…
It's not like I care if they listen…
Still… It hurts.
I'll start my fixed-point observation
You know, searching for the criminal
Going day drinking
Was the greatest idea
My shaking hands
Have already stopped
I'm an alcoholic
Trying to see something invisible
I installed a long-range camera
Sprinkle in some noise
Several whatsits were born
You know, whatsit, what are they
I can't remember the word
The mysterious word "whatsit"
You and I thought about that
Oh yeah, a-hah
-Yay!
-I'm so embarrassed.
I'm next.
Komi, let's sing together!
You too, Tadano!
Huh, me? I just sang.
C'mon!
Let's do it!
Yay!
It's starting, Komi! Tadano!
Yeah, but…
I don't have a mic.
That's okay!
Look! It's starting!
When a person
has extreme social anxiety,
they struggle to communicate with others.
Bear in mind.
FOR KOMI
They only struggle to form connections.
-It doesn't mean that…
-TADANO, NAJIMI, AGARI, YAMAI, YADANO
-They don't want to.
-NAKANAKA, ONIGASHIMA, KISHI
CHIARAI, SONODA, SHINOBINO, ONEMINE, OTORI
THIS IS DEDICATED TO EVERYONE
WHO EVER FELT THEIR CHEST TIGHTEN
WHEN TRYING TO COMMUNICATE.
BONUS SCENE
Ready? Action!
THE END
-Komi! That's from last time!
-The next page!
It's the other one this time!
Yeah!
TO BE CONTINUED
L…
-Uh, Komi?
-Shh!
-There are only 24 seconds left!
-Just believe.
Um…
Let's…
Let's keep…
on…
being…
friends.
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka