Year 845.
With the appearance of the Colossal Titan and the Armored Titan, the wall was destroyed along with our daily lives.
And mankind was once again violated by the Titans, who had been fasting for a hundred years.
Stop it!
Mankind abandoned Wall Maria.
One fifth of the population and one third of the territory were lost.
And the human domain fell back inside Wall Rose.
The Night of the Graduation Ceremony
The Restoration of Mankind ②
Year 850
Two years after enrollment
Move it!
Run, you idiots!
What's the matter, Arlert?
You're falling behind!
Too heavy for you?
Are you going to be the only one to drop his gear?
If this was the real thing, you'd be Titan fodder by now.
Damn it!
Give it here!
At this rate, you'll fall out!
Today's training's being graded.
But helping me will reduce your score!
Give it all you've got so he doesn't notice!
Don't make me change my mind.
Reiner Braun.
Possesses both a superb physique and mental fortitude.
He also makes others feel they can rely on him.
I'd rather die than be dead weight!
Armin Arlert.
Physically weak but an intellectual prodigy.
Annie Leonhardt.
Flawless swordsmanship but has difficulty working with others.
Bertholt Huber.
Has great potential but is too passive.
Jean Kirstein.
Top of the class in three-dimensional maneuvering but has a short fuse and is quick to cause trouble.
I can't beat those two in swordsmanship.
I need to find another Titan to attack!
I'll be the one to enlist in the Military Police!
Thanks, Jean!
Following you was the right decision, after all!
Yahoo!
Sasha Blouse.
Possesses an unusually keen perception but is ill-suited for organized combat.
Connie Springer.
Adept at precise maneuvering but not exactly the brightest.
They're coming!
Damn it! I still can't cut it as deep as Mikasa!
Mikasa Ackermann.
A complete master in every area.
Assessed to have unprecedented talent.
Eren Jäger.
Doesn't have any unique talent, but achieves great results through sheer effort.
Furthermore, he possesses a stronger determination than anyone here.
Ouch!
Sorry. I'm bad at holding back.
It's your turn to attack.
What's the matter?
What's with this training?
Why would soldiers be fighting other humans?
And trying to deal with our prey bare-handed is just stupid.
That would be irresponsible.
We're soldiers.
There are times when we shouldn't run, no matter how bad the situation is.
No matter who we're up against, we must master everything from artillery to hand-to-hand combat.
That's our responsibility as soldiers.
By the way, check that out.
Ah, Annie, huh?
She's good at skipping training without the instructor noticing.
All right, Eren!
Let's teach her how to take training seriously.
We'll show her how a true soldier should act.
Huh?
You don't like the instructor's headbutts, do you?
If you don't want to get any shorter, you should remember why you're here and train seriously.
Come on, what are you doing?
She's really pissed.
She always looks scary, but her angry face really gives me the chills.
Come on. You're up, Eren!
Me?
Annie, you know that we're just training, right?
Here I go!
What? She kicked my leg.
Can I go now?
Not yet!
The goal is to disarm the opponent.
W-Wait, Annie!
There's a proper way to do it!
Here!
Now it's your turn to attack me.
N-No... I...
Do it, Reiner.
You wanted to teach her what it means to be a soldier, right?
Yeah, there are times when a soldier cannot retreat.
And this is one of them!
You're really good at this.
Did someone teach you those techniques?
My father.
So he taught you how to—
It doesn't matter.
This is meaningless.
You mean the training?
Hand-to-hand combat doesn't count toward our grades.
People don't normally take it seriously.
After all, only the top ten get to enlist in the Military Police and live in the inner district.
The only ones taking it seriously are naive people like you and idiots like them.
Shit! The instructor!
For some unearthly reason, the better you are at opposing
the Titans, the farther you are distanced from them.
Why do you think it's come to this farce?
I have no idea.
I guess that's human nature.
Anyway, I'm not stupid enough to be able to amuse myself by playing soldier in this ridiculous world.
Apparently, you don't value warriors at all.
I was so concentrated on becoming strong that I never noticed...
such a simple contradiction.
They're all training to kill Titans in order to distance themselves from them.
Well, it's normal.
Before the destruction of Wall Maria, three-dimensional maneuvering
was considered only necessary for the few who would join the Recon Corps.
So the techniques have been in decline.
You have to have a strong first thrust
Because of that...
and then use the inertia to waste less gas.
You make it sound simple, but...
Well, yeah. Not just anyone can pull it off.
But there's no harm keeping it in mind.
That is if you want to join the Military Police.
Ah, it'd be great if I managed to make it.
What greater honor could you ask for than working near the king?
Hey, Marco!
Stop beating around the bush and just say it outright!
You want to enlist in the Military Police because of the safe and cozy life awaiting you in the inner district.
No! I'm not like that!
You think life in the inner district is cozy?
This here was an inner district five years ago too.
What are you trying to say, Eren?
Jean, it's not like you need to worry about getting into the inner district
since you already live quite the cozy life inside your head.
Why, you!
Don't you think it's strange?
They're having people hone their Titan-killing skills in order to be distanced from the Titans.
What are you trying to say?
That works just fine for me.
You piece of shit!
Shut up! That's reality!
Stop it, Eren!
Stop!
Don't fuck with me, bastard!
Let go or you'll tear my shirt!
Who cares about your clothes?! I'm jealous!
Huh? What are you talking about?!
That's right. So far, he's only seen my feelings get the better of me.
But I'm different now.
I'll use the techniques I've learned to take control of the situation.
What did you just do?!
I used the hand-to-hand combat skills I painfully learned while you were slacking off.
You're saying that kicking back with smug self-satisfaction is how we're supposed to live?
And you call yourself a soldier?
I just heard a loud crash.
Who wants to explain what happened?
It was Sasha breaking wind.
You again...
Learn some self-control already!
And so, 218 trainees reached graduation.
Offer your hearts!
You who have today graduated the military training program have three choices:
the Border Guard that mans the walls which protect us,
the Recon Corps filled with those prepared to give their lives fighting the Titans for territory,
or the Military Police that serves directly under the king keeping civil order.
Of course, only the top ten students have the right to enlist in the Military Police.
I've finally made it!
Now it's our turn to devour the Titans!
104th Military Training Class Top Ten Trainees ①
Currently Disclosable Information
10th
Christa Lenz
9th
Sasha Blouse
8th
Connie Springer
7th
Marco Bott
6th
Jean Kirstein
104th Military Training Class Top Ten Trainees ②
Currently Disclosable Information
4th
Annie Leonhardt
5th
Eren Jäger
3rd - Bertholt Huber
2nd - Reiner Braun
Top Trainee
Mikasa Ackermann
Yeah! I made it into the Military Police!
Now I'll never have to worry about food again!
Why am I lower than Eren?!
Damn it!
Are you seriously not enlisting in the Military Police, Eren?!
You made it into the top ten, man!
I made my decision long ago.
I didn't train so I can live a cozy life in the inner district.
I trained to fight Titans.
We can't win!
It's not like you don't know how many tens of thousands were eaten.
We lost one fifth of the population and we now know:
mankind cannot defeat the Titans.
And?
You'll just give up because you don't think we can win?
Well...
It's true that we've always been beaten.
But that's because we didn't know enough about them.
Going against them with numbers is meaningless.
We were beaten, but the information we got from the fight will surely lead us to new hope!
Are we going to throw away the battle techniques learned through the sacrifices of hundreds of thousands of people
and sit still while the Titans eat us?
You've got to be kidding!
I'll slaughter every single Titan and escape from these confining walls!
That's my dream!
Mankind hasn't been defeated yet!
Wait, Eren!
Go outside the walls if you're so eager to die!
Nothing will stop me from joining the Military Police!
Eren, that dream you were talking about...
Yeah. I got it from you.
Going outside the walls instead of staying inside.
I'll join the Recon Corps!
Are you serious, Armin?!
You're the top in academics. You shouldn't waste that!
I'll die before I slow you down!
I'll choose the Recon Corps too.
Hey! You're the top of the class!
Choose the Military Police!
If you join the Military Police, so will I.
But if you join the Recon Corps, then so will I.
You'd die too quickly without me around.
I never asked you to take care of me.
I don't want to lose any more family.
Here they are!
The main force of the Recon Corps!
Captain Irvin! Go kick some Titan ass!
Look! It's Corporal Rivaille!
They say he's as powerful as an entire brigade!
I can't stand this.
This is completely different from five years ago.
People have restored faith in the Recon Corps.
Everyone's in high spirits.
There haven't been any problems for five years now.
And now we have the improved cannons.
The Colossal Titans haven't shown up either.
You're right.
What's with that relaxed attitude, you stupid newlyweds?!
Y-You think we'd make a good couple?
Don't marry us so quickly, Eren.
Hey, you guys!
Mr. Hanneth!
I heard you graduated yesterday.
And you were just a bunch of brats a few years ago.
You yourself were just a drunkard, but now you're a military engineers' captain.
Oh, you.
I'm sorry that I couldn't save your mother.
It wasn't your fault.
We're no longer that ignorant.
We won't allow such horrible things to happen again.
We'll defeat the Titans.
I wonder if I should be happy that he's all grown up.
Don't die!
What? You're choosing the Recon Corps?
Connie! You were so hyped about the Military Police.
Yeah, I was.
But you know...
I guess your speech yesterday had an effect.
Shut up!
I decided it myself!
You don't need to be embarrassed about it.
It's not just you.
Thomas...
You too?
Um, guys...
I got some meat from the officers' food pantry.
Sasha! Do you want to get thrown in the brig?!
You really are stupid!
Stupidity is scary!
I'll split it with you guys when we get off.
We'll slice it and make sandwiches.
Put it back!
Yeah! Meat is really expensive since our territory shrunk.
Don't worry!
When we get our land back, we'll have more cattle and sheep again.
I'll have some of that meat!
Save some for me too!
I'll have some too, of course!
Guys...
What are you standing around for, Eren?
They might find us out if we don't get back to work.
There's still time left before lunch.
It's been five years.
Mankind has finally begun to regain its dignity.
We can win!
Mankind's counterattack will begin now!
That's hot!
What is this?
Samuel!
Sasha!
Don't move!
That was close!
The wall's...
been destroyed...
Not again! The Titans have broken through again!
I'm gonna kill them all!
Every last one of them!
4th Cannon Maintenance Squad!
Prepare for battle!
Target that Colossal Titan!
This is our chance! Don't let it slip by!
Hey! It's been five years.
Preview
Hell has opened its gates once again.
Without a chance to catch their breaths, soldiers are devoured by the Titans.
In the midst of that, Eren saves Armin from the brink of death.
The First Battle
The Defense of Trost ①