Year 850 in the Trost District.
The sight of Eren Jäger invoking a mysterious Titan power filled the hearts of his fellow soldiers with dread.
I-I'm human!
He's not an enemy of humanity!
For the glory of mankind!
In what little time I have before my death,
I advise that we make tactical use of his strength!
Eren's group, which could do nothing to avoid their own execution,
was saved by Dot Pixis, the chief commander of the southern region.
I think it's best to hear the boy out.
Idol
The Defense of Trost ⑦
I'll do it!
I don't know if I can plug that hole or not.
But I'll do it!
Well said!
You're a real man!
I'll call my staff officers!
We need to discuss the specifics!
But...
That was just something I came up with on the spot.
Isn't it a bit rash to put it into action so quickly?
I thought so at first too, but there's no sense in hesitating.
Commander Pixis is probably trying to see something that we can't.
Something we can't see?
Also, there is a much more fundamental problem than whether we put your plan into action or not.
The commander has assessed the situation correctly.
What do you mean?
The Titans are not our only enemies.
Time is against us.
I'll need your help here, young soldiers.
An operation to retake the Trost District?!
They can't be serious!
We have no way to seal the hole in the gate!
What the hell are the higher-ups thinking?!
Going into the Trost District now would be suicide!
If we can't seal that hole, our only option is to defend Wall Rose's gate.
Damn it! Are they that desperate for glory?!
Going back to that hell...
No! I don't want to die!
I want to see my family!
Come on, Tazz! Keep it down!
You there! I heard that!
Do you intend to abandon your post?!
That's right!
There's no reason to go through with this mass suicide mission!
How dare you belittle mankind?!
Where's your discipline?!
I have the authority to execute you on the spot!
All right, then!
That's a hundred times better than being eaten alive by a Titan!
Stop it. Tazz!
Get off! Let go of me!
I'm not gonna let you send me back out there!
Did you hear that?
Can you really blame him under these circumstances?
Hey, should we mutiny too?
I'd at least like to choose how I die.
Hey, you two!
I-I was joking!
Do it!
What?
Make it flashy with as many people as possible!
Many of us in the Border Guard are discontent.
We'll take advantage of the chaos and get out of here!
And where would you go?
I'll go see my daughter!
This wall is about to be breached anyway.
It's said that before the world was ruled by the Titans,
humans of various tribes with different ideals used to kill each other in unending wars.
And then someone said this:
"If a powerful non-human threat were to appear, mankind would cease all conflicts and unite."
What do you think about that?
I hadn't heard that before.
But I'd say that's too idealistic.
It makes me yawn.
I see you have an unconventional view of things, just like me.
Even now that we're cornered by this powerful threat,
I wouldn't say that we've really come together.
Yes, but we must do that soon.
Otherwise, it'll be hard to fight.
Eren?!
You're safe.
Are you telling me to get back to my duties?!
What kind of attitude is that toward a superior officer?
If he's that calm, Mikasa and Armin must also be all right.
But why is Eren walking with the commander?
Want some?
Yes, please.
Kill me!
If you're going to execute me, get on with it!
Come on, let's do it!
Attention!
I'm going to brief you on the operation to retake the Trost District!
The objective of this operation is to seal the hole left in the destroyed gate.
Seal it?
How in the world?
Let me first introduce you to the man who is going to seal the hole.
This is Cadet Eren Jäger.
E-Eren?!
He is the successful result of top-secret Titan transformation experiments we've conducted on humans.
He is able to create a Titan body and control it at will!
Hey, it's not just because I'm dumb that I don't understand what the commander's saying, right?
Shut up, stupid. I'm listening.
After transforming into a Titan, he will carry the giant rock near the front gate and seal the hole with it!
Your mission is to protect him from other Titans while he carries that rock!
There's no need to fight the Titans?
F-Forgive me.
I know it's not my place to speak as a mere cadet.
Don't worry about it. Let's hear your plan.
Y-Yes, sir.
The Titans are drawn toward areas with more people.
We can place a lot of people on the wall and lure them there.
That way we can keep most of them away from Eren without having to engage them directly.
And we can eliminate the Titans we've lured in by using the cannons without risking any casualties.
Still, we can't leave Eren unprotected.
We should send a small elite squad with him.
We can't really avoid fighting the Titans that come in through the hole.
So we'll have to rely on the elite squad's ability to deal with them.
All right, that sounds good.
Let's rework the plan based on that.
The problem with this plan is that it assumes Eren can carry the rock and seal the hole.
But since we still have no definitive proof that he can, I'm hesitant about it.
Indeed, risking the lives of so many people using a plan based on uncertainties is worrisome.
But I can understand why Commander Pixis is doing it.
Yes. Our time is limited.
As we speak, more Titans continue to enter the district.
The more Titans that get inside, the less likely it is for the recapture operation to succeed.
And at the same time, the chance of Wall Rose being breached is rising.
There is one more thing to consider.
There is a limit to how far you can push people using fear.
Carrying that huge rock?
That's...
Have we finally learned how to control the Titans?
Lies!
Who would risk their life on such nonsense?!
What the hell do you think we are?
We're not just some disposable swords!
Turning people into weapons?!
It's an obvious lie!
What do they take us for?
They want us to die here today!
I'm leaving!
I'm leaving too!
Me too!
I'm out too!
Stop!
You piece of shit! This is a capital offense!
I'll spend the rest of mankind's last moments with my family!
This is getting out of control.
Yeah, if we don't do something, the discipline will collapse.
I hope you're prepared to die, you traitors!
I'll cut each one of you down where you stand!
This is an order!
I exempt anyone who decides to leave now.
Once you have lost to your fear of the Titans, you cannot hope to fight them!
Those among you who have succumbed to that fear are free to leave!
And those who wish that same fear upon their parents, siblings, and loved ones are free to leave as well.
Daddy!
I can't let that happen.
My daughter is...
my last hope.
Let me tell you something about what happened four years ago.
It's about the operation to recapture Wall Maria.
You probably already know this without me saying, but...
They only called it a recapture operation to make it sound good.
It was merely the government reducing the number of mouths to feed during the food shortage.
No one is admitting to it
because forcing them out is the only reason we managed to survive inside these narrow walls.
All of mankind, myself included, bears that sin!
Because the people who used to live within Wall Maria were the minority, a conflict did not arise.
But this time would be different.
If Wall Rose is breached, reducing the mouths to feed by a fifth will not be enough!
We can only support half our current population within Wall Sina.
If mankind falls, it will not be to the Titans!
Humans will kill each other!
We must not die behind a wall other than this one!
I ask you to die here!
I don't know if I can carry the rock with my Titan power.
But I know the role I must play.
It may not be real.
But I have to make it work, no matter what.
I have to become...
everyone's hope!
Currently Disclosable Information
Three-Dimensional Maneuver Gear Body Weight Shifting Equipment ①
The technique of making minute shifts in the user's weight by using
tightly strapped belts across the entire body is necessary for three-dimensional
maneuvering.
Three-Dimensional Maneuver Gear Body Weight Shifting Equipment ①
The technique of making minute shifts in the user's weight by using
tightly strapped belts across the entire body is necessary for three-dimensional
maneuvering.
Currently Disclosable Information
Three-Dimensional Maneuver Gear Body Weight Shifting Equipment ②
Because the equipment's purpose is to provide high-speed,
three-dimensional mobility, its weight has been optimized as much
as possible.
Three-Dimensional Maneuver Gear Body Weight Shifting Equipment ②
Because the equipment's purpose is to provide high-speed,
three-dimensional mobility, its weight has been optimized as much
as possible.
I see you're all here.
You three have one mission.
You must escort Eren Jäger and eliminate any threats that come up during the operation.
This is a difficult mission and the most dangerous role to play in this operation.
It would not be an exaggeration to say that mankind's fate rests on your shoulders.
Commander, may I ask something?
What is it?
Can this human weapon really perform as planned?
Don't go there, Rico!
I'm sure you have your doubts as well.
Commander, this plan depends on an extremely uncertain variable that is Eren Jäger.
If he can't execute his part, many soldiers will die for nothing.
Now that's a problem.
Do you like losing to the Titans that much?
I myself don't like it at all.
I really hate to lose.
But unfortunately, we've been losing since we were born.
I want a victory over the Titans.
I want to beat those blockheads no matter what.
Th-That's what we want too!
Then we have no choice but to bet on him.
Because that extremely uncertain variable is our only chance to beat the Titans.
Commander, it's time to begin the decoy operation.
All right.
Ian Dietrich.
Rico Brzenska.
Mitabi Jarnach.
You're the elite of the elite in the Border Guard.
I leave the fate of mankind in your hands.
Yes, sir!
Ian, you'll take charge.
I entrust you with the decision making during the mission.
Me? Are you sure?
I have no objections.
Me neither.
But I'm not skilled enough.
Don't worry.
You're a man who knows his liquor.
You can tell the good stuff from cheap booze.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry, Eren.
In the end, you have to bear all the responsibility.
I told you already.
You have the ability to determine the right course of action.
I trust in that.
Eren, I really should—
Don't say that you want to come with me!
You were attached to the decoy unit.
But I can't leave you alone.
If you're alone again, you'll—
Stop that already!
I'm not your little brother or your son!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Ackermann!
I want you in the elite squad protecting Jäger.
We need your skills.
Let's go!
We're commencing the operation!
Later, Armin.
Don't die.
All right. You too.
They said you're a top-secret human weapon.
If you can seal that hole, I'll protect you at any cost, no matter what you are.
I'm counting on you!
Yes, sir!
Eren, do you feel well enough to go through with this?
Yeah.
Eren?
I said I'm fine.
I've already somewhat recovered from when we were surrounded.
Stop playing house, Jäger!
I wasn't!
I can't believe we have to wager mankind's fate on a spoiled brat like you.
Cut that out!
We're almost at the rock.
There are no Titans in sight for the moment.
It looks like the decoy plan is going well.
Listen up!
Just lead them to the corner of the wall!
Avoid engaging in combat!
Let me tell you this, Jäger.
Many soldiers will die in this operation.
They'll die for you.
They're our peers, the soldiers who were there before us and the soldiers who came after us.
Of course, as soldiers, they're prepared to give their lives.
But they're not worthless pawns.
Wait!
Not yet!
Wait for it!
Withdraw!
They have names, families, and hearts.
Alyosha.
Dominic.
Finné.
Isabel.
Ludwig.
Martina.
Kid.
Hans.
Each one is a flesh-and-blood human.
I've even eaten food from the same pot with some of them as a cadet.
Many of them will probably die for you today.
You have a responsibility to not let them die in vain.
No matter what happens,
keep that in your spoiled mind.
And fulfill that responsibility even if it's the last thing you do.
Yes, ma'am!
I'll do it!
I'll make this work no matter what!
Ever since the Titans appeared, mankind has never had a victory against them.
The more the Titans advance, the more mankind withdraws, giving up territory.
But when this operation succeeds, mankind will have managed to take back territory for the first time!
This is it!
Let's go!
And that will be the moment when mankind obtains its first victory over the Titans!
Green smoke signal confirmed.
The elite squad has begun the operation.
This may be incredibly small compared to what mankind has lost so far.
But for mankind, that small step constitutes a great advance!
Thinking in terms of human proportions, he wouldn't be able to lift that rock.
But I'm sure Eren has the strength to lead us.
Eren?
Preview
The operation to retake the Trost District has begun.
As many soldiers lose their lives,
Eren, who has transformed into a Titan, loses control and destroys his own escape route.
But just when it seems like the plan has failed...
Wound
The Defense of Trost ⑧