Hey, why you stayed out all night?
Yeah.
You even left this kind of letter!
We absolutely disagree!
Darkness, Darkness!
-Please go back.
-Darkness!
-The young lady says she is not going to see anyone.
This thing came loose from your pocket.
That's right, as long as you let us in…
I-I don't need this!
What does it mean
that you write this kind of letter?
We want an explanation from you!
Darkness, Darkness!
-G-Guards!
-Darkness!
-Quick, get the guards!
We will get lunch ready and wait for you!
Come back before that!
(Konosuba Season 3)
(Episode 9: Preaching to the Runaway Girl)
She's a pain in the ass.
Don't care, don't care!
I don't care about her anymore!
Yes, you say that,
but are not you still
making things for Darkness?
That is not at all how it is.
I only want to make my life easier
and scam a significant sum of money.
All right, all right.
Listen.
The advice of the demon
is generally not a good one.
(Konosuba)
All I want to do is put off work!
Hey, I'll give you pocket money.
Can you please go back to the mansion?
I should totally get to
pick a new team member.
To actually ditch the buddies
who went through good times and bad,
you are a devil.
Devil.
I am not.
Darkness is the one who wants us
to pick a new team member.
I see.
All three of us have
zero stamina, like, at all!
(Konosuba)
We need a shield role!
I was just introducing myself.
Don't reveal your cards!
I'm Megumin,
the top magician in Axel
who controls explosion magic!
In Axel,
I go by the nickname
"crazy explosive girl"!
Is she the one they are rumored about?
I'm sorry!
I can't handle this job!
Please find someone else!
I had a tough time
getting everyone interested,
but look at what you have done!
You screamed,
and now everyone's too scared
to even look at us.
Can't be helped.
Let's just go back for today.
You totally did that on purpose, right?
You are keeping everyone away on purpose--
Kazuma!
What is up? You seem super flustered.
Something bad happened,
can you help me out?
This dude previously went off to attack
a water snake all by himself before,
and now he is freaking out like this.
It is like a pretty big deal.
Megumin, I will be out for a sec.
(Konosuba)
Rin have a boyfriend?
Yeah.
I am really concerned
because my close friend
has been tricked by some random guy.
R-Right.
You know, Rin has been so difficult
to get in touch with lately.
It has been bothering me,
so I ended up spending
the whole day following her.
And guess what? I found out she went to
a motel with an unknown man.
That's…
That's stalk--
I was just sorta worried about my buddy!
Please, help me out!
I don't think that's a good idea…
Alright.
You're so nice, Kazuma.
Here, these are for you.
Here it is.
The jerk who tricked Rin is right here.
So, you are not planning
on going in straight, huh?
How long do you think
I have been an adventurer?
If I do not watch my back and be smart,
I will not make it
in this gig for much longer.
The walls are super thin,
so we gotta be careful.
That's…
That's stalk--
Miss Rin.
Now that I have fallen for you,
there is nothing I can do.
C-Calm down.
How can a noble like you
fall for an adventurer?
I understand that
our statuses may not align…
But at least…
At least let me take a photo
with this magic camera.
Calm down.
Please calm down!
Keep your reason!
I see.
He knows they can't be together,
so he hopes to at least snap a photo?
He is not, like, a bad person or anything.
I'd like to see something sensational.
Like this! More sensational!
He's a piece of shit!
I am going to pummel him.
Hey, wait, don't go!
Calm down.
Alright, just clean your heart first.
Let's head downstairs
and grab a cup of tea.
-Calm down, please!
-Please
(Konosuba)
I'd like to see something sensational!
Really?
Unforgivable.
This jerk!
I am going to screw it up!
Hey, if you mess up the room…
Ouch.
Kazuma.
Yes?
Just grab that camera over there
and snap a pic of me.
I want to fill up all the photo film
with my nudity
and leave him with some serious
long-term psychological scars.
Don't you run away.
(Konosuba)
Of course.
Very good, Dust.
That's right.
So, how many pics did we actually snap?
I stand on the table,
looking down at Dust,
and roll around on the ground,
shooting him fiercely from all angles.
Good!
Now, give it a cool vibe.
Spread your legs. Squat low.
Yes, that's right.
Go on!
So, what are you doing?
Sorry.
I totally got hooked on taking photos.
You had me freaking out for no reason.
Feel free to handle that jerk.
Okay, Kazuma.
Let's go.
Nah, letting them both
stay together is kinda…
Enough, hurry up.
I was not expecting to see you in my room.
What? Got any issues with that?
Right.
How about we have a candid and
honest conversation, just between us guys?
Be prepared.
Hey, Rin.
We should probably stop them.
In this rate…
I have put in a lot of effort, you know.
Yeah, a lot.
But he showed up in the room
dressed that way in the end.
It is like a fool just walking right
into the trap, ya know?
I could not even save him, man.
I am really touched.
I never saw it coming…
You would be completely wrong
if you assumed that
I would be scared just
because you are a noble.
I gotta say, I am pretty used to dealing
with royal families and nobles.
Used to…
So there really is a god.
I am glad I joined the order.
Listen.
There are two men here.
Nothing more than that!
Wha--
Forget about the status.
Today is so freaking awesome!
I appreciate you very much,
Lady Aqua.
Actually,
that noble dude is into Dust.
What'd you just say?
That noble
told me he likes Dust,
and he came to talk to me about it.
I politely told him that
there is probably no chance,
but he said he hopes
to get a photo of Dust, at least.
So this means, Dust…
Today, nothing went down.
R-Right.
Speaking of nobles…
Stop it!
I am so over this whole nobles thing!
No, no, it's not that.
I'm talking about Lalatina.
Darkness?
Everyone is buzzing about it -
the young lady from the Dustiness family
is about to tie the knot with Aldarp.
Huh?
Tell me more.
Marriage?
This is really annoying.
Then it will totally match up
with the demon's fortune-telling.
Do you really believe it?
I think Vanir talks about
a lot of stuff in a vague way,
but anything about that lord
is a whole different story.
We gotta track down Darkness
and ask for some clarification!
Right, right?
Really!
That guy has been a real pain
in the butt since forever.
Since Rin told us about this,
I don't have any other option.
Don't have any other option.
So, Aqua, I am counting on you.
Leave it to me.
Powered.
Speed Gain.
Resist Magic.
Versatile Entertainer.
What's the last one for?
Magic that transforms one
into a master of talents.
It hurts!
-Are you going by yourself?
-Don't pull so hard, okay?
-Since I have got this lurk skill,
-Ouch!
it would be way easier for me
to succeed if I went alone.
Just wait for me in the mansion.
You must do a good job.
I'll be back shortly.
That's strange.
Nothing is going on, Norris.
Hey, let us head to the kitchen downstairs
and fix us a late-night snack.
I think I heard something.
Alright.
Where's Darkness?
That's right, the kitchen…
If Darkness orders a late-night snack,
I could just go to her room
with the delivered meal.
It does not really seem doable.
I wish I could imitate voices…
My name is Norris.
I was just trying.
Can a master of talents truly
accomplish something like this?
Mr. Kazuma is amazing.
Hold me.
This is so useful.
This is extremely useful.
Once I am back, I gotta say sorry to Aqua.
I have got some food for you.
I don't think I ordered anything.
But Mr. Norris said…
Sorry.
Just give me a break, okay?
Young lady.
A man named Satou Kazuma
is coming in the middle of the night…
I already told you,
no need to tell me these.
He actually comes at this hour.
Geez.
But, young lady,
that Kazuma man told me
that if I do not tell you,
he will tell everyone in the guild
your embarrassing secret.
That guy really is…
Tell him to do as he likes.
I am not going to go to
the guild again, anyway.
But, young lady,
that guy told me
that you have abs now,
and that made him uneasy.
He thinks you should eat less protein.
Wha…
He also said you would
put on a cute dress,
look at yourself in the mirror,
and then laugh to yourself.
He wants us to get you such cute clothes.
T-Those are lies.
Don't let him fool you.
But he said something
even more mind-blowing.
Can I say it?
Let's hear it.
You can't hold on
your curvy body all the time,
every night…
Break in!
I have been boosted by some support magic,
so I will not easily
lose to your strength.
D-Don't get me wrong.
I just want to ask some questions.
Hey!
Don't close your eyes
like you are giving up!
Don't close your eyes.
Don't close your eyes!
Listen.
I'm letting go of you now.
Don't scream, okay?
Okay.
Then, I'm going to let go.
Thief!
You set me up!
Ugh, I have been way too careless!
L-Lady Lalatina!
How dare you set me up?
What happened?
I'll open the door right away!
Don't!
I can't be seen in this outfit right now.
I was playing this really intense game
and I couldn't help but scream
because it was so exciting!
Is it really late at night to play games?
It is a game that adults
can play by themselves.
Please, don't make me say it.
It is really embarrassing.
Y-Young lady.
-What?
-Seriously?
So, you are saying you want to
make sure I am safe,
but you are actually interested
in seeing my less refined side, huh?
You are quite the pervert!
What's wrong with you?
I-It's nothing!
I totally forgot to turn off
that erotic, magical toy!
I-It's going to break!
Things are about to get really weird!
If this keeps going like this,
it is going to break!
S-Sorry to interrupt!
Geez.
From tomorrow on, people at home
will start calling me
a perverted young lady.
You just thought that might
not be a bad idea, right?
(Konosuba)
Not that I thought.
That is exactly what you thought.
In debt?
That's right.
So basically, the nobleman's daughter
has to marry the person who lent us money.
That is all there is to it.
You are familiar with my interests
and hobbies, aren't you?
I guess the guy will be
starving and thirsty,
craving my body.
It's really exciting.
Idiot.
Why do you look so lonely,
if that is the case?
That's why you are hoping we can
take on the water snake on our own?
I ended up getting a bunch of people
involved and interfering.
How much is the debt?
For the insufficient money…
Don't say you're going to pay, Kazuma.
I am a noble.
How can I allow the regular folks,
whom I am supposed to look out for,
to use the money they earn
from their hard work
to pay off my debt?
If that is the situation,
I would rather just sell myself.
I would rather have
my body taken away by that lord.
Hey, Kazuma.
Yes?
How about we…
Darkness…
You…
You really do have abs.
(Konosuba)
Sorry, it's my fault!
I really can't handle this atmosphere!
There are definitely times
when I get really angry.
How dare you do this to a woman
who's made up her mind…
I'm going to kill you!
What?
You are really into me, huh?
Just say it straight up, young lady!
I will not like someone like you, dummy!
It is so frustrating, you know?
And stop calling me young lady!
Young lady, I'm going to open the door!
Don't!
Lalatina is totally naked at the moment!
-You can't look!
-Totally…
My deepest apologies!
Don't use my voice to say that!
Hey, there's an intruder!
He is got this skill
where he can imitate my voice.
Yes, we'll go in right away!
Damn it.
Create Earth.
Everyone, close your eyes!
Wind Breath.
(Konosuba)
Lurk.
We must not allow him to get away!
Kazuma!
If you will only step out now
and take ten full punches from me,
I will let you go.
You better believe I will not
give you much of a pass
if I track you down.
This is bad. Things are looking bleak.
Let's go back.
Okay.
All I have to do
is jump out of the window…
Is anybody there?
It's you.
Why did you come here
in the middle of the night?
W-Well.
I see.
It looks like my daughter
has found an amazing companion.
A true confidant
of the kingdom, I must say.
He totally gets why I came here.
I'm sorry to be a bother
when you're not feeling well.
Your daughter is really mad.
Can you go and convince her?
I see.
My daughter has been feeling
really down lately,
and now she is getting so angry.
This is not funny at all.
I heard you have debts.
I honestly don't think
you would borrow money
from someone like that.
You are pretty smart, Kazuma, aren't you?
I think I should trust you
with my daughter.
What?
I'm sorry.
Can you just take her
and run away somewhere else?
I was just asking you about the debt.
Why are you suggesting
that I elope with your daughter?
I refuse.
I absolutely refuse.
It's your daughter who is chasing me.
That is why I have run away to this room.
Kazuma.
Can you please not ask why?
Don't worry.
I will just sell this mansion
after you run away with my daughter…
Are you feeling unwell?
Our team has this amazing
Arch Priest who is really great
at healing magic.
No, healing magic can't cure illness,
and it can't resurrect someone
who has died from a disease, either.
When someone gets sick, it's like
they are getting closer to their end.
If you are nearing the end,
don't expect a miracle from God.
There is
no need for that face.
Kazuma!
Come out!
I will definitely make you
regret imitating my voice!
This time I must…
Okay? I am trusting you with her.
I'm going to kill you!
Oh, I really don't want that.
Gotcha!
So, how do you plan on compensating me?
Hey, please be quiet!
Shut up!
The person I am worried about
hurt my image so badly
in such a short time.
What I just said is totally true!
How could it be true?
Forget about the debt.
Let's all run away together!
Aqua and Megumin
will not sit on their hands
if I return alone.
Megumin might just blow up
the wedding ceremony too!
Go ahead and give it a shot
if you are up for it!
Everyone's going to
be sentenced to hanging!
Make sure to look after them for me!
You are such an inflexible
and stubborn woman!
I won't run away.
If I run away,
someone is going to
get implicated for sure.
Forget it, do as you please!
If you need me to save you,
just come over to the mansion,
say sorry, and tell me,
"I need Lord Kazuma's rescue."
So hard…
A-Are you okay, Kazuma?
You should be the one saying,
"Sorry, and please save me."
I can provide medical treatment.
D-Damn it.
I will not save you until you come
to me crying and begging, no doubt!
Idiot, idiot!
It hurts!
It not hurts, idiot!
Aqua!
Heal me.
(Episode 10: Wishes
for the Stubborn Bride)
I am Beldia,
a leader of the Devil King's army.
On behalf of the entire Devil King's Army,
I congratulate
Lalatina Ford Dustiness.