On that day, mankind remembered...
The fear of oppression under them,
and the humiliation of being caged like birds.
All hands, prepare for battle!
The target is alone!
Eliminate it at all costs, and make this
mankind's first base on the outside!
Approaching target!
Split up into five groups, just like in training!
My group will act as the decoys!
Assault squads, switch to
three-dimensional maneuvers!
We'll attack simultaneously from every direction!
Behold the power of mankind!
Sie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
und wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
fumareta hana no namae mo shirazu ni
Ignorant of the trampled flower's name,
chi ni ochita tori wa kaze wo machiwabiru
the bird that fell to the earth waits impatiently for the wind.
inotta tokoro de nanimo kawaranai
Even if you pray, nothing will be changed.
ima wo kaeru no wa tatakau kakugo da
But that which can alter the present is the resolution to fight.
shikabane fumikoete
Trampling over corpses,
susumu ishi wo warau buta yo
swine who mock the will to advance.
kachiku no annei
Peace of the cattle,
kyogi no hanei
and the prosperity of deception.
shiseru garou no jiyuu wo
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
torawareta kutsujoku wa hangeki no koushi da
Our caged humiliation signals the start of our retaliation.
jouheki no sono kanata emono wo hofuru Jäger
Beyond the ramparts, we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
hotobashiru shoudou ni sono mi wo yaki nagara
As these surging urges burn away our bodies,
tasogare ni hi wo ugatsu guren no yumiya
we ignite the dusk with a crimson bow and arrow.
und wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
To You, 2000 Years Later
————— The Fall of Shiganshina Part    —————
①
Huh? Mikasa?
Let's start heading back.
Why am I here?
You were sleeping that soundly?
No, it just feels like I was
having a really long dream.
What was it again?
I don't remember a thing.
Eren? Why are you crying?
Year 845 Shiganshina District
Listen up!
The walls were made with the wisdom of God!
The walls are the works of God!
No matter the person,
none may desecrate the walls!
Don't tell anyone.
About me crying.
I won't.
But for you to start crying for no reason...
Why not ask Uncle to take a look at you?
Don't be stupid!
As if I could tell Dad.
What're you crying over, Eren?
Hannes-san.
Did you get scolded by Mikasa?
Huh? What makes you think I'd cry?
You reek of booze!
Come on, it's cool.
You're drinking again?
Why don't you two join us?
Well, uh...
What about work?
Ah, we're wall guards today.
Having been here all day, hunger and
thirst were bound to catch up to us.
The fact that alcohol happened to be
in our drinks is but a trivial matter.
But will you be able to fight when you need to?
And when would that be?
Isn't that obvious?! When they break
down the wall and storm the city!
Oh, damn.
Hey, Eren, don't start yelling so suddenly.
You're real lively, doctor's son.
If they ever manage to do that,
you bet we'll get the job done.
Then again, it's been nothing but
peace and quiet these past 100 years.
Even so, my dad said it's the most dangerous
when everyone lets their guard down like that!
Dr. Jaeger, huh?
Come to think of it, Doc was the one
who saved this town from an epidemic,
and we're all greatly indebted to him.
However, they're an entirely different matter.
If you're a soldier, there'll be
times when you see them
wandering outside while reinforcing the wall.
Still, I can't imagine them being able to do
anything about this fifty-meter-tall wall.
W-Wait... So you're saying you don't even have
the resolve to fight them to begin with?
Pretty much.
Seriously?!
Quit calling yourselves the
"Stationed Army Corps",
and go by "Wall Construction Corps" instead!
That doesn't sound half bad.
But you know, Eren, to see soldiers
working wouldn't bode well for us all.
It's when we're criticized by people who call us
useless freeloaders that everyone's living in peace.
Even if we're confined within these walls,
we can keep on living, just eating and sleeping.
But... That would be as if...
As if we're just cattle.
What a valiant little brat!
Even though he can't do anything
himself, right, Hannes?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Hey, Eren!
What a queer kid.
Don't tell me...
Does he want to join the Survey Corps?
Eren, you should give up on
joining the Survey Corps.
What? You're gonna look down on them too?
It doesn't have anything to
do with how I see them—
The Survey Corps is back!
The front gate is gonna open!
Let's go, Mikasa! It's the
triumphant return of the heroes!
Shoot, I can't see.
Only this many of them made it back?
They must've all been eaten.
This is what happens when
you go outside the walls.
Moses? Moses!
Excuse me, I don't see my son, Moses...
Where can I find him?
It's Moses's mother.
Bring it over.
That's all we were able to recover.
But... my son... carried out his duty, right?
Although it may not have
been anything significant,
he contributed to mankind's
retaliation somehow, didn't he?!
Of course!
No...
Through this mission, we...
No, through all of our missions...
We've failed to achieve anything!
Because of my incompetence,
I've gotten soldiers killed for nothing,
and failed to learn the slightest thing about them!
What a real mess.
Tell me about it.
All this shows is that our taxes are being
spent fattening them up for nothing.
What's your problem, you damn brat?!
H-Hey! What're you doing, Mikasa?!
Hey, get your ass back here!
Mikasa! This is far enough, isn't it?!
What was that for?
The wood's all over the place now!
Eren, did that change your mind
about joining the Survey Corps?
Help me pick them up.
There isn't much to begin with.
Currently Disclosable Information
About the Walls Part
①
Mankind lives enclosed within three walls.
The outermost wall is Wall Maria,
the middle wall is Wall Rose, and the
final, innermost wall is Wall Sina.
Currently Disclosable Information
About the Walls Part
②
The area between the walls
are approximately equal.
There's about 100km between
Maria and Rose, about 130km
between Rose and Sina, and
about 250km between Sina
and the center.
We're back.
Welcome home.
My, Eren, I see you've worked harder than usual.
Y-Yeah.
What?
Your ears are warm.
I can tell you're lying.
Mikasa helped you out, didn't she?
Oh, are you heading out, Dad?
Work?
Yes. Medical examinations within the inner walls.
It should take around two to three days.
Oh.
Eren says he wants to join the Survey Corps.
M-Mikasa, I told you that's a secret!
Eren! What are you thinking?
Do you know how many people
have died outside the walls?
I do!
Then why—
Eren.
Why do you wish to venture outside?
I want to know... what's
become of the outside world.
I don't want to simply live out
my life within the walls like this!
Besides, if nobody follows in their footsteps...
the sacrifice of all those who lost
their lives would be in vain!
I see.
The ferry will depart soon.
I'll be off now.
Wait, dear!
Say something to Eren!
Carla, a human's spirit of inquiry isn't
something that can be talked down.
Eren.
When I return, I'll show you the basement
that I've always kept a secret.
Really?!
Have a safe trip!
I'm still against it.
Only fools would consider
joining the Survey Corps.
What? Fools?!
To me, people that are content with living
like cattle seem way more stupid!
Eren!
Mikasa, that boy has a habit
of getting into trouble,
so when something happens,
be there for each other.
Okay.
What's wrong, heretic?
If you don't like it, why don't you fight back?
As if I'd ever do that.
The last thing I'd do is stoop to your level.
What was that?!
You're only resorting to physical abuse
because you can't prove that I'm wrong.
Doesn't that mean you admit I'm right?!
Shut your trap, you rambling nitwit!
Stop right there!
It's Eren!
What an idiot.
He came back for more.
Itching for a beating, huh?
We'll make you our sandbag!
Mi-Mikasa's right behind him!
W-We're screwed! Run!
Hey, they took off after seeing me!
No, they probably ran because of Mikasa.
O-Ow.
Hey, you okay, Armin?
I can stand up on my own.
Oh, all right.
So, when I said mankind would eventually need
to go outside, they hit me, saying I was a heretic.
Damn it.
Why does simply wanting to go
outside turn everyone against us?
Well, it's because it's been peaceful
within the walls for the past 100 years.
In order to prevent inviting them in
through a reckless attempt to go outside,
the king's government created policy that made
holding interest in the outside world taboo.
We're risking our own lives.
It's our choice to make.
I won't let you.
You can't.
Oh yeah, I can't believe you ratted me out!
I don't remember saying I'd help.
Wh-What'd they say?
Well, they weren't happy about it.
I figured.
True, I think those who believe the walls will
forever provide a life of peace need to face reality.
Just because the wall has done
its job for the past 100 years,
it doesn't guarantee that it
won't be destroyed today...
Not in the slightest.
Wh-What the...?
An explosion?
It came from there!
Seems like something fell.
I have no idea.
Hey, Armin!
What's wrong?
Just what are you staring at?
No way...
That wall is fifty meters tall!
It's them.
A Titan.
Th-They blew a h-hole into the wall.
They're coming inside!
The Titans are coming!
We need to—
Eren!
Our house is...
Mom is...
Mikasa!
It's all over.
This town is...
going to be overrun by Titans!
There's no way our house got hit.
Once I turn that corner, our house will... like always...
Mom!
Eren.
Mikasa, hold that side!
We'll lift the pillar!
Hurry, Mikasa!
I'm trying!
The Titans have come inside, haven't they?
Eren, take Mikasa and run away.
Hurry!
I want to run away!
Get up already!
My legs are crushed by the rubble.
Even if I get out of here, I can't run.
You understand, right?
I'll run away carrying you!
Why don't you ever listen to what I tell you?!
At least listen to my final request!
Mikasa!
No...
No!
At this rate, the three of us will...
Hannes!
Take the children and run!
I can't have you thinking
I'm that small a man, Carla.
I'll butcher the Titan and make
sure to save all three of you!
Wait! Don't fight it!
She's right. If it's just the two
of them, we can get away.
But this is the time for me to make good on my debt!
Hey, Hannes!
What're you doing?!
Thank you.
Mom is...
She's still...
Eren, Mikasa! You two need to live on!
Don't go.
Stop!
On that day, mankind remembered...
The fear of oppression under them,
and the humiliation of being caged like birds.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's more fragile than a life.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, sleep in peace.
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing urges
negai wa okasare
trample upon my wishes.
wasureteshimau hodo
As often as I sadly forget,
mata omoidasu yo
I remember once again.
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
Ah, with this strength and weakness,
nani wo mamoru no darou
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
mou risei nado nai naraba
when a reason ceases to exist.
The fall of Shiganshina.
The only things remaining for mankind
were prayer, screams, and death.
In the midst of it all, Eren alone swears
vengeance upon his small chest.
On That Day
————— The Fall of Shiganshina Part    —————
②