Go for it, Eren!
Year 850:
For the first time in history,
mankind recaptured its territory from the Titans,
but at a great cost.
Now then, I accept all of you that
remain as new Survey Corps soldiers!
This will be a true salute!
Offer your lives!
Sir!
You've all done well to suppress your fear.
Every one of you is a brave soldier.
You have my deepest respect.
A month later,
the Survey Corps departed from Karanese District
under Erwin Smith's command
in an attempt to find a route
to Shiganshina District,
where the Titans' secrets are thought to be held.
We now begin the 57th expedition!
Advance!
Wohlan, Freund!
Well, friend!
Jetzt hier ist ein Sieg.
Victory stands before us.
Dies ist die erste Glorie.
Our legend begins now.
O, mein Freund!
O, my friend!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
muimi na shi de atta to iwasenai
I won't let you say, "My death is meaningless."
saigo no hitori ni naru made
Not until but a single arrow remains.
Der feind ist grausam... Wir bringen.
The enemy is cruel... But we'll prevail.
Der feind ist riesig... Wir springen.
The enemy is titanic... So we'll jump.
ryoute ni wa Gloria utau no wa Sieg
Bearing steel blades of glory, we sing an anthem of victory.
senaka ni wa Flügel der Freiheit
On our backs are the Wings of Liberty.
nigirishimeta ketsui wo hidarimune ni
On our chests are our fists, tightly clenched with determination.
kirisaku no wa Ringen der Torheit
The screw of folly rips through.
soukyuu wo mau Flügel der Freiheit
Wings of Liberty dance in the blue sky.
The Female Titan
————— The 57th Expedition Part    —————
①
A 10-meter-class approaching
from ahead, on the left!
While I'm quite interested in
the contents of its stomach,
I'll leave this to the support squad!
Damn.
Too shallow.
Defend the ranks!
Don't falter!
Leave it to the support squad and advance!
Forward! Forward!
The support squad will only
escort us to the old town area.
Beyond that is all Titan territory.
All we can count on is the long-distance
scouting formation Commander Erwin devised.
This is where we of the special-ops squad will be.
Oluo, can they...
Can my comrades beat the Titans?
Huh?
What the hell have you been
doing this past month?
Listen, you damn brat.
During an expedition,
the point is to avoid the Titans if possi—
Assume the long-distance scouting formation!
Later, Armin.
Don't wet yourself even if you run into a Titan!
Right.
Same to you.
Line 3-3: Relay
The vanguard will form a semicircle.
Although we're spread out,
Line 5-Center: Standby
stay within eyesight of someone on all sides,
in fixed distances from one another.
Line 2-5: Relay
Extend survey and relay range as far as possible.
Line 3-4: Relay
Line 2-4: Relay
We'll be fine.
Calm down.
The vanguard scout squad
encounters the Titans most often.
Line 1-8: Scout
Upon sighting a Titan,
they'll fire a red smoke signal.
Soldiers that see it should relay it
by firing one of the same color.
Line 2-Center: Command
After observing the signals to
determine the Titan's position,
the Commander will fire a green smoke signal
that will indicate the formation's new course.
Thus, the entire formation can advance to
its destination while avoiding the Titans.
Line 2-3: Relay
However, terrain or obstacles can delay a sighting,
which may allow Titans to breach the formation.
Red... Red smoke signal...
Blouse! This way!
Damn!
Looks like we missed one.
Let's draw it toward us.
Blouse! Come this way!
I'll handle it.
Withdraw!
Sir!
Squad Leader...
Get back in position!
He's out of gas.
Something's strange...
It's been a while since the red
smoke signal was fired,
but we've yet to regroup.
Don't tell me...
Note that the methods I've discussed are
only for use against easily
predictable, normal Titans.
A black smoke signal?
Is one ignoring nearby people and heading
straight for the formation's center?
There's no doubt about it.
It's...
an Abnormal!
Combat is only necessary against
Abnormals, which are unpredictable.
Damn, guess we have no other choice.
Sys, you get its nape!
I'll stop it in its tracks!
Roger!
Fighting with the device on level
ground is clearly unfavorable.
The chance of success is extremely low,
but I can't risk having the formation torn apart.
Arlert should be over there.
I don't want to let a new
recruit run into one of these.
We'll kill it here!
Now, Sys!
Squad Leader Ness did it!
We got it, huh?
You came for me?
That's why you're my favorite.
I love you, Shallot!
Again?
What's the right flank scout squad doing?
If it ignored them and came this way,
then it must be an Abnormal too.
Here we go again.
Sys, let's do it once more.
Sir.
But really, to think we have
to do this twice in a row...
And it looks like it's a 14-meter-class at least.
This one will be tough.
What's that?
It's so fast!
Don't let it get to Arlert!
Sys!
Sir!
No, wait a minute.
That's not an Abnormal.
It has intelligence!
Like the Armored Titan,
Colossus Titan, and Eren...
It's a human controlling the body of a Titan!
Wh-Who is she?!
Why?!
This is bad. What do I do?
I'll die too.
I'll be killed!
Go! Run away!
What is she...
No, what are they...
aiming for?
Currently Disclosable Information
Long-distance Scouting Formation Part ①
Devised by Survey Corps Commander Erwin Smith,
survival rates beyond the walls were drastically
improved through its implementation.
Currently Disclosable Information
Long-distance Scouting Formation Part ②
Put simply, it's a type of human "radar". By allowing Erwin, who's
positioned at the center of the formation, to be quickly informed of any
Titan sightings, it became possible to change the formation's course
before encounters.
Someone tell them...
The right flank survey squad
has been all but wiped out.
A female Titan brought a large army of Titans.
Is anyone here?
She's not going to kill me?
What just happened?
She took off my hood...
and looked...
at my face?
Armin!
Reiner!
Hey, can you stand?
Well, for starters, you're dead meat if
you don't have a horse outside the walls.
Hurry!
Right!
I saw a smoke signal for Abnormals...
Was it for that one with the nice ass?
She's not an Abnormal.
She's a human controlling a Titan's body!
What?!
Wait a second.
I should fire a smoke signal first.
Q-Quickly...
I have to let them know...
with a smoke signal...
Wait.
Looks like Jean fired one.
From the right flank?
Does that mean we got hit
so bad we can't continue?
It seems we lost part of
the right flank scout squad.
Hordes of Titans came.
And I don't know why,
but a lot of them are extremely agile.
They're somehow being held back for now,
but the formation can't function.
Many have died already,
and if we're not careful, all of us will!
That's the same direction she came from.
No way...
Was she leading the Titans here?
"She"?
Why is a Titan over there?
Is it an Abnormal?
No, that's wrong.
She's a human controlling a Titan's body.
Someone with the same power as Eren.
What?
Armin, what makes you think that?
Titans merely prey on people.
People die as a result,
but the act of killing isn't their intention.
But in her case, the moment
her vitals were targeted,
she flung Sys to the ground, crushing him.
She didn't kill to consume,
but for the sake of killing.
In that regard, her very nature is unique.
When the Colossus Titan and
Armored Titan destroyed the walls,
she must've been the one
that brought all the Titans.
Their goal has always been to attack mankind!
Wait, maybe not.
I get the feeling she's looking for someone.
Assuming that's true,
she must be searching for...
Could it be Eren?
Eren?
But the Levi Squad, which Eren's in,
should've been in charge of the
right flank that she passed through.
The right flank?
The plans I got had them around
the rear of the left flank.
But mine had them around
the front of the right flank.
Well, there's no way they
would've been put so far ahead.
Then where are they?
Most likely in the safest spot of this formation.
So I guess they're somewhere in the center rear.
Armin!
We don't have time to think right now.
It's impossible for us to signal how
dangerous it is with smoke signals!
Before long, even the command
squad will be destroyed.
If that happens, the formation will
fall apart and everyone will die.
What are you getting at?
In other words,
at this distance, we might still
be able to draw her attention.
We can buy time until everyone has withdrawn.
At least... I hope we can.
She really is intelligent.
To her, we're literally nothing more than insects.
We'd be crushed by even the slightest blow.
Seriously?
That's pretty scary.
Are you really Jean?
The Jean I know is someone
who only thinks about himself.
It hurts to hear that.
It's just that I don't want to disappoint those...
indiscernible, scorched bones.
I-I...
I know what needs to be done now!
Not to mention, this is the job we chose!
Lend me a hand!
Pull up your hood. All the way.
That way, she can't see your face.
She shouldn't mindlessly kill us
until she knows who we are!
I see.
So you think she won't kill
people who might be Eren?
I'm relieved to hear that.
And while we're at it, let's
hope she has bad eyesight!
Armin, you always stuck to Eren like glue,
so I thought you were a creep,
but I knew you were a capable guy.
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
But "creep" is a bit mean.
She's slowed down a lot from when I first saw her.
Is she tired?
If she starts running at full
speed again, we won't make it.
Now's our chance.
Otherwise...
All right, guys... Just like we planned.
Draw her attention for as long as possible
so that the formation can withdraw.
Even if it's only for a second longer.
If we cut a leg tendon, that'd be more than enough.
Don't push your luck though.
Killing her isn't necessary!
She's aware that her nape is a vital.
She's completely different from average Titans.
It's probably impossible to kill her.
At least not according to the limits
defined by human knowledge.
But... if it's those two, then maybe...
Armin!
Why you...
Her movements are on a
completely different level!
Damn.
We...
We underestimated her!
She covered her nape.
Jean!
Damn, I can't get away!
I'm going to die!
Once she grabs my wire, I'm finished!
Jean!
Avenge that reckless idiot!
Armin?
She stopped moving?
That's the one!
That's the one that killed him!
He really ended up dying on the right flank!
Avenge that reckless idiot!
What happened?
Did he hit his head and go insane?
This really isn't the time for that!
Reiner?
It crushed my best friend with one stomp!
I saw his body stuck under its foot!
He's going straight for the nape?
Wait, that might work!
Now that she's distracted by Armin!
H-Hey...
Reiner, you...
Reiner did it!
Mikasa's so strong, I almost forgot.
He's an exceptionally capable
guy you can count on.
We bought enough time, right?!
Let's get away from her already!
If she doesn't eat people,
she shouldn't follow us!
Look.
The giant bitch got scared
and is running home now!
What... Why?
That's toward the center rear.
Could she be...
heading toward Eren?
tatoeba ore ga ore janai toshite
If we were to assume that I'm not me,
omae wa omae da to iikireru no ka
then could you be sure that you are you?
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
I shattered a vessel of sand, spilling its contents.
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareru ka
Could you retrieve your heart and gather it all?
dareka no yobu koe ga
The sound of others calling my name
miminari ni kawatta
is now all but noise to me.
toki ga tomatta mitai da
It's as if time is standing still.
saa me wo samase
Now, open your eyes.
fukai yami wo ore wa nukedashita
I slipped out of the vast darkness,
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
and fled from it as swiftly as a gale.
ikita shikabane mitai datta
It's as if I was a living corpse.
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
We now head beyond the walls.
mata aouze chizu ni nai basho de
Let us meet again in those uncharted lands.
"You damn monster!"
Not even the highly experienced Survey Corps
soldiers can stop the female Titan.
And so, the monster finally spots
Eren in a forest of giant trees.
The Forest of Giant Trees
————— The 57th Expedition Part    —————
②