[Script Info]
Title:AccelWorld 07
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Haru,方正兰亭中黑_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00707078,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,方正兰亭中粗黑_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00721A63,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: All,方正兰亭中黑_GBK,22,&H00707078,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Jimaku,华文细黑,25,&H00A0CD3C,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: lrc_JPN,DFGMinchoP-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00575757,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,5,1
Style: lrc_CHN,方正大标宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00575757,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: Staff,方正兰亭中粗黑_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 副本AWTXT,微软雅黑,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00721A63,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: titleE,OCR A Extended,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,4,30,30,10,1
Style: titleC,华文中宋,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,80,0,0.00,1,0,3,4,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------OPCHNlrc----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.98,0:01:05.56,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}鮮豔而躍動的雙瞳  僅映出你的身影
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.61,0:01:09.15,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}初次涉足後才得以覺醒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.53,0:01:13.91,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}前往新世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.95,0:01:20.33,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}低頭蜷縮顯得渺小
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.62,0:01:25.29,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眼裡景色一片灰蒙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.88,0:01:32.38,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}資料構建的虛擬實境亦為假象
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.47,0:01:38.06,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}意識到那期待的視線難以相迎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.56,0:01:42.23,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}指引未來揚帆起航的是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.39,0:01:48.40,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中那份美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.82,0:01:57.12,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}各自暗問何處才是渴望飛往的藍天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.66,0:02:06.25,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}鮮豔而躍動的雙瞳  僅映出你的身影
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.29,0:02:11.76,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}進行「加速」的我  才能飛往心之所向
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.88,0:02:13.30,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飛得更高
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.34,0:02:14.76,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}變得更強
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.76,0:02:17.47,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}直至抵達你的心坎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.55,0:02:21.14,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}初次涉足後才得以覺醒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.60,0:02:25.39,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Chasin'  the  world
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------OPJPNlrc----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.98,0:01:05.56,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}この瞳は　鮮やかに舞う　キミしか知覚らない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.61,0:01:09.15,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}踏み込んで覚醒ざめる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.53,0:01:13.91,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}セカイへ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.95,0:01:20.33,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}俯き過ぎて小さい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.62,0:01:25.29,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕だけの景色が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.88,0:01:32.38,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}組み立てたジオラマも嘘だと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.47,0:01:38.06,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}合わせ辛い視点に　気付いている
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.56,0:01:42.23,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}駆け出してゆく未来は
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.39,0:01:48.40,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}美しさを手に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.82,0:01:57.12,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}それぞれが翔べる場所を　問い掛けてく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.66,0:02:06.25,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}この瞳は　鮮やかに舞う　キミしか知覚らない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.29,0:02:11.76,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}加速して初めて  往ける僕は僕の先へ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.88,0:02:13.30,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと昂く
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.34,0:02:14.76,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと強く
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.76,0:02:17.47,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}キミに届きたい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.55,0:02:21.14,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}踏み込んで覚醒ざめる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.60,0:02:25.39,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Chasin'  the  world
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Haru,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------EDCHNlrc----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.83,0:22:15.24,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我們掙扎在無盡的痛苦與淚水中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.24,0:22:17.24,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使遍體鱗傷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.24,0:22:19.07,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}也只能接受命運的擺佈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.21,0:22:20.76,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}喚醒自己的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.87,0:22:22.77,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在藍天中綻放光彩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.99,0:22:25.32,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}迸發出生命的激情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.44,0:22:31.62,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自暴自棄得來的安樂 停滯的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.85,0:22:34.55,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}世界不知從何日而起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.70,0:22:37.81,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}抹上一層希望的明亮
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.81,0:22:41.06,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}願望分毫未變  盼你留在我身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.10,0:22:44.67,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我們卻活在瞬息萬變的長流之中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.72,0:22:46.32,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}真實的嗓音
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.43,0:22:47.90,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}難以言表的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.90,0:22:50.32,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}皆帶往與你相系的雲霄
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.32,0:22:52.12,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}響徹天際
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.99,0:22:56.09,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}若能勇敢地用雙手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.25,0:22:59.42,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}抹去眼瞼邊上的淚珠
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.49,0:23:02.81,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}絕不白費此刻堅定的心念
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.85,0:23:06.02,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}以及一路經歷的道道傷痕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.09,0:23:09.38,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}及早地飛往你的所在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.43,0:23:12.56,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}哪怕雙翅被撕裂得不堪入目
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.65,0:23:15.98,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}也要穿過歪曲的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.04,0:23:19.10,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}抵達感覺的盡頭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.19,0:23:24.66,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}與「真實」一道  繼續加速
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.10,0:00:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------EDJPNlrc----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.83,0:22:15.24,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an8}We are tossed by the waves of pain and tears
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.24,0:22:17.24,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an8}I'm tossed into the fray
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.24,0:22:19.07,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an8}tossed by various fortune
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.21,0:22:20.76,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an8}wake up your brain!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.87,0:22:22.77,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an8}flashed in the sky
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.99,0:22:25.32,lrc_CHN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an8}It's a burst of sensation
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.44,0:22:31.62,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}「諦め」がくれた安楽  沈滞の世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.85,0:22:34.55,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}いつからだっただろう？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.70,0:22:37.81,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ふいに輝き始めた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.81,0:22:41.06,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}変わらずにいてと願うこと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.10,0:22:44.67,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}変わりゆく時に生きる僕ら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.72,0:22:46.32,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}本当の声を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.43,0:22:47.90,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}言い得ぬ夢を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.90,0:22:50.32,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君と繋がった空へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.32,0:22:52.12,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}響かせて！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.99,0:22:56.09,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと強く…この両手で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.25,0:22:59.42,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙全て振り払えたら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.49,0:23:02.81,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}「今度こそは…」つぶやく今と
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.85,0:23:06.02,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}傷さえも無駄にしない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.09,0:23:09.38,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと早…く君のもとへ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.43,0:23:12.56,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}たとえ羽が千切れようとも
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.65,0:23:15.98,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}歪む世界走り抜けて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.04,0:23:19.10,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}感覚のその向うへ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.19,0:23:24.66,lrc_JPN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}「真実」と 加速してく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------title----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.06,0:02:39.02,titleE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\fsp2\pos(316,296)}R{\1c&HEF562F&}es{\r}to{\1c&HEF562F&\fsp2}r{\r}at{\1c&HEF562F&\fsp2}io{\r}n
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.06,0:02:39.02,titleC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\fsp-1\pos(532,296)}; 修復
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------TXT----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.08,0:00:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退出了…劍道部嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.02,0:00:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.21,0:00:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說實話  我最初聽到的時候也驚訝得說不出話了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.76,0:00:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您有問他的理由是什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.79,0:00:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他沒有說完  只是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.12,0:00:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他說自己還有其他非做不可的事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.95,0:00:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.48,0:00:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來  開戰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.02,0:00:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Black  Lotus  為什麼要…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.75,0:00:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒聽到嗎  我在叫你跟我戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.02,0:00:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請等一下  我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.47,0:00:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(387,328)}Burst  Linker
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.46,0:00:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻的你作為一名超頻連線者…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.99,0:00:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人正向你發出挑戰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.78,0:00:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以全力回應找上門來的挑戰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.55,0:00:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不就是這個世界的規則嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.17,0:00:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不動的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.24,0:00:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不客氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.58,0:02:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在思索著兩種可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.31,0:02:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是個演技非常好的大騙子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.42,0:02:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了曝光我的現實身份而故意撞過來的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.43,0:02:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者  你是個單純的粗神經
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.94,0:02:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫無疑問  答案是第二項
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.32,0:02:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說  這兩週裡打出70%平均勝率的Silver  Crow
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.67,0:02:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子就陷入瀕死狀態這點實在非常可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.33,0:02:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我的事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.38,0:02:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是不能說出口的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.61,0:03:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.55,0:03:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加速世界裡還沒聽說過你的人  估計只有你自己了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.60,0:03:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的完全飛行型  還是用腦派
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.47,0:03:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過獎了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.75,0:03:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…看上去是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.30,0:03:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上卻是個魯莽行事和愛耍花招的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.48,0:03:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本人也意外地相當遲鈍
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.80,0:03:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是剛剛你不也說了嗎  我相當遲鈍
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.54,0:03:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上也是那樣  我明明只有308點還選擇了升級
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.70,0:03:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果這就是令你陷入了瀕死狀態的原因…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此  我可以判斷你是個貨真價實的粗神經
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.49,0:03:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.31,0:03:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  你能相信我真是太好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.40,0:03:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.47,0:03:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然脫離了常規狀況  我還是重新介紹一次好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.66,0:03:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Aqua  Current
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.07,0:03:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會幫助你回復到50點以上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.14,0:03:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以叫我卡蓮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.68,0:03:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  請多多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.17,0:03:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  馬上開始團體戰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.06,0:03:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確定登陸為組合
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.61,0:03:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連上全球網路後  立即進行加速
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.00,0:03:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.04,0:04:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能在這個千代田區域取得目標點數的話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.80,0:04:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任務就到此結束
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.71,0:04:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不夠的話  就移動到旁邊的秋葉原特區繼續對戰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.70,0:04:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有不清楚的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.23,0:04:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…沒什麼問題
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.87,0:04:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該為剛才摸到她胸部的事道歉嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.53,0:04:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  又沒什麼手感
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.85,0:04:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定沒摸到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.37,0:04:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都聽到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.71,0:04:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(320,328)}Burst  Link
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.72,0:04:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超頻連線
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.80,0:04:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確確實實地摸到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.44,0:04:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉  非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.52,0:04:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直連的時候  需要好好控制自己的思考
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.04,0:04:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然你說什麼我都聽見了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.01,0:04:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.67,0:04:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要挑戰的對手就選…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.54,0:04:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.43,0:04:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才你是不是想選Lv.3或Lv.4的對手？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.32,0:04:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是Lv.2  而我是Lv.1
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.59,0:04:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要選的對手組合  其合計級別要在Lv.6以上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.23,0:05:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合計的級別差有Lv.3的話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.24,0:05:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使打輸  也能避免一下子失去全部點數
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.28,0:05:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道理上來說的確是那樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.78,0:05:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以卡蓮你才故意一直不升級保持在Lv.1嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.27,0:05:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這只是一半的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.40,0:05:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一半理由  我以後會告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.27,0:05:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這當然是既可能會也可能不會了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.91,0:05:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.60,0:05:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sand  Duct和Nickel  Doll這隊恰好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.03,0:05:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這對組合雖然是Lv.3和Lv.4
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.52,0:05:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他們點數還算充裕  所以應該會從正面直接攻過來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.91,0:05:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種對手的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.49,0:05:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你能冷靜發揮實力  大概就不會輸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.72,0:05:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為我考慮了這麼多之後  才選擇對手的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.81,0:05:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個人  真的很瞭解我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.43,0:05:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會努力的！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.84,0:05:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹勁固然重要  但也要保持平常心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.00,0:05:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是不可敗北的一戰
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.91,0:05:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  最重要的不是勝敗的結果
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.25,0:06:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…而是享受過程
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.74,0:06:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我的上輩告訴我的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.56,0:06:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫我要好好享受現在的每一戰
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.99,0:06:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.63,0:06:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  我們該開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.13,0:06:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是「腐蝕林」場地啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.65,0:06:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是水  的確人如其名
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.62,0:06:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.22,0:06:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往下方去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.01,0:06:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.23,0:07:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毒沼澤嗎  真是棘手的場地啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.87,0:07:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等很久了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.77,0:07:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.97,0:07:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒什麼好顧慮的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.85,0:07:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的點數已經回復好了  即使打輸給你也沒任何問題
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.70,0:07:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是你大賺點數的好機會
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.39,0:07:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是說  這已經是你的實力了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.78,0:07:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(236,328)}Leonids
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.77,0:07:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從獅子座流星雨的使者處聽說了你的情況
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.39,0:07:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說你連劍道大賽也沒有參加
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.37,0:07:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.15,0:07:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了做個了結
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.53,0:07:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了結？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.19,0:07:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我犯了錯  不能夠毫無代價地留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.62,0:07:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.33,0:08:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將自己得到的和獲得的東西一概捨棄
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.45,0:08:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通過喪失一切來彌補所謂的過錯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.74,0:08:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你輔助春雪成為獨當一面的超頻連線者之後
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.43,0:08:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就打算自己親手移除Brain  Burst  不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.70,0:08:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只能這樣…只有做到這樣才能…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.46,0:08:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣做又有誰會得益
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.74,0:08:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春雪會怎樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.84,0:08:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力想要原諒你的倉嶋又會怎樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.12,0:08:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣做將會踐踏他們對你的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.36,0:08:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然你要我怎麼辦？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.36,0:08:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你叫我怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.62,0:08:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  終於有幹勁了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.33,0:08:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就憑你們的等級還敢挑戰我們  膽子真大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.79,0:08:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.63,0:08:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sand  Duct就交給我了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.44,0:08:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去負責對付Nickel  Doll
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.03,0:09:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她會從兩手心之間放出電流  小心不要被抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.98,0:09:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在爆什麼料啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.87,0:09:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(320,328)}Sand  Blast
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.86,0:09:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風沙爆擊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.01,0:09:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的對手可是我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.77,0:09:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.84,0:09:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.53,0:09:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太過分了  居然把我一頭栽進這樣的臭水溝裡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.35,0:09:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個家庭暴力男
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.51,0:09:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.72,0:09:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來  你撐得住嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.26,0:09:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡可是毒沼澤  傷害很大的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.45,0:09:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說在前面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.45,0:09:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經是Lv.4了  體力先歸零的可是你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.16,0:09:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毒對銀沒效果
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.34,0:09:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.35,0:09:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.43,0:09:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是金屬色相條的左端
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.96,0:09:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊  你可是銀啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.81,0:09:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.74,0:09:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好再去學學自己顏色的性質
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.48,0:10:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀雖然有抗菌性…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.72,0:10:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻是金屬裡面最易導電的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.31,0:10:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧看吧  銀的導電率可是鎳的四倍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.30,0:10:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很快就能說再見了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.70,0:10:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛起來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.63,0:10:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是飛行能力！？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.91,0:10:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(320,328)}Dive  Attack
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.92,0:10:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,急墜重擊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.13,0:10:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹掉了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.20,0:10:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  還沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.22,0:10:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒的一擊  美妙且具威力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.09,0:10:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  勝敗已定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.59,0:10:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們注定失敗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.85,0:10:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(320,328)}Splash  Stinger
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.85,0:10:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛針四射
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.06,0:10:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要我怎麼做
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.53,0:10:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底要我獻出什麼  才能洗清我的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.20,0:11:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就說個明明白白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.91,0:11:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要移除程式並非為了洗清罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.45,0:11:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是因為你只要繼續玩Brain  Burst
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.00,0:11:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會一直對自己所犯的錯感到內疚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.21,0:11:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是討厭那樣而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.37,0:11:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒那回事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.17,0:11:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春雪原諒你以及倉嶋跟往日一樣對待你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.88,0:11:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這都令你不斷地感受到罪惡感
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.05,0:11:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你無法忍受自己獲得原諒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.97,0:11:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你無法忍受自己不再完美
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.73,0:11:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.69,0:11:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是沉醉於自己而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.13,0:11:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是通過自虐來逃避過錯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.71,0:11:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.21,0:11:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼不對的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.31,0:11:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對不對…不對！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.90,0:11:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風沙爆擊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.47,0:11:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,團體戰中最重要的是隊友間的配合  而你們一點都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.58,0:11:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們只會用一對一的攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.90,0:12:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使個人再強也打不贏團體戰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.77,0:12:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如你所說
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.21,0:12:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…勝敗還沒定下來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.84,0:12:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在來這裡之前  我和摯友搭檔打過很多團體戰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.81,0:12:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我能明白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.10,0:12:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在團體戰當中彼此相信對方比一切都重要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.93,0:12:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此我信任卡蓮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.51,0:12:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一個人在裝什麼帥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.11,0:12:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sandy
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.07,0:12:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這時候只能用超豪華的絕招一氣刮跑他們
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.50,0:12:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乾脆地做個了結
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.66,0:12:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.25,0:12:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打起精神  他們要用聯合技了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.85,0:12:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.46,0:12:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能讓兩個人同時被幹掉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.19,0:12:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,判斷戰局後  必要時我會去救你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.05,0:12:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  剛才不是說了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.65,0:13:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,團體戰所需要的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.57,0:13:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(320,328)}Turbo  Molecular
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.58,0:13:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分子渦輪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.22,0:13:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從右手排出狂風  而左腕卻不斷吸收著
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.38,0:13:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.14,0:13:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.22,0:13:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雙手的渦輪抽取氣體分子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.81,0:13:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從而製造真空領域
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.24,0:13:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風本身並沒有攻擊力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.59,0:13:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是將你吸過去  變成打近身戰而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.71,0:13:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近身戰
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.21,0:13:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確  接近那東西之後
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.81,0:13:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁機給予一下踢擊的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.86,0:13:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.32,0:13:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(345,328)}Anode  Cathode
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.34,0:13:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  陰陽電極
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.56,0:13:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  又沒碰到又沒有水
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.52,0:13:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何啊  我和Sandy的超豪華的聯合技
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.30,0:13:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然比不上那個紫色大媽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.44,0:14:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過還是很奏效的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.05,0:14:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輝光放電
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.62,0:14:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在接近真空的低壓環境中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.60,0:14:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電極的絕緣性會被破壞
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.03,0:14:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電流將流入機體之中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.69,0:14:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,置之不理的話  你的委託人就玩完囉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.66,0:14:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  你的身體根本無能為力嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.39,0:14:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春雪他一定說過無論如何都需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.75,0:14:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼不聽聽他的話
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.61,0:14:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.68,0:14:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聆聽他的願望  難道不是你的第一步嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.15,0:14:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春雪他說了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.36,0:14:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是他的摯友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.71,0:14:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投降怎麼樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.31,0:14:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管再花多少心思  憑你的HP值都不可能逆轉了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.19,0:14:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.11,0:14:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我絕不能輸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.65,0:14:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的摯友——阿拓  我們這才剛開始
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.45,0:15:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從現在才開始  所以！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.66,0:15:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.23,0:15:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nicky
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.36,0:15:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.68,0:15:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水明明是導電體
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.86,0:15:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身上的水是不含任何雜質的理論純水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.28,0:15:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不含雜質的水  幾乎等同於完全的絕緣體
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.77,0:15:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.43,0:15:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,團體戰裡所需要的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.88,0:15:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隊友間的配合
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.46,0:15:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(408,328)}Legion
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.48,0:15:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你認為加速世界裡為何會有軍團存在？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.27,0:15:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是因為  同伴間的競爭與扶持…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.61,0:15:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能將一切都變為可能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.78,0:15:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,獨自走來的你  至今仍未親嘗這份喜悅與甘甜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.89,0:15:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賭一把吧  為了那無限的可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.92,0:15:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就能彌補你的過錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.59,0:16:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,點數恢復到了54
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.98,0:16:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下委託就達成了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.73,0:16:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的太感謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.40,0:16:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很享受
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.31,0:16:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托你的福  我看到了很多超頻連線者的必殺技
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.40,0:16:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡蓮你一直都在這附近嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.42,0:16:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎麼問這個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.26,0:16:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼  我在想如果以後還碰見的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.43,0:16:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會再見了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.60,0:16:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,選這裡是因為這裡超頻連線者很少
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.32,0:16:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收取後付的報酬會比較方便而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.27,0:16:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後付的報酬？有這些…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.98,0:16:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來  我會奪走你全部的點數
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.67,0:17:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直連戰鬥中  在拔掉傳輸線之前就能再次加速
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.85,0:17:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直至失去全部點數  對戰才會結束
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.69,0:17:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說後付的報酬是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.57,0:17:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不這樣的話  做保鏢便顯得毫無意義
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.64,0:17:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來  準備戰鬥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.73,0:17:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向我展現你的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直至最後一點水滴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.71,0:17:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要放棄了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.87,0:17:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才我不是說了嗎  我信任你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.19,0:17:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一開始見到卡蓮的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.54,0:17:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心想這個人會是個好人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.96,0:17:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久之前  我和重要的朋友很認真地對戰了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.13,0:17:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拼上了我們之間的所有悲憤  互相仇恨著打了一場
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.36,0:17:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  到最後我相信了他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.51,0:18:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候我決定了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.47,0:18:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦選擇了信任就要一直信任下去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.69,0:18:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠信任下去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.06,0:18:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你不戰鬥嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.42,0:18:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我不想背叛信任的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.52,0:18:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才是騙你的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.04,0:18:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你毫無防備所以想嚇嚇你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.61,0:18:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過好像沒什麼效果
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.87,0:18:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  有的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.13,0:18:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚇得我腿都軟了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.01,0:18:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前也有朋友和重要的軍團長
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.09,0:18:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過因為某件事  大家都各散東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.49,0:18:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.47,0:18:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你要珍惜你的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.86,0:18:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和我的相遇還稍微早了點
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.85,0:19:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今後你與你的軍團長的漫長路途上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.47,0:19:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(263,328)}Elements
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.47,0:19:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們「元素」是不應該去插手的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.39,0:19:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我將拿走留在你心中關於我的記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.56,0:19:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記憶？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.98,0:19:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(320,328)}Memory  Leak
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.98,0:19:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記憶流散
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.58,0:19:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  我在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.08,0:19:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是誰的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.02,0:20:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才千百合來了一趟  放下了一些東西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.85,0:20:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿千？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.24,0:20:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千百合留下了這些就立刻走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.36,0:20:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽  我有事情要跟你說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.84,0:20:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.90,0:20:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.21,0:20:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還要拘謹到什麼時候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.77,0:20:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件事已經過去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.78,0:20:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是說想再請我吃雪糕？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.41,0:20:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿千…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.55,0:20:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說得沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.92,0:20:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.28,0:20:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那身校服…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.96,0:20:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們學校的…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.30,0:21:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.04,0:21:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這年頭還戴眼鏡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.43,0:21:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(210,328)}Neuro  Linker
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.43,0:21:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有神經連接裝置的視力修正  就沒必要戴了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.96,0:21:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從今以後  我希望用自己雙眼去看清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.65,0:21:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的阿千和真正的阿春
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.01,0:21:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…還有真正的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.02,0:21:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你戴得很好看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.66,0:21:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.28,0:21:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.84,0:21:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你會這麼瞭解我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.44,0:21:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一點都不瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.59,0:21:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是  正如你所知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.57,0:21:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昔日的我也犯下了無法彌補的過錯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.95,0:21:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僅是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.40,0:21:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多指教了  我的軍團長
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.39,0:21:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拓！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.01,0:21:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.36,0:23:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(346,328)}Temptation
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.36,0:23:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回  誘惑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.57,0:23:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少女突如其來 盡顯誘惑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.13,0:23:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想從春雪身上得到的到底是…


