Nandemo dekiru hazu dawa...
...soko ni aru mono de.
Juumon to atama ga...
...tsukai you!
Onaka ga sukeba...
...juumon wa PIPOPA.
Suguni osobaya-san ga...
...demae niyatte kuruwa.
Nemuku nattara...
...battan no juuten.
Yoko ni nareba...
...asa niwa...
...genki ni nareruwa.
Kimi nimo kanarazu aruwa.
Fushigi na chikara ga.
Yume mireba yume mo...
...yume janai.
Good morning, everyone!
Let's give our best today!
Okay!
All right, everyone's here.
Let's work out before breakfast!
- Yes!
- Excuse me...!
Peter! You're forgetting
about me!
Who's interrupting my lovely
dream of sweet-smelling hay?!
Huh?
They're increasing their leg
strength on a hilly, grassy path.
Very logical exercise.
No wonder Peter's a famous young
breeder throughout the world.
P-Peter...!
Hang in there, Fake Sick Girl!
This is heavy! You shouldn't
be carrying this!
It's no use. I can't make it.
When all the leaves have
fallen from that tree...
...my life will also be over.
- Right?
- You'll be fine!
It's so fresh and green
and thick!
Huh...?
There.
Oh, my head's spinning.
I'm right here. Be strong!
Thank you, Peter.
I love you.
Fake Sick Girl...!
Everyone's magical powers
are growing much stronger.
Fake Sick Girl's fake
sickness is fantastic, too.
Now, even if
Pretty Sammy shows up...
...it'll turn out like this ideal
simulation. This is the institute...
...to strengthen the Love-love Monsters
so they can overthrow Sammy!
And they call it...
The Island of Love-love Monsters
What's so funny...?
Sasami's gone on a trip with her father
now that it's summer vacation.
I wonder what distant friends
she'll make happy this time?
I'm looking forward to seeing this.
That's a little bitter.
I wonder where Ginji and
Sasami are riding, right now...
Oh, my!
Oh!
It must've been old.
That's terrible. It's defective.
Here, Hiroto.
Open wide.
Don't want it.
You're awful! You mean you
would've taken it from Amano?!
W-What are you saying?!
Stop your fighting, you two!
Smile, everybody!
Cheese!
Okay, one more!
Why do I have to lead them
during the summer vacation?
Especially when it's not my class!
Oh, come on now. The American, Stephen,
said that travel is all about companions.
Who's he?
It's okay, Kiyone.
Professor Washu has covered
all the costs for our trip.
Right?
I know. I understand.
But what I can't understand
is you!
What?
What's with that outfit?!
This? She said we'd be swimming!
Put it away!
You could've changed there.
But I wanted to wear it sooner!
How embarrassing...
Yay!
- How's this?
- Looking good, Miss Mihoshi.
But I think what you're doing
isn't common sense!
I wish I could get off now...!
Huh?
You look beautiful in your
casual clothes, Miss Kiyone.
What are you saying,
all of a sudden?
I think you're beautiful.
Try to catch me, Teacher!
Wait, my love!
Enough!
What is it, Kiyone?
Nothing at all.
Can I have a sip?
No way, it's mine.
Right.
Oh! Oh, my!
What is it?
We're getting off at the next stop.
What? We're not at the beach, yet.
I'm the sponsor here.
I'm the special school instructor.
And I'm the genius. Get it?
So quit grumbling and get off.
Okay, students?
Yes!
Ryo-Ohki?
Sasami. Are you awake?
Morning, Dad.
You had quite a sleep there, huh?
Yeah, I was really comfortable here.
So? Where are we?
Maybe a deserted island.
What?! Maybe?!
A deserted island?!
I can't be sure, so, "maybe."
No people are on this island,
so, "deserted island."
Oh, I see.
But that's not the point!
What are we doing here?
Why?! How?! Tell me!
I don't know.
Y-You don't know?
No.
All I can say is...
Yeah? Yeah?
You were in a deep sleep.
Yeah!
Ryo-Ohki was sleeping, too.
Dad was sleeping, too.
What?! What do you mean?
First this...
...then that...
-...then...
- We were here.
I see! It's no big deal,
now that we've figured it out.
Right? Good lesson, huh?
Yeah!
Falling asleep at the wheel
causes accidents!
Do they really think this
is going to be okay...?
Oh, yeah! If I transform into
Pretty Sammy, we can get home, right?
Sammy doesn't know how to
use translocation magic yet.
Oh.
Mom will be worried, huh?
No problem. We have an
"I love you" sign.
Honoka!
I love you!
Oh, Ginji! You devil!
I'm so stupid...
There!
I'm with you right now...
...but my mind is absent and empty.
Good shot!
Wait up, Sasami!
Come and get me!
Okay! Here!
That's cold, Dad!
- Take that! And that! And that!
- I'll get you back!
More! More! A little more right!
...I can hear your voice...
...but I don't know what to say to you.
- Dad?
- What?
I'm hungry.
Okay.
Ramia-is-evil, Ramia-is-a-devil.
Misa was right. This way's
much easier to remember.
What are you calling for, out of
the blue? Something up, Rumiya?
Sis, Sasami's here.
Where?
The Love-love Monster farm.
What's that? That Pretty Sammy!
How dare she?!
Despicable magical girl!
Rumiya! Tell Misa to
launch a counterattack!
Y-Yes, I know.
Go, go, Kiyone!
Come on, Mihoshi!
You can do it!
I get it. That's why
she invited us along.
I'm starting to resent
my low teaching salary.
Smile, everyone!
Wow!
Isn't it great, Ryo-Ohki?!
Who's there?
Why?! Pretty Sammy
is on this island?!
Yeah. So we have to come up
with a plan, quick.
I've got something powerful!
Love-love Monsters! Go find Sammy...
...and make sure she'll never
return to society again!
Stand up, Fake Sick Girl!
- What's wrong?
- I'm dizzy.
Don't pull that on me!
What's wrong, Misa?
Oh, sorry.
Peter's been looking after them.
Seems they only listen to him.
Oh, Peter. I'll die
without you here.
Where are you?!
Where are you, Peter?
"She seems healthy."
- Come back!
- What'll we do, Misa?
- What'll we do?
- What?!
This is delicious!
Thanks, uh...
My name's Heita Hirata.
But everybody calls me Peter.
And you?
I'm Sasami Kawai.
You can call me Sasami.
Sasami, huh.
Isn't this a deserted island, Peter?
Yeah. It's a small island.
Just me and some animals live here.
- Animals?
- Peter!
- Animals at the ranch where I work.
- Stop!
Could you tell us the
way off this island?
Sure thing! The opposite shore is only
2 km. away from a place I'll show you.
Huh? We have to swim 2 km.?!
That's right. How did you
get to this island, anyway?
Well, funny you should ask.
Huh? What's the matter, Ryo-Ohki?
There's a magic smell coming
from that boy, Sasami.
A magic smell?
No way, there's no magic here.
I know, but still...
The sound of rippling waves
pushing forward.
The glimmering ocean,
just for the two of us...
He's running along the beach.
I tackle and run into him.
Then I tell him.
"I have something simple to
say, to express my feelings."
"I love you."
Haida! You're putting me in
a difficult ethical position, here!
Where's Hiroto?
He went that way with
Professor Washu and the others.
Oh, that Hiroto! But I love
that cool part of him, too!
Where are we going,
Professor Washu?
- We're looking for something.
- Oh! That's...
Isn't that Kawai's dad's bike?
Definitely.
What's it doing here?
Oh, my. I guess Sasami
wanted to join us HERE.
I hate this!
I don't want to be in the same
profession as this woman!
Hiroto!
Here comes that big mouth, again!
Where's Peter?!
That's...!
A Love-love Monster!
Why do you look so excited?!
Just got carried away.
This isn't the time for
that, Kenji! Run for it!
Oh, well, I should go
with him. Let's go!
I'm hallucinating from this heat.
Yeah, that's it. Yeah.
Kiyone! Kiyone!
We've got to hurry and escape!
Peter!
Say something, Kiyone!
Here she comes!
Where are you, Peter?
Sasami! Something magic
is going on here!
What?!
Definitely! A Love-love Monster!
Sasami, you've got to transform
into Pretty Sammy!
Easy for you to say!
What's wrong, Sasami?
Huh? Uh... um...
My tummy suddenly hurts.
So I'm gonna go to the bathroom!
- Do you have tissue?
- I'll be okay!
Here, Sasami!
Oh, I even have to be
a magical girl on my vacation...
Pretty Mutation...
...Magical Recall!
Magical Girl Pretty Sammy!
Just a little further!
Know where Peter is?
Monsters up ahead, too!
She's heavy!
Sorry...!
More importantly...
Kiyone's passed out, it's okay.
I see.
At times like this, leave it to
the genius, Washu-chan!
I press this...
No! Our escape route's destroyed!
That's your fault!
You got me.
A little further, Sammy!
Meanwhile, onward ran the magical girl...
Where is Peter?
- Stop! Fake Sick Girl!
- Peter!
It's her!
Pixy Misa!
Excuse me? Could you pose
more like a magical girl?
I have to think up a pose
for my entrance...
Why, why, why?!
Why?! What are you people
doing here?!
Washu the genius brought
them here!
It seems that everybody
knows my plans.
Um, what plan are you
talking about?
I won't listen to you!
And please don't start bragging!
Okay, Love-love Monsters!
Get these lost vacationers
and force them out of here!
Wait a minute!
I don't want to hear!
Listen to me!
Okay. Speak your mind, please.
Leave your summer vacations
up to Sammy!
Magical Girl Pretty Sammy!
I'll even land on the beach!
Ugh, I ran out of breath!
You need some more training.
What?!
Wonderful. Really terrific.
Especially that winning pose.
Sammy! What are you doing here?
That should be my question, too!
Whose idea was it to come here?
That figures.
Sammy, meeting here means
you're merely a summer insect.
Come on, Love-love Monsters!
We saw them already...
It's rude to tell the truth, Ryo-Ohki.
Shut up!
This is the way it has to be!
Don't forget it!
S-Sorry.
Action!
Where is Peter?
Listen to what I tell you!
Sammy, who knows what's going
on, but here's your chance!
You can do it, Sammy!
I'll answer your cheers!
Converge, magic powers of justice!
Wait!
- Yes, you do need training.
- But he interrupted!
Are you all okay?
That was terrible,
bullying the animals I raise!
But they're Love-love Monsters;
they're evil beasts!
Why's that?! They haven't
done anything bad!
Now that you mention it...
It was Professor Washu that
wrecked the boat, too.
They're all quiet and good.
Monsters are human, too!
Wrong
Peter...
You're right. Not all of them
are completely bad, after all.
That's right, Sammy.
It's okay, right, Ryo-Ohki?
Of course!
Thank you! I promise not to let
the monsters do anything bad!
Thanks for the emotional show, Sammy.
But did you know that the
monsters came to this island...
...to strengthen themselves with
the magma energy underground?
Huh?! Do you mean...!
What do you mean?
She's sure stupid!
This island is doomed to erupt!
No way!
I'm afraid it's the honest truth.
Misa, that's horrible!
Oh, I'm afraid. So if
you'll excuse me. Bye.
- Sammy!
- Now we're in real trouble!
The magma's bubbling up!
The island will sink!
Everyone get to the boat!
That's right. It's gone.
Everyone! Get on!
We're saved!
Peter!
It's okay! I'm right beside you!
Peter...!
I've got to save them all!
- Hurry, Sammy!
- Sammy!
What should I do?
Sammy! The Coquettish Bomber!
Transport them somewhere
with your magical powers!
But how am I supposed
to do that?
I'll try! I'll give it a shot!
Please, let me rescue everyone
with my magical powers!
Pretty...Coquettish...Bomber!
It's okay, Peter.
Get along with the monsters.
The fruit you gave me was delicious.
You're Sasami!
Oh! Chemistry Girl!
Don't forget me!
You did a wonderful job,
once again, Pretty Sammy.
Yes, that's still a little bitter.
My magnificent plan has ended
in complete failure.
Rumiya, I know you're out there.
Get on in here.
The island's sinking.
I wonder if Sammy's okay?
Yeah, Sammy's fine!
Huh?!
Sasami. Did you go to
the bathroom?
I got lost, but Pretty Sammy
carried me back here.
We have to thank the magical girl.
Yeah!
Huh? What happened?
What's going on? What happened?
Pretty Sammy put a stop to that
evil magical girl's ambitions.
What are you saying? I'm
asking what we're doing here!
So, like I was saying,
the magical girl...
Enough with that, Mihoshi!
- Hey, Ryo-Ohki?
- Yes?
Peter's fine, right?
- I'm sure.
- Yeah.
You're early today,
Love-love Master.
Yes, everyone got up early.
Good-bye, then.
Thank you, Sasami.
This is a beautiful place!
Anata ga mitsumeteru
watashi wa kyou mo...
...hontou no watashi janai.
Kono koi no tame ni...
...anata no tame ni...
... tsukuriageta onna na no yo.
Shoujikina tokoro ga iito...
...anata iu keredo.
Sore wa maboroshi.
Taburakasu noga ikikatayo.
Onna no roman yo.
Dareyori mo suki dakara.
Ii yume misete agetakunaru.
Anata ga tottemo suki dakara.
Damashi tsuzukeruwa.
Sekaijuu no dareyori...
...shiawasena otoko ni shiteageru.