The invincible Pretty Sammy
has one weak spot;...
...jumping over the vaulting box.
At this rate my grade for gym
will be an "F"!
Coming next:
Jump Over The Top!
Call Sammy
when you're in trouble!
Nandemo dekiru hazu dawa...
...soko ni aru mono de.
Juumon to atama ga...
...tsukai you!
Onaka ga sukeba...
...juumon wa PIPOPA.
Suguni osobaya-san ga...
...demae niyatte kuruwa.
Nemuku nattara...
...battan no juuten.
Yoko ni nareba...
...asa niwa...
...genki ni nareruwa.
Kimi nimo kanarazu aruwa.
Fushigi na chikara ga.
Yume mireba yume mo...
...yume janai.
I'm Ryo-Ohki, and I come from
the magic kingdom of Juraihelm.
Sasami's the kindred spirit of
our candidate for queen, Tsunami.
I'm here to help Sasami out.
But strangely, Sasami doesn't
like turning into a magical girl.
And the evil Pixy Misa...
...and her Love-love Monsters
also showed up.
How will this all turn out?
Jump Over The Top!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!!
This week we're going to practice
with the vaulting box.
What a drag. I wish we were
playing soccer instead.
Right, Kenji?
Kenji?
She's great.
Even more wonderful than usual.
What are you talking about?
I'll test you tomorrow. If you
can't do this, practice hard.
Okay, split into groups.
Yes.
Wonder what's going on?
Why?
How come?! Why am I in
a different group from Hiroto?!
Hurry up and go, Haida.
On top of that, how come
he's with that shy bimbo?!
I won't forget this!
You're better off keeping
those thoughts to yourself.
What is it, Misao?
Nothing.
What's taking you?
Hurry up and jump.
Why can't the boys go first?
Okay, I guess I'll have to
show you how it's done.
Hiroto's so wonderful!
You're backing up the system here!
Wow! That was fantastic!
It was nothing.
You're up, Kenji.
What's the matter?
She's elegant.
Forget that and take your turn.
Go for it, Oyamada!
Thank you!
Watch where you're going!
Oops.
This isn't my best sport.
Yeah, yeah. Hurry and get off.
Next it's my turn!
Way to go, Sasami!
Your turn, Misao.
Yeah.
You can do it, Misao!
Amano can't even jump over
that little vaulting box.
Don't say that! Everybody
has something they can't do!
Is that so?
Misao.
Sasami.
Let's practice and I'll
show you how to do it.
We'll practice too.
Give it your best.
You need practice, not me!
Anyone could vault over this.
What do you think you're doing?!
I thought I'd make it over.
Sorry to keep you after school.
It's okay.
Let's practice vaults
so you make it tomorrow.
You're here too?
Oyamada's training.
What about you?
Misao's practicing.
I don't mind. Just
don't get in our way.
We won't get in your way!
Misao, you've got to be
stronger off the springboard.
I know, but I'm scared.
You'll be fine; be brave!
Hiroto.
Here goes!
Listen.
At least spread your legs!
Don't sit on top!
Don't think of anything else!
Wham! Bring your arms down!
Spring! Off the board!
And boom! Land on your feet!
"Wham! Spring! And boom!"?
Wow, vaulting is really hard.
Hiroto?
Majima?
It's so irritating!
What're you afraid of?
Have some guts and spring
higher off the board.
When your hands hit the top,
push off them and swing over.
Got it?
What's gotten into you?
You two are so sloppy
I can't stand it.
That's no way to talk!
Try it, Amano.
Faster!
Jump!
I did it.
You did it, Misao!
Sasami.
See, you can do it if you try.
Um...
What is it?
Thank you.
What's going on between them?!
My Hiroto's with that girl.
Even if God forgives them, I won't.
What a beautiful friendship!
Teacher!
Konoha!
I'm so happy to be
in charge of you all!
I hope you'll always
be my friend.
S-sure.
I'll split them up!
So? What should I do now?
Oyamada was sitting on top!
He was?
Like an old woman drinking tea.
And Misao got really good
at the vaulting box.
What a nice surprise;
good for her.
Didn't you think she could?
I've known that for a long time.
She is Sasami's friend after all.
You got me there!
You want some more?
Okay, hang on.
Eat up.
He's become part of the family.
That's what happened.
I didn't think a vaulting box
would be an obstacle for Misao.
She is my partner after all.
What's our next plan?
Well... of course we'll get
that fool Sammy.
But maybe we should teach
that mean girl a lesson too.
Because she's bullying
our little Misao.
Tagging along wasn't a good idea.
Time for gym class.
Is everyone ready to start?
Ready?
Isn't our teacher mistaking us
for kindergarten kids?
She looks wonderful again today.
I see.
Did you learn how to vault, Oyamada?
With room to spare, Kawai.
After LOTS of work.
That's great.
We'll all pass the test.
Let's start testing you
on the vaulting box.
Excuse me! I have a suggestion
before we start!
Oh? What's that?
Test us a block higher,
at 6 blocks.
Even third graders can
jump over 5 blocks!
6 blocks?
What are you suggesting, suddenly?
Are you afraid or something?
That's not it...
Then there's no problem.
Or maybe there's someone else...
...who's afraid to vault?
Well, uh...
It's decided! We'll do the test
with 6 blocks.
Yes!
If no one disagrees,
then I suppose...
The first boy is Oyamada.
- Yes.
- Show your stuff!
- Yeah, Oyamada!
- Way to go!
It was a cinch!
A check for Oyamada.
Next is Amano.
Yes.
You can do it, Misao!
It's high.
Come on, what's taking you?
I'm scared.
Can't you even jump over that?!
You're a disgrace.
No!
Misao...?
What are you doing?
I can't.
What's the matter?
Misao!
I've kept you waiting.
I'm Magical Girl Pixy Misa!
Not again!
The girl from
the Success Prep School!
A friend of yours, Konoha?
She's no friend of mine,
she's a magical girl!
A magical girl...?
That gaudy outfit is
against school rules!
You can't stop me with
those petty rules.
I'm a crab. I'm a crab...
Where are you going, Sasami?
Let me go! I'm going
to look for Misao.
Before that, why don't we
play a while?
Calling Mystics!
HE-E-EY!
Who is this?
This week's Love-love Monster
is P.E. Girl!
The pleasure's mine.
What is it?
I know. A monster!
P.E. Girl! Show these kids
how wonderful sports are.
Ready... go!
Shot put!
Everyone! In this situation...
Yeah?
...first, we must breathe deeply.
That hurt...
Sweating while doing sports
is so beautiful.
Right, Sasami?
She took off!
That Misa...!
Sasami.
Don't scare me!
Transform into Pretty Sammy!
But the whole class is there!
And I've got to find Misao.
Sammy's the only one who
can rescue the class.
I'm getting into this
deeper and deeper.
Pretty Mutation...
...Magical Recall!
Pretty Sammy is here!
Go, go, go, go!
Shot put!
This is it! I'm going to die!
Aha. You finally made it.
I come when needed!
Hello! I'm Magical Girl Pretty Sammy!
I'm a little late, but I made it!
Been waiting, Sammy!
Outdoor shoes aren't
allowed in the gym!
Don't be such a stickler!
P.E. Girl! Give her
a good thrashing!
Here comes one!
Pretty Home Run!
Not bad, Sammy.
How about this?
Magical Whistle!
What?
My body's moving by itself!
You're trapped! This is the end!
I can't move!
The final blow, P.E. Girl!
Joints for the final blow!
I'm gigantic!!!
The parts combined!
Ready... go!
It's gonna hit me!
Victory!
I can move!
I won.
One, two, three!
Why?!
They're vaulting boxes.
They're hollow.
Hey! Darn!
Pretty Jump!
- Unreal!
- What a great jump!
Oops.
Converge, magic powers of justice!
What is this?!
The Pretty Space.
This is Sammy's magic, too.
This is our second time here.
This is my second time too, Hiroto!
Get off me!
- P.E. Girl?
- Yes?
Catch you later. Bye!
Don't leave me!
Pretty...Coquettish...Bomber!
Sudden Death!
Magical Girl Pretty Sammy!
Today's problem is solved!
Right?
Well, not entirely.
Anyway... see you!
She ran away!
Wh-what just happened here...?
Look, Ramia! I made it over!
Ramia?
Huh... I...?
Misao!
Sasami.
Let's go back.
But...
Just think about yesterday.
All you need is courage.
Courage?
Yeah. Don't give in to your
fears before you try!
You'll jump over if you
have courage.
Courage... courage.
- Did it!
- No way!
Amano... 6 blocks. Check.
V...
We messed up again.
Sis won't be happy about this.
Oh, well.