I should be able to do anything...
...with all the things around me.
I just have to use my head...
...and the incantation.
If I get hungry...
...my incantation is "Pipopa"...
...and the noodle shop...
...will make a speedy delivery.
When I get sleepy...
...I flop out.
If I lie down a while...
...I'll be feeling fine...
...by the next morning.
You have it in you, too.
This mysterious power.
If you have a dream,
then even a dream...
...is more than just a dream.
What's the matter? Are you okay?
Hey, are you all right?!
It's nothing serious. Just
a bit of a fever, that's all.
Oh, no! I'll take you
to the nurse's office!
I can go by myself.
Gym class is gonna start...
...so go on ahead.
No way! I'm not gonna
just leave you.
Hold on. There.
I'm sorry, um....
Sasami!
I'm Sasami Kawai!
Thank you, Sasami...
No problem! That's what
friends are for!
Huh...?
No?
Does it hurt? Are you okay?
No...
...I'm fine.
That was how Sasami
and I first met.
And Sasami was the first
friend I ever had.
Friends
It can't be...!
S-Sasami!
No...!
I am Pixy Misa,
the evil magical girl.
I've been cruel to everyone,
and I've fought against Sammy.
That was me. It was I
who was the bad girl.
I was the one who caused
so much trouble.
It was me!
Sasami must be so angry.
She must've told everyone
I tricked her all along.
What should I do...?
I haven't got anywhere
left to go.
I can't even see Dad anymore.
I... I...
This is all myfault.
It's my fault for
listening to my sister...
...and making Misao
transform into Misa.
M-My chest...!
She forcefully undid
her transformation...
...so it started working
backward! I can't leave her!
I've gotta call Sis.
My magic isn't strong enough!
Be patient a little longer, Misao!
Nice to meet you!!
No!!
Time for my magical
transformation!
Don't come out! Please!
Don't come out!
I just can't believe that
Misao was Pixy Misa.
Misao's had an evil magic
spell cast on her.
An evil magic spell?
Otherwise that shy Misao
couldn't have turned into Misa.
Someone forced her to transform,
to interfere with Sammy.
You mean... If I hadn't
turned into Sammy...
...Misao wouldn't have
turned into Misa?
I don't know.
But that's possible.
Then it's my fault.
It's my fault for getting
her into this mess.
Misao turned into Misa all
because I accepted this baton!
I knew I should have
given it back, then!
This stupid baton!
I don't want it!!
Sasami!
I'm going to look for Misao.
Don't follow me, Ryo-Ohki.
Sasami...
I'm sorry, Sasami.
Where are you going, Tsunami?
You are only allowed to
descend to the Earth once...
...during the queen's
deliberation process.
Break the rules, and we'll strip
you of your qualifications...
...as candidate to be queen.
It doesn't matter.
Sasami Kawai
is the girl you chose.
Won't you believe in her?
Misao! Misao!!
Yes, that's right.
It isn't magical powers
that can save Misao.
You are the only one
who can save her.
Please, Sasami.
Save your friend!
Hello, CD Vision.
Oh, Mrs. Amano.
Yes, that's right. Misao
isn't over there, is she?
I see. No,
thank you very much.
No luck. It looks like she's
not at Sasami's place, either.
She couldn't be caught up in
that monster's wake, could she?
I don't think we need to worry about
that, since everyone returned to normal.
But if she doesn't
come home soon...
...I'll call her teacher.
Yes, I suppose.
You know, she really was
looking forward to seeing you.
Dear, when are you leaving
for your next performance?
I have to leave Japan
tomorrow morning.
I want to see Dad.
What is it?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
Sis! Sis! Sis! Sis!
Sis!
Misao's in trouble!
We can't just leave her...
It's all over.
The Project to make me queen...
Keep your chin up, Sis.
Misao!
Misao! Misao!
I want to see you.
I really want to see you.
Where are you?
I can't go back home...
Misao?
What are you doing in
a place like this?
Aren't you going back home?
I'll go home soon.
Oh?
Um...
Yes?
Um, I have a very close friend.
But I've been lying to her
all along, without knowing it.
I'm sure she's really mad at me.
Did you say you were sorry?
There's no way
she'd forgive me!
You won't know
until you tell her.
And if you tell her
exactly what you think...
...I'm sure your friend
will understand.
There, there. It's gotten
a little chilly out.
Misao, it's getting late.
Why not go home, and apologize
to your friend tomorrow?
But...
But, Sasami won't forgive me.
All the things that are
important to me...
Mom, Dad, Sasami...
...the bird, Dad's piano piece...
...my hair bands, the picture of
Dad and I at the amusement park.
And also... also...
This place.
I had a feeling
you might come here.
After all, it's the place
where you and I first met!
Wait!
Look at me!
No!
- Look at me!
- No!
What's the matter, Misao?
Are you in pain?
What is it? What's going on?!
She's trying to change to Misa.
Ryo-Ohki!
The evil magic in her heart
is swelling up!
How can we make her
change back into Misao?
Please tell me!
Sasami. Magic isn't omnipotent.
I don't wanna hear that!!
But magic will react to
people's feelings toward others.
The only one who can remove the
evil magic from Misao's heart...
...is you, because you care
the most for Misao.
I can...?
For Misao...
Use your strength and magic
and align your heart with Misao's.
Sorry that I threw you
and stuff, earlier.
Please give me the strength
I need to save Misao!
Pretty Mutation...
...Magical Recall!
Just wait, Misao!
I'll save you soon!
Because I'm going to
drive away this evil magic!
This is the inside
of Misao's heart...
Misao...
Misao!
Who would've thought you'd
come all the way in here.
Pretty Sammy.
No, Sasami Kawai!!
Misa!
Welcome to the inside
of Misao's heart!
Misa! Change Misao back to
normal, and get out of here!!
You don't understand a thing.
Misa is Misao, and Misao is Misa.
The sad feelings in her heart,
along with the magical powers...
...are what brought me
into the world.
Me, Pixy Misa.
In otherwords, we're
one and the same person.
No...! Misao!
Misao doesn't want to see
the likes of you!
Why not?
It's all your fault!
My fault...?
You were covering for Misao
all along, weren't you.
Misao developed a real complex
about you, over that.
"I'm so timid. I envy
Sasami, who's so cheery."
Misao's not like that at all!
That's what the other
side of me said.
It couldn't be a lie.
And when you were
covering for Misao...
...you were probably steeping
in a superiority complex, huh.
Thinking, "I'm saving
poor, weak little Misao."
That's not true!
You really loved
saving Misao, didn't you.
You were proud of yourself
for saving Misao, right?
No! That's not true, Misao!
And now you're going
to save her again?
You're being a nuisance!!
I just... I...
Get out of here! Now!!
I...
Misao, listen to me.
The very first time
I talked to you...
...you were really struggling,
and I admired you!
Even though you had a fever,
and you were in pain...
...you smiled at me. Remember?
I'm your friend, right?
We're friends, so can't
I want to be together?
I want to help you?
You've given me so many things!
That's why... that's why...
There are so many things
I still want to do with you!!
Like playing, and staying over,
and going on trips...
...and comparing homework!
There's lots and lots
and lots of things!!
Please, Misao! Answer me!!
Misao! Answer me!!
Even if you stay
as Pixy Misa forever...
...I'll still really love you, Misao!
Sa...
Sa-sa-mi...
Sasami!
Misao!
I'm sorry, Sasami!
I... I...
I want to be your friend!
We are friends! Of course.
I want to be with you!
I'll always be with you, Misao!
I care so much for you!
I care about you, too, Misao!
Sasami!
Misao.
I'm going to get better.
I'm gonna try my best.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
What is it?
Sasami!
That's the true form of the evil
magic that was in your heart.
Misao, let's do it together!
Converge, magic powers of justice!
Pretty Coquettish Bomber!!
Misa.
Good-bye, Pixy Misa.
The other side of me.
Sasa...!
That's great!
Thank you, Pretty Sammy.
Good-bye, Misao.
I'm coming back, for sure.
I'll see you soon, Misao.
Hurry, Dad! Misao will
get tired of waiting!
Thanks, Dad!
Good-night!
What's going on? Suddenly
Sasami seems kind of grown up.
Must be imagining it.
Misao!
Huh?
Sorry I'm late!
There were these runaway
horses on the way...
WHAT?!!
Welcome, Sasami!
I'M PIXY MISA!
What...?!!
Did I scare you?
I made it to try to get better...
...and to try to cheer myself up!
What do you think?
Misao! I don't think that's the
right way to cheer yourself up.
Huh?
Really?
Misao, are you sad because
you couldn't see your dad?
No! I'm fine, because
I've got you here!
It may be too late, saying this
after such a long time...
...but I was wrong.
To say there are any number
of guys out there...
...I should've known better.
Midnight,
Comes to anyone,
...not only to Cinderella.
It may be too late, saying this
after such a long time...
...but I've made light
of the whole world.
To think that somehow things
would turn out all right...
...I should've known better.
Misao's going to play the
piano at the school festival.
I sure wish her dad could hear
her playing that beautiful song!
Coming next: I'm Glad to
Have the Mystic Force.
I'm glad I became Sammy!