I should be able to do anything...
...with all the things around me.
I just have to use my head...
...and the incantation.
If I get hungry...
...my incantation is "Pipopa"...
...and the noodle shop...
...will make a speedy delivery.
When I get sleepy...
...I flop out.
If I lie down a while...
...I'll be feeling fine...
...by the next morning.
You have it in you, too.
This mysterious power.
If you have a dream,
then even a dream...
...is more than just a dream.
Tsunami. Some nerve being late
for the ascension ceremony.
I forgot to water the flowers
in my room.
You mean flowers are more
important than this ceremony?!
Why is this bungling girl
aspiring to be queen?
Girls of unrivaled magical powers.
As you know, our former queen
passed on one year ago.
The time has come.
We will commence selecting
a queen for the next term.
First Contact
There is merely one question
for the prospective queens.
If you are chosen, what do you
propose to do for our kingdom?
Answer the question.
Romio.
I would continue the work of
our former queen.
How about you, Ramia?
Please see the overhead projection.
The population of our kingdom
of Juraihelm has been declining.
To stop this, families with over
2 children should get subsidies.
Divorced couples will be
punished by law.
Forbidden!
For people to pledge allegiance
to the Imperial Rule...
...we need weapons, more public
order and a complaints box.
All right!
And Tsunami?
Yes...
If I were to become
queen of Juraihelm...
I would...
...plant flowers throughout
the kingdom!
That is your wish, mistress?
It is.
What a fool.
Juraihelm's decision shall
now be heard.
At last, the moment that I'll
become queen!
Thanks for making me
look so good, Tsunami.
The 208th queen to reign
shall be...
This is it!
...Tsunami.
Thank you very...!
Tsunami?
That's wonderful.
No way!
It can't be! It can't be!
Listen well. During
the absence of a queen...
...the balance of Gemini
has tilted toward evil.
Yes.
As queen, you must restore
Gemini to its original balance.
You must meet a kindred spirit
on the planet called Earth.
When this girl bestows us with
the light of goodness...
...you will become the true queen.
Choose this human
you have acknowledged.
My kindred spirit is...
...this girl.
Hi, Sis.
I take it you lost.
How can one kick possibly
calm me down?!
It can't! I'm furious!
I have the strongest magic, the
best reputation and best looks!
Why's that flower girl
the queen?!
Tell me! Somebody tell me!
Please?
I won't stand for it! I won't!
Why you... Tsunami!
Oh, yeah.
Rumiya. I came up
with a great idea.
Let it go, Sis.
It's a great plan. If we don't let
Tsunami restore the balance...
I know, but how do we stop her?
Still don't get it?
What if the girl she chose from
the odd planet does no good?
The council's decision
will be overturned.
And I will become the queen!
Queen Ramia!
Mean and wily as usual, Sis.
Juraihelm belongs to me.
Ha ha ha!
Ramia.
I'm going down to the Earth
for a bit.
Are you? Well, good luck.
Thanks, Ramia.
Tsunami's magical powers are
pathetic! Why is she queen?!
Especially when I possess
such great magical powers!
I'll find my kindred spirit
before Tsunami finds hers!
Shall we, Rumiya?
I'm going too?
Of course. We're going to make
my master plan work!
I call it, "The Plan to
Reinstate Queen Ramia."
No way.
You just thought it up now!
Miss Tsunami? What am I
supposed to be?
An earth animal, called a "cat."
A cat?
That's right.
You're going to be living
with an earthling girl...
...so I think that form is
best for you.
I know. Ryo-Ohki, why don't
you go and meet Sasami first?
I'm so nervous,
I don't think I'm ready.
Good luck! Thank you!
Miss Tsunami!
Umi no Hoshi Shopping District
Sasami.
Sasami?
Mom. Dad.
Ready for breakfast?
Or do you want to be late?
This is so typical!
Got to brush!
Come with me, Sasami!
Dad!
Take care!
Have a good day!
G-good morning.
I'm no good at these things.
Misao!
Sorry!
Thank goodness! I thought
you weren't coming.
My alarm didn't go off.
I'm off, Sasami.
Thanks, Dad. Take care.
Good night.
It's still morning.
I like how it sounds.
Good night.
Your dad's so cool, Sasami.
Isn't he?!
Miss Kawai! You're not allowed
to come to school by motorbike!
The class leader!
I'll report this to the teacher!
You broke the school rules!
No, please!
Looks like you're in trouble,
Miss Kawai.
What's it to you, Konoha?!
Nothing special.
Come with me.
Run for it, Misao!
What's this creature?!
Wait, Sasami!
I've found her.
That girl is Sasami Kawai.
Good morning, everybody.
My future dreams
And so...
...this morning I'd like you
to tell us your future dreams.
Majima, you go first.
I'll be a soccer player.
That's wonderful.
Good luck. Who's next?
Me!
Go ahead, Eimi.
I'm going to be an actress.
Well, that's impossible.
Me!
Yes, Konoha?
My cousin and I are going to
conquer the world!
All right, do your best.
How about you, Kyoko?
I want to be an adorable wife,
and have an adorable baby.
We'll do cosplay together!
Have you decided, Misao?
I gave it a lot of thought.
What's your dream? Tell me.
It's...
Misao Amano?
Yes?
It's your turn, Misao.
I, uh...
What's that? I can't hear you!
Um... a pianist.
I can't hear!
Can I tell you my dream?
Sure, go ahead.
I, uh...
I want to be a kind mother
like my mom.
Marry a cool guy like my dad.
And live happily ever after!
I'm sorry, Sasami.
That just isn't meant to be.
Your life is going to be anything
but normal, from now on.
Sasami.
Thanks for helping me in homeroom.
I heard your dream, Misao.
You want to be a pianist, right?
Don't tell anyone.
What a cutie!
Think it's a rabbit?
I think it's a cat.
Whatever. It's still cute.
Won't it bite?
No, it looks tame.
You're right.
Wait a minute.
You're the one that
saved me, earlier.
I'll thank him with some milk!
Hi, Mom!
You're just in time, Sasami.
Someone's been waiting for you.
A beautiful older girl.
She said she wants to
scout you.
Scout me?
Who could she be?
Hello.
Who are you?
My name's Tsunami.
Misao, I'll be working late
again tonight.
Dinner will be delivered at
the usual time. Eat it all up.
Leave early so you won't
be late for prep school.
Don 't forget anything...
Same old message.
Mom's always working.
Dad isn't coming back here.
I'm always home alone.
My! Even that gloomy
face of yours is nice.
Who are you?
My name is Ramia.
Candidate to be queen.
Although she lost.
Don't be afraid.
I came for you from
a magical kingdom.
A magical girl?!
Yes.
I want you to be " Pretty Sammy,"
a magical girl...
...and you must restore
world peace.
You can't make me!
I don't know what to do!
Please! You're the only one
who can do it!
No way! The bunny talked!
My name's Ryo-Ohki. I live
in the magical kingdom too.
Ryo-Ohki's purpose here is
to support you, Pretty Sammy.
He's a cat, as you can see.
Cat? Not a rabbit?
Well...
No, I'm a cat!
Sasami.
Take this magic baton and
transform into Pretty Sammy.
Magic baton?
It looks crummy.
Think so?
Sasami. Change into Pretty Sammy
and you'll have magical powers!
Magical powers?
If I had magic...
...I could get that
electronic organizer!
And clothes, and games!
Wow!
I'll try it!
I'm so glad.
The incantation is
"Pretty Mutation Magical Recall."
No problem!
Pretty Mutation...
...Magical Recall!
Pretty Sammy is here!
Huh. So this is the new,
magical me.
I don't want this.
Why not?
Because!
I look stupid in this.
If anyone finds out about this,
I'll be the laugh of the town.
I can't explain it but now I'm
Magical Girl Pretty Sammy!
What is that?!
What a freak!
That's against the rules!
Is that some kind of joke, Sasami?
That's what'll happen!
It'd be the worst!
There's nothing to worry about,
because you'll be Pretty Sammy.
That's not the point!
It's getting late.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
No!
Oh!?
Sasami?
I mean Pretty Sammy.
I'm counting on your help.
No!
How irresponsible...
Hello, CD Vision.
Hello. I'd like a CD delivered.
All right.
4 chome, number 16.
Thank you very much.
Okay, get going.
Go and give Tsunami's chosen girl,
Sasami, a hard time.
There. Handle the rest, Rumiya.
Wait, Sis!
Bye-bye.
It's your job! You can't leave!
No way!
What happened to that scout?
She left.
Oh, yeah? What was she
scouting for, anyway?
For magical girls...
Is this for delivery, mom?
Yes.
I'll take it.
Look after him.
All right.
You're sure cute.
I hope I wasn't too mean.
How can she expect me to
suddenly become a magical girl?
What should I do?
Sasami!
- Why did you follow me?!
- Because!
I came to this planet to help you!
Think of the trouble you'll cause me!
Sasami!
Go away!
Sorry, but good-bye!
He'll never find me here...
I hope.
4 chome, number 16.
It's close by.
That's strange.
It should be right here.
Who's there?
What?
What's going on?!
Stop!
Welcome, Sasami!!
Who are you?
My name is...
Tell you next time.
See you next week.
Once again, the girl you're watching...
...isn't the real me.
It's a girl...
...that was made up...
...for you and for our love.
You like my honesty.
That's what you say...
...but it's an illusion.
Deceiving others is a way of life.
It's a woman's romance.
I love you more than anyone.
I want to show you
a wonderful dream.
I love you so much.
I'm going to keep deceiving you.
I'll make you happier...
...than any other guy in the world.
The girl was a fiendish coach.
She came from her kingdom
to teach Sammy some skills.
Huh? I have to do squat jumps?!
That's bad for my health!
Coming next: The Crash Course.