Nandemo dekiru hazu dawa...
...soko ni aru mono de.
Juumon to atama ga...
... tsukai you!
Onaka ga sukeba...
...juumon wa PIPOPA.
Suguni osobaya-san ga...
...demae niyatte kuruwa.
Nemuku nattara...
...battan no juuten.
Yoko ni nareba...
...asa niwa...
...genki ni nareruwa.
Kimi nimo kanarazu aruwa.
Fushigi na chikara ga.
Yume mireba yume mo...
...yume janai.
A wooden building.
That'll be tough.
- It'll be okay!
- Huh?
Take a look! Isn't he brave?!
That's Ginji, my husband.
Gin... ji...?
H-Hey! Put those down!
People's lives are at stake!
It's okay!
Incredible...!
He leads the Kawai family,
after all!
- Bingo!
- Cool!
Ginji! I'm absolutely melting!
Mihoshi Mizutani
Huh...?
All I Want Is You
It's Sunday! Today's Sunday!
I don't have to get up early.
My precious time to myself!
Bon appetit!
You still don't get it, bonehead?!
I was wrong, sir!
Listen, Sato. You are NOT
a rotten apple, okay?
Sir...!
Ridiculous! There aren't any fervent
teachers like that, these days.
Oh...?
The teacher in charge of the
class next door acts fervent...
Ooh, sounds like
a fantastic teacher.
She's only getting
excited with herself.
If you look at it objectively,
it's nothing but a nuisance.
Huh?
T-The fervent teacher!
How did... where
did you come from?!
Well actually,
my apartment burned down.
So I thought I'd come and see
if I could stay with you.
You're the only one I could ask!
Oh. Well, that's just awful.
Kiyone!
Whoah! Whoah!
What did you do that for, Kiyone?
And don't come back!!
My precious, unbelievably
precious time to myself...!!
As if I'm gonna let someone
like Mihoshi ruin it!
Huh?
Hello, Amayuri residence.
Oh, Kiyone's mother?
I'm Mihoshi!
Yes! I'll be staying with
Kiyone for a little while.
Don't be so sure!
Here, give me that!
Hi, Mom?
What? Say that again...
Like I said, it's about
time for you to do it.
You can't stay single forever,
you know.
So I've set up a meeting
for your arranged marriage.
What?! Arranged marriage?!
It was out of your mom 's
love, dear. Out of love!
You are one lucky lady!
I have no interest in
arranged marriage.
Oh, what a shame.
The fellow is so handsome...
...you'll want to pounce on him!
Oh...!
Really?
Really, I'm telling you.
He saw your photograph,
and seemed very interested.
How charitable.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Anyway, you'll get
his picture, soon.
Miss Amayuri, special delivery.
Coming!
The day's set for the holiday,
the day after tomorrow.
T-That soon?
I've already set up your meeting,
SO GO AND GET THAT MAN!
- Bye!
- Wait, Mom!
Here, Kiyone!
Wow!
It's not that big a deal...
What...?!
Andou Toyokawa, 28 years old
Wow! What a nice-looking guy!!
H-He's nothing.
"Andou Toyokawa. 28 years old."
Wow! He graduated from
Harvard University.
And he's a first-rate violinist
who tours around the world!!
His family owns a lot
of land in Okayama.
- R-Really?
- Yes!
Completely different from a
grade school teacher, huh?
I don't want to hear
that from you!!
Arranged marriage, huh...
Give it your best, Kiyone!
Okay?
A prospect like this
hardly ever comes along!
I'll give you my
full-fledged support!!
I don't need any support.
How come?
I haven't made up my mind
to have an arranged marriage...
Oh! Then you'll never be
able to get married!
Keep your nose out of it!!
Umi no Hoshi
Elementary School
- Miss Kiyone!!
- Huh?
Are you really going to have
an arranged marriage?!
What?!
Congratulations, Miss Kiyone.
H-How did you know that?
Oh, everybody knows!!
And so, she got a call
from her mom.
Kiyone's gonna meet someone...
...for arranged marriage, Principal!
I see. Then we'll have to think
about a replacement for Miss Kiyone.
No! No! No!
NO!!
Mihoshi! YOU IDIOT!!
Figures. With the meeting near
at hand, she's full of energy.
Yes!
- And so, our country of Japan...
- No way!
-...is 5 + 6 x 2 to the perpendicular...
- You're kidding!
Miss Kiyone!
This is language class!
Yes, right.
So agriculture, fishing, and...
Miss Kiyone...!
These are what Beethoven composed...
She seems really agitated.
How come? She's gonna have
an arranged marriage, right?
Maybe she thinks this'll
be her last chance.
Poor Kiyone, full of
anticipation and insecurities...
I didn't know arranged marriage
was that tough!
What are you guys doing?!
We're supposed to be in class!!
Pretty Sammy, do
everything in your power...
...to help Miss Kiyone become happy.
She's plotting to restore
the balance by aiding love?!
I won't let that happen!
What is it, Sis?
Operation Zero is underway!
What's that?
Forget it, just get
Operation Zero going!
Yeah, but tell me what
it's about!
YOU THINK IT UP!!
Who would have known that
Kiyone was that worried...
We'll all do whatever
we can to help out!
I agree! Miss Kiyone's
so snappy, anyway!
It'll be way better
without her around!
Haida! That's the kind of thing
you should say quietly!
What do you think, Misao?
I think we should support her,
if she really wants to get married.
- Then it's settled!
- Wait a minute...
I don't know where she's
going to be meeting him.
What's this?
Hey you guys, take a look.
This is the hotel where
Miss Kiyone will meet him.
Where could this have fallen from?
Make sure you help out, okay?
You kind-hearted students.
I feel the same.
Yeah? Miss Kiyone's gonna meet
someone for arranged marriage?
It's the beginning of a
beautiful relationship.
And we've decided we're
going to help, too!
What a good intention!
Okay! I'll pitch in, as well!
Thanks, Dad!
Good for you, Ginji!
That's wonderful!
It's the natural thing to do,
as a father!
Uh-huh! Wonderful!
Hey, how did you meet,
Mom and Dad?
Huh?
Well, uh... I was a student, and
your dad was an upper-classman.
And that's uh, how we met...
Dad...?
Anyway, Sasami, I met your dad...
...and this happened!
And this!
And this, too!
And then we got married.
I don't really get it,
but, wow!
We're meeting tomorrow...
Not bad...
Kiyone...
Will you marry me?
Yes!
Yeah, as if...
You're going to wear
that suit again, huh?
You wore that to the entrance
ceremony in university...
...at graduation, and when you
were looking for work, too.
You sure like that suit,
don't you?
It's the only one I've got!!
Come on, Kiyone!
You'll be late unless you hurry up!
Aah! How come you're
tagging along, anyway?!
And what the heck's with that outfit?!
You're primped up more than me!
I'm just worried about you
being on your own.
I should be more worried about
your coming along with me!!
If you really care about my
happiness, then don't tag along!
Kiyone...
Don't tag along!!
Good luck, Kiyone!
'Cause this is your very,
very last chance!
Butt out!!
Here it is...
Are you Kiyone?
Y-Yes...
Let's not bother to go
through with this.
I'm gonna go home...
I tripped on a rock!
How awful!
Ouch!!
- Welcome!
- Huh?
I have a vague feeling there
was a plot to get me here...
Hm?
It seems familiar.
This all seems very familiar.
Hello. Your order?
Uh, I'll have a coffee.
Coming up.
I feel it. I distinctly
sense something mysterious.
Huh? What is it? A black out?
M-Mr. Toyokawa.
You must be Kiyone Amayuri.
Y-Yes!
No, he doesn't like me...?
It's a pleasure.
I'm Andou Toyokawa!
What?!
Kiyone! Kiyone! Kiyone!
Kiyone. You're just
as I imagined you.
Oh...
You've suffered, haven't you...
Yes...
- Wonderful!
- Nice guy!
- Do it!
- Perfect!
- Wow!
- Stupid!
- Yeah, maybe.
- Totally stupid!
Is that guy a Love-love Monster?
No, I think he's
just a regular guy.
Is that right? I worked in
the school cafeteria too...
...before I became well known.
I may not look it, but I've
had my share of suffering.
Oh, is that right? I've
had nothing but troubles...
What are your hobbies, Kiyone?
Um, reading.
Oh, I like reading books, too.
Especially encyclopedias.
I read them every day.
My, you certainly like to study.
We've got a lot in common,
don't we.
Yes, we do.
He seems so nice.
In that case, maybe...
This is cupid,
the cherub of love, Kiyone.
Y-yes...
Being able to see something
as unusual as this...
...it feels like destiny.
- Wonderful!
- Cute!
- Go for it!
- Perfect!
- Wow!
- Stupid!
- Totally stupid!
- TOTALLY stupid!
Something's definitely
strange about that guy!
Uh, I agree with you.
- Kiyone...
- Y-Yes...
This is it. He's gonna propose.
W-Who are you?!
Huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's wrap up this lovey-dovey
talk right about here.
All right?
Pixy Misa...!
Get off of here! How rude!
I don't wanna hear that from the
enemy of all the world's girls.
What's that supposed to mean?
Over there...!
I... I don't know her!
Oh? There's another one.
And there! And here!
And over here, too.
Honestly, how many women have
you made cry, you womanizer...?
I've told you! I don't know them!
I don't! I don't!
You're too stubborn to admit it!
In that case...
Calling Mystics!
Shattered
You're awful!!
Love-love Monster, Break-Up Girl
W-What's this monster?!!
You're awful!
You told me you loved me!!
I don't know what
you're talking about!
Begone!
Magical Barrier!!
Oh! My super-cool rainbow...!
How could you do this to me
when you had my heart...?
This is nothing to laugh at!
Transform into Sammy!
But I'm not really sure I want
to get involved in that...
Forget that, just do it!
Pretty Mutation...
...Magical Recall!
Magical Girl Pretty Sammy!
Give me back all the time
I gave to you!!
You're acting the part,
Break-Up Girl!
Stop right there!
Sammy will help you with
love and arranged marriage!
The would-be matchmaker
has arrived!
Finally arrived, huh, Sammy?
Misa! Send that monster back home!
No, no! You wish!
Nobody can put a stop
to that breakup!
Then I'll have to use force!
Magical Barrier!!
Ow!
Incredible magical power!
Fantastic! Keep it up,
Break-Up Girl!
Oh, my. Sammy's in real trouble.
Good luck, Sammy.
That Tsunami...
she's so relaxed!
But today will be
the end of Sammy!
Aah! What'll I do?!
Go for it, Sammy!
Don't give up! Have guts!
Go and crush that freak!
Sure, easy for you to say...
- Leave it to me!
- Huh?
Count on me when you're
in trouble, Sammy!
I'm Sasami's dad. Ginji Kawai!
I'll come, even if
you don't call!
Cool, Ginji!
All right, let go of that man.
Oh, what a nice man!
What are you doing,
Break-Up Girl?!
Use your barrier
and pulverize him!
Yes, Mistress Misa!
Magical Barrier!
Stop these fruitless antics.
Won't you seek a wonderful
future with me, lady?
Oh, what a heart-wrenching line!
Perhaps I will...!
Oh, Ginji!
Hey...
Ooh! You're making me
jealous, here!!
- Ginji!!
- Honoka...!
GINJI, YOU JERK!!!
Ooh...
She'd conquer the world.
Now, Sammy!
W-What do you mean, "Now"...?
Might be a bit awkward between
them, but now's your chance!
Uh, yeah...
Converge, magic powers of justice!
Pretty...Coquettish...Bomber!
How could you-u!!!
- You did it!
- Way to go, Sammy!
Count on me! Right?
- Ginji!
- Huh?
Oh, Honoka. What a
great punch that was!
You taught me that one.
Just like my mom and dad...
Kiyone! Hang in there, Kiyone!
Kiyone...!
You came to...
Mihoshi. Where's Mr. Toyokawa?
Oh, right. I wonder
what happened...?
- Sammy!
- Huh?
Oh, you're the one I've been
looking for, Pretty Sammy!
It's Miss Kiyone you're
supposed to be with, remember?
I can't believe I've met
a woman as wonderful as you!
Marry me, Sammy!
But I'm still just a kid!
Age doesn't matter,
if it's love!
It matters quite a bit.
Kiyone...!
Cupid... my cupid of love...!
Oh! Wait!
How heartbreaking, Kiyone!
It's inexcusable!
So, like I said,
I'm just not ready to...
Huh? Miss Mihoshi...
You can't go trampling all over
a maiden's heart like that!!
YOU IDIOT!!!
Sammy...!!
I knew Sammy could do it.
Hey, Ramia?
Huh?
Absurd!!
Why was the balance restored
when she was rejected?!!
Should I put up with this?!
What the hell's going on, here?!
Kiyone...
I'm so sorry about
what happened today.
I did something uncalled for...
-Just forget it.
- Kiyone!
I think I was rushing things.
Marriage is a lifetime commitment,
so I need to give it a lot more thought.
One day, the man I was
destined to meet will...
- Here!
- Huh?
The principal told me about him.
There won't be any problems
with this guy.
And you can count on me,
for all my support!
NO!!!
No! No! No! No! No!
What's the matter?
See what a catch he is?
I've had my fill of
arranged marriage!!
Anata ga mitsumeteru
watashi wa kyou mo...
...hontou no watashi janai.
Kono koi no tame ni...
...anata no tame ni...
... tsukuriageta onna na no yo.
Shoujiki na tokoro ga iito...
...anata iu keredo.
Sore wa maboroshi.
Taburakasu no ga ikikata yo.
Onna no roman yo.
Dareyori mo suki dakara.
Iiyume misete agetakunaru.
Anata ga tottemo suki dakara.
Damashi tsuzukeru wa.
Sekaijuu no dareyori...
...shiawase na otoko ni shiteageru.
The boss! A mysterious man
controls the school.
He's a strong fighter, values relationships,
and he has a soft spot for women!
He's always wearing his school
uniform, and wooden sandals!
Coming next:
The Fellow Called Boss.
It's important for men to have
a strong fighting spirit!