Nandemo dekiru hazu dawa...
...soko ni aru mono de.
Juumon to atama ga...
...tsukai you!
Onaka ga sukeba...
...juumon wa PIPOPA.
Suguni osobaya-san ga...
...demae ni yatte kuruwa.
Nemuku nattara...
...battan no juuten.
Yoko ni nareba...
...asa niwa...
...genki ni nareruwa.
Kimi nimo kanarazu aruwa.
Fushigi na chikara ga.
Yume mireba yume mo...
...yume janai.
Two magical girls, Pixy Misa VS. Pretty
Sammy. The people who suddenly came...
...and put a complete stop to their
magical competition on Friday...
...were the bewitching beauties,
the Pixy Mrs. Team.
Otherwise known as the Team,
"Lovely Madams."
Sammy counters with her
Pretty Coquettish Bomber.
But Sammy's Pretty Space is destroyed
by the Lovely Madams' Lovely Space.
Sammy's lethal technique doesn't work.
Does she have any other shots?
What fate's in store for Sammy?!
What fate's in store for the world?!
They'll be like candles in
the wind, of course!
Sammy, hurry and let them do
you in and overthrow you!
Then I'll be queen of Juraihelm!
The one and only me!
Farewell, The Team,
"Lovely Madams"!
Oh!
The balance of the scales
has completely slipped!
Pretty Sammy's lost!
What in the world
will happen to me?
Whether I'll be queen
remains to be seen.
Oh, what a fix, what a mess,
what shall I do?
What a fix, what a mess,
What shall I do?
Sammy...
Sammy! Wake up, Sammy!
Ryo-Ohki...
You're awake.
Where am I?
Misa captured you!
Oh...
Anyway, you've gotta try
to escape somehow!
But how?
Magic! Use your magic!
But if I can't wield the baton,
I can't use my magic.
Too bad, hey, Sammy.
To think the opening story will
be adorned with this mood...!
It makes me super happy!
Umi no Hoshi Elementary School
The world's one and only
Magical Girl Pretty Sammy...
...has lost the battle against the self-
professed evil magical girl, Pixy Misa.
Pretty Sammy has been captured.
Occupying the area
surrounding Sammy are Misa...
...and the mysterious group
calling itself, "Lovely Madams."
Even the police, who rushed to the
scene, cannot get imprudently close.
The government is regarding
this situation as serious...
...and has moved in the Self-
Defense Forces to save Sammy.
Also, a beautiful women warning
has been issued in the Kanto area.
The strategic headquarters
has been established on-site...
...and the rescue operation
is about to get underway.
This is Saotome, reporting live.
So that's the magical girl, huh.
Poor girl. Hey, Captain?
Can people win against
magic with science?
I wouldn't know such a thing. But our
job here is to rescue Pretty Sammy.
She's solved a number of troubles
up till now, so to repay her...
...our mission here
must be a success.
Yes, sir.
The national army division will
arrive from the east any moment.
Right. "Operation Rescue Sammy"
will commence when they arrive!
- Captain?
- What is it?
It seems we're losing some of
the Team, "Lovely Madams"...
- W-What?!
- See?
Fool! Why didn't you
report this sooner?!
S-Sorry, sir!
Attention! We're going all out
to rescue Pretty Sammy.
However, this is a rescue
operation, not a war!
Don't forget it!
A person?!
No, that's the target
headquarters told us about!
She's a beauty!
Absurdly beautiful!
Beauty Rating of 78%!
That's four times the norm!!
Lovely!
Mrs. Kiss!
That's the power of the Team,
"Lovely Madams."
Land Hawk was headed this way,
but communications were cut off!
What...?
C-Captain. This doesn't look good.
They must've been attacked!
Don't let your mind run amok!
What about the air troops?
Doesn't look good!
I can't reach them!
I knew it! They've been attacked!
I told you not to run amok!
Captain! Telephone!
It's me.
Oh, Prime Minister!
My apologies.
Yes. Yes.
What?! You'll send the 7th
Fleet for our backup?!
Jesus...!
Lovely Madam voice!
Where are you off to,
my darling?
Japanese karaoke!
I've got another 50 songs in me!
Well, Kenji?
Both the Self-Defense Forces and the
UN Forces seem to have been attacked.
Darn it! Isn't there
some way to help Sammy?
Aha, I see.
Thought so. The Team, "Lovely
Madams" has incredible abilities.
Oh, Professor Washu! Don't just play with
your gadgets! Can't we do something?!
Like using missiles, or ultra
special weapons, or something?
Well actually, if the Self-Defense
forces could get blown away...
...an ordinary citizen like me
couldn't save Sammy.
That's not grounded in reality.
Sammy...
Ryo-Ohki. I'm hungry.
Me, too.
Mistress Misa. Sorry
to keep you waiting.
Please, help yourself.
Wow! That really looks great!
Oho! You've got the look
of a glutton.
You want to have this, Sammy?
Want it?
Of course, I'll give it to you.
NOT!!
Wow! Wonderful!!
I put caviar inside the cake.
The wisdom of the Lovely
Madams, if you will.
Hooray for the Lovely Madams!
Well, Sammy?
I don't want your cake!
Still giving me lip, are you?!
- Third!
- Right here!
W-What're you gonna do?
Why, you should know that!
I'm gonna tickle you, of course!
Huh?
Stop it!
That tickles!
You've gotta smile and be happy;
that's what life's about!
Sammy, let me hear more
of that beautiful laugh!
I'm dying! I'm dying!
Sammy!
Looks like Sammy's having fun.
If you get any more zoned out,
I'll finish you off!
Sorry...
Sammy's in trouble. Can't
something be done?!
But we got word from the top,
over the phone just now...
...and they said that WE must
handle the rest by ourselves...
I was thinking, sir.
Fleeing might be in order;
escapees come out on top.
You call yourself a soldier?!
I think so...
The Lovely Madams have now
regrouped on the school grounds.
They're on alert, radially
surrounding Pretty Sammy.
They're so strong,
and there's six of them.
There's nothing we can
do to stop them.
You still mouthing off?!
But considering their strength
against these troops alone...
Seems you're in a bit of a trouble.
Who the heck are you?!
I'm the father of Sasami, the girl
rumored to look a lot like Pretty Sammy.
The name's Ginji.
Hey! This is off limits
for civilians!
That move...!
Oops. Seems I've not-so
accidentally dropped my wallet.
Would you get it?
Oh, my!
You were a member of the
special task force SWAT team?!
A long time ago.
You must've come here
with some kind of plan.
The Lovely Madams are
undoubtedly lovely.
"Pretty Power" probably
can't stand up to them.
But what about "Dandy Power"?
Counter "Lovely" with...
...I see! "Dandy"!
In that case, just
leave this up to me.
I have confidence, when it
comes to being a dandy.
"Ginji," wasn't it?
Would you take over this?
- This "Dandy" plan.
- Sure thing.
Ginji!
You're leaving, Ginji...
Yes. I don't know why...
...but seeing Pretty Sammy is like
seeing my very own daughter.
Figure it out already, Ginji
Yes, that's true.
You, too.
Take care.
Johnny.
It's Ginji.
I'll say just one thing.
You're using "Dandy Power"
against "Lovely Power."
In theory, you're not mistaken.
But that alone won't beat
the Lovely Madams.
Is there some other way?
There's some remaining energy
in Sammy's Pretty Space.
I wonder if that girl knows the
meaning behind the heart marks?
Thank you, Catherine.
It's Washu.
Hang on, Sammy.
I'll rescue you, somehow.
I am the future queen!
Tsunami...!
Oh, Ramia.
Sammy, poor Sammy,
she's in quite a bind!
Oh, my. Oh, my.
Please, Ramia?
Won't you dance with me?
Come on, please?
All right.
The balance of the scales
has completely slipped!
Pretty Sammy's lost!
What in the world
will happen to me?
Whether I'll be queen
remains to be seen.
Oh, what a fix, what a mess,
what shall I do?
What a fix, what a mess,
How much could you bear
to bare in a polar bear swim?
Freezing...
Don't lick icy sticks or
you'll stick to the icy sticks.
Like it? This is the
Mrs. Love-love Blizzard!
If they keep up such bad jokes,
I'll freeze to death.
Yeah!
Now, let's move on to the climax!
Yes, Misa!
The humiliation
you've put up with...
...and the anger and sadness!
We'll throw it all
back in the face...
-...of Pretty Sammy, over there!
- Yeah!
Oh, yeah, baby!
What?!
Keep attacking until Dandy gets there!
Yes, sir!
Come on, Sammy!
It's good to stuff
a rock inside, huh.
That's dangerous! Stop it!
Very cunning!
Lovely Madams' Snowball!
- D-Damn!
- We're snowmen!
Now suck your thumbs and watch us!
They can't even find their thumbs,
let alone suck on them!
- Misa! Finish Sammy off!
- Yeah!
All right, whatever.
No!
Sammy! This is good-bye!
Ow! Ow! Ow!! Ow!!
She's weak.
Are you okay, Sammy?
Dad!
I'm Sasami's dad,
not your dad, Sammy.
Oh, yeah, right.
That was SO unfair!
Mrs.! Go for it!
Lovely!
Dandy!
What a dandy face!
I have a soft spot for
guys like him!
He stopped the Lovely Madams
in their tracks!
Unreal!
No, this is just temporary.
That's right. Your Pretty Space
is adorable, and nothing more.
Oh, how adorable!
Precisely! Even this monkey
can be adorable.
Trying to beat the Lovely Madams
with something adorable is a joke!
Then what'll we do?
Catherine told me this.
What you're lacking is love!
The power of love!
Pour the power of love
into the Pretty Space!
That's easy for you to say.
But I'm just a kid!
I don't know anything
about love!
Just fake it for now!
But, with who?
He's right there!
Beside you!
What?!!
During all that, we were
surrounded by the Lovely Space.
It's love! Show them
the love between you two!
- Ryo-Ohki...
- Sammy...
Um...
...I love you, you know.
You can't be shy!
But the important thing
is to be a TEENY bit shy!
Sammy, I love you!
More heartrending!
I really love you.
More bittersweetly!
Huh? Hey, why aren't
you starting the battle?!
The Lovely Madams are
soldiers of love.
We cannot interfere with
matters of the heart.
Ryo-Ohki.
Sammy!
I love you.
Me, too.
Throw much stronger feelings
at each other!
I love you! I really
love you, Ryo-Ohki!
Sammy! I love you more
than anyone in the world!
I'm so happy to be with you!
Let's stay together forever, Sammy!
Ryo-Ohki, you're embarrassing me...
That's the ticket!!
Way to go,
Magical Girl Pretty Sammy.
Wonderful!
But it's still nothing compared
to our Lovely Space.
You said it!
Why? What's happening,
Mrs. One?!
They're calling for me.
Oh, where did Miyuki get to...?
That's a good boy.
What to do...
Satoshi and Saki are calling me.
I have to go!
No way, One! Keep focused!
- Our Lovely Space...!
- It's pretty!
That's the power of love!
Now's your chance, Sammy!
Converge, magical powers of justice!
Pretty...Coquettish...Bomber!
I'm in mega-trouble!
Huh?
Mrs.!
Don't cry, Misa.
You'll make a mess of
your precious pixy face.
Misa, you can use Lovely
Power, too. Just like us.
- We guarantee it.
- Yeah!
Don't leave me!
Misa, being affectionate,
and having sympathy...
...those are the fundamental
points of being a Mrs.
Mrs.!
There, there.
- Satoshi.
- Oh...
Sorry I'm so late.
There, there. Sorry, Saki.
Mrs... I've definitely received it.
Your Lovely Power!
W-We're back to normal...
The magical girl did it.
Yeah.
We did it! We did it!
Way to go, Sammy!
You still had all that power!
No wonder Tsunami picked
you to be the magical girl!
Thanks, Ryo-Ohki!
Ow, you're squishing me, Sammy!
Oops, sorry.
The balance of the scales
has completely returned!
Pretty Sammy's won!
Hooray! Hooray! She did it again!
Hooray! Hooray!! A perfect "10"!
No...
Hooray! Hooray! She did it again!
- NOOO!!!
- Hooray! Hooray!! A perfect "10"!
Here are the notes from today.
Thanks.
Are you okay, Misao?
Yeah, I'm fine. I just fell
down the stairs, that's all.
I made some cake, Misao.
Would you like some?
Thanks a lot!
It's fantastic!
Yeah, it is!
I tried putting
some caviar inside.
That's the wisdom
of the Lovely Madams.
Then, hooray for
the Lovely Madams.
Yeah, hooray!
Imasara ieta girijanai keredo...
...watashi wa warukattawa.
Otokowa ikuramo iru, nante...
...choushini notte orimashita.
Mayonakano juuni-jiwa,
Darenidemo yattekuru,
...Cinderella dake janai.
Imasara ieta giri janai keredo...
...yononaka nametemashita.
Konomama nantoka naru, nante...
...choushini notte orimashita.
A girl named Hikari Asahina
transfers to my school.
She says she's come to our town
in search of Ryo-Ohki.
Coming next:
You Are the Sunshine Girl.
I'm sorry, Hikari. But I
wanna stay with Ryo-Ohki.