Nurse Witch
Komugi
R
She Who Succeeds R
Lilia-chan was amazing!
She was shining so brightly.
I think some of her power rubbed off on me.
I'm going to work even harder!
Yoshida Clinic
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Usa-P?
W-Welcome home, pyon, Komugi-chan.
See you later, Tsukasa-chan.
Yeah.
I'm home...
Welcome home, poko.
Welcome home, nyan.
K-Komugi-chan...
Did you miss me while I was visiting
the Fanta-C World, pyon?
It was nice and quiet.
Actually, I forgot you were even gone.
Ouch!
You're so mean, pyon!
This whole time, I've been thinking about taking
a bath with you when I got back, pyon!
I'd never do that.
These are for you, pyon.
Fanta-C World manju, Fanta-C World cookies,
Fanta-C World soda, and Fanta-C World crêpes.
Wow, thanks!
So, what happened?
Well, actually...
Whisper whisper, mumble mumble, pyon pyon.
What? A girl monster stole all your Fanta-C Cards?
Yeah, pyon...
We'll steal them back, pyon.
My ears will stand at attention
when another monster appears!
I'll get them then for sure, pyon!
It can't be helped, I guess.
I'm not sure what's going on, but fine.
I'm going to rest for a bit, then, pyon.
Hey, what did you do while I was gone, pyon?
I made a new friend.
She's a super popular idol named Lilia-chan.
It's this girl.
She's cute, pyon...
Poko?!
Nyanyan?!
It's her!
What about her?
She's the mysterious girl monster
who stole my Fanta-C Cards, pyon!
What are you talking about? There's no way.
It's definitely her, pyon!
Huh?
You still haven't found Maid-chan or Sister-chan
in their un-transformed forms.
How can you be so sure?
It's most definitely her, pyon!
It's her, pyon! Let's go find out, pyon!
How do we do that, though?
She's a monster, pyon!
An enemy we must defeat, pyon!
Sheesh. Fine, fine.
Okay, okay. Goodnight.
Unbelievable. There's no way
Lilia-chan is a monster.
There's...
...no way.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Yeah.
You look cute again today.
Did you sense anything?
Maybe, maybe not...
What does that mean?
My ears aren't stiff, pyon.
But I sense something sort of off, pyon.
It's just a little... I guess
you could say I'm half stiff.
Half stiff? So you mean...
She isn't a monster, poko.
See?
But I knyow I'm sensing something.
I hope you have fun today.
Yeah!
Thanks for inviting us to
your Tokyo Skydome concert!
How very gracious of Lilia to invite us, too.
Now, now... As long as we're here,
let's enjoy ourselves.
We're finally here!
Lilia-chan's going to be singing, though.
But we can see what our Tokyo
Skydome concert might be like.
She filled an arena that
accommodates 570,000 people.
Incredible.
That's about the same as
the population of Tottori.
It's still just a distant dream.
But Kokona-chan, Tsukasa-kun,
someday we'll sing here, too.
Yeah.
Together.
I'll do my best again today.
I'll put on the greatest performance.
So my fans will enjoy it.
So my friends will enjoy it.
And so I can gain even more
fans and friends.
Come in.
The time has come.
Okay.
As I scatter diamonds to make
even ordinary days glitter
I imagine a special version of myself
This is a place where dreams, hopes,
and aspirations can come true
Komugi-chan, Komugi-chan!
What, Usa-P?
My ears are stiff, pyon! It's a monster, pyon!
But it's not a place easily reached
What? Where?
There, pyon!
That's an Infrared Camera Monster, nyan.
This stage isn't easily reached
That monster will make your
clothes transparent, poko.
Lilia-chan is in danger!
Far beyond the brilliance
What's wrong?
Uh, I need to go to the bathroom.
Everyone has a chance within their grasp
M-Me, too.
I need to powder my nose.
Uh, I'll go to another bathroom.
A-Are you sure?
I feel like going this way.
I guess I'll go that way.
O-Okay, see you later.
Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
Shuffle, shuffle.
Fidget, fidget. Fidget, fidget.
Parasol shiny chloroform!
Marisol miral sparklism!
Pretty flower sunshine!
Chanting it deciphers the code
programmed into the incantation,
Shiny lovely tenipole!
Flaming miral penifore!
Fluffy coquettish player!
scanning their entire bodies.
The rays turn Komugi's caring
heart, Kokona's dutiful heart,
and Tsukasa's loving spirit into Amazoni-N Cells,
activating their maximum Tombo-E potential
and reconstructing their bodies and costumes,
completing the Chan-G.
On average, the transformation
takes 0.02 seconds.
Huh? What is this?
Transparent, transparent...
Infrared rays make things transparent.
Even if you're wearing clothes,
I can see right through them.
Transparent, transparent...
I can see right through to your bones.
Transparent, transparent!
Hold it right there!
...rent?
Who are you?
You can count on me to disinfect your heart.
I'm the Magical Nurse!
A pure heart for a pure world.
Magical Maid!
Have you said your prayers?
Magical Sister!
What's going on?
Maybe it's a skit.
Is that Sister-chan?
Infrared Camera Monster!
We won't let you...
...touch Lilia-chan!
Transparent...
I've got a perfect shot!
I've been waiting for you.
Lilia-chan?
...rent?
Worldwide Revolutionary!
Super Excellent Marvelous!
Top of Top Idol!
There's another monster over here!
Sticking a Fan-C Card on her stuffed animal,
Kumami, turned it into a monster.
Though it can't speak or move
on its own, by fusing with her,
it can control Lilia's body.
During this time, Lilia is unconscious.
By the way, it takes 0.015
seconds for her to transform.
That's 0.005 seconds faster
than the magical girls.
Standing at the pinnacle of the
world and the pinnacle of idols,
I am Lilia of Idora!
Top Beam!
The "Heart-Pounding Galactic
Beautiful Girl Beam of the
Glittering Supernova Next to Your Heart"
is fired when the enzymes produced by
Amazoni-N Cells rapidly
break down evil hearts,
making them transparent and purifying them.
My film was exposed! How pleasurable!
Transparent! I'm turning transparent!
Lilia-chan!
I knew it, pyon.
She's a monster, poko.
Nya've gotta defeat her!
I was the final card.
Now Lilia has all the Fan-C Cards.
This power will
grant her wish!
Lilia...
What?
What is this?
What's going on?
Lilia...
Yuto?
This is the power of the Fan-C Cards.
The "Fan" in Fan-C Card means
the fans who support you.
Really, pyon?
I'm surprised, poko.
I had no idea.
This power will turn everyone
in the world into Lilia's fans.
Then she'll never be lonely again.
I will make everyone in the world a fan of Lilia,
who took such good care of me.
Every year, 365 days, 24 hours,
and every day, 1,440 minutes, and 86,400 seconds,
they will continue thinking only of Lilia!
Lilia...
Lilia, Lilia...
You can't do that!
I can't?
Even if they become your fans that
way, they won't be real fans.
Yeah, they'd be fake.
You think that would make her happy?
Tens of thousands of times
the population of Tottori...
Seven billion fans,
all for Lilia!
Lilia...
She won't listen.
What should we do? We have to stop her.
You have to use the Triple Tombo-E Girl Attack!
The Triple Tombo-E Girl Attack?
Three Tombo-E Girls...
...combine their strength to invoke...
...a fan-nya-stic power!
Did you just come up with that?
Of course not, pyon!
This is fate, pyon!
Fate?
Okay, let's do it!
Let's go! The Triple Tombo-E Girl Attack!
Magical Relieve
Starlight Stage!
Now this is the "Power that Whispers
to Modern, Young, Handsome,
and Intense Ladies to Shine Even Brighter!"
The Triple Tombo-E Girl Attack:
Power that Whispers to
Modern, Young, Handsome,
and Intense Ladies to Shine Even Brighter!
It combines the Magical Sister's prayers,
the Magical Maid's subservient spirit,
and the Magical Nurse's healing thoughts
into a ray of light that shines upon all hearts.
What is this?
Let's pray to the shining stars
Forever and ever starlight stars
Seeing myself in fashionable
clothes in the mirror
Hey, wait
They don't look that good on me
But if I start running in my own way
My youth should shine even brighter
On three, we'll make our dreams blossom
To the end of the universe
Let's pray to the shining stars
I'm sure my heart is reaching them
Let's connect the shining present to our futures
Forever and ever, endless starlight stars
You'll be fine, Lilia-chan.
But if you ever get hurt,
I, the Magical Nurse,
will heal your wounds!
...we'll never lose!
Let's pray to the shining stars
I'm sure my heart is reaching them
Let's connect the shining present to our futures
Enjoy this moment in this endless story
It always starts from right here
Forever and ever, endless starlight stars
Huh?
Thank goodness.
It's over.
Let go! This is mine, pyon!
Finders keepers, poko!
They're all mine, nyan!
Hey, wait!
Huh?
Since the mission is over...
I'm not a Tombo-E Girl anymore?
What?!
Komugi-chan and Tsukasa-chan?
Komugi and Kokona?
Kokona-chan and Tsukasa-kun?
We should...
...train more, and then, as idols...
...perform here together someday.
Sister-chan.
Yu-nii?
Yuto...
So you're Sister-chan, Tsukasa?
Um, I...
I had hoped that you were.
Huh?
I hoped that Sister-chan was you.
Yuto...
I like you.
I like you, too!
What?!
Oh, my.
Yuto!
Tsukasa.
What? Wait, Yu-nii!
Since when have you...
Wait, what's going on?
Um, I...
I'll explain later.
And I expect an explanation
from you guys, too.
What have I been doing?
I was dreaming!
What happened after that?
The concert was canceled because
the set was destroyed.
But it was held several days later,
and it was a huge success.
Lilia, you're beautiful.
Hime-P used her mysterious powers
to turn Kumami-chan into a mascot.
Now she can be by Lilia-chan's side forever.
Good for you, Kumami-chan!
Thanks, everyone!
My fans are my treasure!
Usa-P and the other two took the Fan-C Cards
and returned to the Fanta-C World.
I hear they're living happily under Hime-P.
Hime-P, you're such a benevolent widow,
to turn Kumami into a mascot, pyon.
Indeed I am.
You're a widow among widows, poko.
It gives me chills, poko.
Praise me more.
You're the greatest widow, nyan.
Say, let's get our meow on.
Oh, my. Calm down, boys.
Wait. Your. Turn.
There, there...
Hey, come to think of it, I wonder who
gathered the most Fan-C Cards...
Well, not that it matters.
Lilia-chan's busy, so we don't see her often.
But let's hang out again sometime!
It's a promise!
Kokona-chan has been training
for marathons, too.
She's even going to join the regular
cast of a marathon program.
Good! Keep your back straight!
That's it! Don't give up!
Yes, sir! I'll train even harder!
Nijigaoka Academy
Yu-nii was scouted by the
producer of the swim meet.
He's going to be debuting in America.
He won't be back for ten years.
My name is Yuto.
Wait for me.
I'll head there someday.
Misuzu-sensei became a female pro wrestler.
She may be the first schoolteacher
to also be a pro wrestler.
Iron Claw!
Misuzu-sensei, you can do it!
You can do it!
Now's your chance, yo!
That's it! Get her!
Giant Swing!
Flying Body Attack!
Victory!
They're making a Buri Bara anime after all?
Yeah! We're going to start dubbing it soon.
I'm so excited for Kokonacchi's Short Ribs.
I wonder if they'll make merchandise.
Lilia-chan's going to be playing
Skirt Steak instead of Yu-nii.
She can imitate a boy's voice.
Lilia-chan is so versatile.
Come on. You'd better get
going, or you'll be late.
Okay!
I'm Yoshida Komugi. 14 years old.
Sagittarius, blood type O.
My favorite food is Japanese sweets.
My motto is "Let's Komugication!"
Ow...
Komugi-chan, it's been a while, pyon!
There's trouble, pyon!
Usa-P? What's wrong?
The Fanta-C World and Earth are
in danger of being destroyed, pyon!
You need to transform immediately,
pyon! Become a Tombo-E Girl...
No, a powered-up Tombo-E Girl R, pyon!
R?!
End