Good and bad news, you say?
I'd like to report it to you
first, Prince Sion.
Is that okay?
Prince Abel, how's your wound?
It's fine,
your retainer saved me.
It feels like Prince Abel
got a bit manlier again...
Princess Mia? It looks like your
face is a bit red, are you okay?
It's nothing!
Did you push yourself
too hard to get here?
I think it's you who's
pushing yourself too hard...
Geez, I don't care anymore!
You ignored me and did
something dangerous just now.
And Sion, he almost cut
Prince Abel for real too!
It's outrageous!
So you call Prince Sion
just with his name now...
It's just to hide our identity,
there's no deep meaning to it.
Ah, I see. That's a relief.
Is he jealous?
Gee, can't help it then.
As an adult,
I'll suggest something nice for you!
Let's call each other
by name, like that!
Ah, erm...
I... Don't mind too.
You can...
Erm...
Just call me Mia...
But in exchange, I'd like to...
Erm...
Call you as Abel...
Really?
If that's so, then, Mi-Mia...
Yes!
A-Abel...
Prince Abel, Mia.
I have something to tell you.
I have to apologize.
What do you mean?!
This revolt was caused by a rogue squad
from our intelligence agency, Wind Crow.
What did you say?!
A goddess! A saint!
Wisdom! Intelligence!
Kindness! Fraternity! That is it!
I am a princess, as you know
I am the heroine in this life
I am!
Throughout life, I am on easy mode-going
through as a helpless princess
If that's what you thought,
then go ahead!?
The world is always dependent
on the direction of wind
There are too many useless
things and people, seriously
I can't believe in anybody
I have noticed that, the world is
so heartless
That is not good,
This is not good
It is not good,
everything is not good
The reality is harsh
Alteration... alteration... alteration...
Everything is going to be altered...!
I am a princess, as you know
I am the heroine in this life
Even in a sad scenario
I am going to rewrite
everything, everything
Because, because,
I am a princess
At least of my own story
I must enjoy it as much as possible
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I have to live with
all my strength
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Just wait and see!
I shall alter my own destiny!
A goddess! A saint! Wisdom! Intelligence!
Kindness! Fraternity! That is it!
But, that makes sense.
In both of the rebellions
in the Empire and Remno Kingdom
Sunkland was always
the one who profits.
If that's so, all the things
that led me to the guillotine,
was actually caused by
the people who judged me?!
This feels like the time when I
was forced to bow and apologize...
It doesn't feel nice
to look at it at all...
I wonder what Prince Abel would do?
Strictly speaking, the one who brought
this to Remno Kingdom is not Sion himself,
and the one who has to be
responsible is the king of Sunkland.
But, it'll go against
Sion's conscience.
Besides, Prince Abel also has
all the rights to condemn Sion...
Raise your head, Prince Sion.
But...
Royals have their own ways
of taking responsibility.
What we have to do,
is govern for the sake of people.
And to do that, I thought I had to
suppress this war by using military power.
But, there was someone who showed me
a way to stop this conflict.
A way to end this ridiculous battle.
There was someone who shone a light
on the path that we should take.
If that's so, what we need to do
is just walk down that path.
Don't you agree?
Even if I bow down,
and ask for forgiveness,
it only serves my
self-satisfaction.
...is what you're saying, huh...
We were saved, both you and me.
We just need to walk the path that
the Wisdom of the Empire has shown.
Seems like you managed
to forgive him, that's great.
Well, to be honest, I can't really
say that my dad is free of guilt too.
I can't just put
all the blame on Sunkland.
Mia, it's all thanks to you.
I'm glad.
But really...
Sion, so you finally learned
the taste of failure.
Failure is normal
for humans after all.
No human is able to
live a perfect life.
That's why, at the very least,
we all deserve a second chance.
Especially me!
It's carved deep in Mia's heart,
that in the previous timeline, she wasn't
given any chance to redeem herself at all.
But if what happened
in Remno Kingdom this time
were to happen in
the potential rebellion in the Empire,
I can't say this guy who'd act and stand
in the name of justice, is free of guilt.
If I think of it that way,
it made me a bit pissed.
In this situation, I think I can put
him through the wringer for a bit...
Sion, so that you won't forget this
failure, I'll carve it deep into you.
What do you mean?
When a mistake is punished,
that's when the case is closed.
Punishment?!
Hold on, Princess Mia!
No... She's right.
I'll comply and
receive the punishment.
What should I do?
What a big heart you have!
If that's so,
please stand over there.
I have something that I've trained
myself so much, all this time.
Do you know? Your kicks aren't
painful at all, you know?
The strength of the kick that
I've trained ever since that day!
I'll make it as
painful as it can be!
Go and carve it into your heart,
along with that pain, Sion!
It doesn't hurt at all...
What is she doing...?
Don't tell me, it's on purpose?
To the public,
it looks like I was punished by that.
But in reality, I'm the only one who knows
that I'm not receiving any punishment...
And so, this crime, this
suffering, will never disappear.
From now on,
when I act in the name of justice,
I'll have to rethink whether
I made the right decision or not.
And then,
just like how I was forgiven,
I will rethink whether my enemy
should be forgiven or not too...
Carry out justice,
and behave righteously...
Those words were taught
to me since childhood.
The real meaning, the weight of it,
and the difficulty...
This is the first time
I've experienced it.
Um, Sion?
Mia, I'm grateful.
You really are the Wisdom of the Empire.
He got kicked and thanked me
instead, what the heck?
If you didn't say it to me,
I'm sure I wouldn't have figured it out.
Figure it out? About what?
What did he figure out?
Besides, he mentioned
the Wisdom of the Empire...
A kick has nothing to do with wisdom!
Does he mean that strength
and angle are important in a kick?
Since I'm good at it, what if he
asked me to do a kick another time?
I, I see, that's great then...
By the way, do you know where
Prime Minister Dasayev is being held?
According to my intel, he's being
monitored in a city called Senia.
Prince Abel,
do you know where this is?
No, but there might be someone
among the soldiers who knows.
If that's so,
isn't better to just ask Lynsha?
Lynsha?
Actually, I became acquainted with
the sister of the rebel army leader...
I see...
So you've even done that much...
Sorry, but do you mind if we
go with that retainer of yours?
I don't want to tell Bernard yet
that Sunkland is involved in this...
Well...
I won't say that I mind, but...
This situation...
I'll end up having to go too, as if that's
the most natural thing to do, right?
Fine, fine, I get it already...
We're here.
The mansion on that map is here.
The culprit that caused so much pain
to me, is inside this building...
It's fine...
I'm sure it'll be okay.
Damn! It should've been the perfect
time to cause chaos in the Empire!
Yet that Wisdom of the Empire...
It's all because of
that Mia Luna Tearmoon!
Starting from the ruin of the Empire,
then a systematic collapse
of other countries...
Then comes chaos from
the collapse of order...
That's our dearest wish...
I won't let a little girl
bother us even further!
Everyone in the building!
Drop your weapon and come out!
My name is Sion Sol Sunkland!
The white crow's scheme
has come to light!
There's no reason
for you to fight!
To think that he'll shout
before we break and enter...
Will this really be okay?
I have a bad feeling about this,
but I hope it's just my imagination...
The bad feeling Mia had,
unexpectedly wasn't correct.
Let's go!
The Prince that they served
turns into an enemy,
and against strong people whom
they can't ever dream of beating,
the enemies lost the will to fight
and came out of the mansion one by one.
Seems like things will go well.
Miss Mia,
your hair looks rough...
Yeah,
the shampoo here wasn't good,
the one I received from
Prince Abel is more slippery...
Don't worry, Princess Mia!
Here! I've brought it with me!
That's wonderful, Anne!
I was planning to enjoy myself in
the bath once this battle was over!
I have one more thing
to look forward to now!
Mia said the lines no one should
ever say in a battlefield,
confidently, and heartily.
Just right after her bad premonitions
didn't come true...
Look what we have here...
Princess Mia.
I'm honored to meet you.
Mia, are you okay?!
So you're Jem...
I see, so the speech
just now was true.
That's right.
Your comrades have surrendered.
Stop your meaningless
resistance.
We've saved Prime Minister
Dasayev Donovan as well!
You're the only one left now.
To think that you found a way
to the underground dungeon...
It's not just Prince Sion, but your
retainer is better than the rumors too...
Let's have you stop
moving, okay?
Mia!
Don't do anything stupid.
It's easy for me to just
cut off your head, you know?
Stop with this lunacy.
Sunkland won't protect both the
Wind Crow and the White Crow.
Your plans are already foiled!
Please don't be
such a killjoy, Prince Sion.
It might shock me and make me
lose my grip, you know?
In any case,
this girl is the one who destroyed
the plans we spent time and effort on.
She's the target of our grudge!
Even if you're the Wisdom of the Empire,
you're just a brat in the end.
What an embarrassment.
Seeing something leaking from Mia's skirt,
everyone had the same thought.
"Ah, Mia is so scared she
ended up soiling herself".
But, there's one person...
One person who realized
that it's something else.
No! This smell is...
Princess Mia! Run!
This brat!
I didn't expect the princess would be
the one who deals the finishing blow...
And so, one of the masterminds,
Jem, was defeated.
The one who ended the incident was the
Wisdom of the Empire, Mia Luna Tearmoon,
And her brilliant kick
delivered by her delicate legs.
Prince Abel, Prince Sion...
I have a request.
These people...
Can you at least
spare their lives?
Normally, they won't accept
a wish to spare someone's life...
But, these two princes
thought at the same time.
I knew it.
That's what Mia wants.
Those people from the intelligence...
Even if I can persuade everyone,
the most lenient is a deportation...
But the ones in trouble are those locals
who are involved in the rebellion...
Both Lynsha and her brother, Lambert,
will most probably be executed.
Mia gave her best effort.
If that's so, I should use all
my power to answer her wish too.
But that's hard...
If Remno Kingdom gave a light
punishment like deportation,
it'll be hard for Sunkland to
give them capital punishment too.
They'll end up suspecting that
we did that to cover our tracks.
Well, for that part, let's have
Prince Abel do some reminding too...
The problem is how to
deal with these people...
I wonder what Mia has in mind.
Are you serious about
not executing us?
Are you to put us
through torture instead?
Don't think that we'll tell you
everything that easily though!
Torture...
So the Princess thinks that something
is still being hidden by them...
But, as he said, I don't think
they'll just admit that easily.
So Princess,
what are you thinking?
It goes without saying, but it's not like
Mia was sympathizing with the culprits.
What if they're given a second chance
at life like me? Is that possible?
If it is, then what are the triggers?
I don't know for sure...
I don't know, but maybe, getting killed
in the same place and time as last time...
Or maybe, getting beheaded by the
guillotine, or dying with regrets...
If these people from this
conspiracy got executed...
There's a lot of chances
that might happen, right?
In any case...
If these people were killed, and
receive a second chance just like me...
All the effort I made to alter the history
until now might go to waste!
There's no way I'm
getting guillotined again!
That's the feeling that moved Mia
ever since she was reincarnated.
But...
Mia realized that there was another
strong emotion welling up in her.
That's not the only reason.
I like the present, this timeline.
I mean, Sion who used to be my enemy,
his retainer, Keithwood,
Tiona,
Dion, who chopped my head off,
Abel, who was just like anyone else,
Chloe,
who helped me all the way here,
Rafina...
and then Anne and Ludwig...
Just a short while ago, I was all alone...
But, my world right now
feels so warm...
If I can, I'd like to stay
by everyone's side forever...
But don't get me wrong, Sion, Tiona!
It's not like I like you guys now, okay?
Abel, I know it will
cause you problems, but...
Yeah, I understand.
I'll persuade my dad, somehow.
But, even if we managed to save them from
execution, what should we do with them?
Hey, are you seriously
thinking of letting us live?
Are you some kind of saint?
He's starting to piss me off...
Oh, right!
How about we leave them to Rafina...
And have her scold them
for three years every day?
Are you ready?
That's nice.
How naive...
Stop messing around!
That's just ridiculous!
But I thought you said we can
torture, or do anything to you?
The truth is,
this decision from Mia
will become the first step to uncover
a lying darkness in the future,
But that's a story
for another time.
And so, the rebellion in
Remno Kingdom finally ends...
Then, Ludwig and Tiona
who understood Mia, went to the capital,
and Lambert and Lynsha
whom they worried about
were treated warmly, along with the
other core members of the rebellion army.
After she subdued the rebellion without
trouble, Mia went back to the academy.
Well! Well, well, well!
What a wonderful sight!
This was all prepared by Anne?
Yes! I gave my all for
today's tea party preparation!
I see...
This is from me!
I feel like I've seen this before...
She didn't roast it outside this time,
and she used a proper stove.
The saltiness is perfect too!
Well done, Riora!
Sweetness and saltiness
bring an infinite loop of happiness!
I brought various kinds of tea!
What a nice smell...
Oh right, Rafina.
I'm really sorry to push
all that trouble to you...
Ah, those people...
Just as Mia suggested,
we're giving them sermons every day.
Oh! This is really delicious!
Abel, try it too!
You have something on your face.
Is something wrong?
I'm just so happy drinking tea
with everyone like this.
That's right.
The future is still not set, and no one
knows what kind of life awaits Mia...
But, I want to have more
and more happiness in my life.
But, the fact that Mia will never give in
remains unchanged.
For the sake of her happiness,
and those she holds dear to her...
This is a redo story of a Princess,
who slightly put herself
first over anything else.
How will the seeds of hope that
she sowed color her future...
No one knows that yet.