So you want to go to the forest
to search for your hairpin, huh...
Yeah.
I know that I'm being
selfish, but...
But...
I don't really mind though.
I owe you for giving my soldiers
a reason to retreat, Princess.
If you're fine with just me,
I'll go with you.
There's no way I'm bringing
my troops back there again.
Just the two of us?!
In the first place,
this guy did that to me...
You gotta be kidding me...
A goddess! A saint!
Wisdom! Intelligence!
Kindness! Fraternity! That is it!
I am a princess, as you know
I am the heroine in this life
I am!
Throughout life, I am on easy mode-going
through as a helpless princess
If that's what you thought,
then go ahead!?
The world is always dependent
on the direction of wind
There are too many useless
things and people, seriously
I can't believe in anybody
I have noticed that, the world is
so heartless
That is not good,
This is not good
It is not good,
everything is not good
The reality is harsh
Alteration... alteration... alteration...
Everything is going to be altered...!
I am a princess, as you know
I am the heroine in this life
Even in a sad scenario
I am going to rewrite
everything, everything
Because, because,
I am a princess
At least of my own story
I must enjoy it as much as possible
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I have to live with
all my strength
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Just wait and see!
I shall alter my own destiny!
A goddess! A saint! Wisdom! Intelligence!
Kindness! Fraternity! That is it!
Captain Dion.
Ah, Sir Ludwig.
I have a request...
What is it?
Once everything is over, I'd like you
to become the princess's ally too.
Ally?
Do you want me to join the Imperial
Guard and protect the princess?
No...
I'd like you to
become a general.
Me? A general?
To achieve what Miss Mia wants to do,
we'll need an ally in the military too.
So you're telling me to
climb the ranks for it?
I'm not interested in
getting promoted though...
But well,
that might be fun to do too.
Sir Dion...
In any case,
there's no point talking about it now.
There's no guarantee I'll be able to go
back safely from the forest, after all.
Wait, what's funny?
No, nothing.
It's nothing important.
If it's the princess,
I'm sure it'll be fine,
so worrying is just a waste of time.
Don't tell me,
that's what you're thinking?
To me, you're the one who have
that in your mind, Sir Dion.
The forest at night is
already scary enough,
but I have to be alone with
this cold-blooded guy...
But really...
You're sloppy when it comes to
the important parts, Princess.
Looking for something in the middle of
the night, is not convincing enough.
It's such a crude reason to
go to the forest at night.
You're too naive
with your reasoning.
You're going to sneak, talk,
and settle things with the
other side by yourself, right?
Wait? That's not it?
You called me when I was
drinking and chilling,
so I thought you had something
that I can look forward to...
Ah, that's how it is, of course!
That's what I thought.
Well, I don't know what you're
planning to do, but I'll follow you.
Depending on the circumstances,
even to hell.
Wait...?
Don't tell me,
this is a dangerous situation...?
Hey, long time no see!
Princess.
What is it?!
We arrived at the place where we
got attacked, so I just called you.
Ah, I see...
Alright then.
Is this really the same place
we went in the afternoon?
There's no doubt about it.
Look, there's a mark left
by an arrow on that tree.
In any case,
I'll have to find it quick...
Princess, seems like everything
went according to plan.
Hey, stop lurking
and show yourself, would you?
Considering how you haven't shot us
yet, you're not here to fight, right?
That's the Lulu tribe...?
As expected from the leader
of the Imperial army.
Little girl, you're the one who
came here in the afternoon, right?
T-That's right. I...
Little girl.
Where did you get this?
That's...
I'm asking you,
where did you get it?
Depending on your answer...
I can't have you
act so rude now.
The one here is the Princess of the
Empire, and I have to protect her.
At least for now.
Depending on the situation,
I won't show any mercy.
You...
How nice!
The guy who killed me, is now
putting his life on the line for me!
By the way, Princess...
I'm sure you already have a plan
on how to settle this, right?
If you've calculated all this,
an order whether to kill them or not,
fight or retreat, would be appreciated.
Here is the meaning
behind his smile.
"If you don't have any plan,
I won't forgive you".
That's right!
Those people look very angry...
But also, it's not like this
guy swore loyalty to me...
Isn't he more like, my enemy?!
Please wait!
You're... Liora?
Princess, good evening to you.
Actually, the person here
is the head of Lulu tribe.
And then...
This hairpin is a present
that I gave to my wife.
When my wife died,
my daughter inherited it.
I see, your daughter...
I'm very sorry to tell you this, but...
Unfortunately,
your daughter has passed away.
She's dead...?
I received that from someone
that might've been your grandson.
It's present for saving him when
he collapsed in the slums, he said.
Chief, the Princess isn't
someone who would tell a lie.
We managed to pull out our troops
because of the Princess too, after all.
But that girl kicked
our tree though.
Pulling out the military
needs a strong reason too.
I think the Chief can
sympathize with us.
That's true. But, it's also hard
to believe everything you said.
This is my chance!
If that's so,
we should have that kid come here.
Leaving him in the slums won't
be good for his upbringing too.
You can make your
judgment afterwards.
Lies!
She's someone brave enough to walk into
enemy territory with just 1 subordinate.
I can't imagine she's lying.
Thank you for taking
care of my grandson.
I'd like to apologize
for my rudeness.
That's not needed.
I also kicked a tree in this forest
that you hold dear.
How about we call it even?
More importantly,
please be good to your grandson, okay?
Rather than letting
him stay in slums,
it's better for him to
go back to this forest.
We don't even know what will
trigger the skirmish after all.
I was being stubborn and
prideful because I'm the chief,
I couldn't even allow my daughter to
marry someone from outside our tribe...
And the Princess is telling me not to
do the same mistake with my grandson!
I'm grateful for your
understanding, Princess.
There's no way this
is all coincidence...
I'm sure she already dug up some
information before coming to the forest.
Don't tell me, she intentionally
dropped the hairpin too?
The Wisdom of the Empire, huh...
If it's for her,
I think I can put more effort...
Few days later,
Mia got back to the capital,
and was summoned by her father,
The Tearmoon Empire's King.
Good day, Your Majesty.
My dear daughter, Mia.
Please don't call me "Your Majesty".
You can call me Father, or even be
more pampered and call me Papa...
Well then, Father,
what is it that you want to talk about?
I heard you went to a disputed
territory of Berman Viscounty.
I was so shocked I felt
like I was going to faint.
Well, nothing dangerous
happened in particular.
That's what you said,
but you ended up bringing the patrol
around the area back with you, right?
Gee, I wonder who the tattletale is...
It's quite an embarrassing story.
I accidentally tripped on
some trees, and fell down.
What?!
How dare that tree
tripped my Mia!
Let's burn down
the whole forest!
No, Father.
I fell in love with that forest.
Is it that good?
Yeah.
That's why, Father, can you add that
territory directly under my jurisdiction?
Well, yeah...
If it's under the Princess direct control,
Sealence Forest will be saved.
But, she will be hated by Viscount Berman.
This is not enough.
Did I expect too
much from Miss Mia?
Is it possible that Mia is not wise,
or even a saint as I thought...?
He finally noticed the truth,
and his clouded eyes
are getting clearer, but then...
If that's so, Berman.
Build Princess Town beside that forest,
and construct a castle for Mia.
He's fanning the flames!
Not only his territory
was shrunken,
now he has to build a town, and even
a castle, out of his own pocket...
Your Majesty!
Thank you very much!
This Berman, will give every fiber in
me to fulfill this honorable mission!
That's right!
Nobles value honors
over everything else!
Under the honor of being tasked with a
territory that's under Princess's control,
losing a bit of territory is nothing!
I knew it, Mia really is
the Wisdom of the Empire...
I'm ashamed that
I second-guessed it for a moment!
No, you were close.
Now that I think of it, I haven't received
any letter from Prince Abel lately...
Princess Mia, you got a letter...
Is it from Prince Abel?
No, it's from Miss Tiona.
Tiona's little brother is...
The Saint of the Revolution army,
Tiona Rudolvon.
Even in this famine,
she shared food with the people.
Why does that girl still
have that much food with her?
You didn't know that a new, stronger
species of wheat has been developed?
A new wheat species?
A cold-resistant wheat, developed by
Tiona's little brother, Cyril Rudolvon.
I didn't know about it at all!
Well, Cyril was under Lady Rafina,
and was working in a research facility in
Holy Principality of Belluga, after all.
That's unfair!
I want a brilliant
little brother too!
A genius kid, Cyril Rudolvon...
A sly little brother...
What's wrong?
It's about Tiona's
little brother.
He's a very talented,
but apparently he can't go to school
due to financial difficulties...
And so, they were asking me to
mediate between them and Lady Rafina.
I see.
So that the little brother can study at
Holy Principality of Belluga as well.
Of course, I won't let that happen.
As expected from the Princess.
To think that she solved the case
without shedding a drop of blood.
Her wisdom is well known
in the school too.
But father, is that okay?
Even though the lands near the
forest got taken away unfairly...
It's not unfair.
The Imperial family
have the right to do so.
More importantly, if it can be resolved
without putting people into suffering,
that's great enough.
I see...
So, why is Princess Mia coming here then?
Most probably about
the forest case, but...
I also sent a letter to her, but to think
that she'd come to the frontier like this.
That's very typical of her.
Both my father and sister are
fawning over Princess Mia.
I wonder what kind of person she is.
These are quite some
beautiful flowers.
Are they Sweet Moon...?
Ah, yeah, that's true...
Miss Mia, it's about time...
Miss Mia?! This person is?!
Let's turn back time for a bit...
The boy who loves flowers...
If he managed to
develop a new wheat,
I'm sure he's
knowledgeable about plants!
Flowers are plants!
That boy is Cyril Rudolvon!
I bet I scored some
affection points with that!
I'm really grateful to you,
for taking care of my daughter at school.
No no,
taking care is a bit too much...
And also, regarding the Sealence
forest incident from a few days ago...
More importantly, Sir Rudolvon.
I'm actually here to
give you a suggestion.
A suggestion, huh...
I heard your son, Cyril,
is a brilliant child.
Are you going to recommend Cyril so he
can enroll in the Saint Noelle Academy?
No. We're not that foolish to send
our talents outside the country.
What do you mean by that?
Do you know that a Princess Town will
be made in Viscount Berman's territory?
Yes...
I'm planning to build
a school in that city.
A school?
Yes. It'll be great if we have a school
like Saint Noelle in the Empire, right?
How about it?
Are you interested in making Cyril
the first student of my school?
Me?!
With this distance,
he can go to school from here.
Moreover, since it's a public school,
we can lessen the tuition fee.
It's such a good deal for
our poor Rudolvon family...
I'm honored with your
considerations for us.
If there's anything
our family can do to repay you...
Well then,
I'd like the wheat that you have.
Wheat...?
It's not like I want you to
sell it to me with lower price,
but I'd like you to store
them as much as possible.
And when a famine comes...
Well, of course, by your orders,
I'll provide them to you.
That's not what I meant,
Outland Count.
If I do that, I'll just end up
getting hated by the people again...
I'd like the Rudolvon house to
distribute it to the people, directly.
And at that time,
I'd like you to mention my name...
So, you're saying that
it's fine to use your name?
That's right.
Please use my name,
and spread it as much as you can!
I'm impressed...
We've experienced
crop failure before.
But then, the high nobles came,
and took away our wheat...
Even so, I tried to distribute it to
the people for free, but they told me...
That is a treason
towards the Empire.
But Princess saw through all that,
and told me this.
So I can answer,
I did it under the order of the Princess.
Such wisdom...
Such compassion...
What's with this response?
I'm basically leaving all the hard work
to them, and hand me the achievements!
Mia's heart was beating
hard for the whole time.
Let me say this to
align ourselves.
The school that Cyril will attend,
is not a grand place where
high nobles would go, okay?
I'm thinking of accepting students from
normal citizens, and Lulu tribe too.
Mia is trying to say that she's not
going to raise their son's status.
That's... I can't be thankful
enough for your consideration...
What?!
To make an environment
where Cyril can learn,
without being bullied by high nobles...
Moreover, she even created a way to build
friendly relations with Lulu tribe...
This person, don't tell me...
He's a bully, or maybe he feels
good from being mistreated?!
What?
Miss Mia... She's beautiful,
and wise to top it off...
W-Well, with this,
I got Cyril on my hand,
and their crops are practically mine too!
It all ends with a good result.
I'm feeling exhausted
after all that...
Oh right, I haven't checked
it for a while now...
What's the meaning of this...?
Why is my diary gone...?
How will I evade the
guillotine without it?!
But wait...
It's the other way around...
As long as I still
have the diary,
it's decided that I'll be
executed by the guillotine...
Now that it's gone,
that means....
Is it that the future where
I die by the Guillotine is gone?
I did it!
I finally did it!
I want to share this joy with
someone, right now!
But, the one I really
want to tell, is Prince Abel!
Seems like the Empire is
getting back on it's feet.
That youngster from Gold Moon Ministry,
Ludwig, is pretty exceptional too...
I thought they'll be done
with just a famine, but...
It seems like Princess Mia and
Prince Sion are getting along well too.
Seems like we have to consider our
plan of breaking them up as failed.
The Wisdom of the Empire, huh...
What an annoying brat.
In any case,
it doesn't change what we have to do.
We'll halt our plan
for the Empire.
Let's change the target...
To remember what went down today
I'll journal every single word
Whether it's good or bad
It's my only life,
gotta seize the day
You never realize the
importance of something
Until it's out of sight
Every beginning is
for a perfect ending
Dear Moon, I won't just pray
Let me stand on my own
feet, just one more time
Sweet Moon,
not just a shiny stone
I'll find sweet joy
And a future that is
sky blue and clear
Queen of the Night
I am the Queen of the Night