Nothing in the news today either?
A monster with two magic stones,
what could it be?
Good morning, Big Brother.
Good morning, Manicia.
Will you read the newspaper to me, please?
I thought you were good at reading.
Read to me, please?
A spoiled Manicia
is too cute!
I heard there are
a lot of new labyrinths popping up lately.
I see.
"Avancier might see
the emergence of a labyrinth too", huh?
Speaking of which, a few days ago…
If we get a labyrinth around here,
this town will prosper.
This one's about
the economic situation in the capital.
This one's about the new system.
And this one…
Former hero Kygras is off
to conquer a new labyrinth.
You used to be in the same party, right?
Yes.
Miss Nin said she couldn't stand him
because he always looked down on you.
Nin's words usually come
with a lot of personal feelings.
That's surprising.
Big Brother, you've noticed
her feelings for you, haven't you?
Did you pretend not to notice
because of my illness?
It's one of the things I considered,
but the real issue lies with me.
I'm not strong.
Once I get close to someone,
I'll become fixated on that relationship,
and I won't be able to focus
on raiding labyrinths.
I'm not skilled.
I can't juggle both.
But I think if it were you,
it would be okay.
So,
if someone you care about
shows up one day,
please continue to take care of me
while you pursue your happiness.
Sure.
That's a given.
THE STRONGEST TANK'S LABYRINTH RAIDS
A TANK WITH A RARE 9999 RESISTANCE SKILL
GOT KICKED FROM THE HERO'S PARTY
Everyone,
I've gathered you here today
to defeat the Chameleon Kong
that was spotted a few days ago.
The Chameleon Kong resides
in a region further south from here,
and it's hard to imagine how it managed
to come to Avancier
without being noticed by anyone.
That's why we'll also need
to investigate why it appeared here.
I'd like to express my gratitude
to all of you for assisting.
Incidentally,
there are suspicions that the Chameleon Kong
could have escaped from a labyrinth.
So, if any of you come across
the entrance to a labyrinth,
please report it to us immediately.
Oh?
Is that…
This thing?
I had the skilled father-daughter
blacksmith duo make a new sword for me.
Rud, your new sword is ready.
I polished your shield for you too.
As far as swords go,
it's an excellent weapon,
but this one even comes
with the "Enchant" skill.
Impressive.
What's "Enchant"?
It's a skill that lets you alter
the magical properties of a magic stone
and infuse them into the weapon.
It should be quicker to show you.
I can use magic of all attributes,
but none of them
are powerful enough as attacks.
However,
by infusing magic into this magic stone…
I can turn the sword
into a fire-attribute weapon.
In other words,
I can alter the weapon's attributes
depending on the monsters' weaknesses.
I see.
You're an F-rank, aren't you?
Giving something like this to you
seems like a waste.
Hey, don't be like that.
You're a C-rank?
That's right.
Even if you wield such a nice sword,
it's useless since you're just an F-rank.
You might as well head back home now,
old man.
What… What's the deal
with that adventurer?
Master, are you just going to take that?
Calm down, Luna.
It's better to be underestimated
than overestimated.
That may be true,
but I don't like it
when they belittle you.
See?
This is what happens
when you refuse to update your rank.
Even though you're strong enough
that even I, a saint,
would want to nominate you as a knight.
Saint Nin, is that true?
Yes, but he refused.
Why?
Because once your rank goes up,
sometimes the guild calls you in for help.
And besides, I only became an adventurer
in the first place
to cure Manicia.
It's the Chameleon Kong!
It's coming from above!
That girl's got skills.
Yes.
Fil is far better
than your ordinary adventurer.
"Taunt".
Every blow is heavy, but…
No one has been hit.
And we've been consistently attacking it.
Everyone, let's bring it down!
But something doesn't feel right.
Such a bold and blatant attack,
roaring as if it's trying
to attract enemy attention,
in human society, we call this a tank.
What? There were others?
I wasn't made aware of this!
Everyone, dodge!
A monster capable
of using diversion.
We've been surrounded.
What do we do?
This… This is beyond my capability.
Fil,
if the leader is scared,
everyone will be affected.
Leader?
Yes, aren't you our leader?
That's right.
Surely you can break through this.
I can.
Let's do this again!
"Taunt"!
Get back in formation!
It's too dangerous
to fight three monsters all at once!
Don't think you can
take me down with this!
I'll make you regret
attacking Master!
"Wind Sword"!
Finish it off!
Let's do this!
It should be fine to leave that to them.
Next…
I remember
Chameleon Kongs are weak to fire.
"Enchant: Fire Attribute."
Not bad.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Got it.
The vigilante corps will take care of it!
Luna!
Yes!
"Wind Sword"!
I won't let you escape.
With this, it's over.
Is everyone all right?
We defeated the Chameleon Kong!
What are you talking about?
If it weren't for Rud,
we wouldn't have been able to do anything.
That's true.
We finished up ours too.
Good.
To not be scared at all in that situation,
are you some kind of monster?
As a tank,
it's moments like those
that I can't back down.
I see…
Um,
I'm sorry I looked down on you.
It's no big deal.
After all, rank represents
an adventurer's strength.
A low-ranking adventurer is bound
to draw second guesses.
The way it died is just like
the monsters in the labyrinth.
Rud, look over there.
Is that… the entrance to the labyrinth?
A… Avancier has a labyrinth now.
Tonight, we drink
to the future prosperity of the town.
Cheers!
Things are going to be busy around here.
Bring them on.
Thank you for your assistance.
It's a big party tonight.
That's right.
After all,
with the appearance of the labyrinth,
we might solve the problem
of the town's declining population.
That would be wonderful, Master.
Indeed…
Manicia.
Would you like to have a drink with me?
Do you have a death wish?
If you're lonely, I'll drink with you.
-My apologies.
-It sure is lively.
Miss Nin.
Are you enjoying yourself?
Yes, very much.
But Master doesn't seem
all too happy about this.
Understandable, there are pros and cons
to the appearance of a labyrinth.
He must be worried about that.
Is that so?
Yes.
A labyrinth can bring about
a great deal of problems.
If no one eliminates
the monsters in the labyrinth,
they will escape
like Chameleon Kongs did today.
Labyrinths that frequently experience
such incidents
are considered a threat
to the nearby residents.
But when such incidents occur,
why not just go and defeat them,
like we did this morning?
Doing that would create other problems.
Because anyone can become an adventurer.
It means
even someone despicable and evil
can become one.
There are quite a few of those
that behave like stalkers,
going after cute girls.
And
you and Manicia
might become their targets.
In that case,
is there any way
to manage these adventurers?
That's where the clans come in.
What's a "clan"?
CLAN
PARTIES
A clan, in essence,
is an organisation
that brings together multiple parties.
Adventurers affiliated with a clan
receive official recognition
from the country
and are obligated to protect
the towns, like knights.
After all,
adventurers want security too.
Without a clan,
the entire town would descend into chaos,
particularly in a small town like Avancier,
where combatants are limited.
Without a clan stationed,
adventurers attempting
to challenge the labyrinth
might cause trouble in the town.
If anything were to happen to Manicia…
Don't look so glum.
I'll help you guys as well.
Rud!
So soothing…
-Stop, Fil! The shield force's going to…
-Good boy…
-It hurts…
-I just want to pet you…
Fil, you're drunk!
You jerk!
Were you staring at me?
Are you asking for it?
Are you two
fighting again?
-I'm sorry!
Good job on patrol.
Didn't expect so many adventurers
to show up
just a week after the labyrinth appeared.
Exactly.
Mister Rud,
thanks again for last time.
Rud,
if anything happens again,
we'll be counting on you.
I heard you've been helping around town.
Well, one-sided restrictions won't work.
I heard there's a fight
going on over there!
This way!
Black Dragon Fang's No.3, Bu,
and White Tiger Claw's No.3, Gali.
They're both A-rank adventurers.
If they start fighting,
it could be dangerous.
Hold it.
You're scaring the townsfolk.
Could you please stop?
Who are you?
The pride of our clans
are on the line here.
Why don't you stay out of this?
Looks like you guys
aren't planning to back down, huh?
Why don't you decide, then?
Whether Black Dragon Fang
or White Tiger Claw
will establish themselves in this town.
We don't want either of you
if you're going to cause trouble.
Why don't you go back?
You!
Don't you dare treat Mister Bu
in such a rude manner!
And don't even think about trying.
Unlike Rud, I won't be showing any mercy.
This town has its own rules.
I'm willing to go all the way
if you try anything here.
Sorry.
We're sorry, too.
By the way,
do you belong to a clan?
-If not, won't you consider us?
-Beat it, Gali!
This guy belongs with us,
the Black Dragon Fang!
Black Dragon.
White Tiger.
I'll be joining neither.
That's enough.
Welcome to Avancier.
Knowing when to call it quits,
adventurers affiliated with clans
are different from non-affiliated ones.
But it looks like I won't be able
to leave town for a while.
I can't believe they invited you
to join their clans.
Same.
I used to aspire to join a clan too.
Dreamed of one day
living the adventurer life in a clan,
like a big family.
Rud!
Has the conflict between the clans
been resolved?
It's all settled.
Well then,
you should head to the headquarters.
Mister Vild needs to see you.
Mister Vild?
In light of the situation in Avancier,
the lord has two proposals.
The lord, you say?
He asked me to choose
one of the two proposals.
The first proposal is...
Rud,
you must establish a clan
and become the clan leader.
Me?
Why, all of a sudden...
It's not sudden.
He has been mentioning you
quite frequently since some time ago,
talking about a young
and talented adventurer.
I appreciate the lord's recognition,
but taking on such a role doesn't suit me
as I will be occupied
with finding a cure for Manicia.
I understand.
However…
that is the wish of the town.
Even though you have no experience,
the people would rather it be you
than some stranger.
I'm truly grateful to have their trust.
When Manicia is cured,
I'd like to be able to continue
to live in peace in this town too.
I'd like to do something
for the town, too, but...
The second proposal is...
to destroy the labyrinth in Avancier.
But then, the development of the town…
There are so many labyrinths
appearing all across the country now
that they cannot manage all of them,
including Avancier's labyrinth.
The higher-ups seem to be averse
to adding more unmanageable labyrinths.
So, if you can't establish a clan,
they hope you can join a party
to investigate the labyrinth
and work together to destroy it.
I'm sorry for asking you to do this,
but could you make the choice?
To become a clan leader
and manage the town and labyrinth
or to destroy the labyrinth,
please make the decision.
I won't ask you
to make an immediate decision,
but if possible,
I hope you can let me know
your answer soon.
Stinking thief!
You were going to steal from me!
I'm not a thief!
It was just a mistake!
Hey, stop it!
Shut up!
You're just an adventurer.
Don't interfere!
The only way to resolve this situation
is to establish a clan, huh?
Found you!
Master!
Master, you must hurry home!
Lady Manicia…
Granny Gigi! How's Manicia?
Don't worry.
She's just a little sick, as usual.
Oh...
You're too much of a worrywart.
More importantly,
is the town doing okay?
You don't have to worry about that.
Rest well.
Okay.
If I become the leader of the clan,
I won't be able to leave Avancier
for extended periods
and won't be able
to explore labyrinths like before.
I don't know if I can obtain a treasure
that can grant any wish for sure,
but
staying here
won't save Manicia.
Nin, Luna,
there's something
I'd like to ask for your help.
I...
I want to destroy Avancier's labyrinth.
Please lend me your support.
Are you sure about this?
Your choice
could ruin the town's prospects.
If I have to choose
between Manicia and the town,
I will choose Manicia.
Um...
Can I ask a question?
If Master becomes the clan leader,
do you have to stay in town?
If I take on the role of clan leader,
I'll likely have to stay until
the situation in Avancier stabilises.
Is that the only solution?
Can't you find someone
to take on your duties while you're away?
No, even if that were possible,
I wouldn't feel right passing
this responsibility to someone else.
I'll do it.
If I can stand in for Master
and protect this town,
I'll do it.
I love this town
that welcomed me and accepted me.
So, just like how Master helped me,
I want to do my best to help you too.
But...
Are you trying to hide
your true feelings again?
Nin...
Don't worry,
I'll be right here supporting Luna.
I was planning
to quit my role as a saint anyway.
The church...
might not be thrilled,
but they'll have to respect my decision.
So,
let me join your clan and lend you a hand.
Why are you two doing this for me?
There are many people
who are grateful to you.
You've always protected them.
It makes sense
that they'd want to return the favour too.
It is as Miss Nin said.
Is this really okay?
Of course.
So, don't look so defeated.
Just do what you want.
You don't need to hold back.
Big Brother.
Manicia!
You should be resting...
I'm not the little girl
who needs to rely on you
for everything anymore.
Just like Miss Luna,
I love this town very much.
If you have the ability
to protect this town,
I want you to keep it safe.
After all, I'm in the pink of health.
No, you're not...
Even you…
I take back what I said.
I want to protect Manicia and this town.
So, please help me.
Of course.