Long ago, when the words of the gods
resonated in the hearts of men…
Two thousand years before
the reign of the Chosen King...
the world had fallen into ruin due to
the spread of monsters called daemons.
The nobles of House Caelum
used their god-given powers
to purge this scourge from the land,
earning the people's trust
and spreading their influence
throughout the realm.
Other lords voiced their support
for House Caelum to lead the realm,
and the gods, too, sought to select
a ruler from among those men...
an absolute sovereign to sit atop
the throne of the world's first kingdom.
There were two candidates.
One was ambitious,
a charismatic leader,
and the younger son of House Caelum:
Somnus Lucis Caelum.
The other was righteous,
Somnus's older brother
who dedicated his life to his people:
Ardyn Lucis Caelum.
As the Oracle,
a vessel for the voice of the gods,
I patiently awaited their decision.
Are you unwell, Lord Caelum?
Tis nothing.
You know, your dear brother did
unspeakable things.
He rounded up those afflicted
by the Starscourge...
even those he merely suspected of infection,
and burned them all alive.
Lord Caelum!
Please, you must save my daughter!
But of course.
Lord Caelum?
- She's all better now.
- Oh, thank the gods.
- And thank YOU, milord!
- Blessed be this day. It's a miracle!
The Starscourge is a disease.
With the proper treatment, anyone can be spared.
We must not condemn our fellow man
and exile them as if they were monsters.
But even with your curative powers,
surely you can't save everyone...
Then we send the rest to the flames.
- Hey! You watch your tongue.
- Why should I?
Imagine if Somnus had
burned YOUR family alive!
Then what do you propose!?
- Such insolence!
- There's nothing we can do!
Lord Caelum...
you are our one true king.
- He's right!
- You're our only hope!
I've no desire to sit the throne,
but if it means the scourge would be purged
and that countless lives would be saved...
then I will gladly be your king.
It wasn't easy, you know.
Fleeing the castle and coming
all the way here to see you.
A word of thanks is in order!
I'm ineffably grateful, Aera.
And I hope you, too, are grateful
for those who so kindly escorted you here.
Grateful for spending more time with me
than a certain fiancé of mine...
Do forgive me.
Hmph!
This place is incredible.
How old do you think these ruins are?
I haven't the slightest.
Neither who made them, nor when nor why.
Whether they faded away on their own
or were erased from the annals of history.
Their creator's name
remains a mystery to all.
You needn't worry.
Even if others forget your name...
I will always remember.
- There he is!
- Over here!
- He's escaping!
- After him!
Find anything?
Not a trace.
Keep looking!
By your leave, milord.
You heard the man: we lost him.
And to think he and his betrothed could have
enjoyed a happy life free of conflict...
No matter.
The hour of the gods' decision is nigh.
Stop, Lord Caelum!
The ritual is already underway.
None must interfere!
Hail, Oracle. What say the gods?
The Crystal, then?
The Crystal has no will of its own.
...Nothing, then?
...Very well.
If you desire it, Somnus,
you shall have my trust...
...and their decision.
We feared the worst, milord!
You hadn't returned by dusk,
and with that torrential downpour...
Thanks for your hospitality.
Lord Caelum!
Last night, the word of the gods was heard.
Ardyn Lucis Caelum,
you have been chosen to serve as king!
- At last!
- Long live our king!
Praise be!
It was me, Brother.
It was me!
I was chosen by the gods!
What!?
Do forgive me for
deceiving you all like this. However,
it was necessary in order to lure
the seditious traitor here today!
What a miserable man.
Did you really covet my throne that badly?
You...
The gods have spoken,
and I, Somnus Lucis Caelum, am king!
And what if I object, Brother?
I will not take your life
so long as you renounce your na—
Stop!
Ardyn...
Aera!
Don't worry. I'm going to...
Foolish woman.
Forgive me, Brother,
but I must fulfill my kingly calling.
- What's happening!?
- He's a monster!
He's become the monster
I made him out to be...
My people...
must know...
Answer me... O gods above...
Who is... your True King?
So that is your answer...
I am unworthy...
Cursed to live as an immortal monster,
Ardyn was dubbed Adagium
and imprisoned on the isle of Angelgard,
where his enmity for the royal family
grew stronger with each passing year...
Yet in all accounts of Lucian history,
the name Ardyn Lucis Caelum is
nowhere to be found.
I'm waiting, Noct...