Year 845:
The Colossus Titan that suddenly appeared along with the Armored Titan
destroyed everything as easily as it did the wall.
Wall Maria was abandoned.
And with a fifth of its population and a third of its land lost,
mankind had its territory reduced to Wall Rose.
Year 850:
The Colossus Titan reappeared and destroyed the wall,
which allowed the Titans to invade.
Soldiers fell before the Titans, one after another.
And then...
Eren, hurry!
Eren Jaegar, who was devoured by a Titan,
emerged from within a mysterious Titan.
Attention!
Then, the chief executive of the southern territories, Dott Pixis,
decided to execute a clever plan
that would make use of Eren Jaegar's Titan transformation,
which was previously demonstrated in the midst of battle.
In his Titan form, he'll lift the large boulder,
carry it to the destroyed gate, and seal it!
When this plan succeeds,
mankind will recapture territory from the Titans for the first time in history!
Despite that, to mankind it will be a great advance.
However, soon after the plan was put into motion, failure was already looming.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
F
umareta hana no
Ignorant of the
amae mo shirazu ni
trampled flower's name,
hi ni ochita tori wa
hi
the bird that fell to the earth
aze wo machiwabiru
a
waits impatiently for the wind.
notta tokoro de
Even if you pray,
animo kawaranai
nothing will be changed.
ma wo kaeru no wa
But that which can alter the present
atakau kakugo da
is the resolution to fight.
hikabane fumikoete
hi
Trampling over corpses,
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
u
swine who mock the will to advance.
achiku no annei
a
Peace of the cattle,
yogi no hanei
yo
and the prosperity of deception.
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
orawareta kutsujoku wa
o
Our caged humiliation
angeki no koushi da
signals the start of our retaliation.
ouheki no sono kanata
Beyond the ramparts,
mono wo hofuru Jäger
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
otobashiru shoudou ni
o
As these surging urges
ono mi wo yaki nagara
burn away our bodies,
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a
we ignite the dusk with
uren no yumiya
u
a crimson bow and arrow.
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
...and we're the hunters.
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Wound
————Battle for Trost District, Part    ————
⑧
We somehow managed to lure the majority of the Titans to the corner of the town,
but even after avoiding combat to the best of our ability,
we ended up losing about a fifth of our troops.
We didn't lose them.
Soldiers don't go off and die on their own.
I let them die on my command.
Mankind's fate rests on this critical moment.
I'm not opposed to being called a murderer,
if that's what it takes to survive.
Ackerman!
Hey, that's enough!
Get away from him!
Eren, don't you recognize me?!
It's Mikasa!
Your family!
You have to seal the hole with that boulder!
The plan has failed.
I knew that we never had a secret weapon to begin with.
Eren, you're human!
You're—
Dodge, Ackerman!!
What's with him?!
He's just another stupid Titan, huh?
Eren!
Squad Leader Jan!
Two approaching from the front!
A 10-meter-class and a 6-meter-class!
Another at the rear!
A 12-meter-class is heading this way!
Jan, we're retreating!
Sealing the gate is the least of his worries.
Yeah.
We have no choice but to abandon him.
The elite squad's red signal confirmed.
A serious problem seems to be obstructing the plan.
They died in vain.
What'd my comrades even die for?
Hey, look at that!
What? What's wrong?
Did they... fail?
How?
Hey!
Armin, where are you going?!
Commander Pixis, reassessing the gate's defense is top priority now.
May we proceed?
We can't.
Have the elite squad retreat.
No need.
Continue to lure the Titans to the corner of the town.
As for the elite squad, I've granted full authority to its leader.
They're not just skilled—
they're elites amongst elites that bear the fate of mankind.
Conceding defeat so easily is out of the question.
To prevent lives from having been lost in vain,
they must struggle through this until their last breath.
Hey, what're you waiting for?
Give us the order!
Jan, it's not your fault.
It was a faulty plan to begin with.
We all know that!
It was certainly worth a shot, and we've given it that already!
Listen, we're going to climb back up the wall!
Wait!
Wait.
Calm down, Ackerman.
Riko's squad has the 12-meter-class at the rear.
Mitabi's squad and mine will take the two at the front.
What?!
I'm the one who was appointed leader!
Shut up and obey.
We can't leave Jaegar unprotected like this.
We'll modify the plan.
Until we can recover Jaegar, we'll protect him from the Titans.
He holds valuable potential for mankind.
We can't give up on him that easily.
Unlike us, there's no replacement for him, after all.
So you're telling me you want to carry on like this,
despite losing hundreds of soldiers,
all for that failure of a human weapon?!
That's right.
No matter the cost, we must continue!
What's up with Eren?
Armin headed over alone.
It'll probably work out.
Probably?
It will.
I'm sure.
Eren can do it.
I don't see the point of luring the Titans to the corner of the town.
Fighting them will only result in a battle of attrition.
They're probably trying to keep deaths to a minimum right now.
So you're saying all the deaths up till now are meaningless?
An all-out war is inevitable.
But until then, it's obvious we should minimize our losses so as to preserve our forces.
The higher-ups are right.
Is that how it is?
Of course!
Well, let's try not to become losses then.
All of us.
Jan, are you serious?!
How else can mankind defeat the Titans?!
Riko, tell me,
what other options do we have to break this deadlock?
A way to maintain our humanity and prevent losses,
all while conquering the Titans' overwhelming power—
how can we do that?!
There's no way I'd know how to defeat the Titans.
Exactly.
That's why we have no choice but to do this.
We can only lay down our lives
as brave sacrifices for that questionable human weapon.
Tragic, isn't it?
But it's the only thing left for us humans to do.
Well, what'll it be?
This is the best we've got.
The only struggle we're capable of.
I can't accept that.
Riko!
But I'll obey your order.
I agree with what you said.
I'll desperately struggle and show them how fearsome we humans can be.
Dying in vain is the last thing I'd accept.
Leave the 12-meter-class at the rear to my squad.
Let's go.
We're taking the two at the front.
Right.
Thank you very much, Squad Leader Jan.
Ackerman, no need for thanks.
I admit I was terrified though, not knowing what you'd do.
Act freely as we planned to begin with.
I'm sure you'll be able to perform better that way.
Sir.
It's to protect your lover, after all.
He's family.
Huh?
His damaged parts aren't regenerating.
Is it because of before?
How will this affect Eren?
There isn't even any guarantee he'll revert to normal.
No, forget that.
I won't be able to figure it out anyway.
Right now, I'll just do what I can.
Eren, Mikasa, what's going on?
Currently Disclosable Information
Three-dimensional Maneuver Device:
Body Weight-shifting Equipment Part ③
Each side of the waist is used to support the entire body.
Although it allows for unrestricted movement midair, it
requires extensive use of muscles throughout the body.
Currently Disclosable Information
Three-dimensionsal Maneuver Device Training Part ③
Therefore, training involving an instructor cutting lifelines
in order to observe recruits' reactions is undertaken. This
training is far from safe, but those who die during it
wouldn't have been fit to fight Titans anyhow.
Huh?
What...
am I... doing?
Sitting?
I can't see anything.
What day is it?
Where am I?
What?
I'm at home?
Guess I'll sleep.
Eren...
What are you doing, Eren?
Listen up.
We just need to keep the Titans in the corner.
Keep that in mind, and lure them accordingly.
Understand?
There's no need for you to fight.
Recruits will travel on foot in groups of three.
Once you reach the wall, climb up.
Try not to die.
We'll eliminate any Titans that somehow get away.
Somehow?
Isn't that a pretty likely scenario?
Permission to act independently in a life-threatening situation?
If that'll save you, sure.
Kirstein's squad, go!
Sir!
This is bad. Behind us!
One 13-meter-class.
It's approaching Jaegar!
There are more Titans entering through the gate!
Looks like four 10-meter-class Titans!
Ackerman, take the rear.
Roger!
Don't let it get to Jaegar!
We'll stop them here!
Got it!
Even two elite squads can't take on four Titans at once.
No way...
Why are there so many?
There aren't many people here though.
Don't tell me...
They're attracted to Eren?
Mikasa!
What's going on with the plan?
Armin?!
What happened to Eren?
It's dangerous here, so get away!
Eren isn't in control of that Titan!
He wouldn't respond even when I spoke to him!
It's pointless for anyone else to try!
And the plan?
It failed.
We can't just leave Eren, so everyone's fighting.
But at this rate...
the Titans will overwhelm us with numbers!
From the back of the head to the nape...
One-meter-long and ten-centimeters-wide...
Armin!
I'll get Eren out of here!
Mikasa, keep the Titans away from here!
Huh? What're you...
Eren came out of the Titan's weak point last time.
That's likely to be related to the mystery involving the true nature of the Titans.
It's okay.
As long as I avoid the center...
he won't die.
It'll just be a little...
painful!
Armin!
Armin, quit being reckless!
Mikasa, do what you can now!
If you go, there are lives that could be saved, right?!
Leave Eren to me, and just go!
Eren, can you hear me?
Get ahold of yourself!
If you don't get out of there, we'll all die!
Don't give in to a Titan's body.
Hurry up and get out of this meatsack!
Get out?
Why?
I'm sleepy right now.
Eren, get out.
Hurry, Eren!
Eren!
What happened to avenging your mom?
You're going to exterminate the Titans, right?!
You despise them for killing your mom, right?!
What're you talking about, Armin?
Mom's right here.
Eren!
Eren, wake up!
Eren, you're in there, right?
Eren, if you stay in there, the Titans will kill you.
Everything will end here!
I'm telling you, I have no idea what you're saying, Armin.
Why do I have to go outside?
That's right.
Why outside?
Why the Survey Corps?
Looks like we have no choice but to think on our feet.
You're mine!
Finally dead, you bastard?!
Withdraw for a bit!
Ackerman, reporting back.
Joining Mitabi's squad!
Huh?!
Jean!
Hurry and run!
No one's dying on my watch anymore!
Damn, it's failing on me now?
Jean!
What's he doing?
Why isn't he using his three-dimensional maneuver device?
Don't tell me...
Is his equipment acting up?!
I'll figure something out!
Damn.
How can I afford to be dead weight?
Will this work out somehow?
Eren.
We're going to explore the outside world someday, right?
Far beyond these walls,
there's flaming water, land made of ice,
and fields of sand spread wide.
It's the world my parents wanted to go to.
I thought you forgot,
but you stopped talking about it
because you didn't want me to join the Survey Corps, right?
The outside... world.
Eren, answer me.
Why do you want to see the outside world so badly,
knowing that with even a step beyond the walls,
a living hell and cruel death might be the only things that await,
just like what my parents had to go through?
"Why?"
Isn't that obvious?
It's because I was born in this world!
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's more fragile than a life.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, sleep in peace.
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing urges
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
negai wa okasare
trample upon my wishes.
wasureteshimau hodo
As often as I sadly forget,
mata omoidasu yo
I remember once again.
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
nani wo mamoru no darou
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
mou risei nado nai naraba
when a reason ceases to exist.
Go, run, live.
As various words come together on the battlefield where many lives are lost,
Eren carries everyone's hopes and heads toward the gate.
Primitive Desire
————Battle for Trost District, Part    ————
⑨