S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
You're the prey, and we're the hunters.
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
F
umareta hana no
Ignorant of the
amae mo shirazu ni
trampled flower's name,
hi ni ochita tori wa
hi
the bird that fell to the earth
aze wo machiwabiru
a
waits impatiently for the wind.
notta tokoro de
Even if you pray,
animo kawaranai
nothing will be changed.
ma wo kaeru no wa
But that which can alter the present
atakau kakugo da
is the resolution to fight.
hikabane fumikoete
hi
Trampling over corpses,
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
u
swine who mock the will to advance.
achiku no annei
a
Peace of the cattle,
yogi no hanei
yo
and the prosperity of deception.
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
orawareta kutsujoku wa
o
Our caged humiliation
angeki no koushi da
signals the start of our retaliation.
ouheki no sono kanata
Beyond the ramparts,
mono wo hofuru Jäger
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
otobashiru shoudou ni
o
As these surging urges
ono mi wo yaki nagara
burn away our bodies,
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a
we ignite the dusk with
uren no yumiya
u
a crimson bow and arrow.
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
...and we're the hunters.
wir
sind
Jä
ger
The World in a Little Girl's Eyes
————Battle for Trost District, Part    ————
②
Hey.
Hey!
What's wrong, Armin?
Snap out of it!
Hey!
Armin!
You awake?
Feeling all right?
Does it hurt anywhere?
What about your squad?
Squad?
Come on, get a hold of yourself.
Why are you alone?
Your body feels kinda slimy.
What in the world happened?
I'm dead weight!
I should just die!
Hey, calm down, Armin!
Damn it!
Where's everyone?
That's enough, Connie.
They're all dead.
Minus this guy.
Shut up!
Armin hasn't said anything yet!
Isn't it obvious from just looking around?
We don't have any more time to waste on him.
Why is Armin the only survivor?
Hell if I know.
Maybe they thought he was a corpse.
While I think it's unfortunate they ran into a swarm of Titans,
the fact that Eren and the others died while this incompetent survived is ridiculous.
Hey, you bitch.
Want me to me shut you up for good?!
Stop it, both of you!
I'm sure we're all just shaken up.
A bunch of our friends are suddenly dying, after all!
It's only natural!
That's my Krista!
Marry me once this operation is over!
True, she's screwing around more than usual.
Anyway, we can't just sit around here.
Can you stand, Armin?
Sorry for being a burden.
I'll go join the rear guard.
H-Hey.
Armin!
Let's move, Connie!
Our orders are to keep advancing!
This is hell.
Wait, that's nothing new.
I just wasn't aware of it until now.
This world has always been hell.
The strong prey on the weak.
It's so mercifully simple.
But... my friends...
sought the strength to live in this world.
They saved a weakling like me.
I couldn't bear that.
To them, I'm just someone who needs protection.
I wanted to be strong like them,
so I could stand as their equal,
and survive in this world.
And this is all my feelings amounted to.
Because of me, Eren was...
Hannah, what are you...
Armin, help me!
Franz isn't breathing!
I've been trying to resuscitate him over and over again,
but Franz isn't...
Hannah, it's dangerous here, so let's just—
I can't just leave Franz like this!
No, Hannah...
Franz is...
Please... just stop.
There's nothing...
that can be done for him.
H-Hey, you guys!
Do you understand the situation we're in?
We're only doing this because we understand!
If you want to live, help push!
Quit screwing around!
That won't fit no matter how you push it!
You should let the people through first!
The Titans will devour us all at this rate!
What the hell are you doing, soldier?!
Arrest those men!
B-But...
Just try it, flunky.
I'm the boss of the company here.
Uh, well...
Who do you think provides the meals you soldiers shit out?
Can you pay to feed all the soldiers in this town?
All of you, push!
The goods here are worth more than what you can ever make in your petty lives!
If you cooperate, you'll be rewarded!
It's all right.
Your father will shoot all the Titans down with his cannon.
Mom, look.
Push it through!
Push if you don't want to die!
Stop! My child is...
Damn, why is it ignoring us?!
It's an Abnormal!
Don't think too much about it!
It's fast!
Even we elites can't catch up to it?!
At this rate...
What... are you doing?
Oh, perfect timing.
Hey you, make these people help me out!
I'll reward you handsomely!
My comrades are dying right now.
Because the evacuation is lagging, they're fighting the Titans and dying.
Course they are!
It's your duty to offer your lives to protect citizens and their property, is it not?!
Don't get full of yourselves just because you freeloaders are finally doing your job
after a hundred years!
If you think it's natural for people to die for others, I'm sure you'll understand
that at times, the sacrifice of a single precious life can save many others.
Just try me!
I've known your employer for many years.
You don't know how easy it'd be for me to order you underlings around!
How can a corpse be speaking?
Wait!
P-President...
Move the wagon.
Thanks, Sis!
We're saved thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
Good work taking it down, Ackerman.
I'm impressed.
Thank you very much.
However... I dulled my blades with a single blow in my impatience.
I'll be more mindful next time.
Just what kind of life have you been living until now...
Never mind, it's nothing.
Why am I remembering that now?
Currently Disclosable Information
Ultra-hard Steel Part ①
Material that possesses both stiffness
and flexibility, which allows it
to slash through Titan flesh.
The "half-edged sword blades" that
are manufactured out of it are widely
known as anti-Titan weapons.
Currently Disclosable Information
Ultra-hard Steel Part ②
To refine "ultra-hard steel",
the blast furnaces of the
factory town are essential,
so they cannot be
manufactured elsewhere.
Year 844
Finished!
Mom, have a look.
My, you did a splendid job, Mikasa.
It's beautiful.
This embroidery has been passed down our family for generations.
If you have children someday, teach it to them.
How do you have children?
Well, you should ask your father.
Hey, Dad.
Uh, well, Dad isn't so sure either.
Ah right, Dr. Jaegar will be here soon, so why don't we ask him?
Oh, looks like he's here already.
Coming!
Mikasa?
That's right.
She's a girl your age.
There aren't any other children around here, so get along with her.
That depends on her attitude.
Eren, this is why you only have one friend.
Maybe they're not home.
Mr. Ackerman, it's Dr. Jaegar.
Pardon the intrusion.
What's wrong?
Hey, Dad?
No good.
Eren, is there a girl nearby?
Did you see Mikasa?
No.
I see.
I'm going to go call the Military Police Brigade and request an investigation.
You go wait at the base of the mountain.
Understand, Eren?
Eren!
Hey, is she really going to be worth anything?
We killed both her parents to nab her...
Take a good look at her face.
Not bad, but she's still just a kid.
Doesn't strike my fancy.
I don't care about your tastes.
She's an Oriental.
In the past, there were different human races.
She's the last descendant of a family that escaped to the walls from the Orient.
We'll auction her to some perverted patron at the underground market of the capital.
The other Orientals have been wiped out,
so she should fetch a handsome price.
Her dad didn't look like an Oriental.
I doubt she's pure-blooded.
Exactly.
Her mom would've been the real jackpot!
You just had to freak out and kill her!
I-I didn't have a choice!
She was putting up a fight!
Is that your best excuse?!
Huh?!
Dr. Jaegar, we've been wait—
Why, hello there.
You'd be wise to listen to us.
Unless you want your head split in half by this—
This bitch...
Mikasa, run away!
M-Mom...
Mikasa, hurry!
Um...
Dad...
Damn it, that's enough!
What the hell, man?!
I told you we'd only kill the dad!
But she was—
Quit your excuses.
Nab the brat!
Hey, now you'd better behave.
Otherwise... I'll do this!
It's cold...
Excuse me.
Hey, you brat!
What are you doing here?!
Um, uh...
I... was lost in the forest...
and I saw this cabin...
A kid shouldn't be walking around in the forest alone.
There are scary wolves roaming there.
But you won't have anything to worry about if you come with—
Thanks, Mister.
I get it now,
so die, you bastard!
You kidding me?!
C-Come back, you damn brat!
You goddamn animals!
Die, die!
This is what you deserve!
You had it coming!
Stay down for good!
It's all right now.
Don't worry.
You're Mikasa, right?
I'm Eren,
Dr. Jaegar's son.
I'm sure you've met him before.
I tagged along with him to your house for medical examinations.
And there...
There should have been a third man.
Did you do it?
Did you do it?!
Did you?!
I'll kill you!
You're dead meat!
F-Fight...
Fight!
If you lose, you die.
If you win, you live.
What are you thinking, you brat?!
If you don't fight, you can't win!
I can't do it!
At that moment, I remembered...
that I'd witnessed this scene before...
time and time again.
It's always been unfolding before me.
But... I turned a blind eye to it.
That's right.
This world is...
cruel.
At that instant, my body stopped shaking.
Since then, I've had complete control over my body.
I thought I could do anything.
Fight.
Fight!
His heart was pierced from the back with one strike.
Those kids did this?
Eren, I told you to wait at the base of the mountain.
Do you understand what you've done?!
I killed some dangerous animals.
They were beasts that just happened to look human!
Eren!
They would've been long gone if we'd waited for the Military Police Brigade to arrive.
It would've been too late!
That's no excuse!
You were just lucky, Eren!
I'm scolding you for thoughtlessly risking your life like that!
But...
I wanted to save her quickly.
Mikasa.
Do you remember me?
We met a few times when you were younger.
Dr. Jaegar, which way...
should I go to return home?
It's cold.
There's nowhere... for me to go home to.
You can have this.
It's warm, right?
It's warm.
Mikasa, why don't you live with us?
You've been through a lot.
You need plenty of rest.
What?
Come on, let's head back already.
To our home.
Okay.
A cruel world where...
only the victors can survive.
We're withdrawing, Ackerman.
Climb up the wall.
I'll support the vanguard's withdrawal.
Hey, Ackerman!
But I have a place to return to in this world.
Eren, if you're here, I can do anything.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's more fragile than a life.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, sleep in peace.
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing urges
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
negai wa okasare
trample upon my wishes.
wasureteshimau hodo
As often as I sadly forget,
mata omoidasu yo
I remember once again.
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
nani wo mamoru no darou
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
mou risei nado nai naraba
when a reason ceases to exist.
"I have a place to return to."
Having accomplished her mission in the rear guard, Mikasa hurried to Eren's side,
but there, only news of his death awaited her.
A Small Blade
————Battle for Trost District, Part    ————
③