Year 845:
The Colossus Titan that suddenly appeared along with the Armored Titan
destroyed everything as easily as it did the wall.
Wall Maria was abandoned.
And with a fifth of its population and a third of its land lost,
mankind had their territory reduced to Wall Rose.
Then, in the year 850, at Trost District,
mankind allowed the Titans to invade further.
Shortly after, Eren Jaegar, who was devoured by a Titan,
emerged from within a mysterious Titan.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
F
umareta hana no
Ignorant of the
amae mo shirazu ni
trampled flower's name,
hi ni ochita tori wa
hi
the bird that fell to the earth
aze wo machiwabiru
a
waits impatiently for the wind.
notta tokoro de
Even if you pray,
animo kawaranai
nothing will be changed.
ma wo kaeru no wa
But that which can alter the present
atakau kakugo da
is the resolution to fight.
hikabane fumikoete
hi
Trampling over corpses,
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
u
swine who mock the will to advance.
achiku no annei
a
Peace of the cattle,
yogi no hanei
yo
and the prosperity of deception.
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
orawareta kutsujoku wa
o
Our caged humiliation
angeki no koushi da
signals the start of our retaliation.
ouheki no sono kanata
Beyond the ramparts,
mono wo hofuru Jäger
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
otobashiru shoudou ni
o
As these surging urges
ono mi wo yaki nagara
burn away our bodies,
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a
we ignite the dusk with
uren no yumiya
u
a crimson bow and arrow.
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
...and we're the hunters.
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
...and we're the hunters.
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Response
————Battle for Trost District, Part    ————
⑥
I'll ask you once again! Just what are you?!
I'm human!
I see.
Don't think ill of me.
Marco, I've had enough.
I can't fight the Titans anymore!
What's wrong?
My comrades were devoured right in front of me!
I didn't feel even feel sad or angry seeing them die like that.
I was just thankful from the bottom of my heart that it wasn't me!
But it must be my turn next.
I finally realized.
Our job is to keep fighting until the Titans devour us, isn't it?!
If that's all I have to live for, I'd rather—
Calm down and get ahold of yourself!
You're not alone in this!
Everyone is battling with fear!
Look at Sasha!
Even after everything that's happened, she's still a noble soldier.
Um, my stomach is hurting, so can I be marked down as a casualty?
That's it!
Stop!
Stop it!
Keeping it confidential really was necessary.
With things as they are now,
if word about Eren spread...
Cannon fire?
But why only one shot?
Look, there's smoke!
It's from within the wall!
What's that?
What's happening?
Was the floodgate broken through?
It's the strongest part of the wall. There's no way!
A high-explosive shell must've accidentally been dropped.
But then why's there so much smoke?
Could it be steam from a Titan?
Hey!
What the hell's going on here?
It's alive!
Captain Felman!
W-We're on standby!
It's too dangerous to approach!
All units are to stand by on full alert!
Stand by!
Have the cannoneers ready another round!
What is this?
I remember up to the cannon fire.
Then there was a tremendous crash, impact, and heat.
We're inside a Titan's skeleton right—
Eren protected us.
That's all that matters now.
Flowers, inside here?
Hey,
you guys okay?
Eren, what is this?
No idea.
But it's evaporating already.
Just like a Titan's corpse.
Let's back away a bit.
Whether they're figuring out what to do or just distracted,
the Garrison can't see what we're doing now.
But in the end, they'll probably continue attacking.
I don't have the confidence to talk them down after showing this.
It reminded me of something though.
The basement.
The basement of my house.
Dad said I'd understand everything if I went there.
He's also the one that turned me into this.
If I get to that basement, I'll probably learn the truth about the Titans.
Damn it!
Why did he keep it all a secret?!
The Survey Corps searched for that information at the cost of thousands of lives.
It's mankind's only hope!
And you're telling me it was locked away in my basement?
Just what was going through his mind?
Come to think of it, where did he disappear to for five years—
Eren, we have other things to worry about now.
Right.
The smoke is clearing.
We'll attack immediately on sight!
Let's finish this quickly!
Remain on standby!
I'm... leaving this place.
Where to?
How?
Anywhere will do for now.
I'll climb the wall from there and head to my basement.
But I'll turn into a Titan first.
You can do that?
I'm not too sure how I do it myself,
but I think I can.
Just like how a person can't explain how they move their arms.
Earlier, I unconsciously focused on blocking the cannon.
That's why the body had no other function and easily fell apart.
This time, I'll go for something stronger.
The 15-meter-class that I kicked around all those Titans with should suffice!
Eren, your nose is bleeding.
You're looking pale, and your breathing's heavy too.
It's clearly taking a toll on your body!
I couldn't care less for my well-being.
I've got two ideas in mind.
If you guys don't try to cover for me, you'll be spared at the least.
I've already gotten you two in a real mess,
so I'll be moving solo from here on out.
No, I—
Eren,
I'm coming too.
You can't.
If I can't keep up, you can just abandon me.
But I don't have to listen to what you say.
I'm telling you to cut it out already!
I'm neither your little brother nor a kid!
Currently Disclosable Information
Yeast Part ①
A special yeast produced only within Wall Sina.
It's known that the presence of this yeast in storehouses
or tents full of fodder, wheat, or soybeans significantly
reduces rate of decay.
Currently Disclosable Information
Yeast Part ②
Building storage plants filled with this yeast in order
to stock up on supplies necessary for the recapture
of Wall Maria has been mankind's strategy thus far.
Captain, the high-explosive shell is almost loaded.
How shall we proceed?
Await my signal!
Sir.
There's no sign of the Garrison planning to launch a close-quarters attack just yet.
If there was, Mikasa would've picked up on it faster than a stray cat.
Even if they loaded the cannon as fast as possible,
it should take at least another 20 seconds.
Eren will probably act within that time and depart from here.
Why am I remembering that now?
Is it because this is the end for us?
So even up to the very end...
I was nothing more than a coward, after all.
They've saved me countless times already.
But I've yet to return the favor even once.
How could I consider myself a friend who's on equal terms with them?
How could I say, "I'm coming too?"
I don't even have the confidence to keep up.
After... all this...
the three of us will never be together again.
Eren, I—
Wait, Mikasa.
I said I had two ideas in mind, didn't I?
Armin, I'll leave everything for you to decide.
I'm well aware of just how unrealistic my plan is.
It would be the most effective to use this Titan power systematically under the army's command.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but if you think you can convince the Garrison that I'm not a threat,
I'll put my trust in you and stay.
That's my second idea.
If you think you can't, I'll have to resort to the first idea.
You have fifteen seconds to decide.
Whether you can do it or not, I'll respect any opinion you have.
Eren, why would you entrust me with such a decision?
The worse a situation is, the better your decisions are, you know?
I'm willing to bet on that.
When did I ever...
Lots of times.
Five years ago, if you didn't call Hannes-san,
Mikasa and I would've been devoured by a Titan.
It was just me convincing myself.
Convincing myself that I was powerless and a burden.
That thought didn't cross their minds at all!
Armin, we're out of time.
The cannon's been loaded.
Ready to fire at any time.
The two entrusting their lives to me now are the people I trust most in this world.
How could I possibly doubt myself now?
I'll convince them no matter what.
Do anything you guys can to show you're not a threat.
Something's been on my mind since I saw Eren fighting as a Titan.
I still haven't figured it out, but I'll pull this off.
I'll think while talking if I have to!
Halt!
So you've finally revealed your true colors, monster!
I'll signal...
I'll signal the cannon!
He is not the enemy of mankind!
We're willing to share any and all information that we have!
I have no intention of hearing your pleas!
We've seen everything we need to know. There's no room for discussion!
If you claim he's not our enemy, then prove it!
If you can't, we'll simply eliminate the threat!
There's no need for proof!
That's right. It's unnecessary!
Besides, how we see him is not an issue!
What?!
I've heard that many have seen him in action!
If that's true, they must've also seen him fighting the Titans!
And that includes the sight of the surrounding Titans swarming him!
In other words, the Titans saw him as a target of predation, just like the rest of mankind!
No matter how we go about it, that fact cannot be denied!
He has a point.
A Titan as an ally.
That's ridiculous.
Prepare to attack!
Don't be fooled by his clever tricks!
Their actions have always been beyond our comprehension.
It must be possible for them to imitate our form and speech to delude us!
We cannot allow them do as they please any longer!
It's no good.
He's abandoned all reason.
He's too scared to think.
Eren, Mikasa!
I am soldier that has long since offered his life for the revival of mankind!
To perish while obeying that conviction would be my life's greatest glory!
If we were to utilize his Titan powers in addition to our remaining forces,
recapturing this town would no longer be impossible!
Praying for the glory of mankind,
I shall elaborate on his strategic worth with all the time I have left!
Captain Felman, perhaps we should consider his—
Silence!
No matter how they plea, they're still rebels!
Those who transgress must be eliminated!
That's the duty of a soldier!
That's enough.
As always, despite having a large body, you're as feeble as a fawn.
Commander Pixis?
Are you blind to the brilliance of that salute?
I just arrived, but a messenger filled me in earlier.
Go take command of the reinforcements.
I think it'd be best to hear what they have to say.
According to the Survey Corps' reports,
the Titans were predicted to approach from the south.
Specifically, Shiganshina, the southernmost district of Wall Maria, was attacked.
Therefore, the town that was the most likely to be attacked next was
the southernmost district of Wall Rose, Trost.
Trost District  Inner Gate
Dott Pixis.
The chief executive in charge of all the southern territories including Trost District,
and the man given full authority over the defense of mankind's most important districts.
I guess I won't find one, after all.
I wouldn't mind being devoured, if it's by an exquisitely beautiful female.
And he's also known as a natural eccentric.
What's the Commander thinking?!
How could he accompany such suspicious people up there?
Well, the Commander's thoughts are beyond the comprehension of average people.
Captain, the soldiers are in formation.
Right. Good work.
I see.
So you say that all the answers lie within that basement.
Yes.
Do you believe me?
As long as you yourself aren't certain,
I'd say I can only keep it in mind at best.
However, I believe myself capable of seeing the truth of things.
I shall guarantee your safety.
Recruit Arlert, was it?
Sir!
Earlier, you said that if we utilize this "Titan power,"
it'd be possible to recapture this town, did you not?
Did you truly believe that, or was it a vain act of desperation?
It was...
both!
What I was trying to say back then
was that Eren could carry the large boulder to seal the destroyed gate in his Titan form.
It's an idea that I came up with on the spot,
but I hoped the possibility to break out of this deadlock could be seen in Eren's power.
Of course, it was all a genuine attempt to survive.
A genuine attempt to survive...
The most trustworthy words I'll ever hear.
Well, Recruit Jaegar?
Sir?
Can you seal that gate?
I...
Well...
I don't know.
I'm just as clueless as the rest of us present here.
So, regardless of whether I can do it or not, I can't answer half-heartedly.
Oh, that's true, I apologize.
That was the wrong question.
Will you do it or not—which is it?
I'll do it.
I'll do it!
I'm not sure whether I can or not, but I'll do it!
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's more fragile than a life.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, sleep in peace.
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing urges
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
negai wa okasare
trample upon my wishes.
wasureteshimau hodo
As often as I sadly forget,
mata omoidasu yo
I remember once again.
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
nani wo mamoru no darou
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
mou risei nado nai naraba
when a reason ceases to exist.
Though they once ran in fear,
they're soldiers that inevitably decided to remain on the battlefield.
Eren makes his decision.
To become the hope of mankind.
Idol
————Battle for Trost District, Part    ————
⑦