Next, it'll be your eye.
Be afraid.
Stop, Fox!
Snake?
How terrible.
Boss... welcome back. When did you...?
Fox.
Yes, sir!
- Come here.
- Yes, sir!
- Badger.
Explain!
Yes, sir!
You idiots.
You guys are idiots.
Why are you guys bullying the slaves?
The young master is the one
who should be doing that.
But... it's because this guy...
was giving us attitude.
Sorry about that.
These guys are just stupid.
I'm Snake.
I'm Thorfinn.
You see, Thorfinn?
Your body is telling you
that it wants to live.
I'm going to sleep.
You guys, kindly send those three back.
- Huh?
- Oh...
I hope you know...
If you cause any more trouble
regarding this case,
you guys will never
be able to eat using your jaws ever again.
- Am I clear?
- Yes, sir!
Thorfinn...
You...
I want to live?
Live...
to do what?
Aside from your ear,
your wounds seem pretty shallow.
They should heal well.
I'm sorry you two had to go through that.
The master is also having a hard time
trying to handle those guests
and their pranks.
Pranks?
We were almost killed
because of their "prank."
Oh, they wouldn't actually kill you.
No...
If that Snake or whatever hadn't come,
we really would've been killed.
To people like them,
our lives are not worth a damn!
It can't be helped.
The strong ones kill the weak ones.
That is only natural.
What did you say?
- You--
- Calm down, Einar.
If they ever bother you again,
don't follow them.
Come and tell me instead.
More importantly,
we don't want your wound to fester.
Let me put medicine on it.
Medicine?
Pater, we...
Don't worry about
the cost of the medicine.
I am in charge of taking care of you guys.
I'm sorry I got there so late.
No...
Thank you very much.
You should thank Arnheid too.
She searched the fields up and down
in order to notify me.
Rest for today, you two.
I will explain to the master.
Also...
This is my old shirt,
so it may be a little big,
but you can have this, Thorfinn.
Since yours was shredded.
Come on...
Don't you have anything to say to Pater?
Jeez! In these situations,
you say, "Thank you very much." Come on!
Just say it!
Why have you been completely silent?
You seem so ungrateful
even though everyone's taking care of you!
I don't mind.
I know Thorfinn is a man of few words.
Thank you very much.
Hey, where are you going?
He said we can take a break
from harvesting wheat today.
The forest...
These wounds are nothing to me.
Wait! I'll go too.
The way he moved when he was
attacked by Snake...
It wasn't normal.
And plus...
The strong ones kill the weak ones.
That is only natural.
Thorfinn.
Have you been to war?
Yeah.
Did you
kill people?
Yeah.
About how many people?
Five...
or ten people?
Why do you want to know?
You hate war, don't you?
It's going to fall.
I don't remember how many.
I killed a lot.
From the time I was five or six years old
I was on the battlefield.
I was part of
the Danish invasion of England too.
I was a warrior.
Are you disgusted, Einar?
I don't remember how many I killed.
I killed a lot.
I found you.
You brat...
Die!
You little brat!
- I'll kill you!
- Kill him!
Die!
Damn it!
Einar...
Why do you...
wake me up every time I have a nightmare?
I've killed...
I've killed many people.
From one battle to another,
I attacked villages
and killed many people.
The people who killed your family...
I am...
no different from them.
You...
Is there anything
good that comes from being alive?
I can't think of anything.
Of all the years I have lived,
I have never once
been glad that I was alive.
You...
You want to die?
I don't know
what kind of horrible things
you went through.
I don't even want to know
what kind of hell you've lived through.
But even though this may be hell,
we are able to chat about nonsense,
eat food, take a shit, and go to sleep...
We can do that
because someone else let us live.
You said you can't think of anything...
but you're wrong.
You're wrong!
Damn it!
Life's not that easy!
First of all...
it's not like you
are the one who killed my family.
The world doesn't revolve around you.
Thank you...
Einar.
Thank you for...
waking me up.
Jeez...
Thanks to all your sleep talking
I'm completely sleep deprived.
I see...
- Sorry, Einar.
- Just go to sleep.
"Path of blood."
Subtitle translation by: Kiko Morita