Why is Zobul's Emperor here?
Why do you come to us?
No, what do you intend to do?
He is a deity.
Deity.
Ouch!
You're stronger than I thought.
I get tired quicker now because of my age.
Whatever. Show me what you got.
Or do you want to run to your friends and cry?
No one is running away, bastard.
The Idaten Deities Know Only Peace
What a drag.
This should work.
Seriously? Attack this way?
Come on!
I can't believe this.
Anyway, I knew I can't win.
Do whatever you want.
What are these strings?
I just realize these strings are on them.
Is someone out there controlling these people?
Correct!
They are my puppets.
You have to fight them forever before you defeat me.
Here you are!
My face...
I got you!
You fool.
How dare you!
What happened?
My hand is chopped off.
I can't believe the simple trap worked.
Maybe I can actually win.
I still need to look for bald Bacode,
the fat woman, and the girl with bunches.
Prontea converts what he sees into electronic signals,
which are sent through his computer
to General Pisara.
Nope...
- I feel like I'm a factory QC. - Nope...
Just shut up and look for them.
How many have you found that look like Miku?
Just one.
(MIKU)
It's hard to believe that someone looks like this.
So...
Who is she? She's so much like her.
A substitute?
Yeah, but why?
Okay, I'll go and ask her.
Let's go.
What do you want!
Shut up. I don't hurt humans. Just be quiet.
Let's get out of here.
No, I...
I'll be here until the end.
Old man.
Can't you extend your tentacles?
Or transform?
He recovers so fast.
That's not good for me.
(Episode 8 Idaten)
No, I'm good at fighting with bare hands.
No trick or scheme is exactly what you want, right?
Right.
Watch this.
He's fast and recovers quickly.
The longer we fight, the bigger chance I may lose.
So naive.
If you didn't show up,
nothing will happen.
Stop joking.
I can kill you on my own.
By the way, old man.
Don't you want to take your hands back?
This hurts so bad.
He's so seriously injured,
but is pain the only thing he felt?
We should get it over with.
I agree.
This should be the end...
What? Are you dead?
Come and hit me again.
She looks like she's about to die.
Am I winning?
What a drag!
This cowardly trick has made me super mad.
What? What's going on?
She recovers so fast!
If you are caught in the strings,
you'll be trapped inside.
Really? Let's make it tighter then.
Damn. I have to cut off my hair...
So, everyone is here.
It's my turn!
This is too much.
Are you the only one left?
So, you're the real manipulator.
You... can't stand up?
I won.
How could he not kill me?
It seems all he cares is winning.
Get ready to launch the missiles.
Even if it succeeds, we may still be wiped out.
Demon Lord,
I asked my kids to run away without your approval.
It's not... over yet.
What are you doing?
What kind of question is this?
You'll die without treatment.
You're stubbornly nice.
It won't work. I weigh over 500 kilos.
Ouch...
Leave me alone. Just run.
It's not bad for me to see a young girl's nude before death.
Stop it.
I like that.
You're like my wife. 20 years after marriage,
if we have sex with the lights on, she would still get mad.
It's fun that women are shy.
Girls like Miku are not my type.
Emperor Takeshita...
You didn't get us into the war,
or take us as hostages.
Even now, you still wish I could run away.
I think...
you're not a bad guy.
Damn... I'm still not recovered.
What's that?
Emperor Takeshita.
This is my last advice.
I think you've realized that
I'm not a human being.
I can never understand human beings.
In all cases,
I can't stop hunting humans.
If you don't want to get caught again,
run to Hotayena.
If so, before you die,
you can live a peaceful life.
What are you talking about?
Even if you're not a human,
you have a human appearance and human mind.
How come you can't understand us?
I'm so useless.
When I was assaulted,
captured, and imprisoned,
I could do nothing but pray.
Deities came to save us regardless of the injuries.
She misunderstood.
But I can't even carry the injured man.
Praying is so useless.
I want power.
I want the power to protect everyone.
I also want... the power deities have.
There are three conditions to make Idatens:
the thoughts of a number of creatures,
a long period of time,
and desire for salvation.
Now, the Zobul Empire
has met these three conditions.
The Idatens that were born
will have their appearance, gender, name and character
the same as the one who prays with the strongest desire
when the conditions are met.
Where are you from?
Are you okay?
You seem wounded.
Really? You were watching the whole time?
No, you must be mistaking me for someone else.
I have no idea.
Ouch... my body...
No!
What's that?
The fast flying speed... Is she...
Before killing you, I have a question.
Where is Demon Lord Over-M?
Or are you him?
Demon Lord Over-M?
How could I know where he is!
You've lived for 800 years and you don't know his identity.
What's the point...
It's true I don't know, but he reminds me of something.
The way he names things is like my grandpa.
If it's something hard, it's called super-K.
If it's weak, looks like a cow and can be eaten by demons,
it's called Minotaurs.
It's a practical low-level demon,
which can be eaten like beef at any time.
How about calling it Minotaurs?
It's not bad...
Coincidence?
Interesting discussion.
May I join you guys?
Who is it? Demon...
It's better to stay quiet.
Rin, after watching your battles, I remember something.
So, I'm here to talk about it.
Why do you know my name?
That sword is the same as Sukis'.
How can I let you fight? You are so clumsy
and only know how to run away.
If you insist,
practice slashing it every day.
Sukis.
Stop underestimating me.
One day...
How... do you know...
As I remember, you were weak and cried a lot.
Grandpa and everyone.
If you're not here, I...
I can only, only...
Who are you?
How do you know all these?
Well, I don't know either.
But, I just remember a lot of things.
For example, you're more afraid of being alone
than the demons.
That's why you'd rather go to the battles.
No, I want to go with you.
Why... this guy...
She stopped.
There are weak points all over her.
Based on previous battles,
I found a way to defeat her.
But, I only have one chance.
I told you already.
I really don't know where Miku goes.
What do you think?
Anyway,
she must have run away.
Even if we ask other demons, they won't know.
So...
she escaped.
What a drag.
I see why General Pisara is most careful with her.
She is right.
I found Bilov and Bacode.
General Nepto. Why do you do this?
Shut up!
You'll be just like me even against your will.
Okay. Hand Bacode to Prontea.
Then explain to Bilov about the situation
and take him to a safe place.
Roger that.
Nepto, what are you up to!
What do you want?
At some point,
you have to create a new country for everyone.
Even Hayato is back here.
Did something happen?
Sorry for making you wait.
Here you go. It's Bacode.
Hayato is coming back.
Do you know what happened?
Nope.
I thought he would not come back even if he's dying.
Where is he now?
Over here.
So slow.
Can you be faster?
That's the best I can do.
I've never walked on the sea...
What?
He's our friend.
I see. It's the new Idaten.
Idaten?
Right. Zobul has met the conditions.
I need to perform the operation.
Paula, I'll leave this to you.
Alright.
Hayato. It seems like a tough battle.
Was the opponent Umeyo or the Emperor?
Emperor, I guess.
Did you lose?
Shut up! I won!
I'll come back once she's settled. Just stay tuned.
Awesome.
The new Idaten, what's your name?
I'm... Gil. I'm Gil.
Gil, nice to meet you.
I'm Prontea.
Now we're in the critical period of the war.
After it finishes, let's talk.
Has everyone escaped?
Who are you?
When did you stand behind me?
That's my line.
You can teleport?
Are you Gil?
Yeah, I'm Gil Tina.
People call me Gil.
How do you know my name?
A human with the same appearance.
Coincidence?
Are you a deity, too?
I see. You met Hayato.
I'm a deity just like him.
You're just a human, but an interesting one.
What have you done...
You're the new sample of summoning rules for Idatens.
Look what you have done.
He's a demon.
If he was not dead, you would be.
But... you took someone's life so easily.
If I was weaker,
and had a hard time killing him,
would you blame me, too?
What can I do to make you satisfied?
I don't know.
I might be dead if you didn't kill him.
But...
taking someone's life like this,
I can't accept it.
She's an interesting human,
but is kind of a drag.
What should I do?
Right now,
a lot of people can't escape because of injuries.
I can't save everyone on my own.
Deities, please send me power...
Sleep until everything is done.
No wars can be so ideal.
You'd better not know it.
He doesn't remember it clearly,
and doesn't look like him.
But he knows things only my grandpa knows.
Some of his habits are just like his.
Are you... my grandpa?
She's good at attacking,
but not defending.
So, with the help of her power,
I can easily chop off her arms.
She would have to take everything she attacks with.
Take your own attack!
So powerful!
Even Demon Lord is affected!
But he's a robot, he should be fine.
Whatever. I just need one more strike,
and she will turn to ashes...
Gran... Grandpa.
I...
always hope to see you again...
Master...
Six hours after Takeshita and Brandy are defeated,
Pisara and Kori led the armies to join in the war.
Hayato is also back.
Bacode is in the control room, replacing Pisara.
He needs to find the remaining demons.
After Prontea's and Hayato's efforts,
the war is put to an end.
We have to start everything all over again.