[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:Yama no Susume #1 chs
Original Script:A.I.R.nesSub(翻译：dgwxx/时轴·校对：cunhan)
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,55,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H32BFA404,&H00C5AD1E,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,60,60,20,1
Style: title,Wenquanyi Micro Hei,56,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,10,20,1
Style: yama_neta,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H64C5AD1E,&H00E2D588,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,7,60,60,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.81,0:00:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘不掉的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.03,0:00:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\fad(1000,0)\c&H6A55A8&\pos(640,270)}登 {\c&HE2D588&}山 {\c&H6A55A8&}少 {\c&HE2D588&}女{\c&H6A55A8&}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.49,0:00:23.50,yama_neta,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合目：登山进度 从山脚到山顶共分十合目
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.75,0:00:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.34,0:00:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她？ 初中倒是跟她一班…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.13,0:00:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过总觉着她不怎么合群 没门吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.52,0:00:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑且问问看嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.98,0:00:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪村同学
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.24,0:00:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫雪村葵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.57,0:00:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天开始就是高中生了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.67,0:00:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3mm圆珠20个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.86,0:00:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圆形小珠112个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.13,0:00:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花饰1个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.38,0:00:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20cm尼龙线4根…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.24,0:00:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪村…同学…？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.99,0:00:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超小圆珠…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.14,0:00:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.25,0:00:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们等下一起去喝点什么 你要不要也…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.26,0:00:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 今天家里有法事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.65,0:00:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后还要给家里买晚饭的食材
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.10,0:01:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后还要带狗狗散步 还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.64,0:01:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.19,0:01:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都跟你说了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.53,0:01:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太合群
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.27,0:01:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 回家路上买些做点心的材料
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.73,0:01:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再去精品店看看新品
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.75,0:01:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后顺便去趟图书馆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.57,0:01:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上了高中 也要一个人玩得高高兴兴！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.92,0:01:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵好久不见！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.53,0:01:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小学毕业第一次见面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.66,0:01:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这谁来着
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.31,0:01:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又上一所学校 我们命中注定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.01,0:01:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得吧 我们以前一起看的日出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.55,0:01:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日向…同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.68,0:01:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又能一起爬了！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.35,0:01:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬 爬什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.17,0:01:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能爬什么 当然是爬山！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.02,0:01:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.46,0:01:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以后一定再来啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.11,0:01:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过那种话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.15,0:01:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还说过更厉害的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.96,0:01:55.13,yama_neta,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剑岳位于日本富山县 处于北阿尔卑斯山脉北部 顶峰海拔2999米 因冰蚀地貌险峻危险而闻名
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.96,0:01:55.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单手攀剑岳toka
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.52,0:01:58.59,yama_neta,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦金利山位于美国阿拉斯加州 海拔6194米是北美大陆最高峰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.52,0:01:58.59,yama_neta,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本著名登山家冒险家植村直己（翻译君的校友） 在人类史上首次完成冬季单独登顶后第二天失踪遇难
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.52,0:01:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去麦金利山吊唁植村直己toka
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.96,0:02:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脑子坏掉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.32,0:02:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经忘却的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.12,0:02:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 小时候有一段时间向往登山
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.08,0:02:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后忘乎所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.23,0:02:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}耶—— 麦金利山耶——
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.22,0:02:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果骨折住院
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.91,0:02:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后就得了严重的恐高症
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.95,0:02:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好的 爬山去！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.50,0:02:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬山咯 爬山咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.98,0:02:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.87,0:02:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太爱户外运动 还有恐高症…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.84,0:02:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么不合群 可交不到朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.54,0:02:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没个阳光点的爱好 男朋友也别想了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.10,0:02:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙 非但不听人说话 吐糟倒是毫不留情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.81,0:02:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起来了 差点忘了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.33,0:02:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}呀 摔进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.15,0:02:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}啊 讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.38,0:02:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}小葵喜欢米田君你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.14,0:02:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要跟她在一起 就绝对没好事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.11,0:02:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先来我家 制定登山计划咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.36,0:02:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.49,0:02:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我…爬山真的不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.53,0:03:00.03,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\blur5}唯\N独\N就\N怕\N山
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.45,0:03:08.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}行こう！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.38,0:03:15.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}スタッカートみたいに 胸を叩くワクワク感
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.36,0:03:17.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}不思議　不安より
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.05,0:03:25.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}楽しみの容量が増えたよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.79,0:03:28.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}また明日！やっほー
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.45,0:03:08.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}出发！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.38,0:03:15.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}昂扬感像断奏音符般拍打胸膛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.36,0:03:17.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}真奇妙 不但没有不安
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.05,0:03:25.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}快乐的容量反而更大了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.79,0:03:28.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs32\blur3\3c&H252527&}明天再见！YAHOO
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.79,0:03:28.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\fs24\blur3\3c&H252527&\pos(610,636)}zhan
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.60,0:03:30.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\fad(300,0)\an8\fs32}翻译dgwxx 后期cunhan
