Hasuta, where are Nyaruko and Kuuko's scents coming from?
Straight ahead.
Nyaruko! Kuuko!
Are you all right, Mahiro?
Y-Yeah.
You two go on ahead.
Kuuko and I will let
our fists do the talking.
Hey, wait.
Boy, this is the destiny
Nyaruko and I share.
Mahiro.
Nyaruko, Kuuko.
Yes?
What?
Let's get this over with soon,
so we can go home and
eat dinner together.
My mom's croquettes are way
better than anything I can cook.
Hasuta, let's go.
Where's my mom?
Huh? Um, probably this way.
He is a good boy.
Of course he is.
He's my husband.
Becoming an adult
is such a sad thing.
If you have something
dear to protect,
you may end up at
odds with yourself.
Is that right?
You're ready to fight, aren't you?
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
uu!
nya!
let's nya!
kokoro nurunuru igyou no kamigami
Strange-looking gods with hearts that go wiggle wiggle
watashi mo anata mo kowagari no monozuki
You and I both love those kinds of scary stories
katachi murumuru ikyouto nigereba
Once the pagans have been scared away
watashi to anata wa entenka de odeeto
We'll go on a date under the blazing sun
tanoshii ne yakeru zo tokeru zo
Isn't this fun? I'll burn! I'll melt!
ikimono janai
Hey, I'm not alive!
mukuro hiyahiya sore demo suki desu
My heart's cold and slimy, but you know I still love you
watashi ga ichiban hoshii no wa naisho yo
What I want most is a total secret
sugata payapaya sore de wa ikimashou
I may not be the best, but let's get going anyway!
watashi ni ichiban niau kana fujouri
What suits me best is total absurdity
kagami ni wa
They won't show up
dan dan dare na no?
Who, Who, Who is that?
utsuranai
in any mirrors
dare nanda? yada yada
Who is it? Oh my
yokubou wa kotoba ni shinakucha
You have to say exactly what you want
uu!
hora
See?
nya!
kiechau deshou
They'll disappear like that
let's nya!
taiyou nanka mabushikutte
The stupid sun is way too bright!
yami no hou ga mugen desu
The darkness is way more free!
doki doki
Thump thump!
taiyou bakka mabushikute
The sun is so very bright!
yami no hou ga
The darkness is way more free!
su
te
ki
Nyaruko!
CAOS CAOS
I wanna CAOS
I wanna chaos
moe yo konton muteki desu
Burn! Anarchy always reigns supreme!
waku waku
So exciting!
CAOS CAOS
una sera CAOS
A night of total chaos!
moeru you na
Feelings that feel like burning!
ki
mo
chi
nyande?!
Why?
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
You're a tough opponent.
Aren't you going to
transform, Nyaruko?
I don't need to
transform to beat you.
But if things continue like
this, I'll have no choice.
I didn't want to have to do this.
The wind blew away my
swimsuit glamor shots!
You're wide open!
Nyaruko, no fair.
There are no photos of you,
let alone a swimsuit.
Just letting you touch them
would tarnish Mahiro.
Now...
Tell me why you sided
with that woman.
Fine. The loser must
obey the winner.
Why are you undressing?
Since I lost, I must surrender
my innocence to you.
I wouldn't take it
even if you paid me.
Use me like an old rag.
Make me so I can never go
out in the sunlight again.
It hurts, yet it feels so good!
Spit it out already!
Fine.
Whisper, whisper.
Is this the place, Hasuta?
Yeah. There's a scent just
like yours on the other side.
Okay.
The War in the Market
Hi there, Hiro.
Mom!
I didn't expect you
to come this far.
Are you that desperate to
interfere with our plans?
Of course I am.
Give me back my mom!
Suppose we do return her to you.
Will you hand her over
to Hastur after that?
Me?
What is she talking about?
I don't know.
My dad just told me
to find your mom.
Don't act like you don't know.
You came to steal information about
our company's next-generation console!
What?
Hiro, this could be amazing.
She says this is a
space gaming console.
With the help of this exceptionally knowledgeable housewife,
we will have the advantage in the
next-generation game console war.
Hold on.
This means you didn't kidnap my mom for her Sononium.
Ta-da! I got you these this time!
You bought another
retro video game console.
Game Console Maniac!
That was the foreshadowing?
Cordless bungee jumping hurts.
Kuuko!
Nyar—
How shameful!
Would you please not do that?
Actually, I need to talk
to you about the reason
she double-crossed
us for that woman.
She is a fanatical gamer who
loves our company's consoles.
To show our respect for
her, we call her "Queen."
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be.
The Cthulhu Corporation's game
console is the Xoth, spelled like this.
Xoth,
the name of the star Cthulhu was based on before coming to Earth.
Stop trying to fit
jokes in everywhere.
The father of the
boy standing there...
is a board member
at CCE, our bitter rivals.
CCE?
Carcosa Computer Entertainment.
The company that
manufactures the HS3.
So Hasuta's dad is one
of their board members.
Huh? Is that what my dad does?
You still insist on playing dumb?
Fine.
We have Yasaka Yoriko and
the Queen as our trump cards.
Victory will be ours!
That's all? We got dragged
into their console war?
Yes.
Hear me, citizens.
What citizens?
The Xoth 731
is a new machine which
will allow users to experience
virtual reality by
sending game data
directly to their brains
from a massive server.
The specs are three times
greater than the HS3.
Unbeatable graphics.
Operability impossible
with a controller.
Download-only distribution
to reduce costs.
It is perfect! Atlantis!
Amazing. I will
purchase an account.
You shut up.
What do you say?
What do you think of the culmination of our company's technology?
But...
I think this will probably fail.
What?
It's obvious if you look
at game console history.
In general, the console
with better specs loses.
The greater the specs,
the higher the R&D costs.
This makes it harder for companies
to produce the all-important games.
Do you think a console
without games is attractive?
Well...
On top of that, retail stores make
most of their money from game sales.
If they can't sell the
all-important games,
do you really think console sales will make up for it?
But ma'am, what about
your promise to help us?
I never said I would help you.
What?
Then you came all
the way here because...
Yes, out of curiosity.
Impossible!
Well, then. It's time for you
to return Mahiro's mother!
She is not yours, girl.
You're right.
I'll have to take her back
like the crawling chaos I am.
I have arrived!
W-Wait. Stay back!
No criminal waits
when she's told to!
I'm not sure you should
be making that comparison.
Oh, go ahead.
Thank you.
Yes, this is Luhy Jistone.
The CEO?
Yes. Yes.
The Xoth 731 is
coming along nicely.
Yes, it should be completed soon.
What? Withdrawing?
Wait.
This console is the next generation of
hardware that will save our company!
It was decided in
a board meeting?
W-Wait, please don't hang up!
CEO, CEO!
I can guess what happened,
but what did he say?
We're withdrawing from
the game industry.
The project department
has been dismissed.
I've been laid off.
I knew it.
What are we going to do?
We can't just sit here.
You're right.
I'm not finished yet!
This isn't over!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Turning on the Xoth 731.
Once I show him its power,
the CEO will have to accept it.
It's on.
What's going to happen?
Why are you here?
The development office
is a restricted area!
Hey, I've got a
bad feeling about this.
So do I.
Mahiro.
Hey, is this your doing?
No. I didn't order
them to do that.
Are you all right, Mahiro?
Yeah.
Mahiro, do you think
the console is transmitting
data to their brains
and they're playing a
game inside their heads?
What?
Luhy, was it?
What kind of game
is running right now?
An action game in
which the player
becomes a zombie
and attacks humans.
So that's it.
Mom!
You don't mind if I
defeat them, do you?
Not that I'll wait
for your answer.
Wait.
They're basically
hypnotized. Don't kill them.
In that case, I'll have to
use my paralyzing forks.
Paralyzing forks?
Let's break away!
What is this Musou Mode?
I'm just good at gathering
up and killing trash.
I'm the type that can hunt an
unlimited number of weaker monsters.
M-Ma'am?
Mom.
Despair awaits you at the finish!
There wasn't any point
in you transforming.
That's not true!
I performed the highly
important love scene of
defeating the mastermind
behind this incident!
You mean the big scene.
Wait! This is the product of
our blood, sweat and tears!
But we cannot allow such
a dangerous object to exist.
Besides, I need something to
make my transformation worth it.
You should hide your
true feelings, Nyaruko.
Nyaruko.
What? What do
you want, Kuuko?
Let me do it.
Huh? Why?
I love the Xoth.
At least let me send it to its grave with my own hands.
No. If I do that, my love scene...
Your big scene.
...really will be ruined!
Let her do it, Nyaruko.
What?!
Nyaruko.
Fine.
I am sorry I could
not love you more.
You were born
ahead of your time.
May you rest in peace.
Our technology...
My ideal...
Now that it's all over,
I can see how
surprisingly stupid it was.
I had fun. I even got to touch
a space game console.
Give me a break.
I was really worried about you.
Sorry, Hiro.
I decided to let the Cthulhu
Corporation handle her.
The Planetary Defense Organization doesn't need to get involved.
I see.
You're still crying about it?
I'm sorry, Mahiro.
I'll go home and tell my dad
not to involve
your mom in this.
Thanks, Hasuta.
Mahiro.
Listen...
Yeah?
I have to go now.
I see.
See you later.
Yeah.
I-It seems a pleasant wind
blows through this city.
See you later.
Bye-bye!
What a weird kid.
Yes, but Mahiro...
What?
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Me too.
My name is Yasaka Hastur.
You can call me Hasuta.
Yasaka Hastur
I knew it.
Yasaka?
How are you
related to our Yasaka?
Um, well... Mahiro is...
Yasaka Hastur
very important to me!
Does that mean you're one of those like we see everywhere these days?
Yasaka Hastur
Hey, you just got here!
What do you think you're saying?
Go for it, Hasuta.
I support you.
Shut up! I know
what you're up to!
You've got a lot to
deal with, Yasaka.
Can't a guy get a break?!
You should apologize.
Over here!
Mahiro, the water feels great!
Aren't you going to go?
I don't feel like it.
Why did this happen?
It was right after
Hasuta transferred.
Hot springs?
Yes. To thank me
for my patronage,
they gave me some
comrade tickets—
I mean, hot springs tickets!
Hot springs sound nice!
Hold on.
I'm still exhausted after what
just happened at R'lyeh!
Then you should rejuvenate
yourself at the hot springs.
There's even a beach nearby.
You can bring up to eight guests.
Shantak-kun counts as one guest?
I can go, too?
Of course.
You can invite two
more of your friends.
Then, let's ask
Tamao and Yoichi!
Um, I don't mind
sitting this out.
You must make haste, Mahiro.
Boy, the ocean is calling us.
Let's go.
W-Wait a minute!
Listen to what I'm saying!
What's this?
As long as you're here,
you should enjoy yourself.
I don't feel like it.
You're no fun.
Don't be such a downer!
That's right. Let's play together!
Hey.
I wonder who Yasaka
is really interested in.
Who knows?
Did you come here because
you wanted to find out?
I am trying to
become a journalist.
I will use this trip
to make memories and
babies with Mahiro.
I will use this trip
to make bright family
plans with Nyaruko.
I'll use this trip to
get with Mahiro.
Those three seem to be
having naughty thoughts.
By the way...
What is that thing?
Who knows?
Mahiro, I'll see you later.
Yeah, yeah.
Hold it!
As long as I'm alive,
I won't let you
bathe with Mahiro!
What?
Sniffle.
The water is wonderful!
Isn't it?
Tonight's the night I'll
make babies with Mahiro.
I must clean every inch of my body.
Tonight is the night I will
make babies with Nyaruko.
I must clean every inch of my body.
Well, good night.
Good night.
You!
I crawled up in the night
like a true Nyarlathotep.
That's not funny at all!
No one is around to bother us.
I made sure of it.
How long must I wait, Nyaruko?
Become one with... Mahiro.
Hiro...
This is our time.
Why are you doing this?
Now, Mahiro.
D-Don't do this, Nyaruko!
Let's make our love take form.
S-Stop!
shirokujichuu be with you
All day through, I want to be with you
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
watashi ga anata no mae
If I were to appear in front of you
arawareta nara "zutto" nan desu
Then it'll be "forever" that I'm with you
suki toka kirai da toka
"I love you" and "I hate you"
kanjou izen ni zettai desu
It's even more important than feelings like those
nijuuyo jikan ana ga aku hodo
nijuuyo
ana ga aku hodo
jikan
24 hours a day, so much I could burn a hole
anata dake wo mitsumetai
I want to watch only you all the time
uchuuteki kibo no love de I want you
uchuuteki kibo no love de I
want
you
With all my love, as vast as the universe, I want you
soba ni iru yo shirokujichuu
shirokujichuu
soba ni iru
yo
I'll be with you all day through
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
hora sunao ni natte love me do
I'll be honest with myself, so love me do
kono chikyuu de randebuu
We'll have on this planet a rendezvous
kibou datte anata to iu
My dreams will always be for you
tokimeki ni deaeta
I found my excitement in you
yakusoku da yo zutto be with you
So I'll promise I'll always be with you
When they said
their hands were full,
what did they mean?
Is that what they meant?
Do not worry. I will kill him.
Why do you have a shotgun?
The next episode is
"The Blue Lagoon."
Don't you mean "Red Sea of Blood"?