H-Hey.
Nyaruko, I love you!
Nyaruko, I love you! With all my heart!
Marry me now!
Wh-Wha... Wh-Wha... Wha...
What?!
Allow me to explain.
Currently, Nyaruko and Mahiro-san's
minds have switched bodies.
Nyaruko! I love you!
I want to make you mine!
Your silver antenna,
your green eyes, everything!
If you'll crawl up to me,
not even the Twelve Zodiac Temples
or the Budokai can scare me!
I can go anywhere if I have you!
If you want me to wear nothing
but glasses and an apron,
I'd be happy to—
Ludon Mesa...
Yasaka-kun got rejected pretty hard.
Um, you two.
Could you please do that someplace where it won't disturb my lesson?
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
uu!
nya!
let's nya!
kokoro nurunuru igyou no kamigami
Strange-looking gods with hearts that go wiggle wiggle
watashi mo anata mo kowagari no monozuki
You and I both love those kinds of scary stories
katachi murumuru ikyouto nigereba
Once the pagans have been scared away
watashi to anata wa entenka de odeeto
We'll go on a date under the blazing sun
tanoshii ne yakeru zo tokeru zo
Isn't this fun? I'll burn! I'll melt!
ikimono janai
Hey, I'm not alive!
mukuro hiyahiya sore demo suki desu
My heart's cold and slimy, but you know I still love you
watashi ga ichiban hoshii no wa naisho yo
What I want most is a total secret
sugata payapaya sore de wa ikimashou
I may not be the best, but let's get going anyway!
watashi ni ichiban niau kana fujouri
What suits me best is total absurdity
kagami ni wa
They won't show up
dan dan dare na no?
Who, Who, Who is that?
utsuranai
in any mirrors
dare nanda? yada yada
Who is it? Oh my
yokubou wa kotoba ni shinakucha
You have to say exactly what you want
uu!
hora
See?
nya!
kiechau deshou
They'll disappear like that
let's nya!
taiyou nanka mabushikutte
The stupid sun is way too bright!
yami no hou ga mugen desu
The darkness is way more free!
doki doki
Thump thump!
taiyou bakka mabushikute
The sun is so very bright!
yami no hou ga
The darkness is way more free!
su
te
ki
Nyaruko!
CAOS CAOS
I wanna CAOS
I wanna chaos
moe yo konton muteki desu
Burn! Anarchy always reigns supreme!
waku waku
So exciting!
CAOS CAOS
una sera CAOS
A night of total chaos!
moeru you na
Feelings that feel like burning!
ki
mo
chi
nyande?!
Why?
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
I don't want to live
like this anymore.
Why are you so down?
We have a bright
future ahead of us!
Boy, I will not forgive you for
confessing your feelings to Nyaruko.
Hey, you know I'm not
the one who confessed.
The one who confessed was
Nyaruko-chan in Mahiro-kun's body.
And if Mahiro-kun in Nyaruko-chan's
body said "sorry," then...
Huh? Wait, what?
This is getting complicated.
It's Isuka! I mean...
Kurei!
I am worn out to exhaustion.
Compiling exhaustion, even.
I am bayoe~n.
You're what?
Did the extremists get you?
I know how people who skip work
for a major RPG release feel.
What?
You might tell yourself that
the next save point is the last one,
but you'll just end up
grinding levels until sunrise.
Hey.
The Ruler of Super Time-Space
This is delicious!
I was so absorbed in the game I was playing that I forgot to eat or drink anything,
so it tastes especially good!
Anyway, what happened to the device to restore us to our original bodies?
It's still recharging.
It won't be fully
charged until tonight.
We have to stay this way
a while longer, then.
What kind of meat is this?
Which Mahiro-kun am
I supposed to love?
Meat! Delicious meat! More meat!
This is fantastic!
That depends on what
sort of role-play you like.
What a difficult question.
I'm not playing any dirty games.
With such an amazing
gastronomic culture,
it's a shame Earth's
going to be erased.
Hey,
what did you just say?
In the future that I'm from,
the Earth does not exist anymore.
The Space Confederation
determined that Earth
was a dangerous planet
and destroyed it.
What?!
Why would they do that to Earth?
Even in the Yith's massive database,
there's hardly any record of it.
But...
Now, now. As long as I'm around,
whether they drop a colony
or an asteroid on us,
I'll blast them away, so don't worry!
I'm nothing but worried.
We're going to Yoichi-san's house?
Yeah, it's rare for him
to miss a day like this,
so I thought I should
check up on him,
but if I go like this, it'll
be all kinds of complicated.
He was absent today, wasn't he?
Huh, ho, hum.
What are you saying?
I just thought the
extremists may have
exchanged their consciousness
with someone else.
For example, Yoichi-san.
No way a coincidence
like that would happen.
I know, right?
Of course.
When an unremarkable character
suddenly falls into the spotlight,
there must be
something going on.
Stop. I was worried about that,
but I didn't want to say anything.
Yoichi-san isn't home.
Why did you follow us?
Kuuko-san was telling me
about RPG strategies.
If you walk clockwise with
your left hand against the wall,
you will not fall into pit traps.
However, this only works in the
original version prior to the remake.
Now I can finally
reach the last boss!
Don't you have
anything else to do?
Huh? What's that?
My Yith locator is responding!
Yoichi!
He's running!
That's the extremist!
Important characters must
be picked up in the first part.
Let's chase after him!
Yoichi!
Stay back!
Don't you care what
happens to the boy's body?
My name is Isurugi.
I have come to this ancient
Earth as a soldier of the Yith!
Watch as our greatest
wish comes to fruition.
Behold.
This device will exchange the minds
of the Earthlings and the Yith!
With this, all of Earth's entertainment will forever belong to the Yith!
Creators who excite
video sharing sites,
popular artists within illustration
communities, all will be ours!
You can't be serious!
I'll never allow it!
Stop, that's my body!
Then, Mahiro-san, would you be willing
to stain your own fists with blood?
Hasuta, Kuuko, take care of him.
Got it, Mahiro-kun!
This is a good opportunity
to put Nyaruko in my debt.
Cthugha and Hastur.
Unfortunately for you, I have made my own preparations!
Space CQC jammer!
He jammed our Space CQC.
That's what a jammer does, duh.
Now I have nothing
to fear from you.
I thought this might happen.
That's why I prepared a
Space CQC jammer canceler!
They are back.
I've prepared something
for that as well!
Space CQC jammer
canceler breaker!
They disappeared again.
Bring it on!
Space CQC jammer
canceler breaker eraser!
There they are.
This isn't over yet!
Space CQC jammer canceler
breaker eraser confiner!
Space CQC jammer canceler breaker
eraser confiner obstructor!
eraser confiner obstructor buster!
Space CQC jammer canceler breaker
eraser confiner obstructor buster closer!
What is this, a kids' fight?
I'm out of cartridges!
It seems my Space CQC jammer
canceler et cetera has won.
The time has come.
This isn't good.
The Yith's destiny will
now become history!
The mind exchange is complete.
Now Earth's entertainment
belongs to the Yith.
Comrades!
Don'tcha 'ink it's a fine time to invade?
What do you think
you're talking about?
Our minds haven't
been transplanted.
Hey, wait! That's Yoichi's body!
But everything was going according to plan.
Isurugi, Isurugi!
That voice!
The chief... no, Mr. President!
President?
Who's that?
The founder and leader of the extremist organization.
I completed the mind exchange
device according to your orders,
but it doesn't seem
to have worked.
No, this is fine.
Everything is going
according to plan.
What?
According to plan...
you will all...
die!
Yoichi!
Mr. President?
You created an Earthling
annihilation device.
The president of the
extremists is only a guise...
My true identity is that of an agent of the Space Confederation organization
Space Child Guardian!
Space Child Guardian?
That's right. Foolish humans, quietly accept your deaths.
Why are you doing this to Earth?
We are destroying Earth because...
Because?
Because of space decency laws!
Space Decency Laws
Pardon?
We cannot turn a blind eye to Earth's
anime, manga, and other entertainment.
Elements hidden by light and fog
are visible in the special features,
and figures can be undressed
at their owner's discretion.
Hey...
According to space decency laws,
Earth's entertainment has been recognized as an agent promoting sex crimes throughout space.
The entire planet must be punished!
You can't just pass
judgment like that!
Child Guardian exists to
protect the future of children
and to ensure my retirement
into a high-profile position!
Looks like you've
revealed your true motive.
We have the law on our side!
Kuuko, Hasuta!
The Earth belongs to
Mahiro-kun and his friends!
I won't let you kill them!
My and Nyaruko's love nest is here.
Are you talking about my house?
Twinkle.
Isn't the Space CQC jammer still active?
Sometimes an alien must fight,
even when she knows she will lose.
Fools! You must really want to die!
How dare you deceive me!
You have fulfilled your purpose!
Now die already!
Yoichi!
This is Nyaruko's body, after all.
Even though it's me inside,
it still moves reasonably well.
Lawless scum!
Wait!
I'm not an Earthling!
Fool! This is what you deserve!
Hey...
Wake up, Nyaruko.
Why are you sleeping?
Your beloved Earth's
entertainment is in trouble.
You said you'd protect
my personal life, too.
Yet... you had to end up like this.
Standing in your shoes,
I finally understand.
Protecting someone
must have been difficult.
I'm sorry for being so mean to you.
Come on.
Wake up, Nyaruko!
Smooch yeah!
I did it! I tasted
every last bit of it!
It was...
Super soft!
Your tongue! You put your
tongue in, didn't you?!
Why are you alive, anyway?
Because of this.
A black crystal?
It's like a protective charm.
Don't just conveniently drag up
old foreshadowing devices like that!
If you were okay, why didn't
you wake up right away?
While listening to you
confess your feelings,
I started getting hot...
and I ended up giving
you a cruel angel's kiss.
That's the kind of bad influence
on minors I'm talking about!
Recharge complete!
Sorry it took so long!
Thanks for waiting!
I'm back in my body!
Nyaruko!
Yes!
I'm the chaos that always crawls up to you with a smile, Nyarlathotep!
You!
Transform.
Why? Your Space CQC
should be sealed!
All obstacles are meaningless
in the face of our love!
What do you think you're saying?
The truth is, even if
I can't use Space CQC,
I can still use my
Space CQC enhancer.
You're just pulling stuff
out of the air now...
Such convenient interpretations are the enemy of the system!
What did you say?
Impossible.
The Space Child Guardian
is protected by the law!
Laws are made to be broken!
Um, hello, Planetary
Defense Organization...
Now dance the Rondo
Towards Destruction!
That's one case completed!
It's over.
Your punchline was
terrible again, too.
So, what are you guys going to do?
I will take Isurugi
back to the future.
I will leave the rest
to the higher-ups.
We'll be good as long as we
get Yoichi and Kurei back.
Of course you will.
However, I will erase
Tamao-san's memory.
See you later.
Den-den-dendrobium bye-bye.
Are they gone?
They must be.
Now that the obstacles are gone...
we can pick up where we left off.
Owie-yith!
I should have saved.
There are monsters.
Isuka?
Oh, no! I am just a cute
little stuffed animal and...
Wait...
Why do you remember me, Tamao-san?
I thought I erased your memory.
But I remember you.
I'm so clumsy.
I thought you went home.
Well, I wanted to see what
happened next in the game.
I mean, I wanted to thank you.
Thank me?
Thank you for everything.
Thanks to you, I was
able to solve the case.
I don't remember much,
but you're welcome.
You're not mad I
borrowed your body?
Having an alien stay in your
body is a valuable experience.
Tamao-san, you're such a good person,
but I have to erase
all your memories.
I see. Even though
we became friends.
I learned much about you while
I was borrowing your body.
Your worries, and the person
you cannot admit that you love...
Stop!
You know all of that?
Yes. And I was with him
the whole time, so...
Don't tell anyone!
Understood!
I will carry your secret
with me into the future!
Tamao-san, I will be cheering for
you from the distant future.
It will be all right.
I'm sure something good
will happen to you soon.
Good morning, Yasaka-kun.
Morning, Yoichi.
Good,
my life is back to normal.
Hey, I thought she rejected him,
so why are they still
coming to school together?
It's not back to normal!
Yasaka Mahiro, could you
come to the faculty office
and explain to me what
happened yesterday?
If you just say you're under a lot
of stress, it won't be a big deal.
My quiet, ordinary life...
Where did it go?
shirokujichuu be with you
All day through, I want to be with you
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
watashi ga anata no mae
If I were to appear in front of you
arawareta nara "zutto" nan desu
Then it'll be "forever" that I'm with you
suki toka kirai da toka
"I love you" and "I hate you"
kanjou izen ni zettai desu
It's even more important than feelings like those
nijuuyo jikan ana ga aku hodo
nijuuyo
ana ga aku hodo
jikan
24 hours a day, so much I could burn a hole
anata dake wo mitsumetai
I want to watch only you all the time
uchuuteki kibo no love de I want you
uchuuteki kibo no love de I
want
you
With all my love, as vast as the universe, I want you
soba ni iru yo shirokujichuu
shirokujichuu
soba ni iru
yo
I'll be with you all day through
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
hora sunao ni natte love me do
I'll be honest with myself, so love me do
kono chikyuu de randebuu
We'll have on this planet a rendezvous
kibou datte anata to iu
My dreams will always be for you
tokimeki ni deaeta
I found my excitement in you
yakusoku da yo zutto be with you
So I'll promise I'll always be with you
Kurei Tamao here!
I'm Yoichi Takehiko!
It seems three cute little sisters
are going to come rolling in.
Oh? Why do I get the feeling that I'm going to be the star?
No, it's just your imagination.
Besides, nothing's coming our way.
You're right.
The next episode is
"Lost Girl From The Stars."
I wish you would listen to Yasaka-kun.