What is that?
What is that thing?
Damn it! Why? Why me?
Why is this happening to me?
Someone...
Someone help!
Okay!
I'm the chaos that always crawls up to you with a smile,
Nyarlathotep!
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
uu!
nya!
let's nya!
kokoro nurunuru igyou no kamigami
Strange-looking gods with hearts that go wiggle wiggle
watashi mo anata mo kowagari no monozuki
You and I both love those kinds of scary stories
katachi murumuru ikyouto nigereba
Once the pagans have been scared away
watashi to anata wa entenka de odeeto
We'll go on a date under the blazing sun
tanoshii ne yakeru zo tokeru zo
Isn't this fun? I'll burn! I'll melt!
ikimono janai
Hey, I'm not alive!
mukuro hiyahiya sore demo suki desu
My heart's cold and slimy, but you know I still love you
watashi ga ichiban hoshii no wa naisho yo
What I want most is a total secret
sugata payapaya sore de wa ikimashou
I may not be the best, but let's get going anyway!
watashi ni ichiban niau kana fujouri
What suits me best is total absurdity
kagami ni wa
They won't show up
dan dan dare na no?
Who, Who, Who is that?
utsuranai
in any mirrors
dare nanda? yada yada
Who is it? Oh my
yokubou wa kotoba ni shinakucha
You have to say exactly what you want
uu!
hora
See?
nya!
kiechau deshou
They'll disappear like that
let's nya!
taiyou nanka mabushikutte
The stupid sun is way too bright!
yami no hou ga mugen desu
The darkness is way more free!
doki doki
Thump thump!
taiyou bakka mabushikute
The sun is so very bright!
yami no hou ga
The darkness is way more free!
su
te
ki
Nyaruko!
CAOS CAOS
I wanna CAOS
I wanna chaos
moe yo konton muteki desu
Burn! Anarchy always reigns supreme!
waku waku
So exciting!
CAOS CAOS
una sera CAOS
A night of total chaos!
moeru you na
Feelings that feel like burning!
ki
mo
chi
nyande?!
Why?
wareware
We're
uu!
yoreyore
worn out
nya!
sekai wa dark
The world is dark!
cosmic!
That was a close one
last night, wasn't it?
If not for me, you'd be in big trouble
right about now.
No need to thank me, though.
You've gotta have white rice with a Japanese breakfast.
Could you explain what
actually happened last night?
Having potato chips first thing in the morning isn't too bad either.
Would you stop yapping
and listen to me?
Oh, look at the time!
Superhero Showtime is starting!
A-Are you saying that you've
returned from Hell alive?
The Iron Striver,
Star Vampire Crusaders!
Ia!
This is why I love Earth!
The morning isn't even over yet,
and my day's already been made!
Ia!
Long live Sunday!
Anyway, why was
that thing chasing me?
Ia!
Miso soup is great,
but seaweed and potatoes go great together, too.
Do you think I could get some more?
Thanks a bunch!
Oh, and pack as much
in there as you can.
Whoa! Is he gonna reveal his new move?
Like a Close Encounter of the Third Kind
Gaplant!
Wh-What do you
think you're doing?
One wrong move and we'd
have been taken off the air!
Wanna go best two out of three?
No, thank you.
So?
"So"?
What was that
monster from last night?
Why was it chasing me?
Also, who are you?
Oh, of course.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Nyarlathotep.
I'm the Crawling Chaos.
Nyarlat—From Cthulhu Mythos?
You're familiar with it?
A little.
I've read Lovecraft's books before,
but I've always thought of
you as more of a monster.
Like with writhing tentacles,
surrounded by a nauseating mist.
If you'd like, I could take that form,
Sanity Points
but you'd lose your sanity.
All right, I'd rather keep it.
If you already know the gist of it,
then this should be easy to explain.
I, Nyarlathotep—
By the way, they call me Nyarlathotep, but I have my own name too.
I came to Earth because
I have work to do.
In other words, you're an alien
who's an employee of the
Planetary Defense Organization,
and you've come here
to defend Earth.
You make it sound so simple.
Who knew the gods of the
Cthulhu Mythos were actually aliens?
By the way, that makes
me a Nyarlathotepian.
I'm not sure I believe all this.
You have to believe me!
Take me to your leader.
We received information that a criminal
organization we've been pursuing for some time
will be conducting a
major transaction on Earth.
They're involved with
space drugs, galactic contraband,
and the slave trade.
Slave trade?
Do you understand now?
Is that why that thing was after me?
Correct. They traffic human slaves.
Don't worry.
I'm here to protect you,
Yasaka Mahiro-san.
How do you know my name?
I've researched everything
there is to know about you.
For instance, I know that
your parents are on their
Age 17 Libra    Blood Type O
Boryo Municipal High School
Year 2 Class 4 Number 22
Grades: Slightly above average
Lifestyle: Extremely normal
School Club: Going Home Club
No Girlfriend or Boyfriend
Family: Father, Mother, no Siblings
Parents currently absent on their 17th
honeymoon in honor of their 17th anniversary
Yasaka Mahiro
seventeenth honeymoon.
Doesn't space have privacy laws?
In any case, I will stay by your side around the clock and protect you!
By my side... around the clock?
From the moment we say "good morning" till bedtime.
We'll be together...
...the whole time!
Together... the whole time.
You're bright red!
You're so cute, Mahiro-san!
Shut up!
No no no!
Don't worry!
I'll keep official and
personal matters separate!
I'll respect your privacy!
O-Okay.
With that said, it's time
to get out of here!
Huh?
This place is dangerous!
We must evacuate!
Don't worry! Leave everything to me!
Hey, hold on!
Hey! Wait!
Marvelous!
Hey.
An Iron Striver Blu-ray box set!
A figurine comes with
the limited edition too?
Hey, Nyarlathotepian.
What on Earth are these
adult-only doujinshi?
They're so indecent!
I must have them.
Hey, alien.
Isn't this a recalled
first-edition erotic game?
Earth, you terrify me.
I will treasure these
as part of my collection.
Braw Bro!
So have you calmed down yet?
Yes.
I thought you came
here to protect me.
I did!
I am here for that,
but I have other duties too!
Protecting you comes first,
but bringing down
the criminal organization,
and shopping are also important.
That last one's obviously personal.
Listen.
Like I've told you,
Earth has been designated
as one of the Planetary Defense Organization's top priorities.
No, you haven't.
This is precisely why!
Anime, manga, and games?
Widely known as pastimes and described by the English language as "entertainment"!
Earth's entertainment is
the best in the universe!
Hey.
That's why the gods of the
Cthulhu Mythos all want to come here.
We'd sprout tentacles from
our throats to get this stuff.
I wish you wouldn't.
The criminal organization we're after is
actually guilty of smuggling works such as these.
There are limits on how many can be
legally imported, so they're hard to come by.
Is something wrong?
So...
Can you take back
anything you bought?
You...
Mahiro-san.
Yes?
It's not a crime if
you don't get caught.
I recorded what you just said.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
If you don't want your bosses to find out about this, then do your job properly.
Okay.
You're still going to buy them?
I'd like to use the loyalty
points I have saved up.
You have a loyalty card?
What a great haul.
She seems happy.
Getting these made begging for this assignment worth it.
What?
I had to bargain with
my boss to get the job.
I guess I don't need to ask why.
The entire universe loves
Earth's entertainment,
but there's another reason.
Another reason?
Yes.
Like what?
When I saw the data on
the person I'd be protecting,
a sound effect, almost like an "Enemy sighted!" alert, went off inside my head.
In other words, he was just my type.
The person you'd be protecting?
Do you get it now?
To be perfectly honest,
it was love at first sight.
Y-You shouldn't mix
business with love!
I thought you said you'd keep
official and personal matters separate!
Don't worry. I'll earn my keep.
How can you say that
after your shopping spree?
Right. Let's get to work, shall we?
There you are.
I knew using Mahiro-san as bait would work.
What? I thought we left the
house because it was dangerous!
Don't worry. I've set up
a convenient barrier
which will allow me to fight without drawing attention.
I've set up a barrier.
That was important,
so I said it twice!
I didn't ask about that!
You're really going
to protect me, right?
Of course I am.
Now, let me show you
the power of Space CQC!
Space CQC?
Close-quarters combat.
Basically, it's hand-to-hand combat.
Actually, it's the "space"
part I don't understand.
Let's start with the climax.
Come on!
Don't think you're
getting away with just that!
I hope you're prepared!
You won't be able to
beat me with that attitude!
Crawling
Chaos!
I can't hear anything. I can't hear anything.
I can't hear anything!
Come on!
...and that's Space CQC!
From where I'm standing,
you look like the criminal.
Still...
You did save me.
Thanks, I guess.
Oh, please!
I'm just doing my job!
If you really want to
thank me, though...
I know!
I love you!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Gao!
Nyarlathotep.
Good morning!
Hey, Nyarlathotepian.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Boryo Municipal High School
Yes? What is it?
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Boryo Municipal High School
Are you sure it's safe for me
to go to school by myself?
Of course.
I may not be with
you the whole time,
but I'll rush to your side at the first sign of danger.
That's a promise!
Good morning, Yasaka-kun.
Morning, Yoichi.
What's wrong? You seem tired.
Yeah, well...
I don't know how to explain it.
Having a tough time
without your parents?
If there's anything I can do,
I'd be happy to help.
Just let me know.
Sure.
Year
Class
I'd like to introduce
our new transfer student.
Come in.
Traveling between the stars
eliminating malign deities with the tears of many on my back...
I am the chaos that always crawls up
to Mahiro-san with a smile, Nyarlathotep!
Call my name, and I will be there!
No one called you!
Gaza-C!
Feel free to
call me "Nyaruko"
Yasaka
Nyarlathotep
I didn't know you had
relatives overseas, Yasaka-kun.
Yeah. I didn't find out
until today, either.
Never mind.
Still, she's quite the character.
She's the center of attention in class,
fluent in Japanese,
and really athletic to top it off.
I know she's supposed to protect me,
but why'd she have to enroll here?
What's this?
Is something bothering you?
What do you want,
Walking Speaker?
I wanted to get an
interview with you.
An interview?
How do you feel about Nyaruko-chan?
Wh-What do you mean?
You're teenagers of the opposite sex living under the same roof.
I bet she's feeling homesick too.
By the way, when I asked Nyaruko-chan...
I could see that romance working out,
but I can't tell how he feels...
...is what she said!
That idiot.
Well? Spill the beans, Yasaka-kun.
Well...
Oh, I see.
You think it's a possibility too.
I didn't say that!
Thanks, Yasaka-kun.
Tell me all about it later!
Hey, Kurei!
Don't worry about it.
Here you go, Mahiro-san.
What's this?
I made you this lunch with all
the love a loving wife could muster!
You didn't have to.
I'll just buy some bread.
I just wanted to move my desk next to yours and each lunch together!
Yasaka-kun.
You think bread is better
than the lunch I made for you.
I didn't say that!
Sob, sob...
Why don't you just eat it?
She put all that effort
into making it for you.
I feel bad for her!
Fine.
Thank you, Mahiro-san!
Go right ahead! Help yourself!
It actually looks pretty normal.
I'm surprised you
had time to make this.
A clocked-up Nyarlathotepian can move at speeds that defy all logic.
You just made that up, didn't you?
Don't worry about that. Just eat.
Fine.
It's delicious.
Isn't it?
It's all because of my love for you!
By the way, I've never had fried meat that tasted like this before.
What sort of meat did you use?
Hey.
I'm going to go throw it up.
Don't worry!
It's not anything dangerous!
I can guarantee that much!
Is that all you can guarantee?
Why don't we have bread tomorrow?
I'll make you a BLT sandwich.
B, L, T!
Could you tell me what
BLT stands for first?
Byakhee, Lloigor and Tsathoggua.
If you put those in a sandwich,
I'll kick the crap out of you!
Dijeh!
Now let's go over mitosis as
described between pages 30 to 32...
Hey, Nyarlathotep...
Mahiro-san, I'm so embarrassed I could get pregnant.
Gyan!
Is something wrong,
Yasaka Nyarlathotep-san?
T-Teacher...
I'm suffering from abnormal and blasphemous
amounts of ominously chaotic pain.
May I go to the nurse's office?
I'll have Mahiro-san take me there.
What?
No one else can
see that monster?
Because I've got
my convenient barrier.
Now to go smite that beast!
Another Nightgaunt?
I'm getting tired of fighting
the same enemy all the time.
What?
Perhaps I'll let the capsule
monster handle this one.
What are you talking abo—
Now where did I put it?
Here it is.
What are you doing?
I could ask you the same thing!
Shantak-kun!
I choose you!
What is that?
One of my many pets,
Shantak-kun the Shantak-bird.
Go get him Shantak-kun! Kill him good!
Do it as brutally as possible.
Are you sure you work for
a public safety organization?
I knew it.
Shantak-kun's at 99 losses and
one draw versus Nightgaunts.
Why'd you use him, then?
They say the worse they are,
the cuter they are.
You know...
Hey, do something.
I have no choice.
It's time for my deadly
Space CQC: Part 2!
Dash!
Sanity Points
That was great.
That was just ink... That was just ink...
What are you doing?
Hey, what is that
thing you're holding?
This?
It's some kind of
unspeakable Bar thing.
Stop trying to mix Cthulhu
references into everything.
I'm exhausted.
Why is this happening to me?
I haven't had a chance to
rest since she showed up.
Mahiro-san!
I am the chaos that always
crawls up to you with a smile.
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
Young
confusion
Lady
chaos
What's wrong with you?
Get out of here!
No, thank you.
I thought we could
consummate our love
before your parents
return from their trip.
Don't worry.
It won't hurt.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Now let's become the Adam
and Eve of a new generation.
Get out!
Zakrello!
shirokujichuu be with you
All day through, I want to be with you
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
watashi ga anata no mae
If I were to appear in front of you
arawareta nara "zutto" nan desu
Then it'll be "forever" that I'm with you
suki toka kirai da toka
"I love you" and "I hate you"
kanjou izen ni zettai desu
It's even more important than feelings like those
nijuuyo jikan ana ga aku hodo
nijuuyo
ana ga aku hodo
jikan
24 hours a day, so much I could burn a hole
anata dake wo mitsumetai
I want to watch only you all the time
uchuuteki kibo no love de I want you
uchuuteki kibo no love de I
want
you
With all my love, as vast as the universe, I want you
soba ni iru yo shirokujichuu
shirokujichuu
soba ni iru
yo
I'll be with you all day through
yoku dekitara give me chu
If I do well, will you give me a kiss?
hora sunao ni natte love me do
I'll be honest with myself, so love me do
kono chikyuu de randebuu
We'll have on this planet a rendezvous
kibou datte anata to iu
My dreams will always be for you
tokimeki ni deaeta
I found my excitement in you
yakusoku da yo zutto be with you
So I'll promise I'll always be with you
Haiyore! Nyaruko-san
has finally begun!
What did you think of our
lovey-dovey life together?
There's nothing
lovey-dovey about it.
It'll get even more
lovey-dovey next time.
No, it won't!
It is Lovecraft, though!
Not funny.
The next episode is
"Goodbye! Nyaruko-san!"
Wait, what?!
We sure got to the
last episode quick.