Till now, during this whole day, I’ve had the wrong idea.
Then again, what's the difference between a world where left and right is reversed, and one that's been flipped around?
Part of me still thinks they're the same.
Regarding the scenery, that might very well be the case, but not with people's personalities.
Hanekawa Tsubasa's example would no doubt be the simplest to understand.
The oddity in question, which appeared during golden week ー
While it was a traditional apparition called the meddlecat, it was still also Hanekawa Tsubasa herself.
The side of herself she suppressed, who took all the hurt.
Hanekawa Tsubasa’s other side.
If we accept the view that people are flipped, we can apply that to others as well.
Tiny Karen was a novel sight, a true innovation.
While to me, it was as shocking as discovering the New World,
Just like Kuchinawa-san said, Karen was conscious of her height,
And a gap between her physical and mental growth no doubt existed within her.
It was always real.
If that hidden side of her were given form, it could very well manifest in such manner.
That form was in no way new.
Just the embodiment of her inner unbalance.
Ononoki-chan’s case is something she told me once.
They simply don’t appear on the surface; she simply cannot express them.
But she’s definitely not emotionless or expressionless.
Koyomi’s ice cream
– do not eat
In fact, my impression of her wasn’t that her personality had changed,
but that the awfulness of her personality had come to light.
In Hachikuji Mayoi’s case, it’s even simpler to put two and two together.
Back then, Hachikuji appeared in front of me as a 10-year-old-girl.
However, even then she was a ghost who’d lost her life 10-odd years before.
If you added everything together, she would be about 21 years old now.
Behind the surface of a 10-year-old girl, were the qualities of an adult woman.
Ghosts don’t age.
The passage of time doesn’t apply to oddities.
While we can’t simply calculate her mental age, her history of having wandered around for 11 years,
Whether she falls to hell or becomes a god, would not disappear.
Although I don’t completely understand it,
While the likes of Kanbaru who’d fawn over her shouting “little girl, little girl, so cute, co cute” wouldn’t see it,
Hachikuji did have such a hidden side.
Kitashirahebi
Shrine
If that side of her would be put in front, it might just take that kind of shape.
Speaking of Kanbaru.
Her left hand, the monkey’s paw was an artifact that would see the hidden intent behind its owners wish, and grant it accordingly.
It in itself was an oddity that would turn things inside out.
What I saw as the Rainy Devil in a raincoat and boots, was the hidden side of Kanbaru.
The affection she feels towards me as her senpai is not a lie, but on the other hand
Completely getting rid of the Araragi-hatred deep in her is likely impossible.
It’s not that it had reappeared.
It had always been there, and still is.
Not a transformation, just a reflection.
It almost sounds like I’m talking mathematics here.
But to put in in simpler terms, the Rainy Devil was Kanbaru Suruga herself.
Speaking of mathematics, let’s talk about poor Oikura Sodachi, who I could barely look at.
With her unburdened personality I haven’t been shown even a glance of before,
And the way she was fitting in at the Araragi household were, more than I could imagine,
A perfect situation she would’ve only dreamed of.
At least, I’d like to think so.
I want to believe that deep down, Oikura Sodachi wished for such a fictitious happiness.
Being able to think that behind her rough attitude and aggressive demeanor
There was such a hidden side would bring me some sort of relief.
While this reading of Oikura Sodachi sounds awfully convenient to me,
I find it impossible to discuss this childhood friend based only on logic.
Compared to that, explaining Sengoku Nadeko’s case is simpler and more convincing.
Kuchinawa-san was created by her,
As a god native to this land, enshrined at Kitashirahebi shrine.
While not exactly a split personality, Shinobu and I have seen her talking to Kuchinawa-san once.
Shinobu and I could not see this god.
It was a snake, nestling in her hidden side.
That rough way of speaking, slovenly attitude.
That was also Sengoku Nadeko.
The very same person, as she put it.
There’s no Sengoku Nadeko who’s only docile, quiet, and cute.
Behind the maturity, childishness. Quiet on surface, outspoken inside. Cheekiness behind the cuteness.
Onigiri-man
There was always such a Sengoku Nadeko deep down, ready to explode and burst out.
That’s how it is.
I thought this world was strange, but upon rereading my adventures so far…
Turns out it isn’t that complicated.
I was simply seeing their other sides.
In this world, inconsistencies and paradoxes are allowed.
But not because it was a mirror world.
It’s because these girls were actors originating from the soul.
Given freedom of thought.
Thinking about it that way, it’s as if I managed to find a rule grounding this unstable, uncertain world.
Allowing me to see the scenery where left and right are reversed through a different lens.
Now, listen to this.
Clean     Spirit
When she said that she’d reveal her opinion last, she wasn’t bluffing.
She had doubts about something.
Still. Let’s put aside whether we’re inside the mirror, in a mirror world, a parallel world or another dimension.
It’s filled with people you know, right?
Your family, friends, kouhai, childhood friend.
Yes, that’s true.
Then where are you, Araragi-kun?
Me?
You haven’t met yourself. Isn’t that strange?
Everyone, including myself and Kuchinawa-san, knows you.
We each have some sort of connection to you.
Another Araragi-kun… Your other side… wouldn’t he have to exist here?
Clean     Spirit
Since they all know me, it’d be strange if a me didn’t exist here.
Even if he’s not here now, he had to exist.
My reflection from this morning, who didn’t follow my movements, staring at me with his eyes.
Maybe you switched places, and he’s in your world right now.
Then he’d be in the same shoes, lost in a world full of inconsistencies he can’t make heads or tails of.
If that’s the case, he might be more troubled than you.
If I think this through, based on the examples of Black Hanekawa and Rainy Devil,
My other self that should’ve been in this world…
Araragi Koyomi… Araragi Koyomi’s other side…
Would be my nemesis.
It can only be Oshino Ougi.
Why don’t you call it a day and rest?
Kuchinawa-san and I will try to keep looking around, so come back around tomorrow evening.
Of course, if you find a chance to return home before that, don’t let it slip away!
If that happens, just leave behind a letter.
Alright. I’m sorry for all this trouble.
Oh, it’s no trouble at all!
Keeping peace in this town is my job right now, after all!
I am troubled though. Being dragged out of retirement like this…
But I suppose I am curious about that cat, so…
Even if we prepare for the long haul, I can’t afford to stay long.
Like I said before, if I get into university, I’ll have to go and deal with the paperwork.
After bath, nothing special happened with the mirror. Having confirmed that, I felt dejected.
I’ll just go to sleep…
Perhaps everything will be solved when I wake up.
Hey, Koyomi! Dry your hair properly or you’ll catch a cold!
Your shining charms alone won’t do it!
Huh? What? What is it? Did I say something bad?
Koyomi, are you angry? Please, don’t act so cold!
Did you get turned on, or what?
Hey, Oik-…
Sodachi.
Is there something special you know about mirrors?
There was something about how mirrors can’t perfectly reflect images…
Mirrors work by reflecting light, but they can’t completely reflect all of it.
I think a normal mirror reflects about 80%.
The mirror’s surface will always be somewhat foggy.
So the reflection seems dimmer than reality.
While we recognize ourselves in the mirror, we only see ourselves vaguely.
We can only have a vague understanding.
The details become blurry, inaccurate…
My sleep was disturbed.
Sssh. Devilish Onii-chan, get up without making a sound so you don’t wake Sodachi-oneechan up.
Change your clothes and get ready to go out.
Where did Ononoki-chan’s emotion-filled, expressive way of talking go?
Stay quiet and follow me, Onii-chan. If you do that, I can help you meet Shinobu.
That is, this world’s Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade.
Let me be straight. Don’t expect too much.
I’m also very far from understanding everything.
Ononoki-chan.
What is it, Onii-chan?
Err, well…
Oh, you’d like an explanation.
Of course, of course.
I know what thoughts make you tick. From little girls, to petite girls.
Don’t put me on such a narrow spectrum.
And those are not thoughts, but tastes!
Thoughts
Tastes
Not my tastes though!
I’m still a pro, you see.
This morning when you saw me, talked to me, you definitely felt something was amiss with this world.
At the same time, I thought there was something amiss with you.
When you stare into the abyss, the abyss stares back.
What’s this? How come Onii-chan left without stripping my panties? Impossible!
Those thoughts served as my starting point.
Couldn’t you have found a better place to start?
Did you say panties? Underwear? Did you mean to say pants, as in trousers? Which one?
Who knows. Put your hand on your heart, and ask yourself.
Speaking of which, you didn’t do the usual thing with my chest either. That also tipped me off.
The usual thing with your chest? What’s that?
What is the thing I usually do with your chest?
I’m unable to ignore uncertain elements, you see.
After you left, I performed a self-check.
I started thinking, why did my behavior surprise you? Why did you force me down?
Force you down? I’m sure I didn’t do that.
I meant “why were you freaking out?”. My mistake.
That’s completely different!
Mistake, my foot.
As a result of my maintenance, while I didn’t find out what freaked you out, at the very least
I realized that the way I was, I couldn’t perform at full capacity.
That as a being in service of Onee-chan, as her shikigami, I was imperfect.
So, I reconstructed my personality.
I shook it up. Brushed it up.
Although I couldn’t tell how it turned out, judging by your response, it seems to have mostly gone well.
Oh, it’s nothing worth great praise. It was only possible with your help.
Onii-chan…
Thank you for not stripping my panties back then.
Please. I simply didn’t do the obvious thing to do.
Like I already told you, I don’t fully understand everything either.
Actually, I’m forcing myself a lot.
Changing my character this much is already pushing the boundaries of what an oddity is allowed to do.
It wouldn’t be strange for the darkness to appear.
Because of that, there’s a limit to how much I can do.
If I get too zealous, I might risk destruction.
And I can’t disappear before we fulfill our promise to see the ocean together.
Did I make such a cool promise?
While stripping her panties every morning?
So, what happened after that?
Just like how I went to the Kitashirahebi shrine to ask for advice, did you also start your investigation?
So you went to the Kitashirahebi shrine. Hmm. Tell me more about that later.
Oh, so you weren’t following what I’ve been doing?
Like I said, don’t expect so much from me.
Forming a new personality was a considerable strain, so my thoughts are all jumbled up.
Of course, I did realize that you were up to something.
But I thought the possibility that you went out to buy a present for Sodachi-oneechan was just as high.
Exit
Where did that possibility come from?
She was pestering you a lot about it, after all.
Talk to her, despite everything
“Koyomi, buy it, please! Pretty please! I won’t let go until you say yes!”
Praise her
Body Touch
Kiss
Change area
Invite to a hotel
Run
She really makes me spoil her, it seems.
What did she even ask for?
And while I’d always try stripping your panties, I’d also fulfill a request like that from Oikura?
Just what kind of person am I in this world?
Aah, I bet Sodachi-oneechan will be disappointed.
Stop that. Don’t put pressure on me.
Disappointing her is a cruel experience for me. Stop adding to my list of tasks.
So, after your investigation, you decided to help me and Shinobu meet, right?
Exactly. I won’t go into details, because I’m excited to see what kind of face you’ll make,
But as you’d expect, that former Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade is not the one you know.
Just be ready for that.
Sure, got it.
Did you say you’re excited to say what face I’ll make?
I did. So what?
That line doesn’t give you a ticket to act cheeky.
I don’t know what exactly goes on in your world, so…
Am I getting along with Onee-chan over there?
Huh? Err, well…
Hmm. Well, that’s about what I expected.
So, whose panties did you strip today, and where?
If you want to know what I did today, you could ask normally.
If I recall, you went to Kitashirahebi shrine first, to strip Mayoi-san’s panties.
That’s blasphemy!
I’d be struck right then and there!
After that exchange, I explained the gist of what happened today.
Uhum. So today,
You stripped the panties of Mayoi-san, monkey Onee-chan, cat Onee-chan, snake Onee-chan, and finally Sodachi-oneechan, is that right?
You’re completely talking in panties now, aren’t you?
Oops. I forgot to include the fire sister.
You don’t need to.
So amazing, devilish Onii-chan. Your sisters’ panties aren’t even worth mentioning.
Could you be amazed by me in a different way?
If that’s the most amazing thing you took away from my story, I’ll be amazingly sad.
Well, how you described everyone is how I always knew them to be.
But there is one point where we are of the same opinion.
Oh, what’s that?
It’s the first time we’re in agreement, isn’t it?
Don’t talk like we’re in some buddy cop skit. I’m sure we agreed on things countless times before.
So, what is it?
The fact that Black Hanekawa saved you.
According to what I know about her, that’s completely impossible.
Still, I can’t think of anyone who would ask Black Hanekawa to help me.
That’s true. I don’t know anyone who would ever help you.
I wouldn’t either, for one.
That’s not what I meant. I’m talking about who could make that request of her.
And what do you mean that you wouldn’t? Don’t just casually hurt my feelings!
Aren’t you helping me right now?
I’m just making you think so, biding my time to see what face you’ll make when it all comes crumbling down.
I can’t believe what an awful personality you have.
Rainy Devil attacks!
Go back and rebuild it from scratch!
Koyomin took 291 points
of damage!
Koyomin died!
Does Shinobu know that I’m coming? I won’t pry much if you tell me not to.
But basically, do we have an appointment?
We do. No need to worry.
I’m not sure what it’s like in your world, but here, that vixen and I are best of friends.
It sure doesn’t sound like it. When you call her a vixen, it just oozes malice.
Whoa. Now that we’ve come this far, I understood where Ononoki-chan was taking me.
NO ENTRY
The derelict building used by the wandering specialist, Oshino meme.
Past here are the remains of the former cram school.
In the world I know, a fire occurred here last summer. It completely burned down, and nothing was left.
But if she’s taking me there, that derelict building might still be intact.
Then in this world, instead of living in my shadow, she might have continued living in that classroom together with Oshino.
In that case, I would expect that she’s not too fond of me – of Araragi Koyomi.
With Ononoki-chan around, I suppose my life isn’t in danger, but it might not hurt to be a little more cautious.
We arrived at our destination.
Is Shinobu… in here? Does she live in this castle, Ononki-chan?
That’s right, devilish Onii-chan. She is right here. She lives here.
Let’s get inside.
Inside? Uh, can we just enter like that?
Do you think a castle like this would have an intercom?
By the way, Ononoki-chan.
What is it, devilish Onii-chan?
I believed that Shinobu didn’t even exist in this world.
That she couldn’t be inside the mirror, since vampires don’t have reflections.
That’s one of the inconsistencies of this world.
I also call you devilish Onii-chan, right?
Yeah, at one point, you stuck with using that name.
Do you know why I call you that?
Why, well… sure, I understand why.
I see. Well, I don’t.
What do you mean…?
We’re here. The former Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade is waiting for you in this bedroom.
Although calling her that, or Oshino Shinobu might not be right.
Does that mean that she’s not “former” here?
Good intuition. There goes one thing to look forward for.
Stop enjoying yourself! Don’t look forward to anything!
Hold up, does that mean that her current self, her self in this world hasn’t lost her powers as a vampire?
That she’s right in her prime?
She’s not the former Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade, not Oshino Shinbou…
But the real Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade?
Just by glancing at that silhouette, I understood.
I understood everything.
Welcome to my humble dwelling, Araragi-sama. This would be our first time meeting, correct?
My name is Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade.
There she was, giving me a peculiar greeting. As beautiful as ever.
But this time, not as a vampire.
She was a human.