Oriana Thomson continues the fight in Academy City amidst the Daihaseisai.
She managed to shake me and Stiyl off and shoot down Tsuchimikado as she escaped.
As if that weren't enough, she attacked Himegami, who just happened by.
Damn it!
I'll never forgive her!
Toaru Majutsu no Index
yubi de hajiku koin mitsumeta
指で弾くコイン見つめた
I watched the coin as I flicked it
omote nara go ura wa stay mazu kotae o kikasete
表ならGO、裏はSTAY。まず答えを聞かせて
Heads is GO, Tails is STAY. But first, let me hear your answer
douka oshiete kuremasen ka
「どうか教えてくれませんか？」
Would you please tell me?
tenshi wa misadameru egao no mama
天使は見定める　笑顔のまま
The angels judges me as they smile
mayoe sono te o hiku mono nado inai
迷え！その手を引く者などいない
Get lost! No one's going to hold your hand!
kami ga kudasu sono kotae wa fukou datta
神が下す　その答えは不幸だった
The answer from God was misfortune
sou sore koso kami kara no okurimono
そう　それこそ神からの贈り物
Yes, but it was still a gift from God!
norikoetara miete kuru sa dakara ima sugu
乗り越えたら見えてくるさ　だから今すぐ
If you get over it, you'll be able to see. But for now...
No buts!
Belvedere
Observatory
Damn it!
Tsuchimikado. I lost Oriana.
Can you tell where she's headed?
It looks like that route makes a large circle around the Seventh District,
but we have no way of knowing where she'll get off.
Wait a minute.
What is it, Kami-yan?
What's Oriana doing moving around the city like this?
Well, we're chasing—
No, before that.
There was no Croce di Pietro deal in the first place, so she shouldn't be meeting anyone.
It's dangerous for her to just wander around the city.
She must have her own reason for acting alone.
What reason could she have?
I don't know.
It may be that she's searching for some place which fits the conditions for using the Croce di Pietro.
Conditions? Do you need to do something special to use it?
You should ask Stiyl about that.
That's right, he forwarded me a text from Orsola.
I'll send it to you now.
I read it, Kami-yan.
This looks like a record concerning a cleaning of the Croce di Pietro's storage place.
And? What did it say?
I seems they went to great lengths to ensure that the Croce di Pietro didn't come into contact with any light sources.
Light sources?
They must have been taking precautions to keep it from activating.
Maybe it activates upon contact with sunlight.
If that were the case, then she would have done that already.
Besides, this record mentions something about the importance of completing the cleaning before the sun goes down.
Time isn't a factor then...
Right.
It seems they ran into some trouble with the workers, though.
One of them was attempting to divine the stars.
The stars?
If the cleaning was so strictly carried out during the day, it must be something that's only present at night.
So, starlight?
That's true. By integrating star positions into a magic circle, one can increase its power tremendously.
If the Croce di Pietro is some sort of antenna that's meant to pick up starlight,
I would guess that Oriana is searching for the best place to set it up.
But Peter died on June 29th.
On top of that, Japan has a completely different set of latitudes and longitudes compared to the Vatican.
Unless she's found some way around those issues, the constellation theory is bust.
Not that we have the time to think about such things any longer.
Let's make a move.
If we assume that she plans to use the constellations, our time limit is still...
Sunset.
So what should I do?
Touma.
What are you doing here?
I-Index?
Looks like Kanzaki Kaori didn't come here after all.
Lidvia.
I know what you want to say.
That girl you laid your hands on was just a commoner.
Her name is Himegami Aisa.
Though she has a remarkable ability, she's not a magician in particular.
That Celtic cross is present purely to seal her powers, and has no offensive ability in itself.
That's terrible...
It is quite terrible.
This is the second time that we've harmed a commoner without any connection to our mission.
They are sinners who are lost, mistaken, and require our salvation and protection.
We can't afford to make any more mistakes.
For her sake as well, we must use the Croce di Pietro and take control of Academy City.
We'll really succeed at this, right?
In taking Academy City, everybody's problems will be fixed, right?
Touma, why aren't you with the rest of the class?
You haven't participated in any afternoon competitions. Why?
I was helping out the Administration Committee.
That's odd, I thought I sent everyone a text about it.
A text?
Maybe I was outside the service area. The signal might not have reached a tower...
Anyway, Index, go ahead and tell everyone that.
Hey, Touma, they said that group gymnastics is next.
You're coming, right?
I'll be there as soon as I can. I need to finish helping out first.
I'll definitely go. Can you wait for me, Index?
Yep!
Sorry, Kami-yan.
Let's get this over with.
But with this many people...
"Wait up!" says MISAKA as MISAKA gives chase.
"Come on, MISAKA was just looking for gifts," says MISAKA as MISAKA mounts an argument.
Misaka?
Hello? Is that you, Stiyl?
I've finished treating the girl.
How is she?
I hope I never have to use that spell again.
In any case, it looks like she's gotten over the shock.
The rest is up to the doctors.
You—
What's with that slacked voice? I'm not here to chit-chat with you—
I haven't had a chance to thank you yet.
If you hadn't been here, Himegami-chan would've...
Himegami-chan would've...
Stop it. We don't know whether she's going to be okay or not yet.
But I... I...
You guys seem busy, so I'll call again later.
Call Tsuchimikado!
Apparently he figured out something.
I'll catch up with you after I get rid of this.
Looks like I was right.
But how do we explain this hole in our theory?
Fukiyose-chan! How are you doing?
I'm fine. Is the Daihaseisai proceeding as planned?
Actually, Himegami-chan ran into a bit of trouble.
Did those idiots do something again?
She was assaulted by someone and taken to the hospital.
Assaulted?!
If Kamijou-chan and his friends hadn't been there, things would have been really bad.
Oh, that's the priest.
Mr. Priest!
Mr. Priest?
What on Earth is happening in this city?
I see...
So the key to activating it is in the constellations.
However, as far as we know, it was last activated during the summer.
I don't think the autumn constellations will work quite so well.
We're still missing something.
A gimmick that we haven't thought of.
But we don't have time to sit around and ponder it.
The Church of England?
Is this Stiyl Magnus-san?
You've got the wrong number!
I'm very sorry!
Wait, that voice...
Is that you, Orsola?
Oh my, thank you for your help last time.
Thanks to you, I've become very well-acquainted with—
Do you have any information to give us?
Yes. Kanzaki-san showed me this delicious Japanese restaurant the other day—
We're asking you to report information you gathered!
Yes. I learned something in regards to the Croce di Pietro's activation conditions.
It's a large-scale artifact that utilizes constellations.
We already managed to figure that much out.
I see...
So you must already know that the conditions to activate it are always present, regardless of the time of year.
When Sherry-san and I found it, we were very excited.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
The Croce di Pietro can only be activated once the user had learned the characteristics of the area,
and chooses one out of the 88 constellations which best corresponds to the chosen area.
That means...
Yes. There are many limitations, but theoretically, the Roman Church can use it to take over any part of the world.
I'm starting to get it.
It means Peter gave some leeway as to the region he affected with his teachings.
She may be able to freely choose the location, but what about the date?
Peter-sama was executed on June 29th.
That is the day the Croce di Pietro can be used at the Vatican.
So he deliberately got caught on that day? Prepared to die?
It's not that far-fetched.
Orsola. Do you know where in Japan the Croce di Pietro can be used today, September 19th?
Yes. But of course.
Look at this, Mikoto-chan!
It's a pseudo-five-dimensional kaleidoscope!
How interesting!
Don't pick something so sketchy.
Get something that's more memorable.
You're such a girl.
Shut up, Mother!
This slimy gaze...
I see. So, that person there is a member of your family.
What is this? She's like a bigger version which still maintains that air of "Onee-sama."
Damn it. Now I must go all the way.
Bring it on!
Kuroko, are you seriously...
Mikoto-chan, don't tell me you're that  kind of girl?
No way!
Kuroko, snap back to reality!
Wake up! Good morning! Good morning!
Onee-sama...
Oh, it's that boy...
So, Oriana was walking around to check out all the important points?
Yeah. The sky was hidden from view in the places she visited, though.
There's one last place. We should find her there.
The 23rd District's Experimental Airport?
There'll be nothing to hide the sky there.
Sorry for being late.
Seriously, what is with that person?
Even when I erase my presence, she notices me as soon as I leave the area of effect.
What are we going to do now?
The 23rd District has some crazy security.
Can we even get in?
Don't worry. This time around we can use the special permission I have.
Special permission?
Strange...
It's time for the final preparations.
Isn't there more time before we can start?
The security here is fluctuating irregularly.
It seems they've noticed my presence.
Then, Belvedere's position is...
Probably. But this is the best place to do it.
We can act freely here without involving civilians.
Then...
Yes. Prepare yourself.
Let's drop Academy City right here.
Like kicking a naive maiden of the light into the mud.
I had them change the 23rd District's security a bit.
We're going to use the confusion to our advantage.
The Croce di Pietro will activate immediately after sunset, most likely between 6 and 7.
It will take 10 minutes to get to the 23rd District's terminal station.
From there on, we will have 25 minutes to complete our mission.
Allow me to ask you one last thing. Do you intend to stand against Oriana as you are now?
I'd love to sit this one out, but I'm not sure you two can make it past the security detail on your own.
I see.
Once we step onto this train, there's no turning back.
From here on, there will be nothing but death.
Are you prepared, Kamijou Touma?
Yeah. We need to bring an end to this.
Also...
What is it?
I don't intend to end it all here.
Touma isn't around?
What do you mean?
I'm so sorry. I lost track of him despite being responsible for him.
I just want to ask one thing.
Of course. What is it?
Touma is acting on his own will, right?
He's not being dragged around by someone?
Yes, it's exactly as you say.
Then whatever he's doing now must be more important to him than the competition.
I can't think of a reason to stop him.
Yes.
May the sky and the heavens become a great roof to protect those within.
May the saints and angels bless this place.
The basic principle of the security here is the utilization of the sky.
There's almost nowhere to hide, after all.
Then, how did Oriana manage to get in?
She must have made prior preparations.
Tsuchimikado. We're short on time.
I'm aware. We're going to be using that.
There's a regular airport nearby, so this airspace is crowed with airliners and such.
In order to avoid a collision, the surveillance planes change their routes periodically.
We can use the blind spot that this creates to slip through unnoticed.
Tsuchimikado, stop!
What's wrong, Kami-yan?
Tsuchimikado!
Are you alright?
Go, Kami-yan.
You have to destroy that page and continue on.
What about you?
Stiyl, can't you do something with your magic?
Do you really think she'll wait for us?
Kamijou Touma!
Fire is in my hand.
Thy shape is a sword; and thy purpose is to cut!
Hurry!
Looks like that saint really isn't going to show. That makes only three of you.
The field that she just erected will cut all communication.
Stiyl!
My, my. I’m not so sensitive that I can be satisfied with one hand.
Shatter!
As always, your hips run out of gas way too quickly.
Your ride ends here. I won't allow you to use the Croce di Pietro.
You think you can just mess with Academy City and disrupt the Daihaseisai like that?
It all ends now!
Disrupt? That's a little mean.
The Croci di Pietro might break the walls between science and magic, leading the world to happiness.
Happiness?
Sounds nice, doesn't it?
I know that it’s a good word.
But my problem is that using the Croce di Pietro will ruin the Daihaseisai.
You don't know how many people were looking forward to the Daihaseisai.
Regardless of your religious beliefs, you have no right to ruin their fun!
You think that kind of emotionally charged speech will reach me?
If there were any risk of people getting hurt, I wouldn't have done this in the first place.
Could you say that in front of Fukiyose and Himegami, the two that you hurt?
That's all I wanted to say to you.
If you still have even a single thought of harming this city in any way,
then I'll have to crush that ridiculous illusion of yours!
karamatta unmei mo kaete ikeru kara
絡まった運命も変えて行けるから
Since even an entangled fate can be changed,
subete wa kono te no naka ni aru
総てはこの手の中に在る！
Everything lies within these hands of mine!
dare ni mo makenai chikara ga koko ni nai nara
誰にも負けない能力が身体に無いなら
Even if I don't have an unsurpassable power,
imajin nante kowashite shimaeba ii
幻想なんて壊してしまえばいい
I'll just destroy this illusion
harimeguru shisutemu bakkuappu insutooru wa OK
張り巡る回路再生強制入力はOK
Backing up the system that stretches all around. Install is OK
kami sae mo shirienai fiirudo ga hiraku
神さえも知り得ない領域が開く
An area that even the gods won't know will open up
juuman no deeta mo isshun no mirakuru sae
10万の記憶も一瞬の奇跡さえ
Even with 100,000 memories, a split second miracle
suisoku fukanou na ikiteru katachi dakara
推測不可能な“生きてる形”だから
cannot be predicted, because "That's the way life goes"
In a Magic∞world
exciting time or space
there’s no limit!
there’s no limit!!
dareka wo mamoreru chikara ga hoshii
誰かを守れる能力がほしい
I want the power to protect someone
karamatta unmei mo kaete ikeru kara
絡まった運命も変えていけるから
Since even an entangled fate can be changed,
subete wa kono te no naka ni aru
総てはこの手の中に在る！
Everything lies within these hands of mine!
Next Episode Preview
Even if you have an objective.
Even if you have a glorious ideal.
I won't allow it.
I'll smash you to pieces!
Next time: "Croce di Pietro."
When science and magic cross, the story begins.