I got a love-call from my teacher saying,
"Kamijou-chan, you're coming to summer school because you're stupid~"
What misfortune...
Well, the weather is nice, so I guess it wouldn't hurt...
to put up my futon and change the atmosphere.
The sky is so blue,
yet my future seems so dark.
It just better not start raining...
I'm...
I'm hungry.
Hello?
I'm hungry!
If you'll let me fill up my stomach,
I'd be really happy ~de-
Like hell I can allow that!!
Galaxian Explosion!!
Geso~
Since I have learned from my mistakes,
I shall not let them happen again.
Here you go!
Kihara-kun!!
I've already won the best new seiyuu award and
now I've won the best co-star award as well!
Now all that's left for me is to be the main protagonist!
Do you understand?!
'The hell you talking about?
Don't get cocky just 'cuz you're young...
I'll fucking crush you!
Ow, I'm sorry.
My bad,
but this is what the script...
What? It's in the script?
That doesn't mean shit to me, 'aight?!
You're just so cute.
And then...
Oh, and I'm going to kil-
You fucking listening?!
-and so, finally, in the year Showa 61...
I got the awards as well!
Cool story, bro.
Here you go!
I wanted to make a pun on Vento of the Front eating a bento but...
I decided not to.
A-are you all right, Himegami?!
W-what is it, should I rub your back?
What's wrong, Himegami?
N-no, it's nothing!
Your face is red. What happened, Himegami?
Trust me, it's nothing!
Come on, you're bright red.
What happened, Himegami?
Really, i-it's nothing!
You're bright as a tomato, tell me.
By the way, my bra today is a front hook.
Say what?!
Any male's dream!
The action-ready, easily accessible front hook?!
Mine is a normal...
Everyone, hear this!
Fukiyose has a front hook on today!
A front-hooked bra, I say!
Huh?!
It's a front hook... Yeaaaaah!!
Yo-Yomikawa-sensei...
not to be rude, but I have to go put things under control!
Hey you! What the heck are you doing?!
Ah, Komoe-sensei, what kind of bra do you wear?
Front-hook? Back-hook?
I don't wear one.
How nice to only have fools...
I wear a training bra.
Really, how nice.
Only to have fools...
Please.
Swinging a beer can over my head...
in front of students is amazing!
Ah, Himegami-chan, the meat is cooked.
Thanks for the fo-
Meat!
The vegetables are ready!
Thanks for the fo-
Veggies!
Fukiyose-chan, could you beat the eggs, please?
The meat...
I wanted to eat the meat...
Go ahead.
"Just what is the fun in playing a game where you spoil your little sister?" asks MISAKA 10032 as she conveys her true feelings.
"On the subject of games, Nei was certainly a superbly cute younger sister,"
replies MISAKA 10039 as she too conveys her genuine thoughts.
"Agreed. Nei was not only cute, but also industrious," comments MISAKA 13577 while...
remembering the past while trying to pull a good line and feeling a painful rush of nostalgia.
"She even had ears,"
"I'm having trouble keeping up with your haphazard train of thought,"
interjects MISAKA 19090 while letting her pained thoughts run their course.
"By the way, aren't you two straying away from the topic of little sister games?"
questions MISAKA 10044 in an interrogative manner.
"You definitely can't tell what they're talking about, right?"
asks MISAKA as MISAKA cheerfully reflects back on past games while devising plans for a new little sister game
I still think Nei is-
G-go ahead.
These stupid tricks of yours...
I've already seen through them!!
Question.
Innocent people who have nothing to do with this....
How many do you think there are?
Hmph,
innocent people?
There are none!
Onee-sama...?
Please.
"I want one of those goggles that  MISAKA 10032 and the other's wear too!" says MISAKA as MISAKA pouts around.
"You mean this?" asks MISAKA as MISAKA attempts to confirm the strange question.
"MISAKA wants that too!" whines MISAKA as MISAKA tries to throw a tantrum like a spoiled child.
"You may be trying to act cute, but that kind of behavior only annoys me," says MISAKA as MISAKA explains gently.
Also, these are not goggles, it's a Virtual Boy.
Huh?
A Virtual Boy.
"An ecstasy of black and red," replies MISAKA 10032 enthusiastically over the product she bought last year.
Please.
Uiharu...
Recently they had that pilgrimage to the Holy Land televised.
I want to make this anime a amazing piece of work and..
carve this it into the history of Japan, no, the world...
Oh, and to show the entire world the romantic beauty between Onee-sama and I...
and make it last for eternity.
How should I do this?
Hey, Uiharu.
Are you listening?
Of course I'm listening.
Then it's fine.
But don't you have any ideas?
Maybe something like a "lucky lecher" every two minutes?
What?
That's too much of a service and it'd be difficult on my end.
Besides, I don't think that's what this anime is about.
Now that you mention it, that is true.
Don't you have any other ideas?
Then how about I get a guitar and sing?
What do you think?
Something like that, but that's obviously a parody...
of another musical anime and that wouldn't be acceptable.
Besides, the producer isn't stupid.
He'll recognize it immediately.
Do you think so?
I think that the would take it as a funny joke.
Ah,
if only Saten-san was here with us right now.
I thought we promised not to say that.
Here you go!
Being the fourth release, we're running out of things to do.
Touma, you can't say that!
If you think of it, it's been five years since
this studio started Shana-tan!
The people who are writing all this are bound to
start running low on ideas eventually!
You say that, Index,
but those who can write at 100%  even if there's nothing to write about are what we call "pros"!
Chut up, Chut up!
You're wrong, you're wrong!
That's not true!
Even if it's hard to write, we don't show it...
and just do as we're supposed to!
Get bald, get bald!
Touma, lose all your hair!
Feel rejected! Sad! Bald!
All right, all right.
If we do this again, I'll see you then, I guess.
Instead, let's talk about Orsola!
'Ey you bastard...