In a few minutes, the opening ceremony for Daihaseisai will begin!
Here, at Academy City, the streets are bustling about with the parents and siblings of our students!
Maid bentos here!
Would you like Academy City's famous maid bentos?
Ryouran Kasei Girl's School maid's—
or rather, maid-in-training bentos?
Oh my, there are a lot of schools in Academy City.
Y-Yeah.
It's a city where all the world's top educational institutions are concentrated into one place.
S-Sorry.
I'm sorry, that was my fault.
Would you happen to know where Tokiwadai Middle School is?
Just a moment...
Tokiwadai... Tokiwadai...
It's not here. Maybe it isn't open to the public?
What, seriously?
Then where on Earth is Mikoto?
Is this Mikoto-san a sister of yours?
Oh my, Touya-san...
Are you at it again?
It really isn't here! What should I do?
M-Mother... what do you mean "again?"
Oh? Isn't that Touma-san over there?
Fine then!
If I lose, I'll do a penalty game.
I'll do anything you ask.
Alright, you're on!
Anything goes, right?
The same goes for you if you lose.
S-So, wait...
I have to do anything you—
What's that?
Is that really all the confidence you have after running your mouth like that?
Fine, you're on.
I'm not letting you cry your way out of it later.
Oh my...
Mikoto-chan looks happy.
Toaru Majutsu no Index
yubi de hajiku koin mitsumeta
指で弾くコイン見つめた
I watched the coin as I flicked it
omote nara go ura wa stay mazu kotae o kikasete
表ならGO、裏はSTAY。まず答えを聞かせて
Heads is GO, Tails is STAY. But first, let me hear your answer
douka oshiete kuremasen ka
「どうか教えてくれませんか？」
Would you please tell me?
tenshi wa misadameru egao no mama
天使は見定める　笑顔のまま
The angels judges me as they smile
mayoe sono te o hiku mono nado inai
迷え！その手を引く者などいない
Get lost! No one's going to hold your hand!
kami ga kudasu sono kotae wa fukou datta
神が下す　その答えは不幸だった
The answer from God was misfortune
sou sore koso kami kara no okurimono
そう　それこそ神からの贈り物
Yes, but it was still a gift from God!
norikoetara miete kuru sa dakara ima sugu
乗り越えたら見えてくるさ　だから今すぐ
If you get over it, you'll be able to see. But for now...
No buts!
Daihaseisai
The Daihaseisai will begin soon, correct?
Won't you be paying them a visit?
Do you really think I can let people see me like this?
Then let's not hesitate to continue our conversation.
About the magicians who've infiltrated Academy City?
They're taking the chance while city security is relaxed.
We've managed to confirm that there are two of them.
A high ranking member of the Roman Catholic Church, and a courier she hired.
Their objective is a particular object.
A particular object?
A sword?
This is just a replica.
"Stab Sword."
They say it can slay a dragon and pin it to the ground.
If successfully handed over, the Church of England will be in a rather dreadful predicament.
A so-called "tactical weapon" for your side?
Here's the biggest issue:
The trade for the sword is happening within Academy City.
Which means...
We'll have to get that boy to be the travel guide.
Hey, Touma!
I'm hungry!
Huh?
You just ate breakfast.
But there's such a delicious smell everywhere that I can't stand it!
Japan's food culture is the essence of food temptation!
Okay, fine.
We can walk around later and check it out.
Later?
Yeah.
The first match is starting soon.
All the events I'm participating in today are marked in this.
Let's go, Index!
T-Touma seems really dull today...
Do we really have to...
Why does everyone look so weary before we've even started?
We used up what little energy we had fighting over what strategy to use to defeat the other schools.
Get your priorities straight!
That's what student matches are.
Such misfortune.
What's with this lack of spirit?
Hey, Kamijou!
Don't tell me you infected everyone else with your laziness!
I only just got here!
So everyone basically lost their motivation because you showed up late.
You were later than I was, Fukiyose!
I had committee duties to take care of, idiot!
Leave me alone!
Kamijou-san has gotten himself into an unfortunate situation and he can't get up for the time being!
That's just anemia getting to you.
Here, this sports drink will fix that.
I hate people who blame bad luck or fate for their own lack of resolve.
Everyone's lost their motivation because of your laziness, so you'd better get it together!
U-Um...
U-Uh...
Is there a problem?
None whatsoever, Ma'am!
Nobody even wants to play Pole Assault anymore.
This may seriously be hopeless...
Like I said, I realize that our equipment and curriculum are lacking!
But that isn't the fault of the students!
Isn't it because their results are so low that the administrative board refuses to raise funding?
You must have it pretty rough, teaching a bunch of failures like that.
S-Students can't simply be labeled as successes or failures!
They just have their own personalities.
That's a pretty idealistic opinion.
The Pole Assault that's starting now...
We'll be sure to completely crush those hopeless failures at your school.
You're wrong...
Our students aren't hopeless...
Hey, guys...
Let me ask again.
Are we going to do this or not?
First match: Pole Assault.
The various school teams are entering.
What a reckless guy.
There's no way they can beat our school.
So hungry...
Could she be suffering from heatstroke?
Oh, so you really are hungry.
What's Miss Short-Hair doing here?
Cheering for Touma?
Wh-Why would I cheer for that guy?!
I just came to see which school will win.
Though it's obvious my school will.
Huh?
What should I do then?
He said he'd do anything I asked...
There's Touma!
Why does he look so determined?
Is he seriously going to try to win?
What is he going to make me do once he wins?!
Get set...
Go!
Why did you all go so far just to win?
Even though you won, seeing you all bruised like that makes me...
Hey, Index!
Man, she's so hopeless.
Oh, my phone...
I left it in my bag.
I-I came here to get my cellphone so I could contact someone I was separated from.
I didn't have any bad intentions...
Huh?
There you are, Touma!
Were you just crying?
Where's your phone?
Right here!
Then why didn't you answer?!
Your battery's dead...
Nevermind that, I'm hungry!
Give me something to eat, Touma!
If you go to the stands, there's mountains of food there.
Mountains!
NO ENTRY
Oh, I'm sorry, there's a parade coming through here soon.
We only need to get over there...
There's a subway you can use to cross the street if you go about 3km west.
3km...
But it's right there...
Well, we'll just have to wait until the Ball Rolling event is over.
Touma...
What?
Wait!
Alright, I've got you! You're my ticket to victory!
The winner of the Borrowed Item Race is Misaka Mikoto of Tokiwadai Middle School!
Borrowed Item Race?
Yep. I had to find a high school student who participated in the first event.
And you just happen to fit the bill.
Aren't there a bunch of other people who'd fit—
What the heck was that for?
Sheesh...
Here, drink this...
There's no other choice, so I'll let you have this!
Well, you see, when I imagined you resting in bed while the rest of us were working in this blazing heat...
I just couldn't stop myself.
I wanted you to help us out, too!
I thank you very much, my dear friend.
So, are there any problems?
Not at the moment.
After taking first place, Misaka Mikoto remains in tip-top shape.
She continues to make everything look so easy.
Onee-sama!
Oh, my beloved Onee-sama!
And here we see her taking care of her partner who ran with her.
I'll kill him!
NO ENTRY
I can't find Index.
Will she be okay?
It's him...
Academy City is most likely relaxing its security in order to attract a bigger audience.
And magicians are taking this chance to infiltrate?
We've only confirmed two of them.
Lidvia Lorenzetti of the Roman Catholic Church, and the courier she hired, Oriana Thomson.
Courier?
They're making a trade with the Church's spiritual weapon here in this city.
Why here?
Isn't Academy City as far from the occult as you can get?
That's precisely why.
This is a place where neither the science side nor magic side can interfere easily.
In other words, the only people who can act are your buddies already in Academy City.
What about Kanzaki then?
Isn't she a Saint or something?
We can't use Kanzaki, especially not this time.
Not with the spiritual weapon being what it is.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Kami-yan, the name of the weapon is "Stab Sword."
They say it can kill any Saint with a single strike.
Watch out!
No!
Huh?
What?
What are you doing, Kamijou Touma?!
Do you know how the Son of God was killed on the cross, Kami-yan?
Wasn't he... nailed there?
He was stabbed to death.
Stab Sword is a weapon that extracts the religious meaning of the nailing and stabbing,
and amplifies, concentrates, and focuses it to its limit.
It would have no effect on normal humans, but it has a one-hit-kill ability if used against a Saint.
What do the magicians have planned, trading something like that?
Preparing for war, of course.
Saints have power equivalent to that of a nuclear weapon in the magical world.
But there are plenty of magicians who aren't Saints, right?
I'd imagine they could fight without Kanzaki...
That's not the issue.
It's not about whether they'd actually win or not.
Wars can start simply because one side has the illusion of having a winning chance.
NO ENTRY
But wait, if this is that serious a problem, shouldn't we ask Index for her help?
No.
We can't use that forbidden index for this.
We can't let her near any of this, or even let her know about it.
Why?
Because if anything were to happen, she'd become the center of attention.
That's how many magicians are looking for her.
If she were to be discovered, magicians would come flooding in, aiming for her.
In other words, we have to do something about it without letting Index notice.
When I rushed back to you after hearing from Yomikawa-sensei,
I really panicked since you looked almost like a leftover shriveled vegetable.
Thanks for the meal!
Where did Touma go, though?
It's almost time for lunch!
U-Um... you just had lunch...
Will...
Will Touma and I be separated like this for the rest of the day?
I see...
You want to enjoy Daihaseisai with Kamijou-chan don't you, Sister?
Don't worry!
There's something you can participate in, Sister!
Yes?
Hey... did you really get lost?
Why are you walking around looking like a hero who's about to face the final boss?
You've got an expression on like you're about to die.
Why not go eat something if you're hungry?
Forget that, have you seen Index anywhere?
I saw the Sister walking over there.
Thanks!
It looked like she was being dragged somewhere by that famous little teacher at your school!
Huh?
Index?
So it's just you?
Where's Index?
I'm sorry...
It pains me to make you change here, but...
Touma!
How many times does this make it?!
Uh, well... Index-san?
Are you okay?
It was an accident!
You don't have to get so serious about it...
Kamijou.
I came here to look for Tsukiyomi-sensei for some committee work...
And you...
What are you doing?!
You traitor!
Sheesh!
Can't you put even a little effort into making this festival a success?
What event is our school in now?
You can't even remember that?
I see. If your brain isn't getting enough nutrients, go get some sugar into your system!
K-Kamijou-san's stupidity won't be cured with that!
Don't you feel bad at all, hearing yourself say that?
Right now, the second-year girls' tug o' war and the third-year boys' restricted triathlon are on.
Which event will you go to support?
The girls, I bet!
But of course, you are Kamijou after all...
At least don't pull me by my neck...
Well then.
Come on already!
Hey, Kamijou.
Do you find Daihaseisai boring?
You seem restless...
Like something else is on your mind.
If you're finding today boring, Kamijou, it means I'm not doing enough as a committee member...
It's not that I think it's boring...
I guess, as someone who worked so hard to come up with all this stuff,
I kind of want everyone to share fond memories of the event.
Maybe I'm just being selfish, though.
You really do have something bothering you, don't you?
No, that's not it—
I'm sorry!
Get away from me, Kamijou Touma!
I'm not used to such crowded areas...
It's fine...
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Your forehead is swelling up.
It's nothing...
As an apology for bumping into you...
Would you like a kiss?
Yes! A kiss would be—
Ow...
Well, then.
I need to get back to work.
Bye now.
Hello? Oriana Thomson here.
Can you hear me?
Don't say your real name out loud.
Is your voice audible to anyone around you?
Nevermind that; I've run into some trouble.
It looks like the spell Onee-san cast on me was dispelled.
How?
I don't know.
But it's turning me on for some reason.
Don't say such obscene things.
Countermeasures?
Let's see...
First, I'll have to lose that boy behind me.
karamatta unmei mo kaete ikeru kara
絡まった運命も変えて行けるから
Since even an entangled fate can be changed,
subete wa kono te no naka ni aru
総てはこの手の中に在る！
Everything lies within these hands of mine!
dare ni mo makenai chikara ga koko ni nai nara
誰にも負けない能力が身体に無いなら
Even if I don't have an unsurpassable power,
imajin nante kowashite shimaeba ii
幻想なんて壊してしまえばいい
I'll just destroy this illusion
harimeguru shisutemu bakkuappu insutooru wa OK
張り巡る回路再生強制入力はOK
Backing up the system that stretches all around. Install is OK
kami sae mo shirienai fiirudo ga hiraku
神さえも知り得ない領域が開く
An area that even the gods won't know will open up
juuman no deeta mo isshun no mirakuru sae
10万の記憶も一瞬の奇跡さえ
Even with 100,000 memories, a split second miracle
suisoku fukanou na ikiteru katachi dakara
推測不可能な“生きてる形”だから
cannot be predicted, because "That's the way life goes"
In a Magic∞world
exciting time or space
there’s no limit!
there’s no limit!!
dareka wo mamoreru chikara ga hoshii
誰かを守れる能力がほしい
I want the power to protect someone
karamatta unmei mo kaete ikeru kara
絡まった運命も変えていけるから
Since even an entangled fate can be changed,
subete wa kono te no naka ni aru
総てはこの手の中に在る！
Everything lies within these hands of mine!
Next Episode Preview
Oriana runs around, toying with us.
Stiyl risks his life to investigate the spell she cast.
And the place we found...
Next time: "Route Disturb."
When science and magic cross, the story begins.