There are many monsters threatening humans.
Many brave adventurers stepped forward bravely.
And I,
Alvin, is one of them.
Forming a party with the healer Carla,
let's continue the adventure today.
DON'T HURT ME, MY HEALER
THE TITLE "THERE'S NO OTHER MAJOR FEMALE ROLE
EXCEPT CARLA IN DON'T HURT ME, MY HEALER."
IN A WAY, IT'S A SPECIAL SHOW.
AFTER EPISODE 5, THE WITCH AND THE ROBBER GIRL APPEARED.
"BUT THE YOUNG-LOOKING WITCH ONLY APPEARED
FOR A WHILE AT THE END." Today is also a peaceful day.
AND THE ROBBER GIRL WILL NOT APPEAR AGAIN. IT'S TIME TO LET
THE NEW FEMALE ROLE APPEAR TO MEET EVERYONE'S PREDICTIONS
"AND EXPECTATIONS. SORRY TO KEEP EVERYONE WAITING."
It's too peaceful.
"THERE'LL BE A NEW FEMALE ROLE THIS TIME. MARIA DESFREM."
It's hard for me to level up.
"BUT ENJOY THE ZOMBIE STORY FIRST."
Where are the monsters?
"WILL IT MEET EVERYONE'S EXPECTATIONS?"
Weak ones?
"PLEASE LOOK FORWARD TO EPISODE SEVEN."
You're so annoying.
That's...
Someone fell to the ground.
Was he attacked by a monster?
Mr. Alvin, hurry up.
We've got to bury him.
It's way too early.
Don't assume someone is dead
without confirming the situation.
He must be dead lying down there.
You haven't checked yet.
Okay. So we need to check first?
Of course.
Can we bury him after that?
It depends on the result.
Cremation or burial after confirming the result?
Think about the possibility
that he's still alive.
Forget it. I'll check myself.
Stop! Hold on a minute.
What? You're here?
It's dangerous to touch strangers.
Some monsters will take advantage of humans.
You can't guarantee that he's a human.
It makes sense.
You lack common sense as an adventurer.
I don't want to be said so by a monster.
But there's a possibility that he's a human.
Then ask him first.
Mr. Alvin, go ahead.
Me? Okay then.
Hello! Are you alive?
Don't you think it's too formal?
Hey! What's wrong with you?
Be more frank.
Wanna hang out for some tea?
Sorry, you're not my type.
I wasn't talking to you!
No. Why did you make me say that?
Such a shameless way of speaking.
Only cockroaches do that.
He's moving. Great! He's alive.
Luckily we didn't bury him.
No, he's dead. We should've buried him.
Could it be this zombie can't stand up?
Great. Then I can beat him.
No!
Don't you feel anything for him
desperately trying to stand up?
I want to beat him.
The zombie is also trying hard to stay alive.
It's dead.
You were going to bury it.
I'm moved by the way it made efforts.
Don't give up. Don't let your heart be rotten.
Keep it up!
Almost there.
Try it again.
Hey! Show me your determination.
He stood up.
The zombie... The zombie stood up.
The zombie stood up.
The zombie stood up. The zombie...
I'm moved.
Amazing.
You...
You've got some guts.
His head is off.
No, that's not it. I didn't mean to.
You killed it.
It's already dead!
Anyway, we buried it.
But it's a zombie.
Maybe it'll come back to life.
Don't worry.
Let someone who has a sacred heart
prays for it can purify it.
Then it can't be you.
You who's still sorrowful after death,
rest in peace. When the night comes,
wake up!
Who are you waking it up?
Don't be so obedient.
Oh no, I accidentally resurrected it.
Haha.
It's not a resurrection.
So it's the holy power.
I feel alive again.
But your head is off.
Thank you for waking me up.
I'm Zobita, a zombie.
What a simple name to understand.
I'm Carla, a real healer.
Real? How ridiculous.
This is Mr. Alvin, a joker.
I'm a warrior.
And I'm a popular...
Be quiet.
A healer, a joker, and a mushroom.
What a rare group.
Mr. Alvin, it said we're rare.
That's great, Carla. We've been praised.
You're adventurers, right?
It's a destiny that we met each other.
I would like to ask you a favour.
Okay, sure.
That was fast.
How could you accept a monster's task?
To make him owe me a favour.
You're so straightforward.
It's mainly to improve my popularity.
You wicked fellow.
And you're still bad at winking.
All right. What do you want us to do?
Please...
"REVENGE"
Help me get revenge.
REVISION
"PREPARATION"
Let's prepare as well.
Well said. Shut up.
Helping you get revenge isn't an easy task.
Tell us why.
His grades must have dropped.
Because he didn't do revision.
Stop joking around.
There's a cemetery ahead forgotten by all.
I was there...
I was the leader of a zombie dance group
called "Be Zombicious".
It's about revenge, right?
One day, a...
A dreadful necromancer appeared.
It's not me. I'm a healer.
I didn't say anything.
The necromancer had a high level.
My companions, one by one, were...
I remember that high-level necromancers
are good at manipulating the souls of the dead.
They were charmed by the dancing skills.
So cool.
Isn't that a dancer?
I can't accept that someone's dancing skills
are better than mine as a leader.
Please get revenge for me!
You're just holding a grudge.
No matter what the reason,
we can't leave the necromancer alone.
We accept the task of revenge.
There's someone more dangerous
next to me who's left alone.
I think this task is very suitable for us.
How?
Holy power is the weakness of the necromancers.
That means I have the advantage.
You don't have holy elements, do you?
Speaking of dancing,
it's your strength, Mr. Alvin.
Aren't you good at dancing in others' hands?
You're talking nonsense!
Let's go.
Let's go to the unknown cemetery first.
Are we really going there?
I'll leave it to you.
Hang on a second.
Wait a second. Stop.
Why are you running away?
The zombies these days run so fast.
It's troublesome.
Carla, what are you doing...
What's on your hand?
It's called "Fire of Redemption".
It can burn the souls
of the monsters of necromancy.
It's the holy magic of hell.
From what you said, I can't tell
what's redemption or holy.
And didn't we come to the cemetery
for the necromancer?
Don't worry.
She'll fall into the trap
if we cause a commotion.
Excuse me. It's a little noisy here.
What happened?
She fell into the trap.
Are you the necromancer?
I'm so sorry.
I'm a necromancer.
Maria Desfrem.
Nice to meet you.
It's totally different from what I imagined.
We have something in common.
Only the "Death Flame" part.
No worries.
I'm Alvin. She's Carla.
Mr. Alvin and Miss Carla.
Nice names.
Really?
It makes me shy.
I think Alvin is a great name, too.
It fits you very well.
Oh, well. It makes me feel bad.
Why are you two here?
It's a forgotten cemetery.
I don't think you're here to visit the grave...
We're here to visit the grave.
Your grave.
Wait a minute. I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Why are you trying to start a fight?
Didn't we accept Zobita's task of revenge?
He's just holding a grudge.
And now we're persuading him
to think about it again.
Is the warrior that weak?
You're much stronger compared to Alvin.
I advise you not to take revenge.
You're right.
But the necromancers can manipulate the dead.
It's profanity to the dead.
We can't leave her alone.
You profane both the living and the dead.
You're not qualified to say that.
She does look pretty.
But she must be like a devil inside.
What? Are you introducing yourself?
Look!
You're being so loud.
She manipulated so many zombies.
Hello, Lord Maria.
Hello.
It's Lord Maria.
Please show me your graceful dance again.
It seems she's adored by the zombies.
She must have threatened the zombies.
Is it necessary to do such a troublesome thing?
I'd do that.
Shameless.
Are you talking about Lord Maria
behind her back?
No...
What?
She was chasing us just now.
Take a closer look. She's a healer.
The enemy of the undead.
You must be here to frame Lord Maria.
Hold on. We can explain this.
That's right.
With our fists.
Can you please shut up?
MARIA
You've shown your true colours.
You wicked healer.
Never lay a finger on Lord Maria.
Don't fight.
What's more, Miss Carla is a cleric.
You all can't beat her.
Even if she's stronger than us,
we also have to protect Lord Maria.
Lord Maria, run now.
Come on and fight.
We become the villains.
They're like knights
protecting the princess instead.
I won't run away this time.
We won't lose.
Fight for someone you cherish.
It's cool, right?
Yes.
Mr. Alvin, there's someone you need to protect.
Oh, no need.
You're Carla's...
Shut up.
There's no choice but to do it.
Well, I'm the frontline.
I won't let you harm Carla.
Is that okay?
Mr. Alvin.
But I don't think you can win.
Are you trying to be funny?
All right.
Are you ready to die?
Come on.
Traitor! Bastard!
Shut up, you idiot!
Geez, let me go.
Honestly. It doesn't work.
Let's just stay quiet.
This happened because you betrayed me.
I mean...
Why am I the only one caught?
Because I caught you.
-The criminal caught should be imprisoned.
-No, I don't want it.
I surrender. It hurts.
I got the traitor. Put him in prison.
Finally, we avoided the fight.
No casualties, and it was solved safely.
But my pride has been hurt badly.
Oh, just throw it away.
Anyway, I'm going to discuss your situation
with the zombies now.
They'll let you go when they find out
that you're useless.
Watch your words.
Maria.
Sorry for getting you involved.
No, Maria. You don't have to apologize.
That's right. Just be careful next time.
-Right?
-You should be careful all the time.
I'm sorry, but...
They just discussed and decided
to turn the warrior into a zombie.
Hold on. Do you mean they're going to kill me?
But he's already socially dead
from being imprisoned.
I'm not dead, and you put me in here!
They want to add more zombie buddies for me.
But I think we can't ignore your thought
and turn you into a zombie.
So I brought the key. Please run away.
Is that okay?
Keep it a secret from the zombies.
What an angel.
Did you call me?
I didn't call you!
Please wait a moment.
I'm Mr. Alvin's companion.
It's my duty to rescue him.
Didn't you put me in jail?
And you don't have the key.
There's unlocking magic.
With the explosive unlocking magic.
Are you a saboteur?
It's a good chance.
Let's see who can rescue Mr. Alvin first.
The necromancer of darkness
can't beat... the healer of light.
Light and darkness.
It should be the other way round.
Maria can just open it with the key.
But I don't know which one it is.
-There's a lot.
-What should I do?
It's okay. Try them one by one.
That's right. Take your time.
Appreciate your last conversation
with Mr. Alvin.
Aren't you competing to save me first?
I'll start chanting.
Not this one.
It's all right. Try the next one.
Ten.
Nine.
-Maria, you just tried that one.
-Eight.
-Huh, how strange.
-Seven.
-I'm confused.
-Four.
Why do you skip the middle?
Don't count down!
Three.
-I'm so stressed.
-Two.
-One.
-Are you all right?
I'm sorry...
I can't watch this anymore.
Miss Carla, what about your chant?
Forget about it.
Pick the keys that don't fit first.
Okay.
Is it a key?
We'll usually mark them
or distinguish them by their uses.
You're right. I'll do that next time.
I've been watching you for a long time.
Miss Maria, you're a clumsy person, aren't you?
What are you laughing at?
No, sorry.
I think Miss Carla is much more gentle
than I thought.
Thank you...
Wait a second. Carla is gentle?
Impossible. You crack me up.
She's not gentle. She's strange.
What kind of weird atmosphere is this?
Please stay here tonight.
As long as you provide me three meals.
Hold on, you two!
You haven't unlocked it.
Why?
Unlock it for me.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW. THANKS TO ALTARGAIA
(IT'S THE MUSHROOM'S NAME, PLEASE DON'T FORGET IT),
"ALVIN ESCAPED FROM THE PRISON. BUT ANOTHER PROBLEM
HAPPENED AGAIN." Can I do the next episode preview?
"MARIA HAS A BELOVED SISTER, ELLIE."
Let me reintroduce myself.
"SOMEHOW IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH HER.
I WANT TO AVOID THE SPOILER," I'm a necromancer.
"BUT IT'S RELATED TO WHY MARIA IS A NECROMANCER."
Maria Desfrem.
"DON'T ANTICIPATE UNTIL ANOTHER LOVELY FEMALE LIKE MARIA
SHOWS UP." I'll appear in the next episode as well.
"INSTEAD, CARLA SHOWS EVERYONE HER COSPLAY DRESS
FOR THE FIRST TIME." Please stay tuned.
"PLEASE LOOK FORWARD TO THIS IN EPISODE EIGHT."
All right.
"STAY TUNED."
Title of the next episode...