Perhaps hell
would be better than here.
(Episode 10 A Fleeting Midsummer Night's Dream)
What should we do? Rush them?
If it were just us two it would be okay,
but carrying fragile goods and dead weight, we don't have a chance.
Aren't you the ones who followed me?
Don't be cocky, brat.
I'm not a child.
Only children ever say that.
Let's do our best together.
Everyone is hungry and waiting for us.
It's no good, we've attracted their attention.
I'll distract them while you two escape back to Tenmaya.
Vampires, you have two roads before you...
Will he be alright?
Kurusu has his own way of dealing with things alone.
Keep up, don't get lost.
I told you, I'm not a child.
How ugly.
Here you are. Where did you go?
Nowhere, just walked around.
How many times have I told you, it's dangerous to go out at night?
I'm back safe, it's fine.
What is it?
There's something only you can help with.
Can I refuse?
This.
That's Misaki's...
This costume miraculously escaped the fire.
I want Eurydice to wear this.
You're performing "L'Orfeo"? Where?
Here, we'll have an opera here.
I can already picture how you play the harp.
I'm performing in "L'Orfeo"? No one told me that.
I just decided.
Don't make that face.
I want to raise everyone's spirits.
People are still scared,
and a lot of people are still homeless, so...
I understand.
"L'Orfeo", although it's not the most interesting opera,
if you can change the fate of Eurydice,
maybe I'll consider.
You'll do it?
I have dreams, too.
If I get on stage, they can be realised.
This is easy to understand.
Every member's life experiences, families,
even social circles have been noted here.
Do you still need information on Code Zero's vampires?
It's not comfortable walking with a pebble in your shoe.
You must be strong, to call them a pebble.
After all, we have the King Kong Troop you created.
But those higher-ups don't know their worth.
Such a nuisance.
With such wrong policy, our country's future is in darkness.
Isn't it you and your King Kong Troop who will cut through that darkness?
Let me take care of the pebble.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now that Maeda is dead, only you can command the King Kong Troop.
Thank you.
I will do my best not to disappoint.
It's lucky that it survived the fire.
The costumes seem to have been hidden away in a hamper.
With this, Eurydice will be perfect.
That's great. Clothes make the man.
Not me. I want to see Deffrot perform.
But if we don't get the costumes together,
shepherds and the hell gaolers...
What else? And why do you need to advertise in the newspaper?
What's wrong with contributing to society?
If you contribute to the society, you will get recognition.
After I saw the opera Nito Shinbun recommended,
my strength returned to me.
I should subscribe to their newspaper.
Sales doubled!
What's your wishful thinking?
If only that were true.
In a world like this, I'll do my best.
Thank you, Chief!
I really want to see Miss Misaki's "Salome" again.
Pull me up.
Kurusu, please pull the rope up.
Got it.
I can't believe you'd send a vampire to find something underwater.
Excellent, the box is unscathed.
All right, let's get it to Tenmaya.
I want to see what's inside, too.
This is the last one.
All right, it's open.
Is it okay to open it?
That's why we brought it.
Wait.
All right.
I'm opening it!
It seems to be fine.
What is it?
Stink bomb prototype.
Stop. Don't shake that.
Why?
Stay away. Stop playing around.
What about this one?
Designs for a flying machine.
Want to fly?
Is that possible?
For A-class Kurusu, maybe.
And I've more or less collected all the materials.
Do you want to have a try?
That would be interesting!
So they're just toys.
The most important stuff is in here.
The source blood for the King Kong Troop.
That's...
It hasn't gone off?
Incredibly, it doesn't rot or coagulate.
It remains permanently in its original state.
But the second sunlight touches it, it will explode.
I've paid the price with my eye, after all.
What did you retrieve this for?
To understand exactly what vampires are.
Only sunlight affects this blood.
I think it's ultraviolet light that's responsible.
Since ultraviolet light can kill vampires,
if used carefully, perhaps it can make them age too.
We can grow up too?
Although you also might die.
Maybe that's okay too.
When will it be ready? Tomorrow?
Not so fast.
But you won't have to wait too long.
200 years. No, 100 years is definitely enough.
After all, only time is infinite.
Is here OK?
Thank you, Santaro.
I'll take it from here.
But why do you need so much bamboo?
I was commissioned by a craftsman.
He said he wanted to make a big kite.
Interesting.
This much bamboo,
could make a kite to scare Goemon Ishikawa himself.
The craftsman will be pleased.
If only this world could fly as high as a kite.
I hope this vampire business will blow over before the new year.
It should be fine, I think it will be a good year.
If Tenmaya says so, then I'm sure it will.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I just wanted to look at it.
You want to grow up?
I want to become human.
You can only dream of that.
Do we still have dreams?
Even I haven't tried.
Like butterflies, like flowers...
What?
Suwa, can you come here?
I know it's sudden, but I want you to deliver something tonight.
Alright, I'll go now.
If all the good in the world is dead, even hell is nothing to fear.
Excellent, a worthy performance.
What are you doing here?
What's her name? Aoi Shirase asked me to come
as her guest.
Then, can I ask you to leave now?
I don't want to have any more connections with you.
I just came to say hello. I also have no interest in seeing you.
But a self-important vampire like you can't be ignored.
Enjoy your journey to hell.
Orpheus, sir, it's time.
Where did he go?
Lights, ready, background, ready.
Next comes the actors...
It's so bright.
I think there's an opera playing overnight at the Imperial Hotel.
Tenmaya said.
What?
Hey, we still have work to do.
It'll just take a second.
Takeuchi told me to keep a close eye on you.
Alright, let's go.
Whatever, when things are better I can go anytime.
Let's do this quickly.
Alright.
Aoi must be there to see the opera too.
Eurydice.
You are the sweet wine of life, the eternal light in a sea of misery.
The flame of my life.
All of my love.
And your doubting heart
has destroyed it all.
That sweetness, light, even the flame of my life
are mere candles in the wind,
But benevolent god of love.
if you have any sympathy for our love,
please carry our ashes to the sky,
where they may become a star.
Let all the lovers looking up at the sky
learn from our mistake.
Being on stage feels as good as I hoped.
If only just for a moment, I could feel the taste of death.
A thistle.
Rufus, what are you thinking?
We're back.
Welcome home.
How did it go?
As you'd expect.
Suwa didn't go to the opera.
Shut up.
Any gift?
A mask? Amazing!
Don't be so clingy.
A gift!
Throw it away.
Good work, it seems the information was correct.
Yes, so we can all move as a group.
Yes, we just need to prepare the transportation.
It's underway.
I put the bamboo you wanted inside.
Thank you, then we should be able to do a test-drive.
What do you want to test?
Wait and see.
It's me, Deffrot, with your invitation.
That voice.
"I am the daughter of Herodias, the princess of Judea."
"Let me hear that voice one more time, John."
What are you plotting, Rufus?
There's something I want to discuss.
Where is that girl?
Here.
If you want to catch a big fish, you have to prepare the right bait.
You thought I would be interested in a human?
You look up to her like an older sister. That should be enough.
Shut your mouth.
It's you who should be quiet.
The sun brings death to us all.
I will make you die by other means.
No need.
You're already turning to ashes.
Rufus, have you no self-respect?
Self-respect?
I lost that when I lost my humanity.
Do you know what I hate most in this world?
Self-important vampires.
Deffrot, are you alright? Are you hurt?
Stay back.
But, you...
Don't treat me like a child.
Where did your self-respect go?
I can't watch this third-rate acting.
Turn to ashes and drop the curtain.
An unexpected performer has entered the stage.
Should I tie it here?
Yes, please.
It's already taking shape.
A huge kite.
What is it?
A flying machine.
Flying? Will it fly?
Yes, I heard that in Europe they're already using planes
to drop bombs and gain a tactical advantage.
I believe that in the future,
he who controls the sky, controls the world.
Even so, what use is a flying vampire?
If you can fly, you bypass all land barriers.
You can move faster and further.
I want to fly!
Suwa, have a go too.
A thing made from cloth tied to bamboo,
it's just a kite. Who would fly on that?
If anything, it's more like a bat.
Isn't it dangerous?
According to my calculations, each wing needs to be 20 meters long.
If we used iron, it would break.
But by using this light and strong bamboo,
it should hold together.
And the person who uses it must be strong.
Thirty times stronger than an average human.
Then humans have no chance.
Yes, it needs to be a vampire.
Right, Kurusu?
What? Me?
There's no way humans can fly.
We want to try, right Yo?
Yes, I want to fly with the birds!
Birds don't fly in the dark,
they fly under the sun, when we can't go out.
If the sun touches us, we ignite and die.
Misaki.
Eradicate
the vampires.
(THE BLACK WING)