Abandoned artificial satellites.
Tanks jettisoned from shuttles.
Debris generated during
space station construction.
This vast amount of junk floating in space,
space debris, is a very serious threat.
This is a story of 2075, a time in which
this space garbage has become a problem.
This is the last of it,
right, Senpai?
Go to a private
channel?
You want to tell me something in secret,
Senpai?
If you want to badmouth our bosses...
It's not that!
I, uh... Tanabe, I was wondering...
Are you, um, seeing anybody?
Huh? Um... What do you
mean by that?
Come on, do I have to spell it out for you?!
I'm asking if you have a boyfriend!
I knew that.
That isn't what I meant.
I...
Tanabe!
Hold that thought!
Behind you!
It's the OSA!
I wonder what that
patrol ship wants with us?
Don't make any funny moves, Tanabe.
They'll arrest us.
You're kidding!
Things have been pretty hairy lately,
what with the Space Defense Front and all.
Oh, wow... He stopped
on a dime.
We're simple debris haulers.
We haven't done anything...
Never jump to conclusions,
Hachimaki.
Didn't I teach you that?
A spaceman makes his decisions quickly,
but very, very carefully.
Sensei!
Regrets
Gigalt Gungulgash of the
Orbital Security Agency.
For the next five days, I will be conducting
security training exercises with you.
I look forward to
working with you.
N-No, sir!
The pleasure is all ours!
It's good to see you
again, Gigalt-san.
It's just like old times, Gan-chan.
How are things at the OSA?
Great. A real diamond in the rough just
joined up. I'm grinding down his rough edges.
That diamond in the rough
has my sympathies.
Hello there, Hourglass!
You still hitting the books?
Yes, sir.
Hitting them hard.
Tanabe, Gigalt worked here
up until two years ago.
So don't do anything
to insult him!
He's the man who taught me
everything I know about space.
Oh, so that's why you
call him "Sensei."
Sorry for scaring you back there, little lady.
I'm Hachimaki's sensei.
Y-Yes, sir!
I'm Tanabe Ai!
So you had a sensei, too,
huh, Senpai?
Of course I did!
Let's have a welcome party!
On the company's tab, of course!
Gigalt-san is a
public servant now.
Oh, so no wining
and dining, huh?
You're the same as ever,
Sunflower.
Have you seen Sunflower's ultimate
party trick, little lady?
Sunflower?
He means Lavie.
Fee is Turbo Lighter.
The Chief is Marshmallow.
I'm not too good at remembering names, so I
give people nicknames that I can remember.
But it looks like "Hachimaki"
is the only nickname that stuck.
You're the one who gave him
the name Hachimaki, Gigalt-san?
Yeah. I felt bad calling him
"rookie" all the time.
Rookie...
What, you got a problem
with that?
For the next month, we will be hosting these
four security instructors from the OSA.
They will observe each
department in turn.
You of Control Section Group B are
scheduled for two weeks from now.
However, the instructors will be
on company grounds at all times,
...so obey all regulations scrupulously and pay
close attention to what you say and do.
I assume I can count on you to provide our
report for the Orbital Security Operating Audit?
Well, um, I have to work out
next quarter's work orbits, so...
And I still have those contract
drafts to prepare...
And the the end-of-month
billing deadline is coming up.
Let me see to it, sir.
But you're overseeing all the shipping related
to the tandem mirror project, aren't you?
I can handle it, sir.
Let me take care of it.
All right. I'll leave
the matter to you.
Thank you, sir.
The arrival of GO-44
will be delayed...
I'm sorry, I have plans
that day.
Cheng-Shin-san, you don't have
a girlfriend, right?
I don't, but there's a girl
that I'm interested in.
This girl...
Is it Tanabe?
Planting explosives in rescue balls is
the Space Defense Front's latest M.O.
Note: 'M.O.' is short for Modus operandi, Latin for 'mode of operation'.
Always remember
to inspect them.
These are the tools of your trade. Make sure
you conduct one last check yourselves.
Too slow! I want to see you do it in under
10 minutes without using a dressing frame!
Work with the suit's inertia!
I want you to do it in six!
Yes, sir!
Got it? Keep the sun's position
memorized at all times!
Yes, sir!
How many times do I have to tell you
to eat your vegetables?
Aw, c'mon, Sensei!
Hachimaki, you must think you're hot stuff,
trying to fight me like this...
What're you talking about...?
Why, you...!
Hachi!
Gan-chan!
Boo-yah!
Son of a...
That was dirty, using a feint!
This is about brute force! Brute force!
Okay, let's start from the top shelf.
Six maintenance packs...
Boy, Sensei hasn't
changed one bit.
So it was Gigalt-san who saved your life
on your first mission, huh, Senpai?
Yeah. After I had my accident,
I was totally terrified of space.
The one thing that let me
keep working this job...
...was that Sensei taught me about lots
of good things space has to offer.
He must have been
a great teacher.
Yeah, that's why I feel so indebted to him
and respect him the way I do.
It's not just because he's some
astronaut superman or something.
He's... I dunno.
He means a lot to me.
That's it.
Please do the
same for me.
Well, you're my sensei,
right, Senpai?
G-Get serious!
It takes a guy a lot more amazing
than me to be a sensei.
Um, Senpai... About what
you asked earlier...
Yeah?
You asked, um... You asked
if I was seeing anybody.
Are you?
No, I'm not!
Oh...
Oh, so you aren't...
Roland-san?
Yeah. I haven't been able to
get in touch with him lately.
Right, you never met him,
did you?
I don't mean to sound like Hachimaki,
but Roland-san is like my own sensei.
He passed away
last month.
Hachi and I... were with him
when he died.
An accident?
No. Suicide.
Or something like it.
He was worried that he'd be kept out
of space because he had leukemia.
Leukemia...
I see.
You just never know it's gonna
turn out with people, do you?
And now, everyone, let's have a toast
to Mr. Gigalt's continued health!
Cheers!
We're really sorry that your welcome party
ended up being a farewell party.
But you're gonna be on Seven
for another month, right?
Your going to Maintenance Section next, right?
I wouldn't be saying my goodbyes just yet.
We still have tomorrow's mission.
Ladies and gentlemen!
I would like to bid you welcome to
Arvind Lavie's palace of illusions!
Now may I present my latest trick which utilizes Balloon Nora, on sale at stores everywhere!
Behold... Rocket Nora-kun!
Hey, watch it!
I can't drink
another drop...
Um, don't you think you've
had too much to drink?
No, I'm doin' fine.
Hakim, top me off.
Who're you callin' Hakim?
I'm Hachimaki, remember...?
You don't seem to be able to hold
your booze like you used to, Sensei...
Hachimaki... How are things going
with you and Swan-san?
What're you talking about,
Sensei?
Who's Swan-san?
Isn't it about time you found
a woman and settled down?
Who's this "Swan-san" person?!
That girl in Control Section.
The one who joined the same time as...
You mean Claire-san?!
Yeah, that was
her name...
She and Sempai are going out?
They're an item?!
Don't ask the man
stuff like that!
So tell me, aren't you?!
It's not like it matters
either way...
Yes it does!
You asked me the same question, remember?!
So give me a straight answer!
That's ancient history... We broke up.
There. You happy now?
One of the OSA instructors will be coming
to our section next week, so be ready.
It seems like a formality.
I don't see why we need security...
Hey, Lucie, I'm home...
Tanabe, have you
been drinking?
We were having a farewell party
for Senpai's sensei...
See you.
Bye.
We drank 'til we dropped...
Say, Tanabe?
Yeah?
There's something I'd like to talk to you
about once my flight gets back.
I wanted to ask you
something, too...
Like what?
Tanabe!
Um... It can wait until your
flight gets back.
You sure?
Yeah...
It feels like the
room is spinning...
You're the one
who's spinning.
Good morning to all regular shift crew workers.
All ISPV-7 stations will now begin...
Good morning, sir!
Wow, you're here early!
Good morning.
You get the booze out of your system?
Yes, sir! I hit the sauna.
I passed the alcohol check and everything!
Okay, that's good.
So, where's Hachimaki?
Senpai went back
for his hachimaki.
This one, I mean.
I suppose he wears that
hachimaki to look tough,
...but it's not like anybody
can see it in his spacesuit.
It acts as a switch
for him.
He uses that hachimaki to put himself
in the proper frame of mind.
Now that you mention it, he does seem
a lot more serious when he's on the job.
Not just on the job.
In his off-hours, too.
He ties it around his head, and then
nothing can make him change course.
"It's my job, so this
is what I have to do",
...or "I'm a man, so this is something
I'm not allowed to do."
Yes, sir!
I get it now!
I didn't give him that nickname simply
because he wears a hachimaki headband.
Yes, sir, I never
thought of that!
Um... Can I ask you
something?
About Claire-san... Why did you
give her the nickname "Swan"?
Oops. Maybe I shouldn't
have said anything.
Um... If you can't tell me,
I'll understand.
Well, it's... You know how swans look all elegant
and graceful as they glide along the water?
Under the water, though, their legs
are paddling away like crazy.
Oh...
That Swan lady pushes
herself too hard.
Claire-kun.
When can I expect to see that plan
for the OSA?
Yes, sir. I'll have it to you
by the end of the day.
You're the one who volunteered to do it,
so don't expect any help from me.
Yes, sir.
I can handle it.
Our debris today is the same age as me.
I was born exactly one month after it was launched.
Why am I getting a heat source
off the debris?
There are two?
Huh? I don't get it.
Fee.
Yeah, I know.
I'll deploy the arm.
Hop to it.
What the heck
is going on?
Every once in a while,
you run into guys like this.
Are they another
debris team?
Yeah, but the
opposite of us.
The opposite?
They come up here into space and dump stuff
like expended atomic fuel or industrial waste.
If they just dumped it, sensors
would detect it right away.
So they attach it to another piece of debris
to make it look like it's all one big piece.
Hey, wait a minute...
Isn't that illegal?!
Which is why we're
gonna nab 'em!
Illegal dumping? Why did they have
to do it during our security audit?
Hey! Contact the OSA!
I'm on it!
You're not getting away
from me!
Okay, gotcha!
Okay, that'll be enough of that, you morons!
This is the INTO Orbital Security Agency!
You're not fooling
anybody, jerk!
You think a bunch of junk
jockeys can catch us?!
Are they gonna try to manually
cut our arm loose?
If you want a fight, we'll give you one.
But...
Hachimaki!
Let's do it, Sensei!
This thing's got a jumbo arm that's supposed to
be used for docking, and even a gantry crane!
What kind of ship
is this?!
Look for the power cable!
Get the cutters!
Cut loose that piece
of crap's arm!
If we get caught, we're looking
at 20 years at hard labor!
Our active stealth
is working, right?
The phase shifter
is functioning.
Okay! Finish up before
the OSA gets here!
Why can't I?
I want to go, too!
I told you, this is
no place for a rookie!
I don't think this is a time for worrying
about who's a rookie or who's a senpai!
You can't use a lifeline this time!
You'll just get in the way!
Sensei! Let's show 'em what
a team like you and I can do!
Hachimaki!
Sir?
Nobody who calls himself a spaceman
ever raises his hand to a woman.
It was my butt.
Hurry it up, damn it!
Finish up!
Cut this thing loose!
It's pretty tough.
This ship is pretty old.
Who uses an arm like this these days...
Oh, you wanna start
something, junk man?
They sent out some
people, too, huh?
Yes, sir. There's only two of them,
but we're being driven back.
What are our guys doing?!
We've got seven people out there!
Everybody who isn't busy,
get out there, and...
What the...?
They're moving their ship, too?
DS-12, this is Seven.
An INTO Orbital Security Agency patrol vessel
is currently en route to your position!
Don't try anything danger...
These guys won't wait until that patrol boat shows up!
Forward the ship's
orbital data to me!
We're gonna march these bozos
straight to the OSA!
It's no use!
We're being dragged along!
What the hell is a debris hauler doing
with an engine that powerful?!
Hey! Haven't you gotten
that arm off us yet?!
It's an old model, so it's
way bigger than it needs to...
Well pardon us
for being so old!
Adhesive?
Must be what they were using
to stick their waste to the debris!
We're not gonna let you
take us in, not now!
Attempted murder.
That's an additional 25 years.
Then I don't have anything
to lose, do I?!
You dumb bastard!
Sensei!
Forget about him! It's yourself that
you should be worrying about!
Hey! We can deal with him later!
We have to cut that arm loose!
Damn...
Behave yourself,
you piece of...
Sensei! Gigalt Sensei!
Do you read me?!
We'll come get you!
Fee! Get back there quick!
Get back there!
Don't make such
a fuss, Hachi.
Roland Sensei...
You too, huh?
Gigalt-san!
Are you okay?
Little lady?!
Hurry! Grab on!
Tanabe! I thought I told you
to stay inside!
Who do you think
you are?!
A debris hauler
of justice!
We can't let those evil debris haulers
get away with this! Right, Senpai?!
What's with this good
and evil crap?
It's important!
What the hell are
you talking about?
Anyway, once you drop off Sensei
back at Toy Box, come get me!
Understood. I'll get there
as soon as I can.
ASAP! You copy?!
I copy!
Oh, crap! They've cut
through the arm!
Roll us!
Increase output!
We're overheating!
We can't pursue.
You piece of junk!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
He can't move. Let's cook
this guy nice and slow.
Come get some! Lemme show you what
a debris hauler of justice is made of!
This is Orbital Security Agency
patrol vessel Cresta-53.
All unauthorized traffic in established shipping
lanes is subject to boarding and inspection.
We took too long, huh?
Heave to immediately and obey
all instructions from this vessel.
I say again,
This is Orbital Security Agency patrol vessel Cresta-53.
Son of a...
Bastards!
Cease any and
all resistance.
Offer any further resistance, and we
will be allowed to use deadly force.
All right, all right...
Impressive.
Thank you for
your cooperation.
Are you here by yourself?
This is some impressive work.
We just held 'em for you,
that's all.
Judging from those moves, you must
be an OSA commander or something.
Senpai! Are you okay?
Yeah, the cavalry
came to the rescue.
Sorry we took so long,
Hachimaki.
Sensei!
Sensei? You're here, too?
Is that you, Hakim?
Yes, sir.
Oh, now I see. It's Security
Instruction Month, isn't it?
I also dropped in to see how an
old student of mine was doing.
Sensei taught you, too?
You, too?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hakim Ashmead.
Hoshino Hachirota.
I'm a debris hauler.
This is a fine
sight to see.
Two of my pupils worked together
to see a single job through.
This means I can retire now
and not have to worry.
It's a little early
for that, Sensei.
You don't plan on retiring,
and you know it.
Caught me, huh?
When you're in space, you don't retire
until you die. Remember that.
I copy.
Our return ETA will be more than
120 minutes behind schedule.
We'll see you in Bay Five
in 150 minutes, then.
Please follow the OSA's instructions
for follow-up paperwork.
Submit your report by
the end of the day.
No one was injured,
correct?
No. Oh, and Astronaut Hoshino
is having his statement taken.
How long does it usually take
for them to take your statement?
If you don't mouth off to the officer,
you're done in 10 minutes.
Knowing Senpai, it'll probably
be more like 30, then.
Okay, got it.
Thank you, Angel.
Huh? Angel?
You mean that's
my nickname?
I can't keep calling you
"little lady," can I?
Oh... Thank you.
But "angel" might not be appropriate
for someone my age...
Oh, you don't like it?
In that case, how about...
Gigalt-san!
Were you hurt in the fight?!
No, I'm okay...
I wasn't hurt.
But...
It's cancer.
This kind of thing happens a lot when
you're out in space a long time.
I don't believe it...
It's already progressed
too far to be treatable.
So I want you to keep this to yourself.
Don't tell him.
Next Time
A Sky of Stardust
You stare out the window
and zone out sometimes.
Do you see something
out there?
Yes. I see space.
I did it! I broke ten minutes!
I can do it in under
ten minutes now...
When you lose
someone you love,
...there's no sadness,
and there's no grief.
You don't feel
anything at all.
Yuri!