Discarded artificial satellites.
Tanks jettisoned from shuttles.
Refuse generated during
space station construction.
This trash, space debris, circles the Earth
at speeds approaching 8 kilometers per second.
Should this debris collide with a spacecraft,
it could result in a terrible accident.
For this reason, mankind has been confronted
by the necessity of collecting this debris.
This is a story of 2075, a time in which
this space garbage has become a problem.
Passengers, may we have
your attention please.
Don't you think this subtle
floating sensation is great?
You mean how it's not zero-G,
and not one-G, either?
Yes, ma'am! It feels like I've turned
into a fairy or something!
Fairy, my ass.
More like a devil.
At least make it "cute little imp."
Oh! "Angel" would be
fine, too.
Serves ya right,
you fallen angel!
Senpai, stop laughing at me
and help me up...
Well, I'll let you get
Tanabe squared away.
I have to pop in for a quick visit
to Third Division.
Thank y...
Moron!
What are you, a kid?
Don't tease me like that!
You're the one who's a kid!
Look at you, making such a big deal out of this!
Big talk from a guy who made all those
red circles in his guide book!
The level we're on now has various companies
and government administration buildings.
The Lunar Flying Squirrels
Shopping centers and residential areas
are below that.
In otherwords, the upper crust are up top,
and the lower classes live below.
Speaking of which, where's
the place you're renting?
Well, the Chief rented it for me,
so I don't...
Here it is!
Arnould Area, 3-14. Room 4.
In that case, I'll walk you partway there.
We're headed in the same direction.
You're renting a place in
Arnould Area, too, Senpai?
No, I have an appointment
at the Grand Hotel. It's nearby.
The Chief asked me
to deliver this.
Aren't we early? We still have
more than two hours.
It takes a while
to get dressed.
Besides, I want to have some time
to unwind after that.
Welcome to the hotel.
Thanks.
We have a reservation under "Sullivan."
Ah, Sullivan-sama.
We've been expecting you.
I'll see to your luggage.
You don't need to go to all that trouble.
I'd like to get changed first.
Of course.
This boy hardly seems like the formal weartype.
I'm Carmichael, Second Division.
I'm here about the end-of-month balance
sheet for the Graveyard Orbit.
Fee!
You transferred here?
I just couldn't keep up with
those lifetime workers.
For a guy from a small
company like me, the numbers and responsibility
were too much to handle.
What's Dolf up to
these days?
He's still a man
who lives for his job.
That man
is amazing.
He's doing so well
for himself.
He's even a department manager
at a big company like Technora.
Rumor has it that he's in line for
the board of directors, too, right?
I wouldn't know. I don't really
keep up with the gossip.
That man is something else. He always
was amazing, even in the old days.
The two of us are like
night and day...
Say, why don't we get some dinner or
something? We can talk about old times.
You bitch! You brought a man home
while I was away again, didn't you?!
If you don't like it, try
being at home for once!
What did you say?!
Shut up,
you deadbeat!
Well, here we are.
Welcome to your new home.
See ya.
You're leaving already?!
I told you, I have to be
at the hotel by four.
See, what did I tell you?
The place is perfectly normal.
Since you've already come this far, walk me
the rest of the way to my room, okay?
You have plenty of time
before 4 o'clock, so...
S-See? There's something
weird about this place!
Don't let it get to you, It's just
a strange door chime, that's all.
What about
those, then?!
Ninja... caltrops?
Exactly right!
Your eyes are indeed sharp,
my good visitors!
First, allow me to offer you
my compliments.
Um, Tanabe?
What's that look like to you?
What do you mean?
What else could he be but a ninja?
Hark and attend
my words!
I am a Koga ninja.
I am known
as Kogenta of the Mist.
Hey, you hear that?
He says so, too!
It wasn't ninjas who used to say
"Hark and attend my words"...
Iga cross attack!
Senpai! He's the real thing!
Yeah, a real head case.
Let's get outta here!
You gotta be
kidding me!
Good for you, Tanabe!
Looks like you've got some fun neighbors!
What makes you
say that?!
Well, I'll let you
get acquainted!
How can you be so
irresponsible, Senpai?!
Ninpo Wall-walking Technique!
Another weirdo showed up!
This way!
There is no escape
from us!
Have a taste of the astonishing
Human Throwing Star!
Iron cudgel!
Finishing move!
Flying Fans!
Hup hup hup hup!
Pretend you don't
see him!
Come forth,
Gamagoemon!
Ignore him, ignore him!
That's strange, it looks like
some of them aren't ninjas!
Seeing ninjas running around in
the first place is what's strange!
Huh? What was that?
I'm talking about Tanabe's apartment!
You rented it out, didn't you?!
That's right.
It came highly recommended for Japanese people.
Recommended, my ass!
It told you it's at 4:00 today, right, Hachi?
It's already 3:30 over there.
I've got bigger things
to worry about!
But I've already spoken
to the other party, and...
Look, I'm trying to
tell you that...
Ninpo, Flying Phonebox
Technique!
No way!
Hoshino-san sure is late...
They said that he would be arriving
on the moon today, so it's possible that
his flight was delayed.
Another water over here,
please!
Damn it, I need to be
at the hotel by four!
Transcendent ninpo!
Tossing in Agony Technique!
Yokozuna, banzai!
What the hell are
you people thinking?!
Roast pork noodles!
Give it a rest,
you lunatics!
Wind demon,
closed gammadion!
Tamaya!
Bravo!
Rally ho!
Huh? That man
is gone!
Where has he
disappeared to?!
Behind us!
Senpai!
I've had about enough
of you guys!
Secret arts!
The white rabbit!
Of!
I-n-a-b-a!
I'm outta here,
Tanabe.
Aw, man!
You little...
You got us!
Truly, the way of the warrior
is to be found in death...
But aren't the people in
Debris Section a little rowdy?
He may not look it, but ever since Hachi met
that new girl, Tanabe, he's really settled down.
Flying butterfly!
Impertinent swine!
Fight us...
...fair and square!
Flying monkey!
Ready... fight!
Ribbit!
Senpai!
Wait for me!
Um...
Backwards pivot throw!
He's still fighting?
In that case, I'll use
my black magic to...
Wait, wait!
It's my turn next!
Hey, would this be a good time
to use my smoke bombs?
No, let's try out
the Ninja Mandala!
Secret arts!
Giant Rolling Ball!
That's some serious ninpo!
Show us, show us!
Senpai, what the heck
are you thinking?!
Huh?
Senpai!
Say something, Senpai!
A one and a two
and a heave-ho!
Senpai!
Are you alive?
We're sorry.
The landlord said that
a Japanese person was coming...
I guess we got a little
too enthusiastic.
Plus, you were wearing the
hachimaki headband of a ninja.
We wanted a real, live Japanese
person to see our moves.
What did you think
of our ninpo?
Everybody in Japan
has a black belt, right?
Once you reach the upper ninja ranks,
you get to marry a geisha girl, right?
Where did you people
learn this garbage?
Miss Kunoichi.
We bid you welcome to
Maison de Yashiki.
You're living there, right?
I'm Crimson Ukon, room 3.
My real name is Macleod.
Gennojo the Missionary. Room 3.
Sanji the Monkey. Room 3.
Jiraiya of Hida. Room 3.
Dragon Chung! Room 3!
You all live
in room 3?
Hey!
You snuck in here again,
didn't you?!
We're sorry!
Thanks for the work
the other day!
Feel free to
call on us again!
I have all the people I need!
Oh, you do?
Sorry!
Sorry to bother you!
We helped out on a construction
job there a while ago.
We can use ninja ninpo techniques, right?
That's why they came to us.
Hey, you! You better do something
about your cleaning bill!
We're sorry, Onee-san.
We'll pay you next month for sure.
If you don't pay up, you're not getting back
the clothes you left here!
Have a heart! I have another
job interview tomorrow!
You'll just get turned down again, right?
Suit or no suit, it'll end the same way!
So you can just go there
dressed in that getup!
Playing ninja again,
are we?
Hurry up and
get a job!
This is an announcement from the municipal
offices of Mare Tranquilitatis City.
Beginning at 2100 hours today,
there will be...
I'm sorry I'm so late.
Oh, right. I have something
from my section chief.
Here.
Oh, my! This is a "get-acquainted gift"
from Hoshino-san!
Open it, open it!
Um, I wasn't
the one who...
It's beautiful!
Thank you so much!
Um, I didn't...
Hoshino-san,
this is Citta Sullivan-san.
Uh...
She came all the way to the moon with
her father when he was transferred here.
You seldom see such devotion
in children these days, do you?
Right...
This is Hoshino Hachirota-san.
He works for Technora.
My, that's a large company.
I bet you have a steady income.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Hoshino-kun.
Now, then, we should give these two
youngsters some time to themselves!
Wha...? Hey!
Do you like roses?
Now that you mention it, I hear that they have...
a Chinese-style garden on the first floor.
Wait, l...
I love everything
about Japan.
Huh?
Look, I think
there's been a...
I'm sorry, I'll only
be a minute.
Hey, uh...
What's going on?
Honestly, thank you for finding
such an excellent match!
Think nothing of it. Your daughter
is quite lovely, after all.
Those two are just
getting started!
I'm gonna make
this one work!
You really do all live
here in room 3, huh?
It's embarrassing to say it,
but we're all unemployed.
Oh...
We don't have jobs, so we
have a lot of spare time.
That's how we ended up getting
hooked on ninja movies.
The gravity is 1/6 G, so you
can do ninpo techniques here!
Oh! We did have jobs
at first, though.
We were brought here by a businessman who
asked us if we wanted helium-3 extraction jobs.
He said the money
would be good.
To make a long story short,
we left home to find work.
And that's what brought you
to the moon...
My wife and I had just had
our third baby...
My business had gone belly up.
I had put up collateral for a friend.
I needed the money.
I had such big dreams...
But the businessman I told you about
skipped town with our pay.
We took the fall for it,
and they fired us.
Then you should look
for new ones!
Like ilmenite mining
or working the drydocks!
But you need worker visas
to get a job, right?
We came here on tourist visas.
It was our own fault for letting that
businessman handle our visas, too...
We don't have the money
to go back to Earth...
We manage to keep ourselves fed
by taking odd jobs...
Note: 'kunoichi' means female ninja.
H-Hey, having a kunoichi here really
brightens things up, doesn't it?
Yeah, kunoichis
are the best.
It's dull with nobody
but guys around.
A name! We have to think of
a name for Tanabe-san!
Let's make it something flowery
this time!
Like Shirogane or Kocho.
"This time"?
Yeah! We used to...
My wife used to act
as our kunoichi.
No, I suppose she isn't
my wife anymore...
She left me.
I can't say
that I blame her.
After all, I can't even support
the woman I love.
An emergency has been declared
in Level E, West Sector 4.
A police car?
Isn't that an ambulance?
An evacuation advisory has been issued
forthe East and North sectors.
No, it's the fire department train.
Stand back!
It's dangerous!
Hey, do something about
those onlookers!
They're verifying IDs
over at the tent!
Clear the way!
Father?
Are you all right?
My daughter's divorce with you went through.
You have no business calling me "Father" now.
You promised that you'd reconsider
if I found a job, though, right?
I set up a
marriage meeting!
I did it to make sure that she wouldn't get
involved with another piece of trash like you!
A marriage meeting?!
She could've been happy if she hadn't
married the likes of you!
Then we wouldn't have had
a marriage meeting at this hotel!
Wait... Are you telling me
that she's still in there?!
You lowlife!
You and your toys!
What good are you and your ninpo if they
can't even make one girl happy?!
You! You! You pauper! You screwup!
You nobody! You loafer!
Chieftain...
You've got no money,
no social standing, and no job, and on top of all that,
you think you're a ninja?!
You think you can call yourself
a husband?!
You lowlife! Lowlife! Lowlife!
He has love!
Even if he's a ninja,
even if he's got no money, if he's got love,
it'll work out in the end!
No matter what kind of social standing or
fortune you've got, if you don't have love, you're a failure
as a husband!
Who in the world
are you?
If you've got love, even the ends
of a loaf of bread are a feast!
Even if she has
fancy dresses, it won't make her happy if a man she loves doesn't see her in them!
Chieftain...?
I can do this
on my own.
We aren't lowlifes,
are we?
Two kunoichis are better
than one, right?
Let's go show 'em!
Let's show 'em
what ninpo can do!
You bunch of fools.
Why won't you understand!
Say something, Chieftain!
Huh?
Darn it, who the heck
cut the power?!
I found this
in the kitchen!
Hurry! Hurry!
Let's go. The place is already
filling up with smoke.
Level E Control Room calling
all police cars on patrol...
Full point!
Quarter point!
Eighth point!
Half point!
Out of bounds!
Foul!
Chieftain, this way's no good.
Let's look for another stairway.
Let's follow
his lead!
Yeah!
The scene of the fire is adjacent
to the redevelopment area,
Oh, wow!
Looks like that hotel had
second-rate firefighting equipment.
...and with the upcoming maintenance work, the
advance of emergency vehicles is hampered...
Forget it! The smoke would overpower us
before we could get through!
But there's smoke everywhere!
There's nowhere to go!
What is it?
Back to the kitchen!
Point!
Face strike!
Veranda!
Sliding door!
Bamboo screens!
My daughter! My daughter
hasn't come down yet!
Other ninjas!
Clear the way, please!
Clear the way!
Chieftain!
I'm all right...
I inhaled a little smoke, that's all.
The way back is blocked
with smoke, too...
Is this... Is this
the end for us?
That's hot!
O-rin!
O-rin, is that you?!
Kogenta?!
Huh? The ninjas?
What're you doing here?
Hachimaki-san?
You saved my wife?
No, we have these
to thank.
A solution of
calcium peroxide.
Basically, if we add it to the fertilized water
for the plants here, it generates oxygen.
We were lucky that they also had some
ceramic pots for their microwave, too.
Now that you mention it, Ai-chan did mention
that you were astronauts...
Oh, I get it! They're like
homemade spacesuits.
All we need to do now is head back
the way you came in, and we should be able
to get out of here.
We can't. The way back is...
We can't go back that way now.
So you're saying that there's
nowhere to run?!
What did you come
here for, then?!
No, we'll be fine!
Nothing is impossible for a ninja!
You people are professionals, aren't you?!
Get in there and save my daughter!
Give me your suit!
I'll go in, too!
We!
Are!
The Ninja Eight!
Ninjas...?
You're kidding!
Even at 1/6 G, it's still...
They wouldn't!
Wind, woods,
fire, mountain!
The Reforms of
the Taika Era!
Chinese royal
full-course banquet!
Don't do it!
Ultimate secret technique!
Mist ninpo! Form cosmic
flying squirrel!
You've gotta be
kidding me...
Even at 1/6 G,
they're still gonna...
Ninjas!
Ninjas?
Did he say ninjas?
It's ninjas!
Ninjas?
Ninja!
Boy, landings sure are tough,
aren't they?
Yeah, your weight hits you all
at once when you touch down...
What the hell is going on here?! Well?!
If I had told you it was a marriage meeting,
would you have agreed to go, Hachi?
Of course not! As if
I'd ever get married!
Are you saying that my daughter's
not good enough for you?!
Father, I'll make her happy,
so you don't have to worry!
Get it straight!
We're divorced!
And a real ninja name
is something like "Saizou!"
What kind of name
is "Kogenta"?!
Chief, how many months is the lease
on my apartment for?
When are you gonna
move in, Ai-chan?
For now,
it's for two years.
The deposit would've gone
to waste, otherwise.
How about "Shooting Star Ai"?
Come on, I'm not
your kunoichi.
Do you have a paring knife
or something?
I have a throwing knife,
if that'll work.
Hey, they said that those
aren't allowed in here!
He's treating my daughter like dirt
just because she's a divorcee!
Hoshino-san makes her 49th Space Marriage Meeting.
The next one will be 50 even!
Let's do it next time!
O-rin-chan~
Go away!
Ninpo Flying Pillow!
Ninpo Flying Pillow Catch!
Ninpo Flying Pillow Return Technique!
It's a bitter pillow
to swallow!
Go pop a pillow!
Here we go again...
Ninpo is hereby
forbidden!
It's banned!
Next Time
Extraterrestrial Girl
What's this?
A get-well gift. It's an apple.
We humans can't live
away from the Earth.
That's just the way it is
right now.
I sure would like to see
your ocean, Hachimaki!
I swear, kids nowadays
aren't worth their salt.
With just two people, it takes
forever to finish a game.
Don't you dare force me
to retire, you hear?!
What do you think, Hachimaki?
This is my sea!