Here we go...
Tanabe, try lowering it a little bit
on your side.
How's this?
No, give it some more.
See? That side strut is caught...
It's slipping!
Chief, hang in there!
Yuri-san! Are you okay?
Yes, I think so...
Are you sure we shouldn't
break it down any further?
If we strip it down any further, we won't
be able to put it back together again.
Why the heck is this thing bigger
than the door, anyway?
This is hopeless!
Let's just forget about it!
We're gonna be on the moon
for at least a month.
You expect me to go without
a smoke for that long?
No, I just thought...
Sure, why not?
Excuse me?
It'll be good for your health. And besides,
air is a precious commodity in space.
Y-Young master Colin?!
You're going to the moon to clear debris, right?
I'm going to be tagging along.
Um, you're...
The moron son of the INTO chairman.
Fee-kun! Watch your language!
This place hasn't changed
one bit.
Did you get into trouble again?
You can't always rely on your father to...
No, no. I'm here on the job
this time.
I graduated from college
a while ago.
I work for the INTO Development
Inspector's Office now.
Thanks to my dad's connections,
of course.
Tandem Mirror
Welcome aboard
the Von Braun.
For third round
of testing,
...you will be learning the Von Braun
inside and out for the next six months.
It is for that reason that I have given
each of you a Level 6 keycard.
It will open 94% of the doors
on the ship.
Incidentally, the highest card level, Level 8,
...are in the possession of only myself
and a handful of others.
If you pass the test and are chosen to be
official members of the crew member,
...that is when I will be able
to give you a Level 8 card.
Each of these six centrifugal crew blocks
has an independent control room.
Also, the Von Braun is designed
with a six-column, axisymmetric layout,
...and is pressurized from the central control
room at her bow to the shield disk at her stern.
Passing through this area, we find our tanks
of deuterium and helium 3 reaction masses,
...as well as our refrigerated
propellant tanks,
...coming at last to the very heart
of the Von Braun.
Yes, the tandem mirror nuclear fusion engine,
the most powerful propulsion device ever built.
We're still testing the magnetic field units,
so the reactor chamber is pressurized.
Your lives will be in the hands of this part,
so it seems most fitting,
...as well as safest from a security standpoint,
that you should be ones to conduct those tests.
Once online, this system will generate plasma,
radiation, and a powerful magnetic field,
...making this a world of death that no human,
much less any living organism, can get near.
We're finally here...
Yeah...
In other words, after the
chamber is depressurized,
...you won't have another chance
to actually touch it.
I'd like you to exercise the utmost
caution during your work...
I made it here...
so as to avoid a repeat of that unfortunate
incident the other day.
I'm amazed that you're conducting a simple
debris hauler spot inspection, master Colin.
It's just because I'm new.
I have to do a little grunt work.
Yes, of course.
Grunt work is important, too.
Just so long as there isn't too much
grunting involved, of course.
It may be presumptuous
of me,
...but I've assigned some of our flight
attendants to accompany you.
If you need anything at all,
just let them know.
Now this is more like it! I really like
this new division director of yours!
This one sounds like the
reasonable type.
Tanabe,
I have some good news.
This is the number for the test site.
Call here, and they'll page
the test applicants for you.
Apparently, they only give
this out to family members,
...so he said to say that you are his
sister or fiancee when you call.
I'm amazed that you got
your hands on this...
You know that ferret I'm looking after?
I used it as a bargaining chip with its owner.
Thank you, Yuri-san.
Don't worry about it.
I owe you two my life, after all.
You've helped me way more times
than I've helped you.
You're not going to call?
The job comes first. I'll call him
after we reach lunar orbit.
Wouldn't you be better off
sleeping in your bed?
Geez, you again?
That's pretty cold. Is that any way
to greet your best friend?
If you were my best friend, you'd
let me get a good night's sleep.
You can't sleep anyway,
so don't blame me.
What's on your mind? The truth is, you're
having regrets about coming here, aren't you?
You're lost and can't find
your way back home?
If that's all you need, just have
Tanabe reel you back in.
I think she'd make you
a fine wife.
I can't do that.
I already made up my mind.
I'm gonna get onto the Von Braun.
See you again soon.
Yeah...
Come visit
all you want.
Attention, all personnel involved
with the 3rd crew exam.
Individual guidance will
begin tomorrow morning.
Please verify your time schedules
at the information desk.
Sorry that took
so long.
That's all right.
I'm used to waiting.
Attention, all loader workers.
There has been a change to a section
of the makeshift direct loading block.
Those workers whose shift data
has not been revised...
Remember, Nono-chan, you have
a checkup at 2.
Okay!
I'm not very good with mechanical stuff,
so I'm not sure if you'll be in focus.
That's fine. It'll be better if they
can't get a good look at me.
So, shall we get started, Artemis?
It's been a long time, Hachimaki.
I've never been able to forget
that time you punched me.
I guess I've got a
masochistic streak in me.
Um, yeah...
Clifford-sama, your
dinner is ready.
You made sure to give me one
without mustard, right?
Yes, sir. We were
told about that.
Ai-san, I'll talk to ya
later, okay?
Sure.
You know Colin-san?
Yeah, we've met before.
What?
Just so we're clear this time,
I'm issuing a declaration of war.
I'm going after Colin-san,
understand?
I'm not trying for a wage slave this time,
I'm gonna bag the Chairman of INTO!
Colin's his son.
It's the same thing!
He's got money, status, and power!
He's got it all!
I'm gonna make my move
while we're en route to the moon.
The minimum-B mirror coil's
magnetic field control unit...
It wasn't a spaceship that I wanted.
When I touched this thing, I figured that out.
What I wanted was to be on a ship
that was faster, more powerful,
...and could go further
than anything else.
Once I realized that, getting onto this
ship was all I could think about.
Hoshino.
The whole human race isn't behind the
Jupiter project, not by a long shot.
There are opposition movements all over,
and even if the project succeeds,
...only a handful of first-world nations
will reap the benefits.
The minority is about to be overshadowed
and swept aside by this huge project.
Haven't you ever had
any second thoughts?
None at all.
Space is never gonna be developed by guys
who are afraid to put their own dreams first.
Sorry I asked, Hoshino. It was a stupid...
Shut the hell up!
I couldn't stand you from the moment
I first laid eyes on you!
Those two idiots...
Don't they know they're being watched?
The more rivals that get weeded out,
the better it is for us.
Let's ignore 'em.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
You asked for it,
momma's boy!
What, you can't fight
with your bare hands?
All that counts in a fight
is results!
Results, huh?
What the...?
Still feel like
taking me on?
You're never gonna hit me
with that thing!
All right,
you asked for it!
Knock it off!
Don't use dangerous crap
like this in a brawl!
You're gonna bust my ship,
you dumb bastards!
Excuse me. I have the
inspection datalog for you.
I was expecting Ai-san.
She's taking a break right now.
Is my job performance unsatisfactory?
Of course not.
I know that you're a capable girl, Claire-san.
You used to be one of the elite, after all.
Tanabe?
Are you
on the moon?
A lot of debris was generated by the
tandem mirror accident, remember?
They also say that INTO's Supreme Council
will be meeting on the moon, so here we are.
Senpai? You don't look so good.
Are you getting enough sleep?
Are you eating enough?
Don't be such a fussy eater. Make sure
you eat your vegetables, too.
If nobody gets on your case about it,
you don't eat anything but meat.
What do you want?
I've got on-the-job training
this afternoon.
If this isn't important, I'm hanging up.
Wait, don't go!
There's so much that I want to ask you
and talk to you about!
You decided all on your own to quit the
company and to try out for the Von Braun.
I wanted you to tell me about it.
To talk to me about it...
The thing is, l...
It was my decision, wasn't it?
What's the point of talking it over with you?
I have my own life.
And you have your own, right?
How can you...
We have work
to do, people!
We've got a debris retrieval order
from the Third Division.
They want us to collect a piece
of debris that's in lunar orbit.
Pick up debris before
we even get to port?
We've only just arrived, and already
they are treating us badly.
Fee-san, do you read me?
And how may I be of assistance, Inspector Clifford?
We're retrieving some debris, right?
Send out the inspection camera.
I'll be able to make my inspection before
I even reach the moon. What a lucky break!
I copy...
Fee-san...
Sorry, Claire, I'm a little busy.
Could you show me
the retrieval plans?
Sure, I'll put them up
on monitor three.
This wording is something a bureaucrat would
use. This didn't come from Control Section.
These recovery directions
are strange, too.
I swear, Control Section sure can't
find good help these days.
Claire, I can count on the
fingers of one hand...
...the number of Control Section people
who are as good as you were.
Thank you.
Hey. Was that call
from your girlfriend?
No way.
Better be careful. All the phones
on this boat are tapped.
Protecting company
secrets, huh?
They're keeping an eye out for terrorists.
Guys like the Space Defense Front, I guess.
Visual confirmation of target debris.
I'm picking up some magnetic resonance.
My face monitor is a little garbled, but I can manage.
I copy. Tanabe and Yuri, give top priority
to assessing the condition of the debris.
If you sense any danger, return to the ship and
we'll revise the mission based on your data.
You copy?
I copy. Once we do a sweep to determine
its condition, we'll return to the Fishbone.
This looks familiar...
This looks like a section of
the tandem mirror engine.
So this is wreckage
from the blast, huh?
So, there are chunks this big
that are still intact...
That's why we came all the way
to the moon to help.
Was there a part like that on it last time?
Illegal dumping again?
No, it doesn't look like
a dumped part.
Tanabe, get some footage of it
with your camera, too.
I copy.
I wonder what
this is...
It now seems possible that
the recent accident...
...involving the #2 tandem mirror
engine was a deliberate act.
A civilian debris retrieval specialist recovered
a section of the engine yesterday,
...and this debris showed signs of stress
fractures caused by localized overloading.
The Meltdown Investigatory Committee
seems to suspect...
...that the structural collapse caused
by this is what led to the meltdown.
And you were the first
to discover it?
Well, I wouldn't
say "discovered"...
All I really did was follow instructions
and recover some debris.
Tanabe?
I wonder if it was the Space Defense Front.
Those guys have been
quiet lately.
It's possible. Those guys have always
been opposed to the Jupiter project.
It's strange.
If it was them, they should've
made a claim of responsibility.
And I can't picture them leaving that
kind of evidence lying around.
You sure know a lot about
these guys, Hakim.
It's 'cause he used to work at the OSA.
He knows all about this stuff!
So why the hell do you sound
so proud about it?
This retrieval operation by a civilian salvage
crew was recorded from beginning to end...
Nicely done. Just as you planned.
...by an INTO inspector who just
happened to be aboard the ship.
Being too clever
can be a problem.
All footage and detailed data has been given
to the Meltdown Investigatory Committee.
You see things that you're
better off not seeing.
With suspicions having surfaced that
the meltdown was a deliberate act,
Colin-san, are you hungry? There's an
excellent restaurant near here.
...it appears that a detailed examination
will now be carried out,
I know all the good
places on the moon.
...with these records providing the crucial data
that will be the key to the investigation.
Sure, why not? Anyway, it looks like they
won't be showing any more of Ai-san on TV.
Excuse me?
Congratulations on
your TV appearance.
All I did was pick up some debris,
same as always...
Maybe, but you need big press events
like this every once in a while.
It must be boring to do nothing
but pick up trash...
...from the nooks and crannies of space
day after day, isn't it?
I don't think it's
boring at all.
It might not be a flashy job,
but when we pick up debris,
...it helps the cause of space
development, right?
When you look at it that way,
doesn't it make you happy somehow?
If space development
keeps advancing,
...our energy problems will be solved,
and even wars and refugees will...
Do you seriously
believe that?
The only people who will reap the
benefits of space development...
...are a handful of first-world countries
like America or Japan.
The space development that
you're so happy about...
...is causing the gap between rich
and poor nations to widen.
If you're a country that doesn't have
the technology to go up into space,
...all you can do is look up at the first-world
countries as they monopolize space resources.
Well, that's how capitalism
is supposed to work.
And it's those first-world countries that both
produce space debris and have it retrieved.
All we really are is lapdogs
for first-world countries.
How can you say things like that? You're a
member of Debris Section now, too, Claire-san!
I didn't come to Debris Section
by choice.
Maybe, but this is
your job now!
You should have a little more
love and pride in your work!
You and your love again...
Your "love" is shallow and meaningless!
Has this "love" of yours ever saved
even a single person's life?
Don't talk to me about love
if you can't back it up.
Break it up,
you two!
Our work's done
for the day.
Go on. You're dismissed.
In the end, you're just one
of the fortunate few.
Love can't save them.
Not El Tanika, and not Mananga.
Welcome, Hoshino-san.
You live up to your legends
as an engineer.
You've done a magnificent job
of stabilizing my engine.
You're not so bad yourself. That program
update of yours was a fine piece of work.
It ought to be, I spent a whole week
locked in my office writing it.
By the way, all this talk I hear
about the Space Defense Front...
That's all a lie, right?
You're putting me in a bind... I've been told
not to discuss that matter with anyone.
I thought so.
They've even added an emergency shutdown
device, so please leave it at that.
Certain people would rather
that the public believed that.
Anyway, I leave those matters
for the President to handle.
President?
Why did you specifically
have DS-12 do it?
Using them would make it a bigger
news story, don't you agree?
They're the team of super
debris haulers...
...who saved ISPV-7 from a terrorist attack
and found that INTO mine.
They're Technora's
pride and joy.
I'm sure you already understand this, but make
sure that Locksmith keeps his mouth shut.
That accident was caused by
the Space Defense Front.
Deliberations on the Space Peacekeeping
Bill are about to begin, as well.
You don't need to
spell it out for me.
You want to return to the
head office, don't you?
This problem isn't limited to just our company.
You understand that, don't you?
I understand.
Nighttime hours are currently in
effect aboard the Von Braun.
Different security levels are in
effect than during daytime hours,
...so test candidates should exercise
caution while moving about the ship.
Oh, it's you, Hoshino. You startled me.
Sorry about that.
Hey, do you know where
I can reach Gigalt Sensei?
I could find out if I went back to my place
on the moon. Are you in a hurry?
No. It's just that I never told him
that I was quitting Technora.
This is the Administration Center
calling all night shift workers.
Oh.
Forget about it.
Sorry I bothered you.
The formatting of the datalogs that are
required to be submitted during your...
Out of the blue, they tell us to step up
the security level around here.
They're kinda nervous now that they found out
the #2 engine meltdown was really terrorism.
Oh, so that's why they even brought in
that emergency shutdown device earlier?
Level 6 confirmed.
That last meltdown was an accident,
but this one won't be...
Hey, Hakim.
I don't want you doing any
suspicious crap to my ship.
That you, Hoshino?
I have a wire anchor launcher
pointed at you.
These things fire ropes
into ship hulls.
If one of these hits you,
you're dead.
How long have
you known?
There was that brawl in here
a while back, remember?
The Von Braun was in danger,
so why didn't you do anything?
Just because
of that?
No. Ever since we got here,
you've lost your edge.
That intensity that said you were gonna
get accepted, come hell or high water.
All you've got now is a content, philosophical
look in your eye like some kinda monk!
Up until now, I thought that
you and I were the same.
But I guess you're not
like that anymore!
I haven't changed.
My objectives are different now, that's all.
The only reason you fought your way
though all those tests...
...was so you could get your hands
on a Level 6 card?!
Hachimaki, have you ever heard
of a country called Mananga?
It's my homeland.
What's that got to do
with anything?!
It's a barren wasteland.
Crops won't grow properly there.
But even so, we managed to get by because
we could get oil out of the ground...
...up until my grandfather's
generation.
But now...
Hakim! If you come any closer,
I swear I'll shoot!
...all that's left in that utterly desolate wasteland
are crumbling oil fields and pipelines.
Poverty triggered a civil war, and now our
children die before ever reaching adulthood.
And all that the first-world countries will sell
us are antipersonnel mines and small arms.
So what? You expect me to feel
sorry for you and let you go?!
Just like what happened with the moon,
Jupiter's resources...
...will belong to the countries that
lead the pack in space development.
In the end, nothing
will change for us.
I'm warning you!
If you come any closer, I'll shoot, Hakim!
You remember what happened
with Temara Poitier, don't you?
It's not just him.
As you were picking up
your debris,
...you must have seen other people struggling
in the shadow of space development.
Haven't you learned anything? Are you
going to ignore it all and walk away?
Or do you think it's somebody else's problem?
That it's none of your concern?
You have no imagination! You see
the world through rose-colored lenses!
So what's that doing
in your hands?!
Don't push me, Hakim!
I can pull this trigger!
Are you sure about that? Those aren't the
eyes of a man who's capable of killing.
You weren't able to kill
during the second test, either.
In the end, you're just one
of the fortunate few.
Don't talk to me about determination
if you can't back it up.
I can back it up!
Shit! You turned around and
stabbed me in the back!
You think you're the only one
who's miserable in this world?!
I... I am, too!
So am I!
HAKIM!
Son of a bitch!
Next Time
Exposure
73% of the OSA's patrol vessels
are gathered in lunar orbit,
...checking out any satellites and debris
pieces that they come across.
It looks like our recent operation against
ISPV-7 had an effect on them.
The work on Catnip is finished. They say it
can cover all of lunar orbit for 40 minutes.
Don't do anything to raise
their suspicions.
With our inferior numbers, our only chance
of victory is with a sneak attack.