Abandoned artificial satellites.
Tanks jettisoned from shuttles.
Debris generated during
space station construction.
This vast amount of junk floating in space,
space debris, is a very serious threat.
This is a story of 2075, a time in which
this space garbage has become a problem.
Go for taking free, roger.
Main umbilical, separate.
Separation complete.
You copy?
I copy.
Taking free.
DS-12, this is Seven.
Now establishing link via Navstar.
Datalink confirmed.
We will be making orbital plane change
using ME to reach transfer orbit,
...so we will separate using OMS
until we reach changeover point.
Please verify vector
and window datalinks.
DS-12, this is Seven.
Downlink of vector and window to navigation matrix complete.
You two have a fight?
I copy. Will make de-orbit burn
five minutes from my mark... Mark.
So, did you and Hachimaki
have a fight?
No, of course not!
Nothing really happened...
Really?
Man, not these
rations again...
That reminds me, Yuri.
I was talking
to Tomord a while ago...
He says you're always down
in Records Section...
Excuse me?
Um, forget it.
It's no big deal.
Oh, it isn't? Sorry.
You stare out the window and
zone out sometimes, Yuri.
Do you see something
out there?
Yes. I see space.
Just space?
Yes. There is nothing else.
The air conditioner?
Crap! It stopped again!
C'mon, show a little spirit,
damn it!
Hoshino-san! Are you all right?
Ow...
It stopped again!
Son of a...
Keep working,
you bastard!
If you don't circulate the air,
we suffocate!
Hang in there, you piece of junk!
Work! Work, damn it!
A Sky of Stardust
Thank you.
Sign here, please.
You understand, don't you? This isn't good.
You need to use up all your
paid vacation days.
I'm sorry.
I will try to use them soon.
You say that, but you haven't used
a single day in the past five years!
Oh.
Why don't you
use any?
Come to think of it, you never go
down to Earth or even the moon.
The rest of us can take care of those animals
you look after, so why don't you?
Well, I...
Is it about the debris?
He's right, he's right! Use your vacation days,
I don't care if it's on moon or on Seven.
I'm the one that General Affairs
yells at, after all.
The bosses have it in for us as it is!
This came for you.
Thank you.
It makes trouble for me when we
show up on their radar, got it?!
Yuri-kun! Are you listening
to me?!
Yes.
It's a bad idea to use too many
paid vacation days, but not using them
at all is just as...
Carnations?
I forget,
is it Mother's Day?
No, that isn't what they are for. I was thinking
of putting them up inside Toy Box.
Gosh, I wish a certain new employee
would also be that thoughtful.
Hello?
Huh? I copy.
What do you see
in Tanabe?
You told me to ask her if she
had a boyfriend, remember?
So, she's available, then?
Yeah, but I can't say that I understand
your taste in women.
I like how she's completely
straightforward.
Even if there's a brick wall
in front of her?
That girl has enough power
to smash through it.
That's what
drives me nuts.
She thinks that love can fix anything
and everything. It's embarrassing, I tell ya.
When you've lived for twenty years, you oughta
know how to bend a bit or make compromises.
Huh?
What?
Nothing. Now that I mention it,
she's been acting kinda strange lately.
She hasn't been herself.
I did it!
I broke ten minutes!
I can do it in under
ten minutes now, Gigalt-san...
Gigalt-san!
Were you hurt in the fight?!
No, I'm okay...
I wasn't hurt.
But...
It's cancer.
It's already progressed
too far to be treatable.
So I want you to keep this to yourself.
Don't tell him.
Here. This is complete
up through yesterday.
Thank you for all
your help, Tomord-san.
Don't mention it. You're always
looking after Pople for me.
This is a big help.
It's not like it's a company secret.
Well, see you later.
I should leave this in the usual
place once I'm done, then?
Sure.
Man... There's a lot more out here
than I thought.
We should be thankful that so much
has collected in one spot, shouldn't we?
You're a mature guy,
you know that, Yuri?
Tanabe, bring the Fishbone around.
Tanabe.
Tanabe!
Coming!
Um, Senpai...
Yeah, what?
Forget it.
I... I guess it's nothing.
What's gotten into you?
Anyway, be careful with your thruster bursts.
The exhaust will scatter the debris.
I copy.
And don't forget the sun's position.
Gigalt-sensei told us that, remember?
What the hell are you doing?!
Be careful!
Oh, crap!
Hoshino-san!
Senpai!
You dumb bitch!
Where the hell was your head
out there?!
You could've killed me!
I'm sorry...
Today isn't the first time, either!
You've been acting weird lately!
You keep spacing out!
I'm sorry...
Apologizing ain't gonna
make this right!
An office lady being sloppy
down on Earth is one thing,
...but up here in space,
it gets people killed!
Do you get that?!
I'm sorry.
What's with you?
Is that all you can say?
Hoshino-san, I think you
have made your point.
Stay out of this, Yuri.
She's supposed to be my partner.
Yes, but...
Of all the stupid...
What's going on, you got boys on the brain
even when you're on the job?
I do not!
It's not like that at all!
I was worried that you might...
That I'd what?
Fine, suit yourself.
If your heart isn't in it, get married or whatever
and go back down to Earth.
Who's in here?
Yuri-san?
Oh, it's you, Tanabe-san.
What are you doing here
at this hour?
I had forgotten
to put these up.
Oh, one of the carnations
from this morning...
What about you, Tanabe-san?
Were you practicing?
No, I'm just hiding...
Damn it, I can't believe
how late we are...
It ain't like we're getting overtime for this.
I can't believe that twerp Tanabe!
Look, don't you think you're
being a little rough on her?
We're debris haulers, right?
You know as well as I do that even a little
lapse in focus can get people killed.
As her senpai, I'm...
If it were only that,
I wouldn't say anything.
What're you so worked up about?
Lashing out at everybody is pretty pathetic.
I'm just...
Give a little consideration
to how she feels.
Tanabe's been practicing in secret
aboard Toy Box a lot lately.
Yuri-san, what's it feel like when you
lose someone important to you?
Someone who's really important
and you look up to.
But if you were to suddenly
lose that person...
...nobody can take
his place.
No one else will do.
Say that you're going to lose
a person like that...
And you won't even be able
to say goodbye properly.
So I want to tell
this other person about it.
But I don't want to betray the person
that told me not to say anything, so I...
I don't know what
I ought to do.
Carrying around secrets
is a difficult thing, isn't it?
So, that is what has
been bothering you.
Yes, sir.
When you lose
someone you love,
...there's no sadness,
and there's no grief.
You don't feel
anything at all.
You don't think about it.
It isn't good to think about it too much.
You eventually have to say goodbye
to everyone you meet.
The only difference is whether that time
will come sooner or later.
But...
If you don't think that way,
it's hurts too much.
All right! All right!
All right!
Okay!
Hey, you put Toy Box
in Bay Four, right?
Yeah.
You forget something?
What's with him?
How about an answer, huh?
Hey...
Thanks for everything.
It is best not to
overthink things.
Yeah. I think I can
deal with...
Senpai?
Hoshino-san?
Oh, you were getting
lessons from him?
I came here to put up
some flowers, that's all.
I bumped into Tanabe-san.
Hey, it doesn't matter
to me.
I don't really have the temperament
to teach people stuff, anyway.
That's not true at all.
You're a fine teacher.
Much better than me.
Gosh, you know all
about me, don't you?
But I don't know you at all, do I, Yuri?
Even after working with you for three years.
What's with all this cloak
and dagger stuff?
Um... Senpai?
I heard something from that guy over in
Records. I was gonna ask you about it today.
He says you've been looking for something
week in and week out.
You could've asked me to help, you know?!
I thought we were teammates!
Why the hell are you
hiding stuff from me?
You don't have to sneak around
behind my back, Yuri...
Hey...
Good morning.
Say, Edel...
If you're looking for Tanabe-san,
she's already done the cleaning and left to fix the
ship's air conditioner.
I don't really care
where she is.
Yuri-san is down in
Records Section.
Did I ask where
they were?
What is it, then?
Well, um...
Where'd that flower
come from?
Yuri-san gave it to me. He said there was a clerical
error and he got one extra shipment.
You sure that isn't an excuse?
Maybe he
planned on giving them to you all along.
I don't think so.
In the language of flowers, white carnations
mean "My love still endures."
You sure know
a lot, Edel.
Thank you.
Who's that?
He's in Half Section. You know, the guy
who looks after people's animals.
What's he doing, looking up
veterinary material or something?
Says he's looking through debris
found by other companies.
For somebody in Half Section,
he's a real go-getter.
I don't think that's why
he's doing it, either.
Thank for you choosing to fly
with Oberth Aerospace today.
A compass? Why would you
go and buy one of those?
Oh, leave me alone.
It's a good-luck charm.
I don't think there's anything
wrong with it.
There's no up or down
in space,
...so they say that what astronauts want more
than anything is to know their bearings.
So that's why they keep
things like this for good luck.
Hey, you wrote something
inside the lid.
No peeking!
Why not?
I think every marriage needs a secret or two.
Besides, it's a good-luck charm.
Good luck, huh?
Still, it is rare to see someone who is afraid
of suborbital airliners in this day and age.
Lay off.
Where are you going?
You scared to be by yourself?
I'm getting some coffee, that's all.
Hey...!
Come on, don't look at me like that.
I'm not going anywhere.
You need to understand
all the trouble I go to, Ai-chan.
It's hard to find suitable prospects
for marriage meetings.
I can certainly understand parents
wanting to see their daughter married off while she's
still in her twenties.
They say that her younger sister got
married and had kids a long time ago.
But I don't know many men who are the
right age. Or even single men, for that matter.
It wasn't all that long ago when I got an earful
from Ha-chan for recommending a divorcee.
H-Hey! Behave yourself!
And Yu-chan used to
be married, so...
Huh? Yuri-san used
to be married?
You remember that accident a few years ago
where debris hit that suborbital liner, right?
The Alnair-8 accident?
Right, right. Yu-chan told me he was
on board that flight. With his wife.
The cabin was torn
to pieces.
Yu-chan was in the rear of the plane at the time,
so he survived, but his wife was never found.
Oh! I didn't find this out
by snooping!
The girl's family told me! They said
that their daughter was all for it,
...but they mentioned that they would prefer
a man who had never been married.
What the hell...?
You didn't have to hide it from us.
These are all of the personal effects
that we've recovered so far.
If you don't see your wife's belongings here,
then I'm afraid they haven't been found yet.
A compass...
Have you seen one here?
A compass.
Sir?
Never mind.
It's not important.
Um... Senpai?
We're all done over here.
Oh. That was quick.
Guys? Come back
inside for now.
I'm picking up a cluster of micro debris on
an intersecting orbit, and it's closing in.
Angle of intersection, 71... 72 degrees.
If you stay out there, it might hit you.
You copy?
I copy.
Returning to base.
We'll just have to come
back again later.
Tanabe, we're doubling back.
I copy.
What a pain. Now we will have
to come back and start over.
Senpai?
Yeah?
Yuri-san's wife was never recovered,
was she?
Yeah...
You don't suppose that the reason
he keeps doing this job is to...
Hey, Yuri?
Get clear of there!
Yuri! Do you read me?
Debris is heading your way!
Yuri? Yuri!
Hachi! Go grab Yuri!
He's breaking off!
Huh? Yuri-san?
Damn it, we don't have
time to turn around!
What's wrong, Yuri?!
You heard me, didn't you?!
You're on an intersecting orbit!
Fire your retros
and lower your orbit!
I'll send you the orbit data!
Tell me when you get it!
Oh, no...
He's out of time.
Yuri!
Yuri's hit! We're going in to assist!
Give me his telemetry!
Got it.
Module, heavy damage.
Suit internal pressure... is still good!
Life pack and batteries are still normal.
Comm system, normal.
Heart rate and respiration, unstable?
He's unconscious?!
I'm not letting him
fall to Earth!
Tanabe!
You ready over there?!
I-I copy!
Altitude, zero-three. Zero-two.
Zero-one.
He just breached the
atmospheric effects boundary!
Wait for us, Yuri...
We're teammates, aren't we?
Altitude, 120 kilometers...
We're falling into
the atmosphere!
Wake up, Yuri!
Someone is calling me...
It's warm...
I forget, where am I?
Um...
Hey, don't look at me like that.
I'm not going anywhere.
Not this time.
Yuri!
Give me your hand! Hurry!
I have him!
Way to go!
Fee, plot us a breakaway orbit!
I copy!
Yuri-san! Are you all right?!
Yuri-san!
We're losing speed due to friction!
Angle, 5.5 degrees! Output at maximum!
Hachi! I've got an ascent orbit for you!
You just need to...
Damn! Fee?
Senpai!
All right, fine!
We'll muscle our way up,
damn it!
Please save Yuri...
C'mon, you son
of a bitch!
Can you see him
from there?
Yeah.
We sure were in a cold sweat
out there, huh?
If Fee-san hadn't grabbed us with the arm, we
wouldn't have been doing much of anything.
I always thought of Yuri
as kinda standoffish.
But now...
But now?
Yuri may be our
teammate and all,
...but maybe there are some things he doesn't
want us to know because we're his teammates.
Right.
It's kind of sad, though, He can only lay out
a single flower for his wife's burial.
I want to leave a bouquet out there, too.
But considering our job... You know?
He's worked his butt off
to bring in debris over the years.
I guess we can overlook
one artificial flower.
Mission complete.
Returning to base.
Next Time
Boundary Line
But what about Diaper Man?
Wha...?
Um... If you don't mind, could
I trouble you for that butter?
What a strange spacesuit.
I think even I could
fit into this one!
Would you like to have dinner
with me at Starney's?
Love beams, huh?
Zap!
Somebody help me! I'm stuck!