Abandoned artificial satellites.
Tanks jettisoned from shuttles.
Refuse generated during
space station construction.
This junk, space debris, is traveling around
the Earth at speeds approaching 8 kilometers per second.
Should this debris collide with a spacecraft,
it could result in a terrible accident.
For this reason, mankind has been confronted
by the necessity of collecting this debris.
This is a story of 2075, a time in which
this space garbage has become a problem.
Fly Me to the Moon
Day One
I have confirmation here, too.
You are passing through
the outer Van Allen belt on a...
We hardly ever get vacations!
Yuri should've come, too!
Don't foist your own interests
off onto other people.
Yeah, yeah...
Wow, I can't wait!
The moon!
You're allowed to take pictures
at Apollo Memorial Park, right?
I hear that there's a statue
of Commander Armstrong there.
What are you, a tourist
or something?
I guess I can't blame her.
It's her first moon trip, after all.
Still, that's no excuse for...
Wow, a commemorative medal!
I-I'm so sorry!
I'm not used
to zero-G yet...
Until you are, it's a lot easier
if you move along the walls.
I'm so sorry!
Gee, he reminds me
of someone I know...
He reminds me of somebody, too.
Say, from three years ago?
I guess everybody's got a past,
huh, Senpai?
Excuse me, I'd like one of those
commemorative medals, please.
Of course.
Thank you.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Huh? Where did l...
It looks like I left my wallet in my cabin.
For the love of...
We thank you for choosing
to fly with us.
I am your captain, Kenji Impadi.
We have cleared the Van Allen belt,
and will now begin normal cruising.
Excuse me, I heard that the way you use the
restroom is different when the ship is underway.
We will do all we can to make our four-day
flight to the moon a safe one,
...and we look forward
to our time with you.
It's frustrating, that's all!
Our factory was in business for three generations!
We could hold our heads high, no matter
where we sent our products, so why...?!
What else
could we do?!
We can't get the gasoline we need
to run our equipment anymore!
Even if we could, it would
add too much to our costs!
The only people who would
lend money to people like us to buy new machinery
are those thugs.
Those people won't chase us
all this way, will they?
No...
Who was it who discovered resources
out here in space, anyway?
That's why we decided
to die in space.
It'll be easier on Sia that way.
You're right.
She loves space,
doesn't she?
No!
There's no escape for you,
little lady!
See, I've already
caught you!
You jerk!
What the hell
do you think you're doing?!
Cut! Cut!
You moron! This is supposed
to be a closed set!
I-I'm sorry, Director...
"Director"?
This is a shoot.
We're making a movie.
A movie?
Uh, you are?
Hey, pull yourself together!
It's useless, Director,
he's out cold!
Suck it up!
We've still got scenes to shoot!
Well, if you didn't leave it
in your cabin...
I guess I must have dropped
my wallet in the lounge, then...
I hope some kind soul finds it
and turns it in for you.
What am I gonna do...?
Excuse me, has anyone turned in
a wallet to the lost and found?
A wallet, miss? In that case,
please give me your ID number...
I can't see anything
at all!
That's strange...
It doesn't have a lens cap,
so it can't be that...
Maybe it's not focused...
Or maybe it's broken.
You're kidding!
I see something!
Yay, it's the moon!
It's the moon!
These cost money.
T-Thank you.
Are you on vacation?
Yes.
Yes, sort of...
Oh, let me repay you...
That's okay,
don't worry about it.
"That's okay,
don't worry about it!"
I'm sorry,
I'll pay you back!
Still, if we haven't found it here,
either, that must mean...
Do you really think
it was stolen?
Well, not everybody in the universe
is a sweetheart, you know?
And what the heck
is keeping Hachimaki?
Hey, you're right!
I think he said he was going
to look around the cargo area or something.
I guess we'd better go
look over there, then.
Right.
Bye, then.
Thank you.
Bye bye!
How many days will it be 'til we
get to the moon? I can't wait...!
You want me
to take his place?!
What choice do we have?
We can't keep filming with him like that!
Maybe so, but still...
We'll use CG to turn your face
into a wolf's, so don't worry.
Yeah, but I've never
acted in anything before.
What's that got to do with anything?
To play a werewolf, you just need to go by instinct!
Right, go by instinct.
Instinct for what?
Okay! Space Wolf Goes to the Moon!
Scene 7, take 18!
And... action!
Hey, you're as stiff as a board, buddy!
Relax, relax!
You're an animal!
You're turning into a lone wolf!
That's right, you're a hungry beast!
And right there in front of you
is a tasty little bunny!
Mmm, delicious!
You can't hold yourself back anymore!
A nice, cute,
first-rate dinner!
If you don't catch her quickly,
she'll get away!
Nice one!
No! Save me!
No!
What do you think
you're doing?!
I knew you were rude and violent, but I didn't
think you were capable of this, Senpai!
Cut! Cut!
Don't jump to conclusions, damn it!
They're shooting a movie!
I'm sorry, our leading man got hurt,
so I asked him to fill in.
See?
I-I'm so sorry!
I just assumed...
You assumed what?
Gee, a movie, huh?
Yeah.
Do you have
a movie permit?
Gimme back
my camera!
Wow, you'll never get permission
for something like this...
That puts food on our tables!
I'm so sorry we interfered
with your "art."
Tanabe, call security
and let them know about this.
The nice lady there
is a Technora employee.
Senpai, so are we...
We'll look after your equipment
until we reach the moon. Good day.
We're really sorry
about that.
They took all
our equipment...
What are we
gonna do now?
Don't worry about it. Being a pro means
always planning ahead for the worst.
Day Two
If you'd been paying attention,
this wouldn't have happened!
You're one to talk!
You weren't watching her, either!
Knowing her, I was positive that she'd be
looking out at space with that telescope again...
Where do you suppose
she went...?
Say...
What if... What if this is a sign
that we shouldn't take her with us?
It's a little late to be saying that,
don't you think?!
We talked this over and over
before deciding to do this, remember?
I know, but...
Those people have even extorted money
from our relatives and friends...
Who are you saying that we
could've left Sia with?!
You're right...
Anyway, it would be cruel
to leave her all alone, wouldn't it?
Fanny...
I hate space...!
Oh, hello!
Thank you
for yesterday.
You know them?
Yes, a little.
Um...
Have you seen our daughter Shia around?
You can't find her?
No...
Then we'll help you
look for her!
Geez, you're always saying you'll do stuff
without thinking it through!
As I recall, you were standing in during
that movie shoot, right, Senpai?
Things just turned out
that way.
I don't see her anywhere...
Sia!
Where are you?
I-I'm sorry!
Hey, watch it!
I'm really sorry.
Sia!
Sia, where are you?!
Spaceships, spaceships,
look at all the spaceships...!
They're so fun, they're so fun,
all my little spaceships!
In the rescue ball depot?
Right. Don't you think that's the perfect
place to play hide-and-seek in?
Hide and seek, huh?
She's here?
Found her!
Hello there!
Onee-chan!
What'cha doing?
I'm riding
in my spaceship!
This isn't yours, kid.
And anyway, it isn't a spaceship.
Sure, it is!
I even gave it a name!
Wow, really?
What do you call it?
Um... She's the Caroline!
That's a cute name.
Would you listen to me? This isn't
a spaceship, it's a rescue ball!
Is not!
It's my spaceship!
Look, kid...
How do you know?
Do you have a spaceship, Onii-chan?
He doesn't have any money,
so he can't buy a spaceship.
A girl with no wallet's got no right
to be talking down to me!
I have one,
I just don't know where it is.
I'm poor, too.
Scary guys keep coming to our house,
saying, "Give us our money!"
I feel sorry for my
mommy and daddy...
Sia!
Daddy! Mommy!
This is where
you've been?
Come on, let's go back
to our cabin.
I'm so sorry for
all the trouble.
That's okay.
Come on, Sia.
Aw, but I wanna play
with them some more...!
We're going back!
Listen Sia, Mommy and Daddy want you
to take some medicine with them.
Why? I don't feel sick
or anything.
We're not taking it because we don't feel well.
We're taking it before we feel bad.
I don't wanna!
I hate medicine!
Don't be such
a baby, Sia.
But I'm not sick!
Mommy and Daddy are going
to take it, too. Okay?
I don't wanna!
I hate bitter stuff!
I said take it,
so just take it!
Hey...!
I-I'm sorry, Sia...
I didn't mean to shout.
It's okay...
I'll take the medicine.
I'm sorry, Sia...
I'm so sorry.
Mommy, why are you crying?
Does your stomach hurt?
Will you feel better
if you take the medicine?
It's all right. Everything will be all right.
You're such a good girl, Sia.
Huh?
What's wrong?
The medicine... It's gone!
Medicine?
Damn it, I thought there'd be something
valuable in here, and what do I find...?
Oh, well.
I guess I'll go pull one more job.
Day Three
Cheng-Shin-san, are you
coming off your shift?
Yes.
I'm just coming off mine, too. If you like,
why not come to my cabin for some tea?
Cheng-Shin-san, do you
have a minute?
What is it?
It's about that movie camera
we confiscated.
This is it here.
Tanabe-san?
No, the man in front.
Right here! Take a look.
I'll enlarge it.
Now that you mention it, we've had six reports
of lost valuables over the past two days!
Take this man into custody
immediately!
Yes, sir!
Excuse me, has anyone
turned in any lost items?
Could you describe it?
It's a silver case
that's about this big.
Senpai, will you treat me
to some soft-serve ice cream?
Geez, would you
give it a rest?
But I don't have
any money!
Sia-chan!
Did you buy your
spaceship yet, mister?
How could I possibly have
bought one this soon?
I'll let you ride in
my Caroline, then.
I keep telling you,
that's not a spaceship.
What's she talking about?
She's a fellow member of Senpai's
"personal spaceship" club.
Oh? She's a darn cute
club member, that's for sure.
Mr. Walken?
Yeah?
I'm sorry, but would you
come with us, please?
We won't take much of your...
What's your problem?! I'm busy!
Hold it!
Don't let him
get away!
See?
You can see it
right next to Polaris.
What's "Polaris"?
You're a spaceship nut and
you don't know what Polaris is?
Nope.
Tell me, kid,
why do you want
a spaceship so much?
'Cause I could go into space whenever I want!
I love space!
Do you hate it
in space, mister?
I love it!
We're finally on the
last scene, huh?
Let's rip through it.
We're on a race against the clock.
Hey, I know!
When I get my spaceship, I'll make you my pilot.
Pilot?
That's the person
who drives the spaceship.
We'll blast through space at escape velocity!
It'll be great!
Yeah!
I'll be your pilot!
But when is that gonna be, I wonder?
Get off my case.
I'm sorry, but could you let us
use that spot, please?
Are you filming again?
H-How could we do that?
Our equipment was confiscated.
Is that the truth?
If you're going to film somewhere,
make sure you get permission first.
With a movie like that, though,
they'd never get permission.
Outta my way!
Is he an actor, too?
No way! I've never seen
that guy before!
Come back here!
Turn yourself in!
Cheng-Shin?
Hachi!
Grab that guy!
Crap!
You bastard!
Stay right where
you are, people!
Bastard!
Hold it!
Even if you do that, there's
nowhere that you can run!
S-Shut your mouth!
Clear everyone out of here!
Sia!
No! Let me go!
B-Be quiet, damn it!
Don't!
Let go of the girl!
Sia!
If you value the kid's life,
do exactly as I tell you!
You, the pilot there!
For starters, I want you outta here!
Hey! You up there!
Would you mind using
this girl here as your hostage?
I'll pay you, okay?!
Pay?!
I'm begging you! I just need to get this scene,
and my movie will be finished!
No way! I don't want
to be a real hostage!
Idiot! You only get a chance to film a scene
with this kind of verisimilitude once in a lifetime!
If you call yourself a pro,
get in there and...
What the heck
are you saying?!
You're trying to make money
off of other people's misery!
If I didn't, do you think that the miserable
people would suddenly become happy?
That's not the point,
and you know it!
Then what
is the point?!
I'm saying that
there's no love in it!
Love? How am I supposed
to make a living off of love?!
Life without love is no better than being dead!
Would you two shut the hell up?!
You! The pilot and his buddies! How long
are you guys gonna keep standing there?!
Beat it!
I'm terribly sorry, but we've temporarily
closed the observation lounge.
Lucie. Tell everyone outside the lounge
to brace for G's from a roll.
Y-Yes, sir!
This is your regular check-in.
Calling Luna Ferry MO-F 57.
Shall I drop the pressure in the observation
lounge and knock everyone out?
We will be handing you over to
L1 Terminal Approach momentarily.
But what if the kidnapper's
had training...?
Captain. I recommend that we execute
an emergency roll maneuver.
Downlink course correction
data via NavStar.
At L1 estimated
rollover point,
What? But what good
would that...
We have Debris Section people in there.
...roll your craft and initiate 0.3G deceleration
burn for 6 minutes, 30 seconds.
We can have them assist us.
Half Section?
Hey! I want you people
out of here, too!
Are you deaf
or something?!
Please, just calm down!
I'll see to it that you're paid well!
A man needs money
even in prison, right?
SHUT THE HELL UP!
Are you people trying to screw with me?!
I mean it, I'll kill this kid!
Don't do it!
Hey! Didn't I tell you not
to move unless I said so?!
Don't you care what
happens to the kid?!
Daddy! Mommy!
Use me as your hostage
instead of our daughter!
Give us our Sia back!
Don't come any closer!
I'll stab your kid in the throat!
This is her father saying this,
but she's such a good girl.
Just great, doting parents...
We're a poor family, so we could
never afford to take her...
...on the space vacation
that she always wanted.
But in spite of that, she says she's going
to buy a spaceship when she grows up,
...and when she does, we'll all go
on a vacation in it together.
That's the kind of sweet girl
she is!
She's beautiful and cheerful! I'm sure she'll
make a great wife when she grows up!
Just a while ago, they went on and on
about her pictures at kindergarten!
Maybe she'll become
an artist!
She learned to walk before
any of the other kids!
Maybe she'll be
a sports star!
Ever since I was a kid, they told me that I
had great hands so maybe I'd be a pianist!
And how'd that turn out? All my nimble fingers
do is steal other people's stuff.
You two had lots of dreams of your own
when you were kids, too, am I right?
But that stuff turns out
to be lies real quick!
Artists and spaceships, all that stuff
is nothing but stupid dreams!
What's that moron
babbling about?
But it'll be different
for Sia!
No it won't!
A pathetic, worthless life
is all that's waiting for her!
Don't try to write Sia's future for her!
Sia's future belongs
to her!
Understood.
I'll leave the timing to you.
Rolling in ten seconds.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Please, give Sia back to us!
Two.
One.
Zero!
What the...?
Man...
Not so tough now, are ya...
Damn, he's out cold.
Ow...
What in the world
just happened?
They rolled the Luna Ferry to
temporarily generate gravity.
Sia!
Sia!!
Daddy! Mommy!
Sia!
Thank goodness!
You aren't hurt anywhere, are you?!
You must have been terrified!
Wow, I'm glad that worked out.
Isn't this great, Director?
Damn straight!
I can sell this movie for big bucks!
Huh? What do you mean?
I'm gonna sell it
to a news program!
This might make more money
than the movie would have!
You don't know when
to quit, do you?
Where's the kidnapper?!
Right here.
Listen, I made a promise
with that nice guy.
He said he'd make me his pilot
once he buys a spaceship.
You did?
Well, you'll have to
keep your word, won't you?
If you're going to be a pilot,
you'll have to study very hard.
Yep! I'm gonna
work real hard!
Sia...
That hurts!
What's wrong?
If you're gonna work hard,
so will Daddy.
Let's all start over from scratch.
Let's start over somewhere new.
You're acting funny. We're on our way
to the moon right now, aren't we?
Of course...
We are, aren't we?
Right! My wallet!
Next Time
The
Lunar Flying Squirrels
Well, here we are.
Welcome to your new home.
See ya.
You're leaving already?
I told you, I have to be
at the hotel by four.
This is for you.
Oh, my!
This is a "get-acquainted gift" from Hoshino-san!
Open it!
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Hoshino, my boy.
I love everything
about Japan.
What are you thinking?!