But this is how I really feel,
so I will say it again and again.
Mahiro-san, I love you.
I love you... love you... love you...
Okay, everyone.
Today, we'll be buying souvenirs.
Let's start by taking a look around.
I shall accompany you, Mother.
I'm so excited to hunt for treasures
in rustic shops like these.
You show much promise, Nyarko-san.
Leave it to me.
I'll find you something amazing.
What's Nyarko up to?
Nyarko.
What's wrong?
Your face is red.
What?
Um, it's nothing.
This is...
Look at this 20-year-old game in
mint condition, and at this price!
I guess some places do still have them.
We might still find even greater treasures.
My, my.
Am I the only one worrying about it?
This is stupid.
What is this?
That's an unusual console.
It looks like a WonderTswan Crystal.
I want to play Ganpei.
Does it still work?
Try turning it on.
Okay...
Haiyore!
Nyarko-san
Huh?
Wasn't I just in the hot springs town?
Mahiro-chan, get up.
Hurry, hurry.
Mahiro-chan?
Sheesh. You wouldn't get up no matter
how many times I called you.
Humph.
Humph
If you don't hurry, you'll be late.
You're a high schooler now.
Get it together.
Humph.
Humph
Mom, why do you keep making that noise?
If you don't hurry,
you really will be late.
Yeah, but...
It's our top priority.
Now, hurry up.
What's going on?
Where are Nyarko and the others?
Knowing them, they're probably...
Crash
Ow...
That hurt!
You came out of nowhere.
Nyarko?
What are you looking at, you pervert?
Huh? Uh, Nyarko?
I'll never be able to get married now.
I can't be the next queen or
Dragon God priestess.
Hey.
Doki-Doki Private Academy
Even school's messed up.
Greetings, Yasaka-san.
What?
Kuuko?
Yasaka-san, your tie is crooked.
You must always maintain
your appearance.
Azathoth watches over us.
What?
Hey, Yasaka.
If you don't hurry, you'll be late,
but don't abandon hope.
Once you give up thinking
it's too late, the game's over.
Hasuta, you too?
What are you talking about, Yasaka?
Well, see you later.
Hey, wait.
Hey, I'm Yoichi Takehiko.
If you want any information
about the girls, just ask me.
Hey, I'm Yoichi Takehiko.
If you want any information about the...
Yoichi! I trusted you!
Good morning, Yasaka-kun. What's wrong?
Kurei! You haven't changed, right?
You're still the same, right?
What are you talking about?
Your current standing with the girls...
Nyarko
Advancing Love Heart
Kuuko
Falling Full Speed in Desire
Hasuta
For ten thousand years and two thousand
more, has wanted to become one.
Tamao
Seriously Fell in Love 555 Seconds Ago
is this.
What is this?
I found you, Yasaka Mahiro.
Luhy.
I must speak with you.
Come with me.
Could Luhy have changed, too?
Nurse's Office
What? Inside a game?
Yes. You have been sucked inside the
cursed dating simulation game,
"Doki-Doki High School."
Sucked inside?
Of course. That's what happened.
Doki-Doki High School
Is this all because
of that game console?
I am accessing the game from the outside,
but those of you who were sucked in
have been assigned characters
from the dating sim.
I see.
That's why they're acting like that.
I do not know what
caused this situation.
However, I do know this.
Unless you reach a good
ending with someone,
you will not be able to
escape from this world.
Huh? What is that?
Your choices are Nyarlathotep, Cthugha,
Hastur, and Kurei Tamao.
Ultimately, you must become
lovers with one of them.
Why is Hasuta one of my choices?
Luhy?
It seems I cannot stay any longer.
Yasaka Mahiro, be careful.
Not even I know what
will happen in the...
Luhy?
You've finally discovered
the truth, Mahiro-san.
That's right. In order
to escape this place,
you must accept the way
of this dating game world.
In other words,
you must cooperate no
matter what flags I set.
All right!
Play time is over.
We will have the boy hook
up with Hasuta-kun,
and Nyarko and I will enjoy
our very own Endless Eight.
Mahiro-kun...
This character doesn't suit me.
As long as I'm in this game,
I might as well be more aggressive.
I see...
how...
this game...
ends!
Nyarko's Exciting
High School
Why did it have to be a dating sim?
Give me a break.
Mahiro-san!
Whoops, that's not it.
Yasaka-kun!
You've obviously made up a character.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I want to hit you.
Let's move right along
to the next event.
Let's set all sorts of flags with me.
Super Nyarko-chan Time
is about to begin.
In English, they call
this a quick start.
Don't Lose!
Way of Life
The next event's a swimming class.
Mahiro-san, I'm going to drown now.
Please give me mouth-to-mouth.
Don't announce that!
Nyarko, I can give you mouth-to-mouth.
Huh? What?
Mouth-to-breast.
Mouth-to-inner-thigh.
Hey, stop that.
Mouth-to-mouth.
Enough already.
Mahiro-san, your main heroine's
already in trouble.
Huh? Where is Mahiro-san?
Hasuta-kun collapsed,
so Yasaka-kun took him
to the nurse's office.
What did you say?
Nurse's Office
Are you okay, Hasuta?
Thanks, Ma-Mahiro-kun.
Mahiro-kun.
You don't seem to have a fever.
What's wrong, Hasuta?
Mahiro-kun, let's make
our final fusion today.
What?
I want to have your child, Mahiro-kun.
Hasuta, what are you talking about?
Ouch.
What is this?
Did the event change?
When did that happen?
I have grown tired of
observing a static subject.
What?
As a humanoid interface,
I create explosions of data using force
and gather information
through observation.
That is the scenario.
Scenario?
Whose class president
do you think you are?
I will kill you and see
how Nyarko responds.
Hey, wait.
Huh?
Is this the next event?
What's next?
Mahiro-san, this is for you.
Please listen to me sing
"Malign Deity Knows."
Enough, you moron.
Huh?
Mahiro-san, what about
that famous scene with
the excellent key animation?
Shut up.
Doki-Doki Private Academy
Haiyore!
Nyarko-san
Doki-Doki Private Academy
Haiyore!
Nyarko-san
Welcome.
Welcome to family restaurant Derleth.
What do you think, Mahiro-san?
Now I'm at work.
It's the perfect event to
raise my standing with you.
Let's do our best.
I'm going to turn in my
resignation to the manager.
Wait.
If you're not careful
dealing with the manager,
a beautiful employee with a Japanese
sword will cut you in half.
What sort of restaurant is this?
Come on. Your customers are calling you.
Whoa...
Miss, please don't keep
ringing the bell.
What would you like?
Change.
We do not use that kind of system.
Kuuko.
Have you come to interfere
with my route?
Nyarko, you look cute in that.
I want to tie you up.
I want to violate you.
I want to make you unable
to live without me.
Quit babbling about your
sexually deviant preferences.
I want to wear matching clothes.
No, no, no.
This outfit wouldn't look
good on a girl with
boobs as tiny as yours.
They're not tiny.
Huh? Why do I get the feeling
someone stole my line?
I'm home.
What's wrong, Mahiro-chan?
Your new loving mother will...
Mom, I know. You don't
have to keep pretending.
Bah! I thought you and I would
finally be lovey-dovey.
Well? Have you already
decided who to pursue?
Not yet.
If you don't choose someone,
maybe Yoichi-kun will confess
his feelings for you.
No way. I don't want a
bad ending like that.
There's no other way to escape the game.
Why don't you just pick someone?
But they're going to confess
their feelings for me.
I don't think I should take
this decision lightly.
I see. You're right.
Hey, I'm Yoichi Takehiko.
If you want any information
about the girls, just ask me.
The current recommended date spot is...
Stop that.
You won't beat me!
Time to end this.
It's finished.
Mahiro-kun, it's snowing.
Now it's Christmas.
The malign deity of romance
must be blessing us.
Are you sure he's not cursing us?
Here.
It's a Christmas present.
Oh...
Thanks.
Open it.
It's a handmade Hasuta.
You can sleep with him, bathe with him,
do whatever you want with him.
But cast off at your own risk.
Space CQC, Pearl of Wisdom number 5,
"Anywhere Lighter."
What convenient close quarters combat.
A present.
Huh? You have something for me, too?
Hey!
Give that to Nyarko.
Give it to her yourself!
Very well.
I will give this to her
after I try it on myself.
Do whatever you want.
Mahiro-san!
Whoops, I slipped!
Merry Christmas, Mahiro-san.
This is my present to you.
It's a marriage registration.
I present you with the rest of my life.
No! How could you?
My flag! My legal document!
Don't try to slip a legally
binding document past me.
No matter. I have more presents!
This is...
I made it myself.
It suits you, Mahiro-san.
Did that set the flag ensuring my victory?
I'm just bursting with emotion, after all.
I know you'll choose me for your ending.
Don't be stupid!
I can't choose anyone like this!
You're always serious about
the strangest things.
That's what I love about you.
You leave me no choice.
I must do battle.
Battle?
If I defeat all my rivals,
there is only one ending.
The final event is hand to hand combat.
I call it...
the Bloody Valentine!
The final flag event of
any dating simulation
is Valentine's Day.
In pursuit of Mahiro-san's purity,
let us speak with our fists
to our hearts' content.
Nyarko is mine.
I will not allow you to
follow a route with the boy.
I... I won't lose.
Bring it on. Follow
your racing instincts.
Awaken your souls.
If you do not fight, you will die.
With Mahiro-san!
With Mahiro-kun!
With Nyarko!
The ending is mine!
Yasaka-kun, is this your first time?
I know things are getting interesting,
but I don't know what's going on.
A boy and a girl are accidentally locked
inside the gym storage closet and have
to spend the night together.
Wait, wait, wait!
This is too sudden!
This is turning into an erotic game!
Too bad.
I was going for the surprise ending.
Unbelievable. You shouldn't
take your jokes so far.
I wasn't joking.
What?
I was serious.
I really do like you, Yasaka-kun.
Kurei...
You're still trying to set a flag?
You noticed?
I have no regrets.
Who's coming?
I don't think it'll be him,
but I really hope it's not Yoichi.
Mahiro-san, I...
Yeah.
I...
I won! Yeah!
Really?
Uh...
Good work.
It's finally time.
In order to reach our good ending,
under this tree with some sort of a history,
we must pledge our love to each
other for eternity with a kiss.
A k-kiss?
I know we're in a game,
but I can't do that.
But if we don't, we will never
escape from this world.
Yeah, but...
I can't do it!
I really do love you.
Please accept how I feel.
I have always been working
towards this moment.
Nyarko...
Mahiro-san, I love you.
This is just to escape from the game...
What?
Huh?
Oh?
What?
What were we doing?
We came to buy souvenirs, and...
Um...
Well, well.
You seem to have made it back safely.
Made it back?
What are you talking about?
It seems you have no memory of
what happened inside the game.
Right, Yasaka Mahiro?
Uh, yeah. Well...
Oh? What is it, Mahiro-san?
Your face is bright red.
It's nothing.
Is everyone finished shopping?
Let's go home.
Okay.
That was fun.
It was fun.
What did you buy?
What?
It's nothing.
Nothing.
What is it?
I told you, it's nothing.
I can tell from your face it's not.
No, it really is nothing.
Mahiro-san, we're finally
reappearing in the preview!
Calm down.
It seems the setting of the
next episode is Onomichi.
It's a three-parter.
What are you talking about?
The next episode is
"I am Him and He is Me."
What about the other two?
Stop that!