What is that?
What is that thing?
Damn it, why? Why?
Why is this happening to me?
Someone...
Someone help!
Okay!
I'm the chaos that always crawls up
to you with a smile, Nyarlathotep!
Haiyore!
Nyarko-san
That was a close one
last night, wasn't it?
If not for me, you'd be in big trouble...
...right about now.
But there's no need to thank me.
With a Japanese breakfast,
white rice is a must!
Could you explain last night's
events in more detail?
But having potato chips when
you get up is good, too.
You've just been going on and on
about nothing important! Listen to me!
Oh, look at the time!
Superhero show time is starting!
Are you saying you've returned
from that hell alive?
The Iron Striver, Star Vampire Crusaders!
This is why I love Earth!
Still early in the morning
and already I feel fulfilled!
Long live Sunday!
Okay, but why was that thing chasing me?
This miso soup is the best.
Though I love the combination
of wakame and potatoes, too.
Could I get some more?
Thank you so much.
Oh, and pack as much in there as you can.
Is this the finishing attack?
Like a Close Encounter of the Third Kind
Gaplant!
Wha... What do you think you're doing?
One misstep and we'll
be taken off the air!
Do you want to try again?
No, thank you.
So?
"So?"
What was the monster from last night?
Why was it chasing me?
And who are you, anyway?
Oh, of course.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Nyarlathotep.
I'm the Crawling Chaos.
Nyarla... From the Cthulhu Mythos?
You're familiar with it?
A little.
I've read Lovecraft's books before,
but I've always thought of
you as more of a monster.
Sometimes one with writhing tentacles,
sometimes a nauseating mist...
If you'd like, I can take that form,
Sanity Points
but you'd lose your sanity.
I'd rather not lose that.
If you have some background knowledge,
this should be easy to explain.
I, Nyarlathotep...
By the way, they call me Nyarlathotep,
but I have a real name.
So I have come to Earth for work.
In other words, you're an alien
and an employee of the
Planetary Defense Organization,
and you've come here to defend Earth.
So succinct.
Who knew the gods of the
Cthulhu Mythos were aliens?
By the way, that makes
me a Nyarlathotepian.
I'm not sure I believe all this.
You have to believe me.
We're aliens.
We received information that
a criminal organization
we've been pursuing for
some time will be conducting
a major transaction on Earth.
Space drugs, galaxy
contraband, and slave trade.
Slave trade?
You understand now?
Is that why that thing was after me?
Correct. They're human traffickers.
Don't worry.
I came here to protect you,
Yasaka Mahiro-san.
How do you know my name?
I've researched everything
there is to know about you.
For instance, I know your parents
are on their 17th honeymoon.
Yasaka Mahiro
Age 17 Libra    Blood Type O
Boryo Municipal High School
Year 2 Class 4 Number 22
Personality: Slightly above average
Lifestyle: Extremely normal
School Club: Going Home Club
No Girlfriend or Boyfriend
Family: Father, Mother, no Siblings
Parents currently absent on their 17th
honeymoon in honor of their 17th anniversary
Doesn't space have private
information protection laws?
In any case, I will stay
by your side around the
clock and protect you.
By my side... around the clock?
From "good morning" until "good night."
The whole time?
We'll be together.
Always...
together.
You're blushing.
You're so cute, Mahiro-san.
Shut up!
No, no, no!
Don't worry.
I'll keep personal and business separate.
I'll respect your privacy.
Right.
So let's get out of here.
What?
This place is dangerous.
We must evacuate.
Hey, wait!
Don't worry! Leave everything to me!
Hey! Wait!
Marvelous!
Hey.
An Iron Striver Blu-ray box.
And it's even the limited
edition with a figure!
Hey, Nyarlathotepian.
What are these doujinshi
for adult audiences?
They're outrageously indecent.
Let's buy some.
Hey, alien.
It's Hard to Be
An Evil God in Love
Isn't this a recalled first edition erotic game?
Earth, what a terrifying child you are...
I will treasure these as
part of my collection.
Braw Bro!
Have you calmed down a little?
Yes.
I thought you came here to protect me.
I did.
Of course I did, but I have
a lot of duties to fulfill.
Protecting you,
destroying the criminal organization,
and shopping.
That last one's obviously personal.
Have you been listening?
As I already explained,
Earth has been designated
one of the Planetary Defense
Organization's top priorities.
You didn't mention that.
This is why.
Anime, manga, and games?
Broadly known as "pleasures,"
known in English as "entertainment!"
Earth's pleasures are
the best in the universe!
Hey.
That's why the gods of the Cthulhu
Mythos all want to come here.
We'd sprout tentacles from
our throats to get this stuff.
Don't do that.
It's works of entertainment such as these
that the criminal organization we're
after smuggles out of Earth.
There are limits on how many
can be legally imported,
so they're hard to come by.
Is something wrong?
Then...
Can you take home the stuff you bought?
You...
Mahiro-san.
What?
It's not a crime if no one finds out.
I recorded what you just said.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
If you don't want your bosses
to find out about this,
do your job properly.
Okay.
You're still going to buy them?
I have some points saved up,
so please use those.
You have a point card?
What a great haul.
She seems happy.
This was worth begging them
to give me this assignment.
What?
I had to bargain with
my boss to get the job.
I guess I don't need to ask why.
The entire universe loves
Earth's entertainment...
but there's another reason, too.
Another reason?
Yes.
Like what?
When I saw the data on
the protectee I'd be guarding,
a sound effect, almost like an
"Enemy sighted!" alert,
went off inside my head.
In other words, he's just my type.
Protectee? You mean...
Do you get it now?
To be perfectly honest,
it was love at first sight.
You shouldn't mix business with love!
I thought you said you'd keep
personal and business separate!
Don't worry. I'll earn my pay.
How can you say that after
your shopping spree?
Then let's get to work, shall we?
There you are.
I knew using Mahiro-san
as bait would work.
What? I thought we left the
house because it was dangerous!
Don't worry. I've set up
a convenient barrier which
will allow me to fight
without drawing attention.
I've set up a barrier.
That's important information,
so I said it twice.
That's not what I'm asking!
You're really going to protect me, right?
Of course I am.
Now let me show you the
power of Space CQC!
Space CQC?
Close quarters combat.
It means fighting hand to hand.
Actually, it's the "Space"
part I don't understand.
Let's start with the climax.
Come on!
Don't think you're getting
away with just that!
I hope you're prepared!
You won't be able to beat
me with that attitude!
Hai
yore!
I can't hear anything,
I can't hear anything.
Come on!
That's what you call Space CQC.
You look more like a member of
the criminal organization to me.
But, well...
You did save me.
Thanks, I guess.
No need to thank me.
Just doing my job.
But if you really want to thank me...
That's right!
I love you!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Gau!
Nyarlathotep.
Haiyore! Nyarko-san
Haiyore!
Nyarko-san
Good morning!
Boryo Municipal High School
Hey, Nyarlathotepian.
Yes? What is it?
Are you sure it's safe for me
to go to school by myself?
Of course.
I'll be away for a short time,
but I'll rush to your side
at the first sign of danger.
That's a promise.
Good morning, Yasaka-kun.
Morning, Yoichi.
What's wrong? You seem tired.
Yeah, well...
I don't know how to explain it.
Is having your parents
gone giving you trouble?
If there's anything I can do,
I'd be happy to help.
Just let me know.
Sure.
Year 2 Class 4
I'd like to introduce our
new transfer student.
Come in.
Traveling between the
stars with the tears
of many on my back and
eliminating malign deities...
I am the chaos that always crawls up to
Mahiro-san with a smile, Nyarlathotep.
Call my name, and I will be there.
No one called you!
Gaza-C!
Feel free to
call me Nyarko.
Yasaka
Nyarlathotep
I didn't know you had relatives
overseas, Yasaka-kun.
Yeah. I didn't know before today, either.
Nothing.
But she's amazing.
She's the center of attention,
she's fluent in Japanese,
and she's really athletic.
I know she's supposed to protect me,
but why'd she have to transfer here?
Is something bothering you?
What do you want, Walking Speaker?
I wanted to get an interview with you.
An interview?
How do you feel about Nyarko-chan?
What do you mean?
You're a boy and girl of that
age living under one roof.
And she must be feeling
lonely so far from home.
By the way, when I asked Nyarko-chan...
I could see that romance working out,
but I can't say how he feels...
...is what she said.
That bitch.
Well? How do you feel, Yasaka-kun?
How do I feel?
Yes, yes, I see.
You think it's a possibility.
I didn't say that!
Thanks, Yasaka-kun.
Tell me all about it later.
Hey, Kurei!
Don't worry about it.
Here you go, Mahiro-san.
What is this?
I made you a lunch with all the
love a loving wife can muster.
You didn't need to do this.
I'll just buy some bread.
But I wanted to move my desk next
to yours and eat lunch with you...
Yasaka-kun.
You think bread's better
than the lunch I made.
I didn't say that!
Sob, sob...
Why don't you eat it?
She put all that effort
into making it for you.
You should feel bad for Nyarko-chan.
Fine.
Thank you, Mahiro-san.
Go right ahead, help yourself.
It actually looks pretty normal.
I'm surprised you had time to make this.
An overclocked Nyarlathotepian
can move at speeds that defy all logic.
You just made that up, didn't you?
Don't worry about that, just eat.
Fine.
It's delicious.
Isn't it?
It's all because of my love for you.
By the way, I've never had fried chicken
that tasted like this before.
What sort of meat did you use?
Hey.
I'm going to go throw it up.
Don't worry.
It's not anything dangerous.
I can guarantee you that much.
Is that all you can guarantee?
Why don't we have bread tomorrow?
I'll make you a BLT sandwich.
B, L, T!
Can you tell me what BLT stands for?
Byakhee, Lloigor, and Tsathoggua.
If you put those in a sandwich,
I'll kick the crap out of you!
Dijeh!
Let's now go over cell division as
described on pages 30 to 32...
Hey, Nyarlathotep...
Mahiro-san, I'm so embarrassed
I think I'll get pregnant.
Gyan!
Is something wrong,
Yasaka Nyarlathotep-san?
T-Teacher...
I'm suffering from abnormal and blasphemous
amounts of ominously chaotic pain.
Could I go to the nurse's office?
I'll have Mahiro-san take me there.
What?
No one else could see that monster?
I've got my convenient barrier.
Now to go smite that beast!
Another Nightgaunt?
I'm getting tired of fighting
the same enemy all the time.
What?
Perhaps I'll let the capsule
monster handle this one.
What are you talking abo—
Now where did I put it?
There it is.
What are you doing?
I could ask you the same thing!
Shanta-kun!
I choose you!
What is that?
One of my many pets,
Shanta-kun the Shantak-bird.
Go, Shanta-kun, and kill him good.
Do it as brutally as possible.
Are you sure you're a member
of a defense organization?
I knew it.
Shanta-kun's got 99 losses and
one draw against Nightgaunts.
Then why'd you use him?
They say the worse they are,
the cuter they are.
You know...
Hey, do something.
I have no choice.
It's time for my deadly
Space CQC: Part 2!
Dash!
Sanity Points
I'm satisfied.
That was just ink...
What are you doing?
Hey, what is that thing you're holding?
This?
It's some kind of unspeakable Bar thing.
Stop trying to mix Cthulhu
references into everything.
I'm exhausted.
Why is this happening to me?
I haven't had a chance to
rest since she showed up.
Mahiro-san!
I am the chaos that always
crawls up to you with a smile.
Mai
den
What's wrong with you? Get out of here!
No, thank you.
I thought we could consummate our love
before your parents
return from their trip.
Don't worry.
It won't hurt.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Now let's become the Adam
and Eve of a new generation.
Get out!
Zakrello!
"Haiyore! Nyarko-san" has finally begun!
What did you think of our lovey life?
There's nothing lovey about it.
It'll get even more lovey next time.
No, it won't!
But it's Lovecraft.
Not funny.
The next episode is
"Good bye! Nyarko-san!"
Wait, what?!
We sure got to the last episode quick.