Ghutatan, are you awake?
Ghutatan?
She's not here.
Where are the others?
Hasuta!
Kuuko!
Nyarko...
They didn't come home last night?
Ghutatan's not here either.
They must have gone out somewhere.
Maybe they went up to space
to see Ghutatan off.
If that's not it, it must be
another one of their pranks.
Probably...
Haiyore!
Nyarko-san
You! Are you saying you made it
out of that alive, Iron Stri...
What's with this?
Is it just reruns today?
I'm going out for a bit.
What's wrong with them?
Usually they follow me around
so closely, it drives me nuts.
Pedestrian and
Bicycle Lane
This is a joke, right?
This can't be...
What's going on?
Why isn't anyone here?
This must be their doing.
That must be it.
Calling
Yoichi Takehiko
Not even Mom... I can't
believe no one answered.
Mahiro-san!
The Crawling Chaos Nyarlathotep is here!
I'm so embarrassed I think I'll get pregnant.
I am Nyarko's...
wife.
Mahiro-kun is... very important to me!
Shanta-kun laid a whole
bunch of them this morning.
What? What's he doing here?
Which Mahiro-kun am I supposed to love?
That depends on what sort of play you like.
What a difficult question.
I'm not playing any dirty games.
Boryo Municipal High School
What's going on?
Nyarko, if you interfere with
the love life of another,
you will be scratched
by the cats of Ulthar.
Shut up.
You're the one trying to set up
Hasuta-kun with Mahiro-san.
You won't make that happen so easily.
A good couple? Really?
What do you think, Mahiro-san?
I'm wet.
You shut up.
New! Memory Metal Glasses Frames
Over here.
Mahiro-san, the water feels great.
Mahiro-san said he doesn't like me.
Hey, remember the souvenir shop and
shrine festival you were talking about?
Would you like to go there?
Nyarko?
Hasuta!
Kuuko!
I'm sure I could love you
and Nyarko-san's baby.
Cheer up, Kuuko.
Boy.
Th-Thank you.
Nyarko!
Mahiro-san, I love you.
What's going on?
Am I really alone?
Damn it!
What in the world's going on?
Nyarko!
I only ever rely on them
in times like this.
This is...
Please work!
Onii-tan!
Ghutatan? What are you doing here?
I'm sorry, Onii-tan.
Was it you?
Did you do this?
I can't understand you if you're crying!
Sorry. Did you do this?
Yes.
Then you can undo it, right?
Can you send me back to my world?
Please, Ghutatan.
Please.
I want to return to my life with them.
Onii-tan.
Get away from that man, Mistress.
It seems I misjudged you.
You are not the man I hoped you were.
What?
You are only a bad influence
on my mistress.
Therefore...
Hey, what's going on?
I will eliminate you.
Haiyore!
Nyarko-san
Nyarko-san!
Yes!
What?
That's Nyarko's...
That was close, Mahiro-san.
Huh? My voice seems to have a delay.
So cute.
Is that you, Nyarko?
I'm your beloved Nyarko.
I come when you call, dun duh duh dun!
Because you used the mirror,
I was finally able to
trace you and come here.
You...
You will not interfere with
my plans, Nyarlathotep.
But first, look at this.
That's...
What do you think of this?
What do I think?
This is light!
What happened to me?
Mahiro-kun!
Boy.
Mahiro-kun, I was so worried about you.
Hasuta, Kuuko, Nyarko.
What is the meaning of this?
You think unpetrifying
him means you've won?
We tried all sorts of things
to reverse the petrification.
Hey, don't think you've won.
I even tried kissing you,
like a fairy tale.
What?
So did I.
Are you even listening?
I indirectly kissed Nyarko on your lips.
Hey!
Hey, listen to me!
What do you want?
Spit it out already.
I miscalculated, Yasaka Mahiro.
I did not expect my mistress
to be so taken with you.
This is all because you said
something you shouldn't have.
Because you said it wasn't for kids.
What?
Tada! This!
It's Hard to Be An Evil God in Love
Worshiping Him Always Makes Me Ia Ia
Stop!
This isn't for kids!
So in other words, you want to...
I love adult games.
I love Key ones.
I love Leaf ones.
I love priestess ones.
I love maid ones.
I love tsundere ones.
I love flirty-love ones.
I love all kinds of adult games!
That sounds like something you'd say.
How rude! I love anime and
superhero shows as well!
That's nothing to brag about.
All of Earth's adult games will be mine.
That is why I needed you.
Huh? Why me?
Because you associate with the
universally famous maniac Nyarlathotep,
you had to be an ultramaniac.
That's a terrible accusation!
Once I got you alone, I was sure
you would head there first.
There?
The legendary game shop
known for its collection
of deep adult games.
How would I know about that?
Once you were alone,
you could play by yourself all you want.
Wouldn't that make you want
to discover new tricks?
Destroy him!
Ara, hora, sassa!
Very well, then we shall fight.
Those are...
That's right. I commanded
them to attack.
And I am the one who hurt
the unconscious mistress.
You were furious with
Nyarlathotep and left her,
saying you wanted to be alone.
He told me to grant your wish.
Getting lost on Earth and
getting near Nyarlathotep,
Error
Your message could not be sent.
OK
and blocking her text all
went according to plan,
but I did not expect trouble here.
I will have to take it by force.
My mistress has already
served her purpose.
Now disappear... for the
sake of adult games!
Please, everyone!
Leave it to me!
Leave it to us.
The Crawling Chaos Nyarlathotep!
My strength has made you cry!
One, two!
Go, Fang.
Windstorm!
Mom, Shanta-kun!
I'm glad we made it in time.
How dare you attack Hiro-kun!
Monsters, count up your crimes!
Damn it.
There are too many.
Well, well.
You always need help, don't you?
Thank you, Luhi-san.
They're coming.
Ice lancer!
Impossible.
I did not expect such a
difference in combat strength.
Nyar Shthan. Now choose.
Die painfully, or die writhing!
They're the same thing.
You should not underestimate me.
What?
What is this?
Nyarko!
The Planetary Defense Organization
agents were preventing me
from sending the adult games
I got back into space.
With these tentacles of ultimate brutality,
I will punish you myself.
Nyarko!
Damn it, isn't there anything we can do?
Now you will surely die.
Good bye.
Nyarko!
Mahiro-san.
What?
Damn you, Nyarlathotep.
This is the power of Mahiro-san and my
love.
It's not. It's really, really not.
I command the sword that cuts evil!
Malign Deity Roar
I cannot die yet!
There is still a mountain of
games I haven't finished yet!
Don't worry.
I will beat your mountain
of games for you.
Damn you!
Malign
Per-
Deity
-son
Hate the person, not
the mountain of games!
He Waits, Dreaming
That was another terrible punch line.
Now that Lloigor's radio
interference is gone,
I managed to get in touch with them.
Ghutatan's parents are
coming to pick her up.
I see.
I'm sorry, Onii-tan.
Ghutatan, you just tried
to grant me my wish.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Mahiro-san, didn't I try hard, too?
Pet me, pet me!
Me, too.
Mom, too.
Hey, wait!
I said "wait!"
Um...
Nyarko, Kuuko, Hasuta.
I was only able to come
back here because of you.
So...
Well...
Thanks.
Mahiro-kun.
Boy.
There's no need to thank us,
but if you insist, you can kiss me!
Marry me!
There you go again!
If I make you my wife,
then your wife Nyarko
will be mine as well.
What?
I want to have your babies, too.
Hey!
Me, too.
Hey, guys!
Shanta-kun, you too?
My, my.
H-Hey!
Come on, I can't breathe!
Get off of me!
I'll come again <3
Ghutatan
Are you sure we should be here?
Of course.
The more the merrier.
Besides, we have plenty of ingredients.
Ingredients?
They're ready.
Okay.
Hey, is that fun?
Can I play later?
You seem happy.
You think so?
I can't call this "my life."
Mahiro-san.
Huh?
I love you.
What? Where did that...
I told you before,
"I'll say it again and again."
So...
Mahiro-san, I love you.
Hey, wait!