I want you to slow down a bit, ability user.
Komaba Ritoku.
Oh my, I ran into the first target.
Don't you think that stealing all of our dispersed funds is a little childish?
I just have to destroy my target.
I don't care about your funds.
Move Point?
That's a troublesome power.
Do you think it's only troublesome?
Yeah, something like that.
It's more odious than troublesome.
I will end this with one shot into your forehead.
Too slow.
I'm serious.
It's fine for me to have such a handicap since I'm fighting with monster like you, right?
You won't hit me.
That mobility... You have hard taping inside of your clothes, right?
I had to go through a series of hardships to acquire this special military ability, Ultrasound Elastic Taping.
You think it won't have any side effects if you're using it on your body?
I'm prepared for that.
I need to finish this now.
I have many other things to do.
So thin.
You can't stop me with such a shield.
Too quick.
Now then...
It seems that her quota ended.
Man, doing overtime alone is-
So maybe you want to rest?
Accelerator?
You're Komaba Ritoku, right?
Let me ask what the reason behind this is.
The reason Skill Out is fighting ability users is not something interesting to hear.
So you'll attack indiscriminately after you throw the city into chaos?
Not indiscriminately.
We choose our targets carefully.
You seem pretty calm.
But do you understand your situation?
I killed her.
It's different from what I heard.
Social outcasts shouldn't hesitate at a point like this.
I see.
Did you know?
All bastards that stand against me end up like minced beef.
That electrode transceiver, is it for some kind of electronic information?
What's this?
Chaff Seeds.
They cause disturbance to electronic radars.
You bastard!
You're going to be covered with blood.
Checkmate.
I'll let you make your final wish.
Where do you want me to shoot you?
Are you just going to cause misfortune to people that haven't sinned?
Don't screw with me, you piece of shit!
Why is your ability back?
Are you an idiot?
Chaff is foil of metal that scatters in the air, and obstructs electronic radars.
In that case it's simple, I just need to get rid of the metal foil. With ventilation for example.
Now then...
I shall show you what happens, when a Level 0 picks a fight with a Level 5.
Too slow!
It was checkmate, right?
You're not evil even if you're Level 0.
People say that you're a burden, since people like Skill Out are causing problems.
Rights to possession?
Safe place?
Nonsense.
Don't you realize that you're strangling yourself by doing such things?
You want to hear the reason?
There is the problem of the personality not being taken into account if someone is a powerful ability user.
Because there are always ugly humans, who brandish their enormous power.
And what if these humans are playing a game in which they hunt down Level 0s...
who don't belong to organizations like Skill Out, what would you do?
I knew that with the actions I took, I would end up like this sooner or later.
You bastard...
It seems that we're in the same circumstances now.
It's a present.
Carve this unsightly spectacle in your heart.
Good job.
We will handle the transportation of the corpses and the destruction of evidence.
I'm sending the garbage truck, so get on please.
No, I'll go home on my own.
I don't mind, but try not to be seen.
We will be diverted.
You're alive right, Musujime Awaki?
I started watching somewhere in the middle, but when did you notice?
It's easy to find you.
It was a gloomy imitation...
Is it fine to talk like that to the one who saved your life?
Life saver?
Keep muttering till you die.
Oh, are you going somewhere?
It's nothing important, just some overtime.
Service overtime.
I'm pretty late because of that overtime.
I think I'll go to some convenience store and buy some coffee.
I don't feel well...
That face...
I have the feeling that I've seen it somewhere.
Who is she?
Yes, yes. I'm Misaka Misuzu-san...
You...
My hobby is studying mathematics, and I'm good at swimming,
my bust is 91 centimeters.
Crap, I'm married.
Hey, it's unfair to Papa, so don't touch me here and there.
Oh?
Do you know where the Dangai University database center is?
Hey you, white one, do you know?
Hey, white one, don't ignore me!
Misuzu-san has to study there.
Like I care!
Take a taxi to get there!
I'll kiss anyone boy or girl, if they're younger then me.
I don't get the meaning of what you just said!
If you say so, then I think that croquettes are some type of nabe meal.
First you put bread crumbs and then you put oil into it.
Maybe it was so delicious since I ate it right after it was made?
In that case, it means that if I eat everything that you're cooking right after it was made, they will have the best taste?
You're for sure...
M-Misaka-san.
Misuzu-san is going to sleep...
No, I didn't stretch or take off my makeup.
Damn it...
All the effort I put forth for my skin...
Yay, I've got a young boy!
Why are you loitering at such a late hour?
What will Mikoto-chan think?
Help me, Index.
Come to think of it, who is that girl over there?
I don't have to introduce myself to someone like you.
What did you say?
Index, I'm Index.
Hey, hey, do you know where the Dangai University database center is?
I was told that the materials I need for my university report are only in Academy City.
So I had to come here.
I see.
Oh yeah, let's exchange telephone numbers and addresses.
Why so suddenly?
I will put your number into my friends category, okay?
Misaka...
It is a coincidence?
No...
Is it related with that brat?
Accelerator. Do you want something?
I was cut in.
You're a bastard with bad taste. So you're the head of GROUP?
I can answer any questions you might have.
I don't have any.
I will do what I need to do on my own.
What you need to do?
What a pity.
There was a subject I wanted to talk with you about, but...
Perfect timing.
It's about to start.
What?
Misaka Misuzu-sama has requested to use the Dangai University database center,
so we attacked her.
Attacked?
Yes.
Who is that Misaka?
Misaka Misuzu-sama is the mother of Misaka Mikoto.
Do you know what recovery motion is?
It's something about parents taking their kids somewhere else, before war starts.
It would be troublesome if a lot of students were to leave Academy City.
And Misaka Misuzu-sama is the representative of the parents in this situation.
So, we decided to stop her.
You will participate as well, right, Accelerator?
What did you say?
We asked Skill Out to deal with it,
but their performance was bad.
If you assist them...
I refuse.
My life is my own.
It doesn't matter what you think about me.
Is that so?
Then hurry up and return.
I will take out your ability until then.
You messed with the electrode...
Excuse me.
Good night, Accelerator.
Misaka Misuzu, was it?
He will rage, if I save her.
That bastard.
It's not the time for that.
Let's save her with the best method, painting everything with blood.
Damn it.
Who forgot to cut off the security?
Anyway we don't have time, let's search for that woman.
What's going on?
I already called Anti-skill.
Mikoto-chan
Those guys are probably Skill Out.
Skill Out?
They're something like a gang that's gathering Level 0s.
Why are they targeting me?
I don't know, but...
Misaka-san, did you call your daughter?
She is one of the seven level 5s in Academy City, so if you call her...
Wait, I won't call to Mikoto-chan.
If I involve her in my problem, then I won't be able to face her.
I understand.
Then I will go.
But I didn't ask you for it...
You still can't find that woman?
I'm asking if you still don't find her, you scums?
Damn that Komaba, why did he have to die like that?
What are we supposed to do now?
Hamazura here.
We found the target.
We will deal with it.
So you guys-
You bastard!
Anti-skill?
You damned bastards.
I will gift you a trip to heaven.
It's a really nice place, so you might not even want to come back.
Five?
They all have guns.
This is bulletproof, right?
Is that woman stupid?
Damn it.
If I can grab the bag with the guns before they recover...
Hey! Don't joke-
Idiots!
You...!
Misaka-san, we're running away.
Misaka-san!
Hurry up!
Damn it!
Interesting, you still haven't given up.
You have some guts.
The back door?
Anyway, let's go to a place with many people.
What?
Why did it have to happen at time like this?
So she was a dummy, and we were set up?
Job?
Komaba was killed, and we didn't have any choice than to listen to them,
or else we wouldn't be able to avoid their "take back the back alley" plan.
Damn it! So we were abandoned from the start?
I came because she called me.
So that's how it is, Hamazura Shiage's life will end here?
I was involved in a big trap...
or some genius was behind all of it,
I can't even act like this?
I can't take it!
I have to kill someone or I really won't stand it.
Stand back.
So that means, that you don't have anything to do with them?
And the job still stands?
I just have to make a corpse out of the target.
Say that again, you bastard!
Don't screw with me.
What do you think a person's life is?
It can't be helped.
If we don't do it, then we Level 0s won't survive.
Don't group me with you.
What?
I'm telling you, not to group all the Level 0s with you.
Right, you haven't used any ability.
There are many Level 0s in Academy City.
And they all normally go to school.
They normally make friends.
And they're living a normal life
Aren't you the one who is making fun of Level 0s?
We're the same.
We're not the same.
I'm a Level 0.
But I don't want to be a minus that manhandles others.
Minus?
You're saying that we're minus?
We Skill Out are 100 times better, compared to those who have abilities and do nothing.
So why don't you lend a hand to someone who needs help instead?
If only you used your power to help those who are in trouble because of ability users...
the people of Academy City would accept you.
Shut up!
Komaba Ritoku, the Level 0's leader lived like that, yet he was killed.
He was protecting the ones who were weak and out of place.
But he had something you don't have.
Isn't that the reason he didn't run and fought till the end?
He wasn't fighting for the weak, he was fighting to protect his comrades.
Don't give me that crap.
You're a Level 0,
you don't have any power,
and you're still making fun of us?
The reason that people are making fun of you, it's not because you don't have any power.
Do something with that dull illusion of yours.
You damned bastard!
To tell the truth, I came here to take back Mikoto-chan.
But now I'm relieved.
If kids like you are here to protect Mikoto-chan, then there won't be any problem.
Kids?
Did you come to punish me like those at the top told you?
No way.
If it's about the Misaka Misuzu case, then it seems like she doesn't want to take her daughter back from Academy City.
That's why her murder was suspended.
Those at the top accepted such a fuzzy conclusion?
They'll accept it.
Because stupid Unabara gave it his best.
Well...
That young boy is keeping his promise to protect the world surrounding someone dear to me,
so I thought that I also have to work hard.
But maybe I overworked myself a little though.
This guy has been answering like this for some time.
He probably used some ugly method to archive it.
Anyway, good work for your first job and overtime work.
Damn you.
If you follow the rules, you won't be able to outsmart them.
Normal methods won't work.
It seems that you're very important, to the ones at the top.
Let's work together, Accelerator.
Interesting...
But if you fail, then I will cut you down without a second thought.
I like that side of you, kid.
Come with us.
It's time for us to attack the top.
Seems like fun...
Having a goal, is really fun.
What is it?
I sent a mail to her.
Why doesn't she answer?
No matter how much I work on it, the mountain of paperwork doesn't disappear at all.
It can't be helped.
Because everyone collapsed.
You need to prepare yourself to work like this for the next three days, okay?
An emporium of interception weapons?
It was just a powered suit demonstration.
So it's just a costume, right?
That's too much to say.
This pudding has awesome flavor, even if it's bought at a convenience store.
You will get fat if you eat sweets at night.
Where is that person?
Says Misaka as Misaka tries to ask.
He will be back soon.
I want to meet him soon, says Misaka as Misaka tries nodding.
Good night.
Touma!
You ran away by yourself again and you got injured.
I don't understand your actions at all.
Well, this time it seems I had a bit of luck...
I'm drawn to misfortune after all!