The troublesome Croce di Pietro, it turns out, can be used regardless of place or season.
At this rate, Academy City will fall under control of the Roman Catholics by sunset.
There's no way I'm letting that happen!
Oh my, your head is in quite a convenient position.
Damn it!
The sky's getting dark.
Hey, isn't it time for you to go home?
Or do you want to experience a stimulating night with this Onee-san?
Just one more...
One more thing... Something to get an advantage...
One more...
Fire is thy name,
bearing the title of sword.
Show yourself. Devour my body and transform into power.
Innocentius!
Let's go, Innocentius.
Fortis931...
I'll prove why my name is called the strongest here!
Die together!
That's dangerous, idiot!
Oh no-
Ashes to ashes.
Dust to dust.
Vampire Hunter Crimson Cross!
Go back home, you useless magician!
Shut up, amateur!
Innocentius!
You're in the way, idiot!
You too, move aside!
What is happening?
I can't read their movements...
A basis.
I want an absolute basis.
A clear rule.
So that everyone will be happy,
and so everyone can avoid conflict arising due to differing values.
I want that wonderful world...
That's why I must win.
I'll win and create an answer.
My name...
My name is Basis104.
Get down, amateur!
Stiyl!
Where are you going?
Boy, your opponent is me, right?
Stop messing around.
How many people must you hurt before you're satisfied?
This Onee-san doesn't want to hurt anyone.
But I have a purpose.
So come!
Once I crush you, boy, this Onee-san's mission will be complete.
The Croce di Pietro and the Roman Catholics will create the world I desire.
What purpose?
Don't speak so arrogantly while letting others decide your future.
Letting others decide...?
Yes, this Onee-san doesn't really care who's in charge.
As long as they dominate and standardize the ideals and principles of the world,
this Onee-san will defend that basis to the end.
Is that your goal?
I don't really understand such difficult and confusing topics.
But I can't accept something stupid like handing over everyone in Academy City for that goal.
Boy, you say those things because you don't know anything.
Someone just standing dumbfounded, helpless against their situation,
because you've never seen that expression.
Because you've never watched someone moan "it hurts" while suffering in anguish.
Even so, that's no excuse for attacking Academy City.
There's never a reason to use someone as a stepping stone for someone else's sake!
Never!
Your problems are something that everyone else feels.
Everyone deals with failure, and sometimes they fall.
However...
If you fall, then just stand back up!
Even if the result is miserable... Even if it doesn't go as planned,
keep standing back up!
You have no right to use other people's lives as you please!
Which one will you choose, Oriana Thomson?
Will you leave everything to someone else because you failed once?
Or will you take that failure, and lend a hand towards those who make the same mistake?
With this, everything will end.
I call on all the talent that dwells within me,
release everything, and destroy the enemy ahead!
Damn it!
Geez!
Can't you put any effort towards making this event a success?
I have a bit of a problem.
Come.
Don't expect too much.
This is not my specialty.
Go, Kami-yan.
Everyone...
They're all trying to protect the present.
I'll be at your hospital room before the Night Parade starts.
So please, wait for me.
I accepted their determination with mine.
I can't let it go waste, not here!
Stiyl!
I'll be fine.
More importantly, find the Croce di Pietro.
Force Oriana to tell where it is.
Stop that thing from activating.
There's no need to worry.
Everything will be over soon.
Lidvia Lorenzetti.
Shortly, the Croce di Pietro will activate.
Academy City will be placed under control of the Roman Catholics.
So you plan to get rid of us meddlers here?
We feel your pain and wish to heal your wounds.
Of course, only if we judge it to be beneficial for the Church.
What?
Don't try to reason with her, Kamijou Touma.
Lidvia must be somewhere near by, the spiritual tool should be there.
To avoid any misunderstandings, let me tell you this,
The Croce di Pietro is not in Academy City.
What...?
The Roman Catholic Church, which was created by the Croce di Pietro,
at its peak occupied 47,000 square kilometers.
Even if it's activated from outside, it will completely cover Academy City.
We were tricked...
Oriana was just a decoy.
It's unfortunate that she was beaten.
But the Croce di Pietro will change the situation to make that beneficial to us.
What's important now is that science will bow to religion.
By denying science of what they believe, we will restore the power of our Lord.
Searching and attacking,
it's impossible for Tsuchimikado to use magic twice.
Damn it!
So what should we do?
We will not destroy Academy City.
Once you forsake science, we will accept you as our fellow comrades.
Call Tsuchimikado.
Have him use the Senjutsu Enjin to calculate Lidvia's location.
I'll use my communication spell to call my allies outside to take care of it-
It's useless.
The time left for Croce di Pietro to change the world is...
107 seconds.
It's checkmate.
Is there nothing else?
Is there an ultimate trump card that can reverse this situation?
A spell used by the constellations in the night sky...
Gathering starlight on the ground...
Tsuchimikado!
How many places outside Academy City can they use the Croce di Pietro and still cover Academy City?!
What?
Shut up and answer!
Among those conditions, which is the furthest point?
The northern perimeter of Academy City.
About 1700 meters away.
What's going on?
Just...
20 more seconds.
It's the end.
That's right, it's the end.
If this is the end, then it's over for me.
You think so too, Lidvia?
Even when I've destroyed your illusion,
I couldn't keep the promise I made with my classmate.
What?
The time is exactly 6:30 PM.
Didn't you know?
This is the time when the Night Parade starts.
With this amount of light, all the stars will be hidden.
No matter where you are.
You lost to the light that everyone released to defend the Daihaseisai.
You should have checked out who the main character of the Daihaseisai was.
What are you going to do?
If you let me destroy the Croce di Pietro,
and promise not to do anything else to Academy City,
then I'll be fine leaving you alone.
Are you serious saying that?
You seem to have forgotten that I'm a devout member of the Roman Catholic Church.
Is that so?
Then, you should get to running around just like in a sports festival,
Lidvia Lorenzetti.
So...
Touma didn't say anything to me,
and ran off to fight a magical battle that involved the fate of the world and Academy City,
and got so badly wounded that he was sent back to the hospital?
But, Index-san,
whenever I mention a magical incident you thoughtlessly walk right into the middle of it.
Touma, your explanation seems to imply that I'm an idiot!
If you haven't realized that yourself, then you must really-
Oh my.
This is truly a pleasant scene.
We're having a serious discussion, so don't interfere, Short-Hair!
Kuroko...
Ordinary civilians are allowed to help Judgment in maintaining discipline, right?
Onee-sama,
that's going too far, this is a hospital.
Damn it!
Never mind.
Have you seen today's final results?
Our school has comfortably surpassed yours and is in the lead.
You haven't forgotten about the penalty game, have you?
N-No, putting aside the penalty game, I can't even participate in matches like this...
Then...
Be prepared to die.
How pitiful, Oriana Thompson.
I have to save her.
I must save, with my own hands, that lost sinner who was arrested-
Ah, ah, attention please!
This is the Archbishop of the Anglican Church, Laura Stuart.
Now that I've introduced myself, why don't you stop being so cold, Miss Lidvia.
How did you find this private jet?
I arranged for a little present to be stuck on the outside of your plane when you stopped at Haneda.
You're as creepy as always.
That personality of yours makes you laugh louder the more pressure you're put under.
Can't that behavior be corrected?
The more difficult the situation is, the greater the joy will be in overcoming it.
I must give thanks to the Lord.
What?
The greater the wall, the more joy will be had in surpassing it, eh?
There is indeed some sense in those words,
when spoken by an animal trapped against the cliff's edge.
Lidvia.
If you give up on Rome's teachings and lick my feet, I'll save you.
What nonsense do you speak?
I see.
Then fall with that thing and make a crater in the ground.
Croce di Pietro?
I won't allow that to happen!
Calculating the descent speed, I should make it-
No, I have to make it!
Time is short...
But that's what makes it so fun!
So Lidvia, which will you choose?
The greatest spiritual tool in the world,
or a poor lost lamb?
When the obstacle ahead is even bigger, when you overcome it,
you'll have an even greater joy trampling over me, who created the challenge.
Trample?
Over that unreachable flower, as much as I want...
That was quite a tremor.
The development of Imagine Breaker, the key, is still unstable.
I wonder if I can use this?
I may have to consider the possibility that I'd have to take action personally.
What are you doing here?
I was sleeping on the bench in the waiting room,
but they told me I can't use it after it's morning...
Such a soft bed...
Are you okay now?
Yes, the Frog-faced doctor said I'll be discharged tomorrow or the day after.
Aisa, you look somewhat lonely.
Why's that?
That guy, did he do something reckless again?
Yeah, that's right.
Listen here, I haven't heard the details yet,
but it seems some Roman Catholic magicians took advantage of the Daihaseisai to attack us.
So then, Touma didn't bother to tell me anything,
and rushed headlong into the battle, and only reported it to me after everything was over.
It's unforgivable, right?
I see...
It doesn't matter who's involved...
That person will save anyone in trouble.
Even if it's not me.
Maybe I shouldn't have been saved.
I seem to only bring trouble to everyone.
That's not true.
Because, Touma and Aisa seem to be happy together.
Say Fukiyose-san, how can you come all the way to the hospital just to slap a patient?
Shut up!
Anyone would be shocked to see a naked boy all of a sudden!
You're the one who barged in when I was changing, right?
What was that?
Hey, do you know why that person continues to fight?
Beats me.
When I asked him, he said it was for his own sake.
Maybe to Touma, that's what happiness means.
Luckily or unluckily, Index and I suddenly won a trip to Italy.
Since that's the case, we ought to enjoy ourselves to the fullest.
Orsola?
The Amakusa too?
Next episode: "The Metropolis of Water."
When science and magic cross paths, the story begins.