Agnese?
Please wait a moment!
Why are you here on the Queen of the Adriatic Sea?
Well...
There was some trouble and we ended up boarding this ship...
So, the Queen of the Adriatic Sea is the name of this ice fleet?
The name of this fleet is "The Queen's Fleet".
This ship is just one of many frigates.
It seems that you really don't know anything.
What are you doing in a place like this?
I'm helping search for intruders.
However...
Since you're the intruders...
I can make use of that.
We were dragged into this unaware.
If you keep talking like that, then I'm going to scream.
I advise you not to anger me if you want to escape this place.
It looks like we'll have to listen her.
How do you benefit from helping us escape?
A reward... you can think of it like that.
What is this "Queen's Fleet" anyway?
It's a fleet crafted to observe the Adriatic Sea.
I've never heard of it before.
We've only gathered fragments of the complete story.
We were suddenly attacked by the people on this ship.
Is this fleet really only for observation?
Maybe you were literally caught by that observation.
You're the people who ruined the Roman Catholics' plans.
One of you all the way from Japan, the other from London.
To be fair, that's a superficial excuse.
This is a labor facility.
Where sinners like me are gathered to pay for our failures.
So the people on this ship are mostly from my squad, or rather from my ex-squad.
Let's move on to the main topic.
In exchange for letting you go, I want you to rescue Sister Lucia and Sister Angelene.
By rescue you mean...
Those two used a spell which dismantled the security, allowing for their escape.
They were planning on rescuing the rest of us after preparing, but...
So...
they were recaptured and are being lectured?
They have to seal the hole that allowed those two to escape.
They're going to make modifications so that they can't use that spell again.
Modify?
So they're going to remove their ability to think?
In other words, it will smash their brain structure.
I want you to save them before that happens.
That is my request.
We'll acquire the escape spell as well.
But don't the Roman Catholics know of this spell already?
The Queen's Fleet has a huge job to do right now.
They shouldn't worry about one or two escapees.
I have to go to the flagship to to distract them.
Please act during that time.
Are you going to help us?
I'm not helping you, I'm using you.
Aren't you a prisoner as well?
Let's escape together.
The supervisors fear mutiny.
I'm a psychological safety mechanism that's meant to prevent this from happening.
I can freely move about the fleet.
I'm excused from labor.
This place is comfortable for me.
The efforts of Sister Lucia and Sister Angelene are going to waste.
They should've just escaped on their own.
And, if you can escape from here safely, don't ever get involved with the Roman Catholics again.
I know.
But we're outnumbered, there's a chance we won't be able to save them.
Is this an appropriate line for the man who challenged an army of Sisters?
Thank you.
Those vestments were designed with a magically binding effect.
If that was The Queen's Fleet,
then I can't handle this by myself.
No one's here.
Yeah, Agnese said it's mostly unmanned.
That must be where Lucia and Angelene are being held.
What's that?
What's wrong?
Stand back, Orsola!
This armor is kind of like a magical robot?
Yeah, it seems like part of the ship changed shape.
Don't move!
How do you think we broke this?
Oh my, I casually said it in Japanese, but you understand me, right?
If you don't listen to my warning,
I'll be forced to use this.
We're here to save you.
Do you think we'll believe those words?
Let me see...
According to Agnese, you can use a spell to get away from this place.
She said we should cooperate with you to escape.
Sister Agnese said that?
Consider the possibility that this is a trap.
This is enemy territory.
Why do you think we'd come all the way here, and using Agnese's name too?
Sister Lucia...
I understand.
Your words make sense.
So, how do we escape?
It's too troublesome to explain it.
Sister Angelene.
Um...
Awesome.
By altering the spell that binds the ship into ice,
we can open holes.
With this, we can solidify seawater to form an underwater pathway.
What's wrong?
T-They've added a counter spell to our binding clothes.
If we break the stitching in a certain pattern, the restraining spell will be destroyed.
Destroyed?
In that case, we can use my-
Oh my, so you mean to strip them naked too?
What's going to happen to us?
More importantly, I'm concerned with what's for dinner.
What do you mean?
There's nothing more important than the Lord in this world...
I'm concerned about that, too.
We've had our food flavored with olives for three days.
The bathwater is too hot, too.
Who cares about the flavoring!
And the bath is lukewarm, not hot.
Is that so?
It's true that the adults don't seem to mind it.
Are you-
What now?
If you're going to talk with them, then I'm coming along.
That's right, that might be nice, too...
When we will meet with Sister Agnese?
I'm sorry.
Agnese probably won't be coming.
She said that, in order to help us, she's going to create a distraction.
It seems that she went to the flagship of The Queen's Fleet.
Don't joke around!
The Queen's Fleet was created to protect the ceremonial place for a large scale magical ritual, the Queen of the Adriatic Sea.
The Queen of the Adriatic Sea?
We know that it will be activated on the flagship.
And the key to activation is another spell called the Appointed Time of the Rosary.
And that Sister Agnese is required for the Appointed Time of the Rosary.
What will happen to Agnese?
We don't know the details, but at the very least her brain will be destroyed,
leaving a body with only the heart beating.
The Queen's Fleet has a huge job to do right now.
They shouldn't worry about one or two escapees.
An attack?
From where?
No way, from the other ships...
The Divine Cannon of St. Barbara?
What on earth are you shooting?
Don't you know, Sister Agnese?
Bishop Biagio.
Ship 37 was sunk.
If we continue to fire we'll hit the shore.
Leave the dealings with others to my subordinates. It does not concern me.
If something were to happen to you, we would be unable to restore anything.
It's really ironic.
The Appointed Time of the Rosary.
Who would have thought that only a heretic like you would be compatible with the spell...
Bishop Biagio, we have an emergency!
What?
A giant vessel has been detected beneath where number 37 was sunk.
It seems to be salvaging the remains.
An underwater spell.
Where are Orsola and others?
This is bad...
I might actually die this time.
Touma!
Index?
Are you alright, Touma?
Yeah.
Tatemiya Saiji?
Yup.
The substitute Supreme Pontiff of the Amakusa Church.
But currently we're affiliated with the Church of England.
Please use it.
Thanks.
No problem.
Anyway, why am I here?
Where are Orsola and others?
We picked up everyone.
We're currently interrogating the men elsewhere.
I see.
Is this the secret base of the Amakusa?
This isn't a building.
No way, is this-
I'd like to call it a submarine,
but it's not such high-tech.
It's just a wooden ship that can go underwater.
It's a ship that can float and sink.
You brought something like this to help with moving?
It's expected that we'd bring our weapons.
Moreover, we specialize in naval warfare.
Paper is made from wood, and wood also makes ships.
Agnese...
What is it?
Nothing.
No matter what we do next, we need details about what's going on.
Then you should ask Lucia or Angelene-
What?
It looks like you're alright.
There's no need to be so embarrassed.
Those two outfits were restraining uniforms that the Roman Catholics prepared.
You're a slow guy.
When you were unconscious, we used your right hand to destroy them.
That means...
Exactly what you're thinking.
Touma!
Getting angry because of this is...
So unreasonable!
Oh, right.
We don't have time for this.
This is weird!
Hey, Sister Agnese is still...
Such a powerful bite attack! Why can't you defend yourself against other magicians?!
We still have work to do. We need to discuss what to do about Sister Agnese...
This poses an even greater threat than those 103,000 grimores!
Itsuwa, this is your chance!
Kiss him on the earlobe!
I'm trying to explain the situation!
Oh my.
This is getting interesting.
I'm begging you, please listen to me!
Attention!
S-Sister Angelene...
W-We were always doing things like this in our squad.
So I carelessly did it out of habit...
Always?
I like chocolate con panna more than coffee or tea.
What's that?
It's a hot chocolate drink with fresh cream on top-
Sister Angelene!
A Christian shouldn't be so attached to food.
Calm down...
Uhm...
Please use it.
Thanks.
No problem.
Again with the hot towel plan, Itsuwa?
It's going far too slow.
No, to be unable to make progress is part of Itsuwa's charm.
Why is the "Queen of the Adriatic Sea" the name of the spell?
Long ago, the Venetians and Roman Catholics were on bad terms.
The Queen of The Adriatic Sea was prepared by the Roman Catholic Church to annihilate Venice with a single blow.
So it's like a bomb?
It's not only physically destructive.
It would completely erase all history and culture of the city.
All?
I'm sure that Sister Agnese doesn't know any of this.
If she knew, there's no way she would just stand quietly by.
Basically, we have to rescue Agnese Sanctis before that spell is activated, but...
it's going to be extremely difficult.
Even so, we have to go.
If we don't hurry, Sister Agnese will be crippled.
Do you expect us to sit by and do nothing?
Sister Agnese has always taken care of me, so I can't let it go without repaying her.
We're up against a powerful foe.
If we set up the underwater pathway, we might be able to stop the fleet from moving.
Don't think that we can defeat the enemy just by halting their movement.
That's...
Hey, Tatemiya. Isn't that enough already?
Huh?
What we should discussing isn't whether to save Agnese or not.
She gave up her own freedom in order to allow her friends to escape.
If we don't act, her kind intentions will be destroyed after she's used.
So we have to go and save her, yeah?
We'll also protect Venice from being destroyed.
Then, there's only one thing we can do.
You don't want to save her?
Fine, then I'll go.
Listen, that problem had already been settled right from the start.
I've already prepared a strategy.
I just needed to make sure you were ready for this or not.
Tatemiya...
Listen up! We're going into battle, but everyone must come back alive.
What has the Priestess taught us?
To reach out to all those in need!
Here, take this.
Oh my...
Since I can't use it, I thought it might be better if you have it.
What is it, Index?
Nothing.
Well then...
Let's get started.
Bishop Biagio!
Enemy fleet inbound! About 30 to 40 ships!
50 seconds until they reach our position.
Sink them!
Roger that.
They aren't shooting back...
Can it be...
All hands, take defensive positions!
What's happening?
They're fireships!
A fleet of unmanned boats filled with explosives.
A large vessel is approaching from a depth of 40 meters!
Most likely a submarine!
Strike on the enemy sub confirmed!
Enemy forces have boarded ship 29!
It's the Amakusa from before!
No way, the sub was a decoy too?
Forget about taking control of every ship!
We need only think about destroying the enemy core.
You guys head to the Queen of the Adriatic Sea.
Got it.
Hurry!
Index!
This way!
Okay!
These idiots...
Why won't you move to save Sister Agnese?!
They're firing at us!
They're hoping to sink us along with the ship.
They're targeting us directly.
No way...
Come out, one of the twelve disciples,
tax collector and lowly servant of the eradicating magician!
This is bad...
Come out, one of the twelve disciples-
Watch out!
Sister Angelene!
We boarded the flagship to prevent the Queen of the Adriatic Sea from activating.
As one question after another remains unanswered, Index is...
Next time: "Appointed Time of the Rosary"
At the time when science and magic cross, the story begins.