Three for the skies, four for the earth,
and twelve point out the world.
You obtain enormous power, by giving each number a specific meaning.
What?
It's a good spell, but it's not Christian.
It's from the theories of the pre-Christian Greek Pythagoreans.
When did you guys ascertain the world, before the son of God was born?
I won't win by drawing out this battle.
Such a pity...
When you see a good spell, you regret destroying it.
If those guys show up again...
I will only be able to go into ability user mode for four minutes.
I'll draw that brat out of the darkness.
The entire facility is clear.
No one's here.
The report says, that they evacuated all personnel and patients
because of the dangerous terrorist activity.
Did they notice us?
This is bad.
Any traps?
None found from the infrared check.
Incoming
Private
Connected
You're late.
Heaven Canceler.
I don't have time, so I will be brief.
Forget about Kihara and run away.
Otherwise your lives will be in danger.
Are you serious?
You will be crushed by Accelerator.
This time he won't hold back.
You mustn't approach Accelerator.
That's all.
What nonsense.
I see, don't die.
If you don't die, I'll save you.
We've received reports from all over the country that people are losing consciousness.
The police is working hard to find the source,
but there are also reports that people overseas have also fallen victim to this phenomenon.
It has spread that far.
I only needed to suppress Academy City though...
Last Order?
No, it's Kihara.
Good, someone picked up.
I've heard this voice somewhere...
I have been calling every number on Last Order's phone.
You're the only one who's picked up.
You may be unaware of the situation, but I'd like you to cooperate.
She is in danger.
What's the situation?
So you split up at that restaurant?
I'll take care of rest.
You should throw away that phone and go back to your normal life.
What are you talking about?
I'm definitely going to help.
Then head for the large railway bridge in Disctict 7.
That's the meeting point we decided to rendezvous at.
If she is still running, then she will be heading there.
Ok, I got it!
Academy City is strange today.
There is some weird person invading from the outside,
and Antiskill and normal citizens are collapsing.
It's seems like an indiscriminate attack, so you should be careful.
What a bother...
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have left her alone.
The same for me.
I also left her alone.
We've lost contact with multiple squads.
They're probably...
Dead or have run away...
Either way, we have to gather their hearts later.
Have you recovered the guys we used as decoys when that woman showed up yet?
Yes.
We don't know what kind of power it was yet, but they had very low oxygen levels.
An artificially induced asphyxiation...
Is it the work of that woman?
Damn it! Because of her, they-
Hey...
Bitch, how does she aim?
Wait, could it be unrelated to science?
Whatever!
We'll do what we have to do.
Is the Testament ready?
Yes.
Right here.
This is...
Her...
How is it going, Accelerator?
What do you want, Kihara-kun?
Hey, did you see some part of that brat's clothing in that area?
If you haven't, you should look for it.
I left it there on purpose.
By the way, Testament is really awesome.
Throwing a virus into a human's head isn't something normal.
So how should I react?
Should I roll on the floor laughing, Masochist-kun?
Hey you...
Has your ability of situation judgment broken?
Why won't you just kill that brat?
I doubt you or your subordinates would even consider recovering her unharmed, right?
Nevertheless, you can't even touch her.
I'll kill you.
I knew it.
Considering that guy's personality, when I said something like that, he would at least have taken an eyeball from her.
But the fact that he didn't means...
Oh my...
He is really a regular gofer.
There's someone who's telling him what to do.
Could it be Academy City itself?
Then I need to check the Board of Directors...
Oh yeah, I'm awesome, since I came up with all of this.
Don't screw with me!
You pieces of shit!
Seems like there's some commotion outside.
Imaginary Number School District Five Line Institution, AIM Diffusion Field has completed expanding.
Every magician who uses magic within Academy City will go on a rampage and self destruct.
Vento of the Front, you're no exception.
The current output is not enough to cover the entire world.
But the situation will change with Fuse Kazakiri's move.
What's this?
This unknown presence, it keeps growing.
You...
Why are you here?
Did you specially come here to be killed?
Where is Last Order?
Last Order?
I don't know what you're talking about!
What's with Vento?
I see.
So this is The Imaginary Number School District Five Layer System.
I have to postpone dealing with you.
Don't underestimate us!
Do you think you can defeat us with this?
She disappeared?
What was she looking at?
No way...
The expansion of The Imaginary Number School District Five Layer System will now begin.
The priority code of Last Order, confirmed.
Fuse Kazakiri will now manifest.
To all personnel, please prepare for a shockwave.
It can't be...
An Angel?
This place is dangerous.
But where is Last Order?
Damn it!
Hey, I'm at the bridge, but Last Order isn't here.
What's your situation?
Are you stupid?
Believing such a lie.
I will figure out that brat's whereabouts soon.
She can't be found by just running around.
I'll take care of the rest.
You go home.
You saw those wings of light too, didn't you?
I have to stop that Angel.
So it will be difficult to cooperate.
I don't care.
I'm sorry, and don't die.
You too.
He is really going to use it, after all?
Is he really trying to annihilate the enemy?
Signal from superior individual No. 20001 confirmed.
Presumed danger level 5.
Misaka 10032 attempts to reject.
Rejection failed.
Signal accepted through routes R, V, Y.
Large payloads on cognitive pathways detected.
Rejection failed.
We have to oppose the order.
Eventually, it will solve this critical situation.
Thomas Platinabank.
One of the twelve Board of Directors members.
Mission's code name: "Angel".
In order to remove the unknown threat, recover Last Order and overwrite the virus with the antibody.
You've gotta be kidding.
It looks like that brat is still alive.
Where are you hiding, Kihara?
What's going on here?
Wait!
What are you doing here?
Let me go!
I have to go, because Hyouka is there.
Hyouka?
No, Touma!
Don't kill Hyouka!
Index.
Misaka.
This way.
Please Touma, don't go there.
The Angel over there, is definitely Hyouka.
That's Kazakiri?
I don't know the reason.
If you touch her she will disappear.
I'll deal with Hyouka somehow, so don't touch her.
I can't do that.
I will stop her.
Besides, she isn't the only problem.
But if you use your right hand then she'll die.
I won't let her die!
I'm not going there to kill her.
I'm go there to save her.
Do you really think that's the normal Kazakiri?
Of course not!
That's why we have to save her!
Let's go, Index.
Lend me your strength to help Kazakiri!
I don't get it, but you got yourself involved in some huge trouble again, right?
And your acquaintance is in the middle of it?
She's not an acquaintance, she's my friend.
Let me confirm one thing, she isn't a bad person, is she?
She isn't.
You've heard Index.
Our friend is over there.
Friend?
So they are bad, right?
Good.
I will deal with them somehow.
You-{\r
I'm sorry, you won't stop me because I'm starting right now!
What...
Misaka!
It's the punishment game.
The day isn't over yet.
You have to save your friend and come back!
You got it?
I will save her for sure, so don't die.
Now I'm really irritated.
Hey Touma, is it this quiet because of that magician?
That's right.
I want to know how her attack works.
We need to know it in order to counter it.
It's probably Divine Punishment.
What?
You make a key from a specific emotion,
then anyone who has that emotion gets smashed up, regardless of distance or location.
That's Divine Punishment.
But Touma, did that magician act in a particular way?
Like inciting a specific emotion?
Specific emotion...
Hatred?
No, hostility?
Could that be key that activates her spell?
Yeah, but no matter what stage they're in.
It won't deactivate until the magician decides he doesn't need Divine Punishment anymore.
Then what about Kazakiri as an Angel?
She should be all right, right?
I don't know.
I do have some grimoires that appear to have related information, but the parts that are being used are messed up.
I've never seen any of them.
At least, I know that the Angel there and the core controlling it, are in different locations.
Kazakiri is from the science side.
What happened, Touma?
Damn it, it won't connect.
Does anyone beside Komoe-sensei know anything about this?
Misaka!
What?
I want to stop that Angel somehow.
You're my only hope!
Hey Misaka, did you get hit?
No.
But you're making me fight and use my head at the same time.
You're really stupid.
Good.
Index, ask her about everything you don't know.
Awesome!
What is this?
Damn, it's flying. Aleister!
I don't understand the logic behind this theory.
You're a scientist, yet you reject science.
Look at it.
When did Bibles start flying out-
Kihara-kun.
Hey, shoot properly.
Otherwise, you'll only bother everyone else
Don't move.
You're so cool!
I might fall for you, Accelerator!
Now then, it's time for scrapping!
You damn bastard!
Kazakiri...
Kazakiri!!!
Kazakiri!
Kaza-{\r
Damn it!
Oh my...
The two fellow sinners.
I wonder if you're about to lick each other's wounds?
I was thinking about postponing killing you, but you came here to get killed by yourself.
Or are you sick of seeing any more of this, and want to get smashed up first?
I won't let you lay a finger on Kazakiri.
I'm one of the God's Right Seats, so I can't overlook that monster over there.
This is a clump of blasphemy, a creation of science that disdains all who carry a cross!
How dare you! Take that back!
Pff, it's fine!
You will disappear along with that Fallen Angel over there!
I won't let you!
She has been put up to this, and on top of that, there are people who treat her like a monster and want to kill her.
Don't screw with me!
What do you think a friend is for?
The various battles that are being fought become more violent.
What answer will Index come up with, within this chaos of science and magic?
"Divine Punishment Spell."
When science and magic cross, the story begins.