The time limit is sixty seconds.
Anyway, if I kill him, everything will end.
If I can't return to the path of light anymore,
then going to hell together with Kihara is the only thing I can come up with.
You damned bastard!
What kind of a shitty face are you making, while standing in front of me?
What's the matter, you shit?
Didn't you come to save that brat?
You damned shit!
By they way, do you think of yourself as someone who's awesome and cool?
You're fighting alone against a major evil, trying to save a pathetic captured brat...
Do you think that by doing this, all your sins will be forgiven?
You will always be stuck in this mess!
You damned shit!
I know.
I will always be stuck in this mess, but what I'm looking for is different.
Going to hell with you is fine.
But don't involve that brat.
You damned bastard!
You've been annoying me for some time now.
You have that disgusting right hand attached to you,
and you're defending that repulsive angel.
How much longer until you're satisfied with making fun of me?
Don't screw with me!
Do you think that your perspective, is the only one that should matter in this world?
Why won't you accept others?
I hate science.
I abhor science.
I hate science because it made me into this!
I abhor science because it let my little brother die!
A person?
Wait!
What?
Kazakiri!
This is what science is.
You're one of them.
Don't you find that to be disgusting?
Once the battery expires, you're just junk that can't move.
The same...
You shit!
What?
Kazakiri.
You hypocrite.
What are you doing?
Unbelievable.
Normally I'd be saying "misfortune," "misfortune".
But isn't his more like a blessing?
Isn't it?
W-What are you talking about?
Wait for me, Kazakiri.
Index is currently coming to save you.
She is your friend, after all.
She will meet your expectations.
Don't worry.
Until then, I will stop her for sure!
Don't screw with me, you crippled bastard!
Damn it!
You damned brat!
Are you messing with me?
Damn it! Let me go!
Damn!
I see, since he can't use his ability,
my countermeasures can't affect him.
Damn, killing him won't be enough.
What do I need to do, so he doesn't want to die?
Look at this!
This is the original script of the virus implanted in that brat's brain.
Without this that brat can't be saved!
So you went silent? Is it that vexing?
You damned brat!
I've completely destroyed everything you value!
You can't take anything back.
Now it's your turn.
You can start wondering if there's something stupid like Heaven or not.
There she is.
It's her.
I can do it...
Vento's preventing her hammer from being caught by my right hand.
Which means I can destroy it.
In that case...
Seems like there isn't anything to gain from getting close to you.
Now that I don't have to care about the people around me, I can go against you with all I have.
It's as if your cooperating with that monster.
It's not "as if," I really am cooperating with her.
What?
This is your limit!
Don't understimate God's Right Seat!
Damn it...
Vento!
What's with that stupid voice of yours?
You are from science side that set this up, aren't you?
Along with the angel's appearance, you have forcibly inflicted a spell of pressure on the entire area.
So now you're causing an imperfect circulation of magical power.
Aleister came up with this disgusting thing...
Idiot!
Is there any reason for you to fight?
Don't say such stupid things.
This is bad, I can't dodge that.
Don't you need to be rescued?
I'm sorry, but I can't let you fight any longer. I will send you to the hospital immediately.
Shut up!
I will never again entrust myself to science.
My younger brother was killed because of science.
What?
It was thanks to a malfunction that occurred at an attraction in an amusement park.
They said that there was no problem, scientifically.
Multiple safety devices, completely automated speed control program...
Just those trustworthy words were lined up.
But when push came to shove, there wasn't any use for it!
You...
And after that, when we were carried to the hospital,
they couldn't prepare a blood transfusion for two people.
The doctor said that only one life could be saved.
My borther said "Please save my sister".
So, I'm the one who survived.
Surprised?
That's the reason why I'm fighting as a member of God's Right Seat.
But you know, I hate science so much that I can use the God's Right Seat to destroy it.
Science stole our futures.
And they're trying to smear the Bible, that shows us the way to salvation.
After all, that is true nature of science.
It's just trouble to people.
That's why I hate and abhor science.
If science is such a cold thing, then I will destroy it and fill the world with a warmer ruler.
It destroyed my brother's future, it is my duty.
Stop spouting such bullshit.
What?
What do you mean, science killed your brother?
It's obvious that the doctor didn't want anyone to die to begin with.
It's obvious that he wanted to save both of you.
The same goes for the accident that occurred at the attraction.
It wasn't moving to hurt people,
but to create smiles.
Shut up!
Your little brother knew very well about the situation he was in.
Even so, he still wanted to save you.
Do you think a person like that would want you to take revenge on science?
He was a person who wished for your happiness more than anyone else!
I said shut up!
Is there any value to the words of a child close to his death?
If there wasn't enough blood, they should have given the blood to my little brother.
They could have given my own blood!
There was a value.
You can live now, because your little brother took that decision.
It means that there was a value.
Aren't you the one, who should be able to understand that value more than anyone else?
How stupid!
Do you think that such words can comfort me?
I destroyed that child's future.
If you were him, would you still be able to say that?
I wouldn't!
That's why I'm against you.
Your way of living is wrong.
Back then, your little brother did the most incredible thing in the world.
You want to smear it all with mud?
Are you going to destroy what he did, by saying that he died hating science?
You make me laugh.
This is the path I chose.
And there is no way I'm changing it because of someone who just heard my story.
The critical situation that Academy City and Kazakiri are in,
and Vento who has been affected by the hate against science.
I will destroy those illusions.
It isn't anything awesome compared to what your little brother did,
but I will save you even if it's only a little bit.
Go and start over again.
You big idiot!
The guy from that time...
Do these people also have a connection with this?
Hey!
What? I'm in the middle of work.
Hey, wait!
Don't just do what you want.
She really is the core of everything.
It's basically an angel construction.
It's creating a human image and it's forcing the normally formless Telesma inside.
But I don't know what to do from here on...
Short hair, I have a question.
Call me Mikoto-sama.
So what is your question?
What is the electronic network that uses brain waves?
Well, there are electric ability users using each others brains to construct an electronic network.
So what is this AIM diffusion field, that is spreading over Academy City?
It's a natural field created by ability users when they exert their powers.
It means that they're using the mind of this girl, who is controlling the special power that the city's full of.
And by binding her mind, they distort the special power, and the angel is created.
In that case, I just need to untie the knot that is inside this girl's brain.
But how do I create the measures for this plan?
A song.
It can be conveyed even with simple words.
You damned bastard!
You damned shit!
Using rhythm and musical interval, I can invoke multiple emotions.
Wait, is there any way that such an analog method can work?
It can.
Prayers can reach everyone.
So we will save everyone with our prayers!
This child, Hyouka and Academy City too...
What's with you bastard?
Starting to move all of sudden.
Ki... hara...
Kihara!
Interesting.
That's right, isn't it?
It would be boring if you were defeated that easily.
Thanks for the great service, Accelerator!
And I'm getting pissed thanks to you.
I will hurt you so much, you'll wish you were dead!
You call that a punch noise, damn kid?
Nice, here we are!
I think I will make it a little more interesting.
Show me more of your guts.
How did you do that?
What are those black wings, that are coming out of your back?
This bastard... What kind of powers does he have?
Did he achieve a new type of clearance?
What numerical values has he inputted into his personal reality?
Could it be an angel or something?
The true form of this power...
You haven't even noticed what you are.
You monster.
What about Kazakiri?
Kazakiri!
If I touch Kazakiri now, I might even erase her real form.
Who are you?
Excuse me.
I have business with this girl.
I asked you who you are.
Acqua of the Back.
Like Vento, I'm a member of God's Right Seat.
You don't have to worry.
For today I will retreat.
Let go of Vento!
If I let her go then she will be captured by the science side, and be executed.
I'm giving that to you.
It has been already destroyed by your right hand.
It's just trash now.
Vento can't use Divine Punishment anymore.
The people collapsed due to it, will recover soon.
With this, it means that you have protected Academy City's peace, so don't worry.
Do you think that all is well?
I will tell you one thing...
I'm a Saint.
Come up with any absurd fight and I will shorten your life span.
Hey, wait!
One fight has ended, but an another one is definitely coming closer.
It could be called war...
Next time: "Until the Outbreak of War."
When science and magic cross, the story begins.