Archbishop.
As I said, don't call me with this name.
But we're out here without any bodyguards.
We should hurry back to St George Cathedral as soon as possible.
I have my own home, and I can't stay always in inside of this old church.
Walking is also good.
Well, I don't really mind.
You are really narrow-minded man, Stiyl.
Can't you even find in yourself to enjoy the walk with me?
Laura Stuart,
may I ask a question?
You are very cautious.
What?
Just why are you speaking like a simpleton?
It is weird?
I even had a real Japanese check it for me!
And just who was that?
Tsuchimikado Motoharu was his name.
Please don't take his advice on standard Japanese!
A communication talisman?
Have you heard of The Book of Law?
A magical grimoire, isn't it?
The author was... Edward Alexander.
The original was kept in the Vatican Library in Rome.
But no one has been able to decipher it.
Even the one who memorized the 103,000 Forbidden Grimoires hasn't been able to.
So, what if someone who could decipher The Book of Law were to appear?
What?
That person is a Roman Catholic Nun named Orsola Aquinas.
Could it be they intend to use The Book of Law to provoke a conflict?
Don't worry.
At least for the time being.
The Book of Law and Orsola Aquinas; both of these have been abducted.
Shall we discuss the details inside?
The second semester seems to be busy.
Grand Champion Star Festival, Grand Ability Festival,
Arts Appreciation Day, Social Learning Day.
All kinds of festivals.
Are you okay, Sphinx?
But free time is boring! I'm bored!
Touma doesn't play with me at all!
Kamijou Touma has his own reasons.
It's not like he stays at school because he likes it.
Why aren't you at school, Maika?
I'm an exception.
A basic of maid training is practical work experience.
Then I'll become a maid.
I'll be able to go to Touma's class to play!
The way of a maid is harsh, you know.
It would be hard for a woman with zero skill in housekeeping.
Then Touma will be a maid!
And I'll get him to play with me.
Do me a favour and don't repeat that to him.
Yeah, that right.
I'm sorry, but...
you don't have time to become a maid.
And neither does he.
Sign: Be prepared! Letfs work hard for Grand Champion Star Festival!
Grand Champion Star Festival.
A huge event that all the schools in Academy City participate in.
The aim is to observe mutual interference between different abilities.
On those days, participants are authorized to use their full power.
I, Kamijou Touma, have lost my memories due to certain circumstances.
So I don't remember anything about such a large event.
Now then, what should we have for dinner?
Ka-K-K-Kamijou Touma!
It's an emergency!
The silver-haired sister was taken away by someone!
It's a kidnapping! Abduction!
Hey, wait! What do you mean?
The kidnapper gave me this when he left.
Kamijou Touma;
if you value her life,
come alone to the abandoned Gloaming House Theatre outside Academy City at seven tonight.
Tell me, just what did this guy look like?
He must have been over 180 cm tall.
His hair was dyed red, and he had a barcode under his right eye.
He had a cigarette in his mouth, and a bunch of piercings.
It's fine, Maika.
Index and I know the offender.
You know the offender?
Is the motive out of twisted love?
What I mean is...
Exit permits?
I think you should understand the situation.
The Book of Law has been stolen.
And the one who can decode it, Orsola Aquinas, was also kidnapped.
And it seems that the culprit is the Amakusa sect.
How did they remove it form the high security Vatican Library?
The Roman Catholic Church sent The Book of Law to a Japanese museum.
That's absurd.
Something that dangerous...
So, the Roman Catholic Church requested the cooperation of the Church of England?
No.
However, there's a more pressing matter.
What?
I can't contact Kanzaki Kaori.
Kanzaki is the former leader of Amakusa.
Once she discovers that they're in conflict with the Roman Catholic Church...
I want you to settle this before Kanzaki does something unfortunate.
I don't care what methods you use.
Kanzaki is a Saint, one of less than twenty in the world.
You can't expect me to fight with Kanzaki.
If it comes to it.
For now, simply go to Academy City.
Stiyl, bring this with you.
This is...
It's a little gift for Orsola Aquinas.
The Index of Forbidden Grimoires.
We'll need the aid of a specialist, won't we?
Why does Touma need to be involved?
I don't know.
Why do I have to get involved with him?
So, are we going to the Amakusa Catholics' base?
No, the situation has changed a little.
Damn it.
Where is that "Gloaming House"?
I don't know anything outside of Academy City.
A sister?
Don't tell me she's an acquaintance of Index.
Excuse me.
Yes, what is it?
Do you know if I can take this bus to get to Academy City?
Academy City?
No, there's no buses to Academy City.
No?
It's not just buses.
All transport to the outside is cut off.
There is gate over there, so if you walk...
Thank you for taking time out of your busy schedule to guide me.
I told you, you can't take the bus!
Oh, yes.
You did say that.
If you go that way, you'll get to the gate.
Understand?
I'm sorry for being such a bother.
Hey, you!
You just smiled and ignored everything I said, didn't you?
Why do you look so frustrated?
No, I'm not really...
Pardon me, but you seem to be sweating quite a lot.
T-Thank you.
By the way, why do you want to go to Academy City?
Actually, I'm...
being hunted.
Hunted?
The situation right now is chaotic.
Our information's confused, too.
We don't know what happened to The Book of Law.
I should introduce myself, first.
I'm Agnese Sanctis of the Roman Catholic Church.
I see.
So, what kind of techniques does the Amakusa sect use?
To be honest, we haven't been able to make a proper analysis.
The Amakusa's speciality is secrecy.
The Amakusa don't use any spells or magical arrays.
They hide all rituals and incantations in everyday actions or customs,
so even a pro magician can't make a proper identification.
This is really troublesome.
Ah, it's Touma!
Orsola Aquinas.
What's this about?
What's with this kidnapping game?
So, you figured it out?
I called you here to help me find a missing person.
Find?
Well, don't worry.
You just need to hand over the sister beside you.
What?
Like I said,
the sister beside you is the person we're looking for: Orsola Aquinas.
Well, thank you, you can go back now.
Why did I have to walk all the way here in this heat?
That's why I thanked you.
What? You want me to treat you to some shaved ice?
Up to now, even though our personalities don't match, I thought we could get along.
Yeah, at least until this!
You expect me to care?
I can't cure your loneliness, and nor do I want to.
Hand Orsola over to Agnese.
Oh yeah, didn't you say that you were being hunted by someone?
What's wrong, Orsola?
My, my.
It won't be that easy to take her away.
Orsola Aquinas, rather than return to the Roman Catholics, perhaps you should join us
and enjoy a much more meaningful life.
Amakusa!
Orsola!
You can't, Touma!
My hand, bring fire, shape it into a blade, and bring forth-
It looks like we were too late.
Hey, Stiyl!
You'd better give me a proper explanation!
I'm the one who needs an explanation.
The Book of Law is a grimoire written in a cipher that no one in the world can decipher.
If someone manages to decode it, they will gain enormous power.
Hey!
Is it really that valuable?
If someone is able to use it,
it's said that the world dominated by the Christian religion will come to an end.
You can just burn the book!
Magic books don't burn.
At best, you can only seal them.
U-Um...
I'd like to start explaining the situation, but-
Touma!
Hey! No! Stop!
Get away!
Touma, this is past the limit of simple mischief!
Don't screw around on the job.
Right now, we can be certain that Orsola Aquinas is in the hands of Amakusa.
There are roughly 50 members of Amakusa involved in this.
It's possible that they're on the surface.
In others words, you don't know anything for sure.
We tried to track Amakusa using the traces of magic they left.
Amakusa specializes in escaping and hiding.
They won't be captured so easily.
But they can't possibly escape our perimeter.
Special movement method:
Map Pilgrimage.
It's a spell that can only be used in Japan.
Simply put, there are 47 special vortexes around Japan.
One can move freely between them.
A magic map.
It's over if they use a vortex.
Why are you sitting around?
There's no need to hurry.
Map Pilgrimage is ruled over by the movement of the stars.
Unless the stars are right, then the special movement can't be used.
Restriction of special movement only lifts just after midnight.
We still have four and a half hours until then.
And also, Touma.
Let me see the map.
Okay.
Here.
Within this area, there's only one vortex they can use.
So, then...
Is there anything I can do to help?
This is why I keep telling you to check it properly.
Yes, I'm sorry.
It seems the sisters have it rough.
Index's tent?
She's not here.
Man, where did she go?
Over there!
Damn it!
Index!
Amakusa!
W-Wait...
That, that...
It's just a slug.
A-A slug...
Hey, hang in there!
Touma?
N-No...
I thought that Amakusa had attacked...
C-Calm down, Index.
This isn't how you usually react.
You're not usually like this.
Just remember your normal-
Hey, Stiyl.
What?
I'm rather annoyed right now.
Which girl do you like?
Hey, Stiyl.
The lady I most respect is Elizabeth the First, the Lady I most admire is St. Martha.
Isn't the Amakusa Catholics the organization Kanzaki Kaori was serving?
Who did you hear that from?
Tsuchimikado?
Then Amakusa are Kanzaki's comrades, right?
Even so, will you do it?
I will.
I have decided to do anything to protect her.
That's why I can kill anyone.
I will burn them alive.
Burn them away to nothing.
A long time ago, I swore.
"Even if you forget everything, I won't forget a thing.
For you, I live and die."
Go to sleep.
Stiyl?
It's not, which means...
Hey wait, Index!
What, Touma?
Agnese?
Papa...
Papa?
A dream.
This is a dream.
So it's okay for me to bite Touma.
It's fine to show him my discontent with all my strength.
H-Hey wait, Index.
This is undoubtedly real-
Such misfortune!
Acting Pope,
all preparations for the Map Pilgrimage are complete.
Then...
Kanzaki Kaori!
I'll show you...
the current form of the Amakusa-style Church of Distinct Doctrines.
We jump into the vortex with the Roman Catholic Church.
The result: Tatemiya Saiji has spoken an unbelievable truth!
And Orsola...
Next Time: Amakusa-style!
When science and magic cross paths, the story begins.