ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
MISSION:32
WHO IS THIS MISSION FOR?
Both of you, stand back!
I've never seen a weapon like that.
Is it an intermediate-range?
It'll be hard to escape
with the two of them.
In that case...
He won't let me get close.
He's very skilled with his weapon.
- What's going on?
- Is it a fight?
- Is he wielding a weapon?
- Someone call State Security.
This is not good!
We're totally attracting attention.
What should I do?
At this rate, we'll cause a commotion!
Wow! How amazing!
Anya? Oh crap! I can't have her
see me like this!
Wow! You're so cool, Circus Lady!
Oh, this is a performance?
This luxury cruise doesn't disappoint!
What a lifesaver.
It seems like Anya hasn't recognized me.
Let's wrap this up quickly.
Amazing!
There's a crowd in this hallway,
and nowhere to take shelter.
Olka and her family are behind me.
This is difficult.
I can't get close to him.
No, that's not it.
I'm dragging my feet.
Why? Am I hesitating to get close to him?
I know that an injury from that weapon
wouldn't be fatal.
You can do it, Miss!
You have to take him down
before Father comes back.
At this rate,
I should just grab the chain and drag
him down even if I'm to get injured.
But if I don't make it look more
like a performance,
will everyone get suspicious?
What should I do?
- You can do it, old man!
- Show us more flashy moves!
Dammit. I was struggling a bit,
so there's a big crowd now.
They're a hassle.
I'll get rid of all the crowd,
together with my target.
Bravo!
What an amazing performance!
Although I didn't understand the story.
Mother is scary.
I think I'll be a little bit more
obedient from now on.
All right! This is perfect.
- She's definitely going to love this!
- Father!
I have to return to the shop!
Where have you been?
There was a circus performance over there...
Anya has accomplished her task!
I helped Mother
and completed my mission
without Father finding out!
Heroic Anya!
I can barely calm my heart
from this exciting adventure!
I'll take all of this.
It... it suits you well.
This is flawless.
No matter how you look at it,
I'm a happy, and cheerful dad!
So damn uncool. I'm disappointed.
Let's go.
But man, what kind of crazy fight
did that couple have in that room?
The ice pick was all finagled!
It's so scary!
I'm glad no one was murdered on this ship.
Seriously!
Blueless No. 89
and Mermaid eau de toilette.
This is a different perfume
from the one at the manor.
I guess she changed her perfume
together with her face.
There was at least one man and two women.
Maybe the one I'm not smelling
is the female bodyguard.
It's me. Where are they now?
Don't know.
It's highly likely that they're hiding
in the second or third-class cabins.
But I haven't picked up anything yet.
I'll post some people around that area.
Judging by this ship's route,
they'll rendezvous with the other ship
after tomorrow night.
When the time comes, they'll have
no choice but to come out of hiding.
Keep doing what you do best.
Yeah.
- Did you find them?
- No, not yet.
They told us to head to Deck Three.
What a useless informant.
He better not be planning
to run away with our money.
I won't let him do that.
In fact, I'll take back
everything I paid him, before I disembark.
- What will you do with the money?
- Let's see...
There's never a shortage of idiots.
I should at least make some preparations.
Hey, where are you going?
Our room is this way.
- Mother is in trouble.
- Yor?
I'm sure she's working until late,
but you don't have to worry.
It's time for kids to be in bed. Let's go.
Anya's adventure has barely begun.
She didn't contact us,
so it must mean that she's busy.
We weren't followed, and no bugs.
I think we can rest here for a while.
It seems like the Director
left food here for us as well.
I think we can stay confined
until your ship comes.
It's all right. Stay quiet.
I was so scared!
Who the hell were they?
They were really assassins?
They were shooting
and wielding chains onboard!
You've got to be kidding me!
I want to leave!
Calm down, you dummy.
But did you see those huge men?
They were huge!
You're such a coward.
You're so pathetic,
it makes me want to cry.
You too, little one?
You can't grow up to be like him, okay?
Why did you come with me anyway?
You didn't have to get yourself involved
in all this danger.
You should've stayed
with the new organization.
It's because...
of you...
- What?
- Well...
Please don't underestimate me.
I'm not so hopeless that I would
forget all that Boss did for me.
After the war, when there was no food,
I would've died of hunger
if it wasn't for your family's
black market.
Here, take this.
It's our secret.
Hey Olka. Where are you?
I still remember the taste of that bread.
That's more than enough reason
for me to be here.
Zeb.
Plus, did you know
Hapoon is currying favors with warmongers
in order to make money
in the arms industry? He's a bastard.
You can count on me!
Even if Hapoon's minions come after us,
I'll beat them up like crazy!
Sorry, that was a lie!
Welcome.
In the last room, you forgot about our
secret knock and tried to open the door.
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful!
The three of you should rest
in preparation for tomorrow.
I'll be placing Forger at the door.
How can we sleep in this situation?
- What about you, Director?
- I'll be patrolling this floor
and if possible, I'll reduce
the number of enemies.
You guys are really amazing.
You guys are so calm even when your
life's on the line. How can you do that?
This is our job.
So "kill or get killed,"
is a normal thing?
I have no words.
It's been over ten years
since the war ended,
but I guess there are still wars going on
all over the place.
As long as humans exist,
there will be no end to fighting.
Whether we're at war or at peace,
we're just soldiers for our country.
If need be, I will send you a signal
with my footsteps.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes, I understand.
- Forger?
- Yes?
Focus on your mission.
Or everyone will die.
How scary!
That's what you call a pro, huh?
Just as the Director said,
all of you should rest.
Or just lie down.
You have to gain strength for tomorrow.
Please keep your shoes on
in case of emergency.
I understand.
I'll turn off the lights.
Come to think of it,
I never got the chance to contact
Loid and Anya.
My situation wouldn't allow that, but...
Maybe I was dragging my feet
because I was afraid of getting hurt.
If I get wounded so badly that I have
no excuse to tell Loid and Anya,
I wouldn't be able to live
with them anymore.
Your family is just for your cover, right?
That's right, Yor.
You must set your priorities straight.
For what...
For what am I...?
APPROXIMATELY 20 HOURS
UNTIL THE RENDEZVOUS
Why am I looking after this dog
so early in the morning?
Don't you bark at me, dammit!
I'm not a pet-sitter or a babysitter!
I'm busy with my underground things!
Give me back my time!
Oh my, what a cute dog!
What?
- Good morning.
This is my first time I've seen you here.
Do you live around here?
Oh... ah... kind of...
I hope we bump into each other again!
Do you want to be my dog?
My name is Twilight.
I'm the number one spy in Westalis.
No matter what the situation,
even if I'm placed in the jaws of death,
I'm trained to remain calm.
The power of observation, discernment,
and adaptability.
I honed such skills to the limit,
and that's how I survived this world
until today.
- But...
- Go away!
So damn uncool.
I had become big-headed.
There are still many things
in this world that I don't know.
I shouldn't let my knowledge
and experience make me overconfident.
The root of all human's fear is
the "unknown."
Death, invisible evil spirits, neighboring
countries, and next door neighbors.
Their "unknown identities"
is what provokes fear.
Some brush it aside as something
"unable to understand,"
and turn a blind eye. Others would
label it as what they see fit,
and put their hearts at ease.
I... I am a spy.
I do not fear the unknown.
No, I will face the fear rationally,
and I will deal with it.
Just like how scientists lit up
the darkness...
and how they discovered
new viruses and vaccines...
Second day of the cruise.
I will overcome this difficult situation!
- What?
- We're done entertaining the guests?
It seems like they had a big fight
last night.
Mrs. Grey got very angry about
Mr. Grey soiling his pants.
So they're not in the mood
for any entertainment.
I... I see.
- What about the business invitation...
- Back to square one.
Don't worry.
You guys didn't do anything wrong.
I'll look after the couple.
You two can enjoy yourselves today.
- I understand.
- Hooray!
Time for an adventure. Time for exploring
Another day of heroic Anya's trip!
- Observe. Discern. Adapt.
- Exciting adventure
- What's the meaning behind these lyrics?
- Exciting time exploring
I fell asleep last night,
but I have to hurry up and find Mother
so that I can help her. But...
Father, Mother's in trouble
so we have to go help her now!
What do you mean?
No way! Yor battles with people?
How can this be? Oh my god!
That's what'll happen,
so I can't tell him!
I have to do something
and ditch Father somewhere.
Look Father! It's a place to play golf!
- You want to try it?
- For some reason, adults love to golf.
While Father is engrossed with golfing,
I'm going to slip away.
A hole-in-one for every hole?
- Bravo!
- Oh no! He finished already!
Here. Give it a try.
It's fun.
Argh!
Calm down, and aim well.
It's almost time for lunch.
I won't leave until it goes in!
A successful experience is important.
I'll let her continue
until she's satisfied.
Discern and adapt.
- Don't get too loud and disturb others.
- Argh!
I fell for Father's trap
and wasted my time!
I need to think of a new plan!
Chew well.
Father loves to take in knowledge.
I'm sure he'll lose
his sense of time here!
These are all books I've read before.
COMIC
But I'm glad she's having fun.
Oh, I forgot!
Puzzles are so much fun.
It looks really difficult,
so I think I'll need your help, Father.
I can probably finish this in two minutes.
Let's see.
Observe.
- Wow!
- Observe.
I haven't been able to ditch Father,
and it's already dinner!
Not only that, I was having so much fun,
I forgot about Mother!
Argh!
Why? Why is she scowling at me?
It seemed like she was having so much fun!
Why does she look so upset right now?
Did I make some sort of a mistake?
Calm down, Twilight. Face the unknown.
Does she hate me?
Is this the rebellious phase?
At this rate,
the Forger family will fall apart.
Does your stomach hurt? Are you okay?
I’m troubling Father.
I'm okay. I'm enjoying this adventure.
Is that so? Then I'm glad.
But I'm a little lonely
that Mother isn't with us.
I want to be with both Father and Mother.
That's why I have to go
by myself to help Mother.
I see.
She's right.
It would've been nice
if Yor had time off work.
She's still a young child.
It won't hurt to ask Yor
if she's open tomorrow.
You know where Mother is?
No, but I'll have the concierge
deliver her a message for me.
- Once she replies, we can meet up.
- Okay!
By the way, there's going to be
a fireworks show on the deck tonight.
It's tonight's main event,
so Yor and her group might be there too.
It might be hard to find her
among the crowd, but want to go?
Fireworks! Yes, I want to go!
Yes.
It was the Director.
He received a message from the ship
waiting for you guys, and they're ready.
We'll be meeting them in four hours,
but we need to make preparations.
More importantly, this deck
is surrounded by enemies,
so we'll leave this room
and head somewhere else.
Please get changed.
We have wigs prepared too.
Okay. Got it.
It's me. Any movement?
I intercepted an unidentified
encrypted communication.
It's not the frequency used
by the State Security.
- Is it a message for those people?
- It's a possibility.
Okay. Notifying everyone.
Get into your stage three positions
and lie in wait for them.
All right. All clear.
Let's go.
MISSION:33
PART A & B: THE SYMPHONY UPON THE SHIP
PART C: SIS'S HERB TEA
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita