ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
MISSION:33
PART A & B: THE SYMPHONY UPON THE SHIP
The fireworks show will begin soon.
Please enjoy
the dazzling show as we light up
the sea tonight!
We hope this will be a memorable
last night of your cruise!
We'll first head to Cargo Room Three,
where the inflatable boats are stored.
That's where the Director will be.
We'll lower the boat from the fore
of Deck Two's emergency exit.
Then the rendezvous ship will pick you up.
- Before the fireworks end...
- What should we do tonight?
- How about the fireworks show?
- You idiot! Let's go to the casino!
Let's hit the jackpot and say goodbye
to our job at city hall.
The Director will get mad at us.
- We shouldn't let our guard down.
- Okay.
Blueless No. 89 and Mermaid.
Both of them are popular fragrances
but the combination of those two,
plus a woman with no scent.
One man, and two women, with one child.
I found you!
Anya loves fireworks!
- Is that right?
- Papa!
I want to go see that side too!
It's so crowded, I can't see the sky.
- I wonder if I'll be able to find Mother.
- It won't be that easy.
When will the fireworks begin?
I won't be able to catch Mother's thoughts
over this buzz of excitement.
I have to concentrate and search her out.
Those guys are most likely assassins.
They're guarding this area too!
Time for a detour.
They're here too!
They're blocking all the routes
to the ship's bow!
I can take them down and move forward,
but they might call for backup
and they might find out our destination.
- Let's head up to the deck for now.
- Will we be okay?
The Director gave me the keys
for the crew members' corridors.
Let's move quietly by passing over
secluded rooftops.
No sign of anyone.
It's loud thanks to the fireworks show,
but try to move as quietly as possible.
Okay.
Let's go!
- That was startling!
- It's okay.
- The fireworks are very pretty.
- Let's move while it's loud.
We'll go up here.
All right.
Wow.
Let's hurry on over to that side.
There are two black-haired women.
Is it the one with the kid?
Right. If possible, kill the child too.
Roger.
She dodged it!
Oh my, he dodged it.
Are you hurt?
- Olka!
- I'm okay...
I think.
- I didn't sense them at all.
- Whoa, whoa!
They're all strong!
There's no way to escape.
I won't miss this time.
I'll take you out first.
Oh sheesh,
I was wondering where you had gone
wandering off to.
Director!
She has backup, huh?
Both of you, run!
Take cover under that hatch!
I won't let them go!
- Hurry, get in!
- What a shame.
My blind spot!
Zeb!
That hurts!
It hurts like hell even though
- I have a bulletproof vest on!
- Don't be so reckless!
Good work, Mr. Husband!
Now the hatch can't be opened that easily.
You're satisfied with that?
I'll blow everything up all together!
Excuse me.
Stay behind the walls!
This is not good. The deck is a mess.
We'll have to clean up
and get rid of any evidence.
Got you--
Try to finish them off
without leaving too much evidence.
The cleanup is a hassle.
Mr. Director! When did you get here?
- I'm sorry, but there's so many of them.
- I guess you have no choice.
It seems like they're all skilled
in this trade.
A lot of foreign faces
with unfamiliar fighting styles.
But,
they're no match for us in the Garden.
They conveniently gathered in one place.
Let's wipe them all out.
It's a red one now!
How can she maintain this excitement
without getting bored?
Bravo!
Vides, this is insane! I won the jackpot!
It's a poisonous mist strong enough
to knock out a bear!
My, my, such bad manners!
I'm Esmerelda, Master of Wire.
I'm King of Chakram--
The fireworks show is reaching
its climactic finale!
- That hurts!
- All it did was give her pain?
The show has come to an end!
I stubbed my finger!
You killed all of them.
You're a horrible woman.
Yes, I killed them. It's only natural.
I'm sorry,
but anyone who points a blade at someone
has no right to complain
when it's pointed back at them.
That goes for me as well.
You're so serious.
I don't care how many you killed,
because I get a bigger share now.
It's a little late to bring it up now,
but can you just give up and leave?
To avoid unnecessary bloodshed.
- You dare to underestimate us?
- We can't accept that offer.
We received our payment in advance,
and we can't leave even if we want to,
because we're on a ship.
And it doesn't seem like that old man
will let us leave to begin with.
Stop glaring at them, Director!
They view war as a game
to make some money.
If we let them go, they will
definitely cause harm to our country.
You're so old-fashioned, Mr. Soldier.
Learn some tips from the west.
Money is power.
Being rich will make everyone happy.
For being a businessman,
you lack foresight.
Repent on playing with fire,
as you're being eaten by sharks.
You guys are the ones
who will be eaten by sharks.
Director!
My grip strength...
It's the end.
Don't fight it.
It'll only prolong the pain.
He's in a different league to the others.
My feet are heavy again.
In any situation you are
seriously injured, or you die,
I will tell Forger that you moved
due to an unexpected transfer.
If I disappear without a word...
I'll really be a horrible woman.
It'll be suspicious
if my hairstyle changes!
Yor, you got a haircut
while entertaining guests?
Oh, I cut my hair because that offer
was turned down...
No, I don't have time
to be worrying about that!
At this rate, I'll be chopped in half!
Young lady, if you're scared of dying,
you should be the one to give up.
That will never happen!
I won't allow you to hurt Olka
and her family!
Underlings like you and I
have it so hard, huh?
If you give up, we'll share
some of the payment with you.
- I don't want to get hurt either.
- I don't want it!
Stop spouting nonsense.
It's not nonsense.
This is a very serious business offer.
You also kill to make a living.
We're both of the same ilk.
We're nothing alike! I'm doing this...
...To support my family... wait...
I guess I'm doing this for money too.
No, I have enough to make a living
right now.
I get rid of bad guys for my country.
For my country? Was I doing it
for such a good cause?
What am I doing this for...
Oh crap!
Oh my, he's about to kill me.
What should I do?
I won't be able to pick up Loid's shirt
at the dry cleaners.
I also have to return
the book Anya borrowed from the library.
Wait, what am I saying?
Why is this man pointing
a big sword at me?
Oh, my head hurts.
I'm a little tired.
Sis!
Yuri is flashing before my eyes.
Yahoo! Sis, I got a job
at the Ministry for Foreign Affairs!
Yuri, you grew up so well.
- I bought this with my first paycheck!
- You can survive without my support.
I don't need to work as an assassin
any longer.
That's right. Let's end it here.
If I die,
I won't be able to go to the dry cleaners,
or the library.
We're done here. Get rid of Olka
and the rest.
Roger.
- I won't allow it.
- This woman...
Olka.
Olka. Why was I protecting her again?
I just want to live a quiet life.
That's right.
The reason why I started doing this job,
and the reason why I continue to do it...
I was so busy with life
that I had forgotten.
Is it for money? For our country?
It is, but it's not.
I just wanted to
protect his
carefree life.
This world is scattered with
unwarranted misfortunes.
In order to reduce that,
and to prevent it from harming him,
I have to keep the world clean.
I'll continue doing that. In fact,
even more so now.
I don't need to be at peace.
I don't care if my hands
are stained with blood.
Even if this way of life
could kill me at any moment...
Even if it means I have to leave
the Forger family...
Enduring
a grueling job for someone,
or for some cause,
is something to be proud of.
I'm sure Loid will give me his approval.
He will understand.
I will not
stop fighting!
MISSION:33
PART C: SIS'S HERB TEA
The suspect went through the back.
- Let's attack from both sides, Yuri!
- Roger!
Yuri! What happened?
Did the suspect injure you?
Lieutenant,
it seems like I've caught a cold.
All of a sudden?
It's so unlike you to get sick.
When...
When I think of how far away my sister is,
my cells begin debilitating...
Oh you said she was on a business trip
on a cruise ship, right?
I'm sorry for letting
the criminal get away.
Just sleep for now.
I'll be going to the pharmacy.
I'm sorry, but can you pick up
some herbal tea as well?
- The one with the bear logo.
- Fine.
Whenever I catch a cold,
it reminds me of my childhood.
Oh no! You have a fever, Yuri!
What should I do?
Calm down, Sis. I'll get better
with some rest.
Let's start by getting you warmed up.
- Here's all the blankets we have!
- That's too much, Sis!
You wrap green onions around the neck
in the Far East.
I can't breathe, Sis!
Nothing works better for a cold
than herbal tea with honey.
Use elderflowers, and sage--
Thank you, neighbor!
I'll head off to the mountains!
I'm back, Yuri!
I picked lots of things that are
good for your body!
Sis! What happened to you?
I ended up annoying the bees a little.
I also fought with a boar.
I'll make some hotpot.
I'll start by making some herbal tea.
This is not good. If I catch a cold again,
Sis will end up dying.
I have to become sturdy and strong!
Get well, Yuri.
- Sis.
- Yeah?
I'm so glad I'm your younger brother.
Stop acting as if you're going to die!
I'm okay.
I'm also very glad
that you're here with me, Yuri.
- Stay healthy forever.
- Sis.
For my kind Sis,
I will make this world a kinder place.
Here. Drink this and get better.
Thank you!
This drink is warming me up!
I'm so glad!
Something strange is happening to my body,
so I no longer feel
the symptoms of my cold!
I'm so glad!
Are you okay? You were groaning
in your sleep.
- I bought what you requested.
- Thank you.
This is famous for its disgusting taste.
This works best.
This also tastes similar
to the tea that Sis made me.
I've recovered!
Let's go catch that criminal!
Let's cleanse this world.
- Before Sis comes back--
- Go to sleep!
MISSION:34
THE HAND THAT CONNECTS TO THE FUTURE
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita