Croce di Pietro is a troublesome item which can be used regardless of place or season.
If nothing is done about it, the Academy City will be taken under the control of the Roman Catholics, they say?
I wouldn't ever let that happen!
Croce di Pietro
My, your head was positioned so perfectly.
Damn it...!
It's getting darker now.
Isn't it about time to go home?
Or would you rather spend an exciting night together with me?
One more...
If I had one more thing...
Just one more...
Its name is annihilation,
Its purpose is a sword,
Appear, shatter my body, and become power!
Innocentius!
Here we go, Innocentius!
Fortis931...
Here we shall prove that my name depicts the strongest!
Die together!
That was dangerous, idiot!
Oh no-
Ashes to ashes,
dust to dust,
Vampire Slaying Crimson Cross!
Go home, you incompetent magician!
Shut up, uber noob!
Innocentius!
You're in my way!
No, you're in my way!
What the heck is this?
I can't see what they would do next this way.
A standard,
I want a universal standard...
A clear cut rule,
making everyone happy,
so that no difference in perspectives would cause any tragedy...
For that brilliant world...
That's why I'm going to win.
By winning, I will create the answer.
I am...
My name is Basis104.
Get down, noob!
Stiyl!
Where are you going?
You're supposed to be dealing with me over here.
Enough of this!
How many do you have to hurt until you're satisfied?
I don't want to hurt anyone either.
But I have a goal.
Now come.
If I screw you, then my job is finished.
The rest of it will be accomplished by the Croce di Pietro,
then the Roman Catholics will create a world I desire.
What is your goal?
Being in a position of having others choose your future,
quit talking like you're some great person.
Letting others choose, you say?
Right.
I don't mind whoever it is.
As long as someone puts together all the ideals and principles in this world,
I would then defend that standard no matter what.
Is that your goal?
I don't understand all these complicated issues.
But I can't answer a stupid request like handing over all the people in the Academy City for this goal of yours.
You can make remarks like that because you don't know anything.
By only being able to stand in disbelief to the situation you're put in,
you've not seen someone with that expression before.
Because you've never heard that one line, "I'm mortified".
Even so,
That's a terrible way to justify you freely attacking Academy City.
You can't change that argument into logic, so you can use someone as a stepping stone for another!
It will never be!
The problems you face are felt by everyone!
Everyone would mess up, and trip at times.
But you know...
If you fall, you can stand back up.
Even if it's awkward,
even if all your efforts seem to be counterproductive,
you just have to stand back up!
Don't give up on other people's lives!
Which do you choose,
Oriana Thomson?
Will you leave everything to someone else just because you failed once?
Or will you lend your hand again, even if those people have failed before?
I will end it with this.
I call upon all my ability within this body,
release them all, and strike the enemy in front of me!
Damnit!
Geez.
Can't you put any effort into trying to make this festival successful?
I have something that I thought of.
Come with me.
Don't expect much.
This is not my specialty either.
Go on, Kamiyan...
Everyone was trying to protect the present.
I will return to your hospital room before the Night Parade ends.
So make sure you'll wait for me.
That was how I showed my determination.
How could I let that be put to waste here?!
Stiyl!
I'm fine.
More importantly, go for the Croce di Pietro.
Make Oriana say the location.
Stop that ceremonial item from activating.
There's no need to worry.
Since everything will end very soon.
Lidvia Lorenzetti...
In no time, the Croce di Pietro will activate.
Academy City will be edited to a part of our Roman Catholic Church.
So you're saying people who are uncooperative like us will be deleted here?
{We only say that we will sympathize with the wounds you've received and will shall heal them too.}We say that we'll sympathize with your pain and heal your wounds.
But of course, that's only if we judge it to be beneficial to the Roman Catholic Church.
What did you say?
Don't try to have a serious discussion with her, Kamijou Touma.
Lidvia should be close by.
The ceremonial item would be there as well.
I will tell you, just to prevent any misunderstanding.
The Croce di Pietro is currently not in Academy City.
What?
The Holy See created by the Croce di Pietro was 47,000 square kilometers at its greatest time.
Even if I were to release it from outside Academy City,
it would completely cover the city area without trouble.
They got us...
Oriana was a decoy.
It's a pity that she was taken down.
But that too would be changed by the Croce di Pietro to something more beneficial for us.
What's important to us, is only one thing: Science yielding to Religion.
By denying science and showing our power,
the authority of our Lord will be restored.
Search and attack,
It would be impossible for Tsuchimikado to use magic twice at this point.
Damn it.
Then, what can we do?
We won't destroy Academy City.
After making you discard the pagan religion by the name of Science,
you will be converted to brothers and sisters that would be loved-
You go call Tsuchimikado.
Find Lidvia's position using Senjutsu Enjin.
If I use my communication spell and let the units outside deal with it...
No use.
The world will be changed by the Croce di Pietro in approximately...
107 more seconds.
Checkmate.
Isn't there anything else?
Like some final trump card to reverse this situation?
A spell that uses the stars in the night sky...
Collecting the light of the stars on the ground,
Tsuchimikado,
how many points are there outside Academy City which could become usage points for the Croce di Pietro to encompass the whole city?
What do you say?
Shut up and answer!
Which point is the furthest with that criterion?
The outskirts north of Academy City,
about 1700m.
What does that have to do?
Just twenty more seconds...
It's already over.
Sure, it's the end.
If the result is like this, I'm finished.
Hey, don't you agree, Lidvia?
Even if I succeed in destroying your illusion,
if I'm not able to keep a promise with my classmate...
What are you saying?
The current time here is 6:30 PM, sharp.
You didn't know?
It's the time when the Night Parade begins.
With this amount of light, it can color up the sky well enough to block out the stars.
No matter where you are...
14:00 Triathlon - 14:30 Ball Throwing
15:00 Shoulder Wars - 16:30 Ladle run
17:00 Tug of War - 17:30 1800m mixed gender relay
18:30 Night Parade - 20:00 Closing Ceremony
You lost to the light everyone made to defend the Daihaseisai.
14:00 Triathlon - 14:30 Ball Throwing
15:00 Shoulder Wars - 16:30 Ladle run
17:00 Tug of War - 17:30 1800m mixed gender relay
18:30 Night Parade - 20:00 Closing Ceremony
14:00 Triathlon - 14:30 Ball Throwing
15:00 Shoulder Wars - 16:30 Ladle run
17:00 Tug of War - 17:30 1800m mixed gender relay
18:30 Night Parade - 20:00 Closing Ceremony
You should have put in some research on who the leading roles were in the Daihaseisai.
What are you going to do now?
If you say that you will destroy the Croce di Pietro, and would never lay hands on Academy City,
I'm fine with that.
Are you seriously saying that?
I guess you've forgotten that I'm a devout Roman Catholic.
I see.
If that's the case, we should have a game of chase to exemplify how an athletic event should truly be.
Lidvia Lorenzetti.
And?
So you never told me once, but you participated in a magic battle that could decide the fate of this world and Academy City,
were beaten up big time, and brought to the hospital?
But Index-san, you would carelessly walk into the center of the incident if you heard anything about magic.
Touma, you're making me sound like a big idiot!
Since you don't realize it yourself, you must be a true-
Oh my.
This is a funny scene.
We're in the middle of a serious discussion, so don't interfere, short hair!
Kuroko,
if I remember correctly, commoners can cooperate in Judgment's social order restoration activities, right?
Onee-sama,
please refrain from doing that in the hospital...
Damn it!
Fine then.
Did you see the final results for today?
Our school is at the top, surpassing your school with ease.
Don't say you forgot about the punishment game.
You talk of a punishment game, but I can't participate in events injured like this...
Then...
You can try hard and put your life on the line.
Ah, how pitiful it is for Oriana Thomson.
I have to save them,
the wandering sinners trapped there with my very own hands...
Uhm, attention please~
This is Laura Stuart, archbishop of the Anglican Church.
Did I have to introduce myself like that for you to realize?
I hope you're not cold like that, young miss Lidvia.
How did you find out about this private jet?
I had them paste one on the aircraft parked in Haneda airport.
You're creepy as usual.
That personality of yours, when you laugh crazily like that the more it means you're cornered.
Can't you do something about it?
The more difficult the situation, the greater the happiness will be when it's overcome.
I must thank my Lord.
What's wrong?
The higher the wall, the greater the happiness will be when you surpass it.
Sure, that's logical in one sense, I thought.
You bastard on the cliff edge!
Lidvia,
If you discard the teachings of Rome and lick my feet, I can save you.
What nonsense do you speak of?
I see.
Then make a crater together with that.
Croce di Pietro?
I won't let you do that!
With my current speed, I will make it.
No, I will surely make it in time.
It will be very close.
But that's what makes it fun!
So Lidvia, which will you choose?
A Ceremonial Item classed as the greatest in this world,
or one pitiful wandering sheep?
The greater the difficulty of the trial,
when you overcome it, you will have a greater happiness in trampling me, who created the challenge.
Trample?
Over that great flower, as much as I want...
It's shaken quite immensely.
The growth of the Imagine Breaker who would become the key is still unstable.
Would this become of use or not?{theres something up on screen so... I think he means if that item? is useful or not}
Maybe I have to think of the possibility for me to take action in person.
What are you doing here?
I was sleeping on the bench in the lobby.
They said I can't use it when morning comes, so...
A nice and soft bed...
Are you all right now?
Yes, according to what the Frog doctor said, I can leave tomorrow or the day after.
Aisa, you look somewhat lonely.
Why is that?
Was that person doing something reckless again?
Yes, he was.
Oh right, I haven't heard the details yet, but...
It was something like the Roman Catholic magicians taking advantage of the Daihaseisai to invade us.
And then Touma ran off on his own without consulting me again.
He then went on a huge rampage on his own,
and told me like he made a report all after it happened.
It's unforgivable, right?
I see.
He didn't care who it was.
He will help anyone that's in trouble.
Even if it isn't me.
Maybe I shouldn't have been helped.
I might only be trouble to everyone.
Of course, that's wrong.
Since it seems like Touma is happy when he's together with Aisa.
Fukiyose-san, how can you slap someone after coming to visit their hospital room?
Shut up!
Anyone would be surprised if they suddenly see a man naked!
It was you who entered while I was changing.
What did you say?
Do you know why that person fights?
Who knows?
The last time I asked that, he said it was for him or something.
For Touma, that must be happiness.
Next Episode Preview
Is it good or bad fortune,
Index and I are suddenly going to Italy.
Next Episode Preview
Since it's the case, we will have a nice sightseeing trip!
Huh? Orsola?
The Amakusa-style are here as well?
Next episode: City of Water.
When science and magic cross, the story begins.