Now for tomorrow's weather, September the 14th.
It should be another sunny day throughout the country,
but the weather will gradually degrade starting from evening all the way into the night.
Touma, Touma.
What?
There are things that look like tree rings on the map.
How do they figure out what the weather will be tomorrow from that?
Oh, those are isobar contour lines.
They probably make forecasts by looking at high- and low-pressure systems.
Huh?
Does that mean the Academy City
has already made fortune-telling a reality through artificial systems?
Here, tasting time for you.
It's still hot since I just made it.
Be careful when you're eating-
Huh?
Touma!!!
Unfair! That's unfair, Touma!
You always get pissed off when I steal food to eat.
You will eat all the food if I don't keep an eye on you.
But Touma,
that weather forecast lady sometimes says things that are off.
Is that clumsiness her charm?
It just means that weather forecasts aren't absolute after all.
They were, until a while ago though...
Huh?
This is Shuttle 258.
We will hereby collect the remnants.
Remnant
Seriously, this is just unacceptable.
We can't keep having these schoolwide P.E. lessons so often because the Daihaseisai is coming up.
It can't be helped.
Our Tokiwadai Academy came in a humiliating second at last year's Daihaseisai,
so the people are desperate to win this year.
By the way Onee-sama, what are your plans after school today?
Why do you ask?
Oh well, I just wanted to go shopping once in a while with you...
and enjoy sweets like cake or something.
Since we keep missing each other these days.
Like me being busy with Judgment duties,
and you, Onee-sama, have been going around searching for some accessory...
Honestly, I'm a little lonely these days.
Kuroko?
Innocent...
I will show her my innocent face today.
And she would deny that,
she will show her desire to be protective, and I will act completely babyish.
What sweets?
You keep having tons of that sweet stuff after your Judgment work or whatever
and that's giving you that large tummy-
Onee-sama~!
American Space Shuttle Launched Successfully
Onee-sama?
They are frequent these days, don't you think?
If I recall correctly, the French and Russians do as well.
Even the Spaniards launched one last week.
Is something the matter, Onee-sama?
You don't seem to be in a very good mood.
Obviously.
Since I got to witness something as outrageous as receiving a fully naked dropkick out of nowhere.
Just finish your shopping already!
It's quite embarrassing to go along with your hobby, you know?
Onee-sama, you should use this chance to dress up appropriately as the Ace of Tokiwadai!
Like this,
and this...
and this too.
Breast pads?
Onee-sama is interested in this kind of stuff?!
Could it be, you're interested in a man?
I-It's not like that.
Of course not.
Onee-sama having such capricious thoughts for a man-
Come to think of it, on the last day of summer vacation...
No, that can't be, for Onee-sama out of all people...
Right, Onee-sama-
Wh-What is this seriously positive reaction that I can't even joke about?
Please don't say you are... you are in love with that ape...
Oh it's not like that. I don't have any interest in such things.
Since even if I put them on, it will be revealed when I undress.
Huh?
Onee-sama...
You have planned for the future that includes such activities?!
I mean it's not like that!
I'm talking about P.E.!
Like when we change for P.E....
Hey, your mobile is ringing.
Geez.
This isn't the time for that.
Hello?
Oh, is it Uiharu?
A robber?
You can leave that stuff to the Antiskills.
In the 23rd Academy District?
You mean that place for aerospace technology matters?
I'm sorry Onee-sama, I had you spend your time with me, but...
Oh, it's fine.
More importantly, you should return early today.
Since the weather might worsen tonight.
Yes, I see...
Oh, Shirai-san!
Are you the only one here, Uiharu?
Everyone happens to be out now.
Ah, I'll make some tea.
Thanks for that, but I don't need it right now.
No way...
I wanted to enjoy, even if it were a little, a taste of being an Ojou-sama!
I'll teach you about the proper manners of a lady on some other occasion.
For now, give me a summary about the incident.
Look at this.
What is this?
A transceiver instead of a mobile phone?
The victims are quite fishy too.
And then this is...
An emblem of the 23rd Academy District...
The model number was matched.
This suitcase is a special type, since it's completely airtight and can counter cosmic rays.
Don't tell me they were supposed to carry it into outer space.
It might be the other way around and they carried it back from outer space.
We might be able to solve this quicker if we can capture the thieves.
What about their escape route?
They abandoned their cars and went into the underground city.
Huh?
There's a traffic jam caused by a problem with the traffic lights.
Things like that don't happen very often though...
Think of it as luck turning in our favor.
Huh?
Uiharu, you pursue those who escaped.
Hey, Shirai-san!
Hurry up!
Excuse me.
What?!
Teleportation?
I'm over here.
I'm from Judgment.
Do I need to explain why I'm here?
Damn it!
Such an obsolete gun...
Are they from the Outside?
Hello, is it Uiharu?
Hey, Kuroko?
Onee-sama?
I have a favor to ask you.
Where are you now?
Oh, you're still in the middle of work.
I'm so sorry.
I must have bothered you.
Not really.
So what is the favor you wanted to ask me?
Well, I heard from a kouhai that we have a sudden room inspection.
I was hoping that you would hide my personal items.
You're still not home either, Onee-sama?
Oh, it's fine.
I'll ask someone else.
You should come home soon as well.
They say it might rain continuously starting tonight until tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Hey, Onee-sama!
I can't allow Onee-sama to ask a favor from someone else other than me!
It means I must teleport to the student dorm immediately!
Huh?
Who are you?
Teleportation?
Ah, so you've figured it out already?
A quick understanding, as expected from a similar ability user.
My ability is Move Point.
Unlike a failure such as you, I don't need to touch the object in order to move it.
Well, isn't it wonderful?
Shirai Kuroko-san, from the Judgment Activities Branch 177.
Too easy!
I said, I'm not that easy!
Didn't I say I didn't need to touch the objects?
Too bad.
I didn't think she was the type of person who would get her kouhai involved in personal matters.
That Misaka Mikoto...
Huh?
Why would you mention Onee-sama's name here?
If you bought this you were ripped off.
Oh, you didn't know?
Although it seems like she's not unknowingly exploiting you.
The Railgun from Tokiwadai must be very noble.
Didn't you think it was a little too convenient?
That our men were caught in a traffic jam.
You surely know what ability the Ace of Tokiwadai controls.
What have you been talking about?
Remnant... Well, you probably don't know what I'm talking about.
Silico-random... Maybe that's too difficult too.
That's right.
You might understand if I call it the remains of the Tree Diagram.
What if I were talking about the central processor of the supercomputer that is considered as the brains of the Academy City,
which still holds enormous possibilities even after its destruction?
You're joking.
It should still be in satellite orbit.
Here's an attached report concerning its destruction.
Rare stuff, right?
The Tree Diagram was destroyed ages ago.
That's why people around the world are racing to get its remains, the Remnants.
It must be tough for Misaka Mikoto.
Thanks to someone destroying the Tree Diagram, her nightmare ended.
But when they restore it, the experiments will repeat again.
I must say I might understand her desire to go on a futile resistance.
Experiment?
You still don't understand?
You really must be out of the picture.
August 21st.
Huh?
If you are able to reach up to that, I might be able to accept you as my friend.
*Splash*
Misaka, Misaka jumps into the bath.
And then with a feeling of openness goes on to kick the water.
Come on, even though you are so small, don't just feel some openness in this small bath-
How inconvenient is it not being able to use reflection ability?
Misaka, Misaka looks with pitying eyes.
Besides, how can ability users be in tears because of shampoo?
Misaka, Misaka is dumbfounded.
I'm not in tears!
And if I use your network to calculate, reflections-
Yomikawa!
Why do I have to take care of this bastard?!
There was no better choice.
Damn that Kikyou.
Forcing me to deal with needless troubles.
Well, they don't look like they're going to create too many problems after all.
Yomikawa!
I found out the name of the ability user you fought against.
Musujime Awaki, a Level 4, 2nd year student from Kirigaoka Girl's Academy.
About her ability, Move Point,
As you said in your report, she's capable of moving objects that are far away from her.
So it's a spatial movement from coordinate A to coordinate B.
Anything else you found out?
Umm... she's unable to interfere with ability users that have similar powers.
Also, she has a tendency to hesitate when teleporting herself.
Maybe it's because she suffered significant injuries two years ago.
Also, this is unconfirmed information, but...
She is one of the Guides.
Guides?
Into that doorless and windowless building...
The HQ of the Chair of the Board of Directors to the Academy City Administration...
But that should have been an urban myth!
Are you okay, Shirai-san?
I'm fine, so continue with your report.
Okay.
According to Antiskill's information, the men in black that were being attacked were detained.
Their identities were carriers recruited by the 23th Academy District.
That was obtained from the Psychometrers reading their memory.
But they knew nothing about the contents of the case.
So the 23th Academy District was in the process of transporting the contents of the case to a different research institution,
when Musujime's group intercepted them and had it taken away.
Remnant... Tree Diagram...
It must be tough for Misaka Mikoto.
The nightmare should have ended.
More importantly, you should return early today.
Since the weather might worsen tonight.
Shirai-san?
Shouldn't we leave the matters of this incident in the hands of the Antiskills?
Somehow it feels like it's gone beyond our capabilities or...
I'm hanging up.
Huh?
Kuroko?
What is it, Onee-sama?
Are you taking a bath?
At least turn the lights on if you've come home.
I-It's what they call saving energy.
I'm an earth friendly woman!
Oh, really?
But the Academy City mainly runs on wind power.
We don't need to worry about carbon dioxide emissions, right?
How mean of you, Onee-sama.
I was thinking of using this as an excuse to lure you into this semi-ominous atmosphere.
What the heck is that?
Where have you been until now, Onee-sama?
I would say, collecting the accessories I failed to buy.
It's quite difficult to find.
As for now, I came home to collect something I forgot.
I will be heading out again.
I hope it doesn't rain.
Since the weather reports are unreliable these days.
That's right.
Thanks for worrying about me.
I'll try as much as I can to come home as soon as possible.
Onee-sama...
August 21st,
Violent winds of unknown causes occurred on that night.
A rail yard was annihilated in the 17th Academy District.
And on the next day...
Uiharu,
Musujime's group has something to do with an organization outside the Academy City.
Can you simulate their escape route?
I'm sorry, Onee-sama.
You carry a darkness unimaginable to us.
Ouch...
And you are trying to prevent me from getting involved in it.
So I will apologize now,
for meddling despite my uselessness, to put an end to the nightmare Musujime talks about.
Onee-sama!
Come out, coward!
How long do you plan to hide like that?!
Onee-sama...
You seem to be in quite a hurry today.
Are you that scared of having the Remnants rebuilt?
Or are you scared of the experiments that will resume?
Shut up!
You should leave those things as they are now.
They were made for the experiment anyway.
You should let them be destroyed, as they were intended to be.
Are you seriously saying that?
In the end, you are fighting for yourself, right?
Regret, grief and anger...
Just for small self-fulfillment like that.
That's right.
I'm annoyed.
So annoyed that my veins in my brain would rupture.
Did that idiot think I wouldn't notice?
Hearing such a fainthearted voice, it's just...horrible.
Sure I am annoyed, at my too-complete-that-it's-stupid kouhai,
the scumbag in front of me,
and most importantly at myself that created this situation!
You're so kind that it's overly sweet.
If you kept grieving that you were a victim too, you didn't need to fight.
Anyway, I can't be caught here.
Whatever the method I use, I will have to escape.
You thought you would succeed?
I see what your plans are already!
Your shield is full of holes!
Question:
How many unrelated commoners are included with them?
It seems that from here onwards, it's my turn.
Now let's go, Shirai Kuroko.
To make sure that you can return home,
go into the deepest part of the battlefield.
If that's true, it must be rushed.
Misaka kicks up the priority level within herself.
Although its curfew time already, I feel there's no time to waste...
Misaka frantically uses many emergency excuses for herself.
That even at this very moment, when things are turning for the worse,
Misaka is...
Next Episode Preview
Shirai Kuroko and Musujime Awaki, a battle between Teleprocess begins.
The sisters start their move concerning the Remnant.
And she does too.
Next episode: Move Point.
When Science and Magic cross, the story begins.