Oh! God damn it!
The neccesary conditions for an ESP-card experiment?
How would a Level Zero Kamijou-san know that?
Imagine Breaker, the mysterious ability residing in my right hand...
It seems that any unnatural power will be cancelled just being in contact with it.
But this 'oh-so-wonderful' ability holds no benefits towards the summer vacation homework.
August the 31st
To make matters worse, Misaka Mikoto forced me to pretend to be her boyfriend on that day... {Even worse on a day like this, I got forced to pretend to be a boyfriend by Misaka Mikoto,}
...while some Aztec magician chased after me...
...and many horrible incidents happened subsequently ...
The result? I've effectively finished none of my homework.
I see.
So in Magical Powered Kanamin,
they use plastic to replicate 'Lotus Wand' and 'Parts of Ether in Elemental.'
The Japanese way of doing things sure is magnificent.
Uhh, Index-san,
I won't tell you to stop watching TV,
but please keep the volume low at leas-
Touma won't play with me at all!
That's why I'm immersing myself in the world of television!!!
Ouch!
Damn! Why are you always giving me more stuff to do when I'm so short on time?
Huh?
Hey where did my half-finished worksheet go?
Where did my classic literature workbook go? And my math reference book?!
Oh, Touma!
Did you find it?!
It's already past three o'clock.
Huh?
I'd like some snacks!
What misfortune...
Index Librorvm Prohibitorvm...
The Index of Forbidden Books, eh?
August 31st
Oh my, what an arduous task of finding the worksheet under a mountain of comic books.
So Touma, aren't I worthy of praise?
Aren't I?
Don't you have something you need to say to me?
Don't you?
What are you trying to imply?
I did a lot of work, so I want proper compensation.
Actually, I want something to eat.
You just had pudding, including mine!
Oh! That looks nice!
Hirayama Rami's 5h Cooking
"How to make soy bean rich Toufu Hamburger"
Today, we will be demonstrating hamburgers that take five hours to make!
Hirayama Rami's 5h Cooking
"How to make soy bean rich Toufu Hamburger"
I've said I have no time to make that stuff!
Currently it's past five in the evening and just about seven hours before the day is over.
Even if I pull an all-nighter, I have less than fifteen hours before I have to go to school.
With just this little time left...
Touma,
It's bad for your health to work under so much stress.
Your mind might slip to a worse state if you're so stressed.
Don't overwork yourself.
You're the last person I want to hear that from!
This is the place.
Bow of Wind Spirits!
Bow of Striking!
Not here...
I just had a bad feeling about something...
Hey Touma!
Can I order anything?
What?
Just what do you want?
Then...
The most expensive thing?
So you want 2,000 yen worth of raw eggs...
Touma!
Index and I, Kamijou Touma went to a family restaurant for a change of environment.
I assumed I started my battle against the remaining forces of summer vacation homework...
Thank you for waitin-ah-
Here!
I will now enter the battlefield.
My report for Introduction to Ability Development...
Uhh... I'll bring something to wipe it off right away!
B-But Touma, it's still legible...
You only have to copy it onto a new sheet of paper.
I already wrote three pages...
You're lucky that you don't have to think up of the content afresh.
I now declare the start of battle!
Bow of Destructive Magic!
Why you!
What are you doing-
I'm over here!
I did not foresee this outcome, but I will be glad with only a few needless casualties.
I will not harm you if you surrender now.
If I attain what I came here for-
M-My homework got turned into confetti!
Hey! You there!
Take responsibility for what you did!
Redo my homework!
It's none of my business.
Okay.
Kamijou-san is somewhat violent today.
Oh, huh?
I will finish the job quickly.
I do not wish to participate in child's play.
What are you thinking?
What are you going to do with Index?
You should already understand.
If you know that this is the Index of Forbidden books with 103,000 books in its memory.
You are a magician!
Indeed.
Bow of Transparent Magic!
Hey, you bastard!
I just grabbed hold of something small and soft!
Are you there, Index?
Wh-What?!
Damn it! He got away!
Excuse me, dear customer...
Although I didn't give her have a phone for such situations...
Of course, she wouldn't pick up.
Damn! Where should I look?
Hey!
Hey, where are you going Sphinx?
Wait for me!
A hotel?
Could she be in there?
Over there, Sphinx?
There?
Index!
Damn you!
Don't you have the least bit of gratitude towards your owner?!
Whatever the circumstances, it was Index who found you!
Let's keep searching.
I'm surprised.
You've already removed two knots in this short period of time.
The culture of using ropes in torture originated in Japan.
You won't be able to force anything out of me by using such a crude method.
I've said before that my goal is not to torture you.
I only wish to acquire a volume from the collection of magic books within you.{From the magic books within you, I just want to have one volume from the collection.}
Now...
I'll first have to create an amplifying magic boundary.
If you bought this you were ripped off.
Just what is that magician planning to do with Index?
Damn it!
Where should I be searching?
Sorry!
Hey, what are you doing here?
You always seem to be running about somewhere.
At least let me know if you're doing all right!
Oh right, you don't have my number...
Huh?!
Geez!
You're always like this.
Quit acting stupid-
Oh, huh?
Why do you look like you're just about to cry?
I'm in a hurry, like a real hurry!
Homework, kidnapping and some incident at the restaurant and other stuff!!!
Hurry, what's your business?
Oh, what?
N-No... Just that...
I was just annoyed that you ignored me and...
It's nothing serious or anything but... nothing serious...
Sorry!
Hey! You're really leaving me here like this?!
Hey!
Note: Kagura - Spiritual music and dancing as an offering to the gods
Is this supposed to be a Kagura stage?{need explanation for Kagura? orz spiritual music and dancing as an offering to the gods}
It is nothing that great.
Note: Kagura - Spiritual music and dancing as an offering to the gods
It would only pass to be the dance stage of a summer festival at best.
Are you going to have something possess me by preparing that?
My purpose for creating this magic boundary is to increase this thing's ability.
An Azusa bow?
It's a ceremonial object used in Shinto practise.
Amazing.
You even cover the cultural traditions of the East.
Against that magic book library of yours...
...this ability will only be able to jolt your mind and correct distortions at best with its original scale of power.
Index!
Hey Index, where are you now?!
...this ability will only be able to jolt your mind and correct distortions at best with its original scale of power.
However under the right conditions, it can read the opponents mind in detail.
Yes... I can even reveal those 103,000 books you secretly hold in your mind.
No you mustn't!
Surely, you know what will happen when someone other than myself comes in contact with the magic books!
Of course.
I couldn't be more sure.
What was that?
That hotel from earlier!
Damn it!
That's the Baopuzi - Master who Embraces Simplicity.
It's a magic book of eternal life from the Sinosphere on becoming an immortal.
Written in it is Chinese alchemy with instructions for the reader to make medicine to cure any disease or curse.
I thought I would be able to do anything if I became a Magician.
I vowed to become a Magician because I didn't want to give up against a curse.
At least not for this stuff.
There was a woman nearly dead from some sort of curse.
With death approaching right behind her, the only thing she could do was smile.
She was a powerless, boring person.
Being unable to save such a boring person,
I cannot talk about being able to do anything or not wanting to give up...
I cannot ruin the precious dream I've always had for such a boring woman.{For such a boring woman I cannot ruin the(can't hurt my) precious dream I've always had.}
Surely not for that boring woman.
Definitely not for the sake of that boring woman!
You're wrong!
I understand.
Your Azusa bow's power is amplified so much that your mind is flowing back into mine.
That's why I understand.
Simply because you love that woman
is why you want to save her even at the cost of your life.
You had to hurt others and commit crimes in your bid to save her
since you didn't want that woman to bear any responsibility.
Which is why you must not taint yourself!
You cannot choose such a method that relies on these half-tainted magic books!
Touma!
Geez you made me worry.
Touma, I'm hungry!
Okay, I'll let you have all the water you can drink.
Hey, Touma!
Am I mistaken?
Am I mistaken to feel the need to protect someone even if it cost me my life?!
Of course you are!
You already know!
The pain of having someone precious die in front of you.
Having someone being hurt and in agony right before you...
Yet you being unable to do anything for them...
You know the pain of being powerless...
You must have felt time was running out, the weight of the burden.
You must have felt distress.
You must have felt anguish.
You must have felt fear.
You must have been shaking.
You must have shouted out loud.
You must have shed tears.
Then what you're doing is wrong!
You cannot let anyone carry such a burden!
Geez.
I'm in this state after just reading one volume...
Look, it was impossible to take in even one original copy in such a small vessel like me.
My life consists only of failures.
I have already given up on life three times.
But still...
Only one thing I couldn't give up... just that one thing...
But even so...
Ouch!
I won't let you have such a peaceful death. {NO YOU NOOO WHERES MY NICEBOAT NICE BOATO NAISU BOOOAAATTTOOO check your anus it's there}
That's for ruining my summer homework.
Geez.
Thanks to you it's impossible for me to finish my homework.
So?
Where is that important person of yours?
What?
I mean, you don't need to use the Index of Forbidden Books to do something about it.
You've seen what my right hand can do, right?
I am no magician, so I don't know what curses are like.
But with this, I can probably erase some curse with a touch.
No way...
I don't understand it well myself, but that's how my right hand works.
So...
Bring me to her.
I will surely save that important person of yours.
But to do that I'll need your cooperation.
So I will have you help me no matter what.
You want to save her with your own power too, right?
Geez.
Magic and curses and all that stuff...
Getting thrown around the place with that weird stuff...
Now let's set off to break all those stupid illusions.
Text on fan: "Imouto"
Do you know who you've just attacked...?
Geez.
The Knights that England is so proud of are in this state.
Did you come to stop me?
I've not been told to stop you as an individual.
And I have my work too.
Where did the order come from, the Anglican Church or the Academy City?
Who knows?
Well it should be easy to figure out if you use some common sense.
Rather, you would figure it out easily if you take into account which side I'm spying for.
I am going now.
Feel free to report to your superiors.
Fine.
Oh yeah, I'll put them away.
Thank you.
And so, why did you need to take this long journey from England?
Who knows?
Next Episode Preview
Index has been kidnapped suddenly.
A huge plot is taking place outside of the Academy City...
Next Episode Preview
What is the true purpose of the syndicate targeting Orsola Aquinas?
Next episode: Liber AL vel Legis.
When Science and Magic cross, the story begins.