What is the emergency patient's condition?
She still remains unconscious.
Was it heat stroke after all?
Heat stroke...?
Oh, so I collapsed and...
But why?
I was taking in fluids...
I also got enough sleep.
I'm such a fool.
Fukiyose, are you all right?
Fukiyose!
Is he going to keep showing this expression?
I don't want that.
I was working hard, so that everyone could enjoy themselves.
Will I be alright?
Just who do you think I am?
Shorthand
I'm in this state just because I lost some of my specialties.
Kami-yan has destroyed Oriana's Shorthand.
Has something changed with your condition?
I'm fine.
Doesn't seem like there's anything wrong anymore.
I see.
Then please perform the search spell of the Rihashijin.
I have already prepared it for you.
You do know how to use it, right?
Don't underestimate me.
Is it okay on your side?
If I remember correctly, Oriana's counterattack spell was within the stadium.
No problem.
But a student fell victim to it.
We left in the confusion that happened as a result.
I see.
Is Kamijou Touma furious?
If you're able to figure that out, then please do your job.
Otherwise, we can't be sorry enough to the student who collapsed.
No one is complete.
That's why they regret their own incompleteness, huh?
I wasn't expecting this outcome.
I've confirmed Oriana Thomson's location.
In the 7th Academy District, near the Futsuka subway station.
Kami-yan, it's Futsuka station!
Futsuka station?
We've already passed that!
She's moving north.
The street splits into three, but...
It came up now.
All right, you'll see in front-
Found her!
Damn it!
A bus!
Hey Kami-yan, did that bus have any passengers other than Oriana?
That doesn't matter!
Kami-yan!
There weren't any!
No passengers, not even a driver!
Then no worries.
Stiyl, it's bus 5144-57.
Stiyl left some runes on it back at the service depot.
Fire doesn't make me hot.
That being said,
I was in such a hurry that I got a little wet down there.
Wanna have a peek?
It's dripping wet right down to my underwear.
Thanks to that spell you set up, an innocent bystander collapsed!
Did it look like she had anything to do with magic?
There's no one who's unrelated.
People can have relationships with anyone if they feel like it.
So you do understand.
I honestly didn't mean to hurt her.
Unlike this.
Tsuchimikado!
Oh my.
It wasn't you who was hurt.
It looks like the Academy City gathers up really rare kids.
What did you do to Tsuchimikado!?
I just cancelled the scarlet properties that are a symbol of rebirth and recovery with blue writing.
{It's a spell that makes those with greater injuries than a certain threshold become unconscious.}It's a spell that knocks people unconscious when their injuries pass a certain threshold.
Tsuchimikado!
Damn it!
I have to destroy that card!
If you want to save him, then you must beat me as fast as you can.
But will he last long enough?
He won't last too long, you know?
Why you...
I don't give a damn about the worth of some Stab Sword.
Nor do I care about how much it could change history.
I don't know how it can move the world.
But...
It's wrong for someone to get hurt for something that stupid!
If it's a tool that only gives birth to such needless results,
I will shatter and destroy it with my own hands!
It's my work, so it can't be helped.
That being said, your comment would be disrespectful towards my client.
Since I have full authority over my methods...
Quit messing with people's lives!
Where?
Crap!
If she uses that spell again...
Next comes a blade of shadows.
I won't allow you to get bored.
Why doesn't she use the same attack?
I have no interest in using the same spell I've used already.
You're such a failure.
That was just the foreplay.
You're worn out already?
Damn it!
Even though she isn't using the same magic she's used before...
How does she have such a huge inventory of combinations?
Next is Blade Crete.
Hey you.
Move from that position and you die.
Move, and I die?
Why should I care about that?
The Daihaseisai that Fukiyose has been working so hard up till this day to prepare,
is about to become a mess!
You thought I could leave it like this?
Of course you wouldn't be satisfied with that!
Kamijou Touma?
T-This idiot!
That right hand...
Even to that extent?
Then...
Drop Left!
Tsuchimikado!
Are you all right?
Tsuchimikado?
You play way too rough.
Look, my buttons came off.
That was a good punch, for a beginner.
I guess.
However, being used to having attacks being read and getting counter attacked,
I would still consider your level as unsatisfactory..
Well for now, I leave that to your side.
Don't think the game is over here.
It's going to heat up from now on.
Wait!
What about Tsuchimikado?
The effect of the spell only lasts for 20 minutes.
It'll wear off soon.
Dear worrywart ability user.
All right.
Then destroy the Stab Sword.
It shouldn't be a problem using your right hand.
But is it okay for me to destroy it?
They might go on attacking people in the Academy City...
It would be them who would be captured if they do so.
This is the Academy City.
For the people on the magic side, it's in the middle of enemy territory.
They will retreat at once and take some time to think of countermeasures.
I got it.
Hurry up.
I will discuss our future course of action with my superiors.
I got it.
Well then...
What is this?
What the hell is this?
Well, though a lot of things happened...
Since I've gone through all the required checkpoints,
there's no need for you to worry.
What do you mean by a lot of things?
Well, leave it to me.
Oh right.
Since they've taken the sign away,
They should have already figured out about the Stab Sword by now as well.
Oh?
It's okay.
Since it's not a situation that would change the outcome of the transaction anyway.
I wouldn't let anyone get in the way.
And no one would be able to do so.
If everyone will be happy from this transaction, then that's all the more reason for it.
There isn't an original of the Stab Sword.
Only people's speculations have formed such a lasting legend.
Oh, really?
Is what's written here the truth?
Charles Conder?
We're very sorry.
We here at the British Museum didn't figure this out until this very day.
Then, what do you say that is?
Well yes...
Since the legends are snowballing and transforming, we have no definite conclusion, but...
This is no sword.
Then what?
In the origin, they call it the Croce di Pietro.
In our words here, it seems it would have been called St. Peter's Cross.
St. Peter's Cross?
Then the meaning of the transaction they are doing has changed from the original one.
With the end of the transaction, the Academy City will collapse.
No, something greater than that would happen.
Geez.
That's absurd!
So this means the item is dangerous after all?
Croce di Pietro,
something that could be considered St. Peter's Cross.
The Episcopal See of the Roman Catholic Church, the Vatican, started ages ago
when St. Peter's body was buried in a great body of land and a cross was placed there.
You could also put it the other way too.
The other way?
The land the Croce di Pietro was thrust into would without choice become under the control of the Roman Catholic Church.
Even if it were the Academy City.
Control?!
Everything would happen in the direction that the Roman Catholics would favor.
And no one would find anything strange with that change, and accept it.
Regardless of how unreasonable the requests may be,
or regardless of how outrageous a burden it may create,
a world where people would only feel happiness would be born.
No way...
If the Academy City conveniently falls into the hands of the Roman Catholics,
the world that's now in balance with one half as the Science side and the other as the Magic side,
would become completely dominated by a single Roman Catholic Church.
Then by transaction you mean...
Yes.
It's both the Academy City as a whole, and the right to rule the world.
We will stop this transaction.
Otherwise, the world would face a reality far worse than just a collapse.
Touma!
A world where everyone would only feel happiness...
I don't really understand after thinking about it.
Touma!
Huh?
No, there's no way Index would be wearing clothes like that.
Touma!
Why won't you look me in the eyes?
That aside, why are you dressed like that?
Come to think of it...
Touma, Touma,
You're trying to recall some lewd scene.
I seem to notice that Touma has a very happy expression.
I don't!
I really don't at all!
Actually, what happened to your usual sister outfit?
I had Komoe hold onto it.
Umm...
What are you so angry about?
Oh, I got it!
You're hungry, aren't you?
We will get together with father and mother and have lunch.
You only need to wait a little longer-
Umm... Index-san?
Ouch!
It's not like that!
You idiot, Touma!
Then what?
I changed into these so that I can cheer for Touma.
Where were you while I was doing that?
Uhh well...
I worked hard thinking that I could be with Touma.
What should I do if you were to go off somewhere on your own?
I'm so sorry.
I thought you were hungry and angry as usual.
Hey, that's not so!
Ouch, ouch!
I'm angry because it seems like you don't care about me!
As you said, I'm angry from being hungry, but that's an emotion that I'm unrelated to, considering that I'm a sister, Touma!
Index! What happened to your usual biting?
Oh no, you really don't have to force yourself to do it.
As you said, I'm angry from being hungry, but that's an emotion that I'm unrelated to, considering that I'm a sister, Touma!
Huh?
Touma, you pervert!
Wha- it was you who was always biting me.
You're the one who's actually perverted!
Ouch!
I think we won't be able to find Touma-san for a while.
Well, they have this many people.
We may not be able to find him after all.
Oh!
Hello!
We meet again.
Oh, you're the one from this morning.
Thank you for this morning.
Thanks to that, see?
Who are they?
Do you know them?
It's the parents of that boy you care so much about.
Nice to meet you, I'm Kamijou.
Hello.
Umm, I'm...
Come on, show some appeal.
I-It's not like that!
What are you saying!?
Oh, by the way, have you had lunch yet?
No, not yet.
If it's fine with you, would you care to join us?
We have a great place.
Really?
We would be grateful for that.
Oh, are you all right?
Oh no, I'm sorry.
I'm just not used to crowded places like this.
I-I wasn't paying enough attention either.
Well then, I shall be leaving.
Y-yes.
My, my.
Touya-san, again you're...
No, it's not like that!
I wasn't hooked by her or anything!
So you see, it's like...
I'm sorry!
They're indeed father and son.
Yo, Touma!
Over here!
Come here!
How did you find a place like this?
Well, this person over here told us.
I'm Misaka.
I see.
Thank you so much.
Phew, I'm really hungry.
Hey, you.
Why are you always with this search result = zero treatment for me?
Well, I thought things would just naturally turn out like this.
Like hell they would!
There's no such thing as a natural outcome with you around!
For starters, who is this girl that is always at your side all time, and where does she live?
Who? Well that's...
That's right, Touma.
Come to think of it, who is that girl?
She came along when we had that sleepover trip at the beach too.
The beach?!
A sleepover at the beach?!
And who's this short haired girl that's asking? Where does she even live?
Are you Touma's girlfriend or something?
No, I'm just...
You came to cheer for Touma's school as well?
If I remember correctly...
It was during stick toppling.
It's not!
Hey!
You shut up!
My, my.
We should have lunch now.
Umm...
You are Kamijou Touma-kun, right?
That's right, but...
Umm... are you Misaka's older sister or something?
Oh no.
I'm Misaka Misuzu.
Mikoto's mother.
Nice to meet you.
Mother?!?
Next Episode Preview
Solving and exposing the hidden mystery.
We will close into their goals one step at a time.
Next Episode Preview
But at that time,something happens to Himegami who was at the place by coincidence.
Next episode: Stab Sword.
When Science and Magic cross, the story begins.