Translation
Char Custom
Translation Check
Floris257
Editing
Tokyoblade
Timing
Floris257
AFX Logo
KakashiCopyNinja
OP / ED
Char Custom
K-timing
Vevlaa
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Typeset
Kaitou[Kid]
Floris257
Quality Control
Chippo   Floris257   Kaitou[Kid]
Encode
FixeR
Project Leading
Naruto-kun / Kaitou[Kid]
A Dull Light in Despair
-Restoration of Humanity  1 -
U
Hey, you maggot!
Yes, sir.
Who the hell are you?
From Shiganshina, Armin Arlart!
Is that so? That name sounds stupid!
Your parents gave you that?
My grandfather named me!
Arlart, what the hell are you here for?
My duty is to be a tool used in humanity's victory!
Ain't that wonderful?!
You'll probably become food for Titans!
Row 3! About face!
Who the hell are you?
From Trost, Thomas Wagner!
You're too fucking quiet!
From Trost, I'm—
Can't hear you! Go practice in the cattle shed!
They're doing a good job.
Next!
Weren't you were just like them when you joined the Training Corps?
From Karanese, Mina Carolina!
How nostalgic.
Wrong!
You are from a pig shed, more worthless than livestock!
Yes, sir! I am less than livestock!
What's the point of intimidating them?
No, you're a fly that swarms around a pig's ass!
It's a rite of passage.
Yes, sir!
We force them to abandon who they are,
Next!
From Snate Village, Samuel Linke-Jackson!
which creates a suitable warrior from scratch.
A horrible name! Change it now!
This process is necessary to achieve that.
What are you doing here?
To sacrifice myself for humanity!
Row 4! About face!
There seem to be some who he didn't talk to.
Listen up! I've seen a lot of shit in my time,
There is no need for those who have already received their rite of passage.
but you are the worst pieces of shit I've ever seen!
Perhaps, it's because they saw hell two years ago.
They have a different expression.
Come on, let's go.
Who the hell are you?
From Trost, Jean Kirschtein!
Why did you come here?
To join the Military Police Brigade and live within the city.
Is that right?
You want to live within the city?
Yes!
Who told you to sit?
Do you think you can join the Military Police Brigade if you lose heart that easily?!
Who the hell are you and why are you here?
From Wall Rose's Southern District, Jinae City, Marco Bodt!
I came to join the Military Police Brigade and dedicate my life to the king!
Is that so?
That's just splendid.
You should make that your goal.
But...
The king doesn't want your body.
You're next!
Who the hell are you?
Conny Springer, from Ragako Village in Wall Rose's Southern District!
That's the wrong side, Conny Springer.
I told you from the very beginning...
This salute signifies the devotion of your entire heart!
Is your fucking heart on the right?
Hey, you maggot.
What are you doing?
I'm talking to you, maggot!
Who the hell are you?!
From the Southern District of Wall Rose, Dauper Village, Sasha Braus!
Sasha Braus, what do you have in your right hand?
A steamed potato!
The kitchen had a fresh batch and I couldn't resist!
Maggot, did you steal it?
Why?
Why did you eat the potato just now?
It would be wasteful if it got cold.
I decided I should eat it right now.
Well, what I don't understand is...
Why did you eat the potato?
You mean, why do people eat potatoes?
Please, have half.
Ha...lf?
Whoa, that potato girl is still running!
That's incredible. She's been running for five hours.
But she seemed more saddened by not getting a meal, rather than running till she felt like dying.
If I remember correctly, Dauper is a hunting village with a small population in the mountains, isn't it?
What's that?
The drop outs.
They wanted to be transferred to the Reclaimed Area.
That can't be! But it's only the first day...
It can't be helped.
Those who are powerless must leave.
I guess they would rather gather rocks and cut weeds.
By the way, you weren't asked where you were from.
The same place as this guy, Shiganshina.
So that's it...
That must mean...
So you are saying, you were also there on that day?
H-Hey!
Did you see it? The freakishly large Titan?
Y-Yeah...
I'm telling you, I saw it.
Are you serious?
How big was it?
You could see its face from the wall.
What?!
I heard that it sat on both sides of the wall!
I did too!
They said the same thing in my village!
No, it wasn't really that big.
What kind of face did it have?
It had very little skin and a huge mouth.
What about the armored Titan that broke Wall Maria?
They call it that, but I thought it looked like a normal Titan.
Th-Then what about normal Titans?
Everyone, we should stop asking questions.
There are things no one wants to remember.
I'm sorry for aski—
That's not it!
Titans are actually not a big deal.
If we can master the 3-D Maneuver Gear...
They won't be an enemy for long!
Finally, I'm able to train as a soldier...
I was just so excited, I forgot myself for a second.
I'm going to join the Scouting Legion and exterminate Titans from this world.
I'll kill them!
Hey, hey, are you crazy?
Did you say you are going to enter the Scouting Legion?
Yeah, that's right...
I remember you said you wanted to join the Military Police Brigade and take it easy, right?
Well, I'm just honest.
It's much more refreshing than trying to act brave when you are frighted to your core.
Are you talking about me?
D-Don't do this...
Hey, hey...
Not in the slightest.
Hey, sorry about that.
I'm not trying to change your way of thinking.
Let's forget this ever happened.
Yeah, I was also at fault.
Hey, you!
W-W-Well, uh...
It's just that you weren't a familiar face, so I...
I'm s-sorry.
Your black hair's really pretty.
Thank you.
It's okay, just leave me alone!
When you get hot, you act impulsively.
Are you talking about that again?
More importantly, isn't your hair getting too long?
It might cause you to get in an accident when you train with the 3-D Maneuver Gear.
I understand.
Let's cut it.
How much should I cut off?
H-Hey! Don't just randomly touch people!
What did you wipe on my shirt?
My faith... in people.
Isn't this...
Bread!
I didn't have anything else but that, so I set it aside.
Umm... But you should drink some water first.
Are you God? Are you?!
Huh?!
Wai—
God!
Hey!
What are you guys doing?
Well... This girl has been running the whole time.
You... were just trying to do a good deed, right?
Did you do that for the potato girl?
Was the effort worth what you got out of that?
I guess it doesn't matter...
For the time being, let's bring her back to her bed.
Are you also gonna do a good deed?
I'm doing her a favor, just so she'll owe me.
I'm expecting a lot of her idiocy.
First, I will observe your aptitude!
Those of you who don't pass can be used as bait!
I'll have you transferred to the Reclaimed Area!
This is still the basics of the basics,
but, even at this stage, you can see their potential with the Maneuver Gear.
Look over there.
She's not swinging at all.
She knows everything about what to do and when.
That's what talent is.
This time we have a lot of talented recruits.
What about him?
That's also a certain kind of "talent."
Even if they have enough fighting spirit,
there are some things people just can't do.
What are you doing, Eren Jaeger?
Raise your upper body!
What's going on? How do I do it?
This can't be happening.
Currently Available Information
U
Three-Dimensional Maneuver Gear Training  1
Three-Dimensional Maneuver Gear training
rigorously adapts humans and animals moving in
two dimensional to move in three dimensions.
Currently Available Information
U
Three-Dimensional Maneuver Gear  2
It takes great physical strength, legwork, spacial
coordination, and spirit. Those who do not
panic easily are important in its use.
If you act by the fundamentals, you can surely do it.
Don't think about doing it well.
Watch your balance through your forward and backward motions.
Slowly rest your weight on the belts attached to your hips and feet.
If you calm down, you can do it.
Even I was able to do it.
All right! This time, I think I'll be able to do it.
Raise me up, Armin.
Hey, Daz...
He's the guy who said he'd kill all Titans, right?
Well, I bet he'll be off to the Reclaimed Area tomorrow.
We have no food to spare for useless people.
Eren.
You just have to let it go.
You'll just have to wait and see if you can get the hang of it by tomorrow.
I'm pathetic...
I'll never be able to kill them all like this.
You don't need to strive for that anymore.
What did you say?!
I'm saying you don't need to strive to become a soldier.
There are other ways to fight than by throwing away your life.
Hey! I saw what happened that day!
Do you think I'd be okay with that logic?
But it doesn't matter how determined you are.
What? Why?
The one who decides whether or not you can become a soldier isn't you.
I'm not saying you should return to the Reclaimed Area alone.
Let's go, Armin.
S-Sure.
Don't worry about it.
When that time comes, I'll also go with you.
Umm... So what you are saying is...
It's okay if I take that?
The trick to staying upright?
Sorry, but I'm a genius, so I can't say anything other than "feel it out."
Actually, I would like to know something.
How do you stay sane after such an ugly performance?
You guys... Even though I'm begging for help...
But didn't you say something yesterday about the powerless leaving?
Oh, was I wrong?
Or was it some something about the talentless leaving?
Which was it?
I'm begging you. I've heard you're both really good!
Bertolt! Reiner!
Sorry, but I can't come up with any trick to just hanging there.
I don't have anything that you are expecting.
Really?
All we can do is bet on tomorrow.
You two are from Shiganshina, right?
That's right, but...
Then you must know about how terrifying the Titans are.
So why are you trying to become soldiers?
Unlike Eren, I didn't see the Titans at close range.
But when I thought about how the government forced that insane plan to retake our territory,
I couldn't just stand still.
I see.
Where are the two of you from?
Reiner and I came from a mountain town, southeast of Wall Maria.
Huh? Isn't that...
Yeah.
Unlike the people who lived by the river, we weren't told immediately.
Anyhow, Titans showed up before we were told they were coming.
It was dawn.
Our livestock were unusually loud,
and I heard a large rumble from the ground.
Before I knew it, I realized that the sound was that of footsteps.
And then, when I quickly went to open the window...
After that... Umm, I don't really remember well.
Everyone was in a panic.
Hey, why are you suddenly talking about this?
I'm sorry.
What I wanted to say is that you are probably different from them.
"Them"?
The people here who don't know the terror of Titans.
Hey!
Most of them are here because they want to maintain an appearance.
They were told, "12 year olds who become workers are cowards."
After turning twelve, they became trainees.
Although, I'm no different myself.
I wanted to join the Military Police just to live safely in the interior city.
If I couldn't, I might have had to abandon everything.
I don't have much willpower.
Caring about your own life is admirable.
I'm going back to my hometown that I couldn't return to.
That's the only thing I can think about.
Absolutely! No matter what happens!
What about you?
Why are you trying to become a soldier?
I...
I thought only of killing them.
I thought about needing to slaughter Titans, by my own hands.
Yes, that's what I thought.
Even when you met the Titans, you didn't lose heart?
Yes, but right now I'm more worried about whether or not I can become a soldier.
Let's try and start by adjusting the belts.
Tomorrow will go better.
I'm sure you can do it.
Eren Jaeger was your name, right?
Yeah, thank you.
Reiner Braun, right?
Eren Jaeger, are you ready?
Yes!
I'll do it! I can do it!
I might not have talent, but...
I won't lose to anyone in willpower!
Let's get started!
I don't care about the theory.
I don't care about the fundamentals.
But that's all I have!
This is my weapon!
Yes!
I did it!
I can still...
I can still do it!
Lower him.
I...
Wagner, switch your belt with Jaeger.
Y-Yes, sir.
It was defective equipment.
The metal on your belt was damaged.
I've never heard of it breaking.
Looks like I need to add it to the maintenance list.
So he trained for a day with broken equipment?
That's incredible!
Th-Then, did I pass?
There's no problem.
Do your best.
I did it! I did it!
Did you see that, Mikasa? I did it!
I can fight the Titans!
I don't need you to look after me anymore!
I guess it all worked out.
He was saying, "What do you think of that?!" with his eyes.
No, he wasn't.
He's happy we don't need to be separated and is relieved.
Grisha, today your son became a soldier.
That place in my dream where my heart belongs
Is the thing that can break more easily than my life
It's tossed away many times yet found again
It becomes at ease and goes to sleep
It urges to start pounding
My wishes are invaded
When they're about to be forgotten
They are remembered again
Within this beautifully cruel world
We keep on living
But we ask why we still live on!
With our strength and weakness
What will we protect
If there is no more reason to?
Next Time
Having graduated from the Training Corps, Eren saw humanity regain its dignity.
"We can beat the Titans."
When he decided that, humanity learned its lesson again.
Night of the Disbanding
-Restoration of Humanity  2 -
U