Go, Eren!
In the year 850...
For the first time,
humanity's recovered part of its territory from the Titans.
Though, it was at great cost.
Hereby, I welcome everyone here to the Scouting Legion!
This is a true salute!
Offer up your hearts!
Yes, sir!
You have done well to endure your fear.
You are brave soldiers.
You have my heartfelt respect.
A month later,
led by Erwin Smith, the Scouting Legion left Karanes
to find a route to Shiganshina,
where it's believed the secrets of the Titans are held.
We will now begin the 57th Expedition Beyond the Walls!
Onward!
Female Titan
-57th Expedition Beyond the Walls   1 -
U
Ahead, to the left, ten-meter class!
I'm very interested in seeing what's inside its stomach...
but I'll leave it to the support team!
Damn!
Not deep enough.
Defend the formation!
Stay strong!
Leave it to the support team and keep going!
Onward! Onward!
The support teams will only accompany us to the old city.
Once we're past that, it's all Titan territory.
The long-range scouting formation devised by Commander Erwin is our only hope.
We, the Special Operations squad, are here.
Sir, can they...
Can my classmates beat the Titans?
Huh?
What have you been doing for the past month?
Listen, brat...
The most crucial aspect of an expedition is how you avoid fighting Titans—
Get in long-range scouting formation!
See ya, Armin.
Don't piss your pants if you run into a Titan.
Right!
Same to you, Jean.
Row 3-3: Relay
The vanguard is to spread out into a semi-circle,
but stay within visual range of one another.
Row 5-Center: Standby
Position yourselves at fixed intervals.
Row 2-5: Relay
Extend the recon and message relay range as far as possible.
Row 3-4: Relay
Row 2-4: Relay
We'll be fine.
Calm down!
It's the Forward Recon Squad that will probably encounter the Titans first.
Row 1-8: Scout
As soon as one is seen, they'll fire a red smoke flare.
Anyone that sees the flare, should fire the same round to relay the signal.
Row 2-Center: Command
When the Commander sees it,
he'll fire a green smoke flare
and show the formation where to go.
This way, the formation can advance toward the goal while avoiding the Titans.
Row 2-3: Relay
But sometimes, due to the terrain or obstacles,
a Titan might not be sighted, until it's within the formation.
Red... Red...
Red smoke flare...
Braus! Over here!
Damn it! Did we let one through?
We'll draw it this way.
Braus, get over here!
I'll handle it!
Split off!
Yes, sir!
Sir...
Back into position!
He ran out of steam.
Something's wrong...
It's been a while, since we saw the red smoke flare,
they still haven't reformed.
It can't be...
This strategy will only work on normal Titans, whose behavior can be easily predicted.
A black smoke round?
Is a Titan ignoring the nearby humans and heading for the formation's center?
No doubt about it.
That's...
an Abnormal!
It's only necessary to fight Abnormals,
whose behavior can't be predicted.
Damn it! We'll have to fight it...
Sys, go for the neck!
I'll stop it!
Roger!
Using Maneuver Gear on flat terrain is a huge disadvantage.
It almost never works.
But I can't let it disrupt the formation.
I think that's Arlert over there.
I don't want one of the new recruits to run into it.
We'll kill it here!
Now, Sys!
You did it, Squad Leader Ness!
Did I get him?
You came for me?
That's my partner...
I love you, Shallot!
Again?
What is the Right Flank Recon Squad doing?
If it ignored them and came this way,
it must be another Abnormal.
It can't be helped...
Sys, we'll do it again.
Right.
We've got the worst luck doing this twice in a row...
And I think it's at least a fourteen-meter class.
This'll be tough.
What's that?
It's too fast!
Don't let it reach Arlert!
Sys!
Right!
No... No.
That's no Abnormal.
It has intelligence!
Like the Armored or Colossal Titans, or Eren...
A human in the body of a Titan!
B-But who?
Why?
This is bad! What should I do?
I'm going to die too...
I'll be killed!
Go! Run!
What does it...
No, what do they...
What do they want?
Currently Available Information
U
Long-Range Scouting Formation 1
Devised by Scouting Legion Commander Erwin Smith.
Its usage has dramatically increased survival rates
outside the walls.
Currently Available Information
U
Long Range Scouting Formation  2
Put simply, it's a form of human "radar."
By quickly alerting Erwin in the center to the discovery of any Titans,
the Scouting Legion can change course.
Someone tell them...
That the Right Flank Recon Squad has been wiped out...
A female Titan brought a huge army of Titans!
Is anyone there?
It's not going to kill me?
Why?
It removed my hood...
to... to look at my face?
Armin!
Reiner!
Hey, can you stand?
You won't last outside the walls unless you're on horseback.
Hurry!
Right!
I saw the smoke flare signaling an Abnormal.
Was it that one with the nice ass?
That's no Abnormal...
It's a human in a Titan body!
What was that?
Wait a second.
We need to fire a smoke flare first.
H-Hurry...
There's an emergency over there.
With a smoke flare, I'll...
Wait... I think Jean fired it.
It came from the Right Flank.
Does that mean we've been so compromised that we can't even continue the mission?
It looks like the Right Flank Recon Squad has been wiped out...
Titans, tons of them.
I don't know why,
but there are lots of fast ones.
For now, we're holding them back,
but recon is no longer possible...
We've taken heavy losses.
If we aren't careful, we'll all be wiped out!
That Titan came from the same direction.
No way...
Was it leading the Titans?
It?
Why is a Titan over there?
An Abnormal?
No, it's a human in a Titan body...
Someone with the same ability as Eren.
What?
What makes you think that, Armin?
The Titans only eat us.
We're just killed in the process.
Killing us isn't their goal.
But when Sys aimed for its weak point,
it crushed him, and smashed him into the ground.
It killed him to kill, rather than to eat.
Its nature is different from the others.
When the Colossal and Armored Titans destroyed the walls,
it must've been the one that brought that army of Titans.
Their goal has consistently been to attack humanity!
No, maybe not.
It felt like it was looking for someone...
If that is the case, could it be looking for...
Could it be looking for Eren?
Eren?
Eren's with Squad Levi, which is in charge of the right flank.
The right flank?
The plans I saw had them to the rear of the left flank.
Mine said they were near the front of the right...
Wait, there's no way they'd be on the front lines.
So where are they?
Probably the safest place in the formation.
Which means in the center and toward the rear...
Armin!
There's no time to think.
There's no way smoke flares could indicate how much of a threat it is.
At this rate, it'll wipe out Command.
The formation will fall apart and everything will be over.
What are you trying to say?
In other words,
at this range, we may still be able to draw its attention.
We may be able to buy time to withdraw.
Maybe... Maybe...
But it really is intelligent.
To it, we are nothing more than insects.
It'll just crush us...
Seriously?
That's scary...
Hey, are you really Jean?
The Jean I know only thinks of himself.
Don't be an ass...
I just don't want those charred bones I saw
to be disappointed in me!
I...
I know what I have to do now!
And this is the job we chose.
Help me!
Put on your hood.
As far forward as you can...
So that your face is hidden.
I don't think it'll kill us until it knows who we are!
Oh...
You think it won't kill us because we could be Eren?
If nothing else, it'll make me feel better.
Let's just hope it has poor eyesight!
Armin, I always thought it was creepy how you used to cling to Eren,
but I've always thought you had it in you.
Uh, thanks.
But "creepy"? That's really mean...
It's going a lot slower than when I first saw it.
Is it tired?
If it runs at that speed again, we'll be too late!
Now's our chance. We have to do it now!
Listen up. Remember what I said.
Try to draw its attention for as long as you can
to give the formation time to withdraw!
Keep it here as long as possible.
If we could cut its Achilles tendon, that'd be more than enough.
But don't do anything stupid...
Don't try to kill it!
It's aware of the weak spot on its neck.
It's completely different than the other Titans...
It is impossible to kill.
At least, not by any normal human being.
However...
If it's those two, maybe...
Armin!
This one...
Its movements are more precise than the others!
Damn it.
I...
I underestimated it!
It protected its neck...
Jean!
Damn it! I can't get away!
I'm going to die!
Once it grabs my wire, it's over!
Jean!
Avenge the bastard who rushed to his death!
Armin?
It stopped?
That's the one...
That's the one that killed him!
He rushed to his death on the right flank!
Avenge him!
What happened?
Did Armin hit his head and go crazy?
This isn't the time...
R-Reiner?
It crushed my best friend!
I saw his body under its foot!
He's going straight for the neck?
No, it's working!
While it's distracted by Armin!
H-Hey...
H-Hey... Reiner, you...
Reiner did it!
Mikasa was so strong, I forgot.
But he's really strong and reliable too.
We've bought enough time, right?
Let's get the hell away from it!
If it isn't a man-eater, it won't follow us!
Look...
That big bitch got scared and decided to go home!
No... Why?
That's toward the center rear.
Is it...
heading towards Eren?
Next Time
"You monster..."
Even the highly trained members of the Scouting Legion
are unable to stop the Female Titan.
The monster finally catches sight of Eren in a forest of giant trees.
Forest of Giant Trees
-57th Expedition Beyond the Walls  2 -
U