Was it shocking for you?
Monster Character Theater!
Something is scaring you.
Enemies will hunt you no matter what you do!
Fly, Trainee Corps!
Fly!
Monster Character Theater
Trainee Corps
Day 08
The Trainee Corps.
This is where the boys and girls who volunteered to halt the advancements of the Titans learn the skills of battle.
It's similar to a school.
*Clang, clang, clang, clang!*
Equip your 3-D Maneuver Gear
and assemble on the training grounds.
Ah, Mikasa, good morning.
Whoa! We suddenly have 3-D
Maneuver Gear training today!
Armin, do you know where Eren is?
I think Eren's probably still asleep.
You didn't wake him up?
I tried to wake him up,
but no matter how much I shook him, he wouldn't wake up.
Something like that won't wake Eren up.
You need to pour water over his head or something.
Wouldn't it be better if you went to wake him up?
Hey, Armin.
The girls are going to use this classroom to change.
Stop chit-chatting and get out already.
O-Okay.
I'm late! So late!
Eren, wait! That room's...
*Open!*
I'm sorry for being la—
Hey! Eren better not have done that on purpose!
I-I'm sure he entered by mistake.
What? You're gonna cover for him?
Eren...
If you wanted to see it that badly,
all you had to do was say.
Hey, Eren!
I didn't have any intention of peeking or anything!
I tried to stop you, but you didn't even listen.
So? How was it?
How? How was what?
You saw what was inside, right?
Everyone wants to hear about it!
No, I didn't have time to look around.
Eren, it's not fair to keep those
wonderful memories to yourself.
Even if you put it like that...
*Open.*
Hey, Eren! You're scum.
Krista was crying.
I-I wasn't cr—
Let's go with this and take advantage of him.
I-I didn't mean any harm!
If apologizing solved everything, there wouldn't be a need for the Military Police Brigade.
We won't be able to do the cleaning because we were shocked by your peeping.
You understand, Eren?
It's not Eren's fault!
He just wanted to see me changing!
No, not at all.
*Shock.*
It's here!
Why did a Titan show up here?
A problem after a problem! What the hell is going on?!
Did I do something wrong or what?
Hey, everyone, listen to me!
Day 09
The food provisions inside the walls were scarce.
The Trainee Corps faced the same problem.
However, the pudding that was distributed gave the trainees some relief after a tough day of training.
Of all the days, they actually gave us a break on a day like this.
Eren's missing out, isn't he?
Eren...
There's a pudding left over.
Krista, you want it?
Eh? I can't take that without permission.
What? The fastest one takes it right?
No, there are other people that want it too.
Chatter
Okay. Let's settle it with rock-paper-scissors.
There'll be no problem then, right?
Chatter
I see. There's a pudding left over since Eren's not here.
That's Eren's pudding.
I won't let anyone have it!
In that case, I'll tell you a last resort technique.
Last resort?
Got it. I'll do as you say.
Okay, first you... *whisper, whisper.*
Just you wait, Eren.
Using the last resort technique Armin told me,
I'll win this pudding for sure!
Ta-da!
I'm strong! Way stronger than you all!
That's why I'm going with "Rock"!
With this, everyone should go with paper to win over rock.
Can't you see over there? Such a horrible sight!
So if I go with scissors,
I can win!
They're devouring all like you.
Rock...
Paper...
Here come the giant hands!
Scissors!
I did it!
Breaking through the wall!
Yay! Too bad for you.
Unlike those two idiots, that's not gonna work on me.
As dawn arrives, we still survive.
Nobody knows what's going on.
Tearing my town, limb by limb!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Sorry, but I'm gonna take the pudding.
Here you go, Krista.
You were completely late this time!
My specialty is cutting meat.
Hey, come on now. You lost the match,
so you're gonna take it by force?
Both of you, stop fighting.
You did all that to get the pudding for me,
but your feelings alone have made me full.
Krista...
Here you go, Mikasa.
You're going to take this pudding to Eren, right?
Take care of Eren, okay?
Thanks, Krista.
Ah! There it is!
What the heck?
Is this the inside of a Titan's stomach?
Ah! Pudding! The pudding's gone!
Maybe the Titan wanted to have some pudding too?
What are you saying at time like this...
Day 10
Even if they are supposed to be cadets, they're still boys and girls who want to have fun.
Occasionally, they need to take a breather and relax a bit too.
And so, since we finally got a day to ourselves,
I was thinking of going to town to buy some stuff.
Oh, really? Actually, I need to go to town to settle some business too.
Seems like I have no choice but to go with you.
*Scratch, scratch.*
Yeah! While we're at it, how about inviting the others as well?
What? Wh-What are you talking about?
Huh? Wouldn't it be more fun if we all went together?
It's not fun for me at all.
Jeez. You keep saying stuff like that.
That's why I'm your only friend.
I'm fine as long as I have you.
Jeez...
However, there might be a lot of things to carry,
so it'd be better to have more people to help out.
Ah! What do you think about inviting Jean?
He looks like he can carry a lot and knows about hidden shops.
Jean's no good.
Huh? Why?
He's always stalking Mikasa, right?
Now that you mention it, he's always watching her.
If Mikasa saw Jean leaving with us, he'd feel troubled by it, right?
You have a point.
You thought that far ahead for him. You're such a nice person.
Th-That's not it...
So what about Reiner?
Reiner's even worse.
Eh? Why?
He's strong and looks reliable.
The way he looks at you is a bit dirty.
Really?
If you ask me, it seems he's closer with Bertholt.
If that's the case, then we can't bother them, right?
That's also true.
Then, what about Sasha?
Sasha won't do at all.
Eh? Why?
She's a girl and we could talk about clothes.
Do you really think we can talk to Sasha about clothes?
If we brought her along, we'd only go places with food.
That's true.
If you want someone with self-control,
then Annie would be the best.
Really?
So Armin?
He's not strong, so he wouldn't even be helpful with carrying the stuff.
He doesn't look like he'd be able to help us if we got attacked by burglars.
True.
So then, Eren would be the best choice!
Idiot. Just forget about about Eren.
Eh? Why?
If you started talking to Eren,
Mikasa wouldn't leave you alone.
That's right. I would rather not be sliced.
Right?
Besides, when you're with them, there's a higher chance of being eaten by a Titan.
I know, right?
We don't have any other choice then.
Let's forget about inviting the others and just go by ourselves.
That's right. We can't do anything about it.
I'll help carry the stuff.
Yeah. Please do so.
*Door open.*
Huh?
How dare you ruin my date?!
Why were you guys over there?
Why?! We just wanted to go to town.
I see. It'd be great if all of us could go together, right?
No, it wouldn't!
Now's not the time to say something like that! You guys...
Fly!
Monster Character Theater
Trainee Corps
Monster Character Theater. Fly, Trainee Corps!
Eren: Kaji Yuuki.
Mikasa: Ishikawa Yui.
Armin: Inoue Marina.
Krista: Mikage Shiori.
Sobakasu: Fujita Saki.
Original work by Isayama Hajime.
Character design by Yuupon (Nitro+).
Music by Sawano Hiroyuki.