Was it a shock for you?
Monster Character Theater!
Was it scaring you?
Fly, Trainee Corps!
Then we will go hunt you and take you down!
Fly!
Monster Character Theater
Trainee Corps
Day 01
The Trainee Corps.
This is where the boys and girls who volunteered to halt the advancements of the Titans learn the skills of battle.
It's similar to a school.
I'm late! I'm late!
If I'm like this right from the first day,
there's no way I can go up against the Titans!
If someone were to see me like this...
*wipe, wipe*
The fence is broken over there.
Looks like I can take a shortcut through here!
Fuck my life!
Eren's late.
Mikasa, weren't you with him this morning?
No.
Don't tell me he's still asleep?
Dunno.
I thought you'd go to wake him up for sure.
Me?
Y-You and Eren share a deep relationship after all.
Deep
Relationship
Indeed.
Of course.
You guys used to live together, so you're practically family.
Yeah.
So I thought I could leave Eren to you, and didn't go and wake him up.
I see.
But still, Eren is really late.
Bang!
Eren!
Whew! That was close. I was almost late for class.
Took you long enough.
What happened?
Well...
Never mind that!
Mikasa! Why didn't you come to wake me up in the morning?
Because weird rumors would spread if I was seen entering the boys' dorm.
What do you mean "rumors"?
Pipe down.
I thought that you'd wake me up today too for sure!
Eren! Are you crying?
I'm not crying!
Stop it, Eren!
Mikasa said she doesn't want people to find out that you two are dating!
We're not dating!
It's here!
Were we swallowed by the Titan?
Dammit... If only I was prepared,
I could have fought back!
Armin! This happened because you said those weird things.
Right, Mikasa?
Dunno.
In the first place, this is all—
Don't argue in a place like this...
Day 02
The Trainee Corps is where the boys and girls who volunteered to halt the advancement of the Titans
learn the skills of battle.
It's similar to a school.
Armin. Armin!
Eren... What was I...
Thank goodness.
You collapsed in the middle of the morning assembly.
Oh, so I...
Shit! Even though I decided that I wouldn't drag the team down!
Armin, are you ill or something?
Nope. The instructor's speech was so long and boring
that I accidentally dozed off.
You fell asleep?!
Eren, don't you think that there's nothing as
pointless as a long-winded, meaningless speech?
Hey, don't say that in front of the instructor.
I agree with Armin.
Why are you also here, Mikasa?
Because I was worried.
Thank you. I'm fine.
Not about you. About Eren.
Um, yeah.
I'm not ill or anything, you know?!
I was worried if you could remain standing through that long speech.
Just how weak do you think I am?
I just have to think of that as training to beat the Titans!
I'm going back.
What...!
What happened to me?
You lost consciousness.
Ah! My head!
You must have hit your head when you fell.
No! It's because you hit me!
Why did you do that all of a sudden?
I didn't want you to go back to that hell.
There's got to be a better way to stop me!
Eren, are you crying?
I'm not crying!
*wipe, wipe*
Stop making such a racket.
I'm still recovering, you know?
You're just playing hooky!
Not again!
If only I was at 100%, I could have fought back!
Armin! Think of a way to get us out of this!
I can't think of a plan on such short notice!
It's fine as long as I'm with Eren.
No, it's not!
Fly!
Monster Character Theater
Trainee Corps
Monster Character Theatre! Fly, Trainee Corps!
Eren: Kaji Yuuki.
Mikasa: Ishikawa Yui.
Armin: Inoue Marina.