Was it shocking for you?
Monster Character Theater!
Something is scaring you.
Enemies will hunt you no matter what you do!
Fly, Trainee Corps!
Fly!
Monster Character Theater
Trainee Corps
Day 03
The Trainee Corps.
This is where the boys and girls who volunteered to halt the advancements of the Titans learn the skills of battle.
It's similar to a school.
Hey, you!
Sir!
Who are you?
I'm Armin Arlert from the Shiganshina district!
Finally, my first day as a part of the Trainee Corps.
I'll show off how cool I am and stand out from the rest!
My hobby is reading!
Should I talk about my hobbies or something too?
Arlert, why did you come here?
What do I do? I don't really have any hobbies.
To help mankind achieve victory against the Titans!
Maybe "devouring the Titans" would work?
That's nice! I'll turn you into bait for the Titans!
Nah, that might sound a bit too cocky.
Who are you?
I'm Mikasa Ackerman.
I haven't seen her face before.
Is she not from around here?
My speciality is cutting flesh.
Flesh? So that means she's good at cooking meat?
*Boil and bubble.*
She's so family oriented!
Fourth line! About face!
*Hair flip!*
Sweet. She's so beautiful.
Next! Who are you?
J-Jean Kirschtein from Trost district!
I'm interested in long, straight, black hair!
*Glance!*
Zzz...
Pay attention!
I'm up next!
Um... I'm Eren Jeager!
My dream is to join the Recon Corps and devour the Titans!
I'm Eren Jeager!
My dream is to join the Recon corps and devour the Titans!
W-Wait a minute! What about me?
I can't think of any more abusive words.
N-No way... I practiced so much for this!
You! What are you laughing at?
Can't you see over there?
Sorry, but I'm an honest guy.
Such a horrible sight.
They're devouring all like you.
Stop showing off! You got whacked on the head, didn't you?
Here come the giant hands!
Who gave you permission to open your mouths?
Breaking through the wall!
Scums like you will be in the front of the line to become bait for the Titans!
What the hell?! Were we swallowed by a Titan?
And I was really looking forward to my debut in the Trainee Corps!
Shut up!
I wasn't able to run away in time because of you!
What?! Don't blame this on me!
Hey, how far are we going to sink?
Don't ask me!
Day 04
The Trainee Corps.
This is where the boys and girls who volunteered to halt the advancements of the Titans learn the skills of battle.
It's similar to a school.
*Open!*
Good morning!
Oh, Mikasa, you cut your hair?
Yeah.
What?
I-Is it because of what I said yesterday?
Long, straight, black hair!
I think this looks better.
*Blush!*
Damn him! Acting all cool in front of Mikasa!
Clang! Clang! Clang! Clang!
Deciding
Groups
Today, we will decide on the groups for cleaning duty.
Deciding
Groups
Three people in a group, with both men and women in a group.
Deciding
Groups
This is my chance!
Hey, you wanna team—
Sorry.
We already have three people.
Please ask someone else.
Oh? Are you alone?
*Stab!*
Hey, someone let Jean join their team!
I don't care.
I can't be bothered with cleaning and stuff.
*Open.*
*Peek.*
God damn it!
I showed my uncool side earlier.
I failed at training today too.
At this rate, I can't eradicate them!
You can't do anything about that. Anyway, just eat up for now!
That's right! I just have to look cool in front of them!
Yo, Eren. Want me to give you some tips on the 3-D Maneuver Gear?
Really? P-Please do!
Ok, watch carefully.
How was that?
That has nothing to do with the 3-D Maneuver Gear.
*Stab!*
*Stab right in the heart!*
Did you just come to make fun of me?
Enough. Let's go, Eren.
Please wait, Mikasa!
Why did it end up like this?
Even getting eaten by a Titan would be better than this.
Jean! We got eaten by a Titan
because of that crap you said!
What?! It's my fault?
Damn right it is!
Eren, don't fight.
I'm not fighting!
Don't show off! I'm so jealous!
Let go! You'll rip my shirt!
Fly!
Monster Character Theater
Trainee Corps
Monster Character Theater! Fly, Trainee Corps!
Eren: Kaji Yuuki.
Mikasa: Ishikawa Yui.
Armin: Inoue Marina.
Jean: Taniyama Kisho.
Keith: Mogami Tsuguo.
And the above mentioned people worked on this episode.