Attention!
I will hereby explain the plan for retaking Trost.
Let me introduce him first.
This is Eren Jaeger from the Trainee Corps.
He is the successful outcome of top-secret Titan transformation research.
Once he transforms into a Titan, he will lift the large boulder near the gate,
carry it to the destroyed gate, and use it to plug the hole.
Your mission is to protect him from the other Titans until he can seal the breach!
When this plan succeeds,
humanity will succeed in recapturing their land from the Titans for the first time in history.
Compared to what humanity has lost so far, it may be extremely little.
However, that one victory will spark a great revolution for humanity!
Eren, don't you recognize me?
It's me! Mikasa!
Your family!
Move, Ackerman!
What the hell?
He's just like any other stupid Titan!
I'm changing the plan.
Until we can retrieve him,
we'll protect Jaeger from the Titans.
He's still valuable as one of humanity's last hopes.
We cannot just abandon him like this.
Die Erde dröhnt wird rot.
The earth resounds in red.
Where am I?
Die Leute erinnern sich an diese Tragödie.
The people remember this tragedy.
I'm home?
Jean!
Why isn't he using the Maneuver Gear?
Don't tell me... Is it malfunctioning?
I'll come up with something!
Mikasa!
What happened to the plan?
Ist das der Zerstörer oder der Schöpfer?
Is that the destroyer or the creator?
It failed.
Everyone's fighting because we can't leave Eren.
But if it goes on like this,
Mit der Glut des Hasses schwenken wir die Schwerter.
With the burning ash of hate, we wave our swords.
there will be too many Titans and we'll be wiped out!
The spot on the back of the neck;
Ist das unser Schicksal oder unser Wille?
Is that our fate or is that our will?
ten centimeters across and a meter high.
Eren... answer me.
Wir werden kämpfen, bis dieser heiβe Wind unsere Flűgel nimmt.
We will fight until the burning wind takes our wings.
You knew that hell was one step beyond the walls.
So why did you want to go?
"Why"?
Was finden wir jenseits dieses Horizontes?
What will we find beyond this horizon?
Because I was born into this world!
Eren!
Translation
Tobikage
Translation Check
No Name
Editing
Tokyoblade
Timing
Floris257
AFX Logo
KakashiCopyNinja
OP / ED
Char Custom
K-timing
Vevlaa
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Typeset
Floris257
Quality Control
ultim  iMark   Kaitou[Kid]
Encode
FixeR
Project Leading
Naruto-kun / Kaitou[Kid]
Primal Desires
-Defense of Trost District   9 -
U
Dammit.
Why am I the one slowing us down?
Can I really come up with something?
Corporal, we're at our limit!
We're the only ones left!
Retreat to the boulder for now!
What's the status?
Five Titans coming from the gate!
There's no way I can wait for the Titans to go away!
Jean!
So his Maneuver Gear was malfunctioning.
What's wrong?
Dammit! What the hell?!
Don't fuck with me!
Not at a time like this!
Jean, calm down!
Marco?!
What are you doing?!
Geez, don't cause us more trouble!
Dammit! Why is the trigger so stiff?
Jean!
What the hell are you doing?
Look who's talking!
Hurry up and go!
You guys are too reckless!
Right back at you!
I don't feel like we're still alive.
Look over there.
Eren...
Mikasa!
Armin!
Eren won!
He's now going to take care of his role in the mission.
If we can just back him up until he reaches the gate...
we will win!
Protect him!
Even if we have to give up our lives,
we're going to protect Eren until he reaches the gate!
Don't let the other Titans get anywhere near him!
Don't let them get in the way!
We're going to back Eren up!
The two of you stay with Eren.
That's an order! Understood?!
Yes, sir!
Mitabi's squad?
What are they—!
The Titans won't take the bait!
We'll just have to get close enough until they do!
Over here, asshole!
Turn, or I'll shove my blade up on your stinkin' ass and kill you!
Here they come!
We got two of them!
Run!
Run to the buildings!
No way!
It's suicide to get down to ground level!
They can't fight without horses or buildings!
No... We don't have a choice.
Follow Mitabi's squad!
Armin, we're going too.
Over here! This way!
My body... feels like it's being beaten into a pulp.
Mikasa? Armin?
What're they doing?
If they keep running around there, they'll end up as bait for Titan!
Hurry up, slowpoke!
Come this way!
H-Hey!
No! Mitabi!
Why do you want to go to the outside world, Eren?
From the moment we're born, we're all free.
When she brings me coffee and see her smile,
Who cares about the strength of the people who try to deny us that right?
I wish I could be with her until my last day.
It doesn't matter whether you're in flaming water or on icy land!
She said she gave all her love to me.
People who see that are the ones who are the most free!
We dreamt of a new life,
Fight!
some place to be at peace,
I don't care for my life if that's my goal!
but things changed so suddenly.
It doesn't matter how scary the world is!
I lost my dreams in this disaster.
It doesn't matter how cruel the world is!
I'm crying,
Fight!
missing my lover.
I don't have the power
Fight!
on my side forever.
There's still one Titan left!
Oh! Where is my lover?
I'll take care of it!
I have got no power.
Get the hell out of the way!
I'm standing alone. No way!
Calling out your name!
Do it, Eren!
We don't know what is wrong tonight.
Fight!
Everybody's got no place to hide.
No one's left and there's no one to go on.
All I know is my life is gone.
Everyone...
Your deaths were... not in vain.
I'm crying,
missing my lover.
For the first time in history,
I don't have the power
humanity won against the Titans!
Yellow smoke flare: confirmed!
on my side forever.
The plan appears to have succeeded.
Send in the reinforcements!
Recover the elite team!
Currently Available Information
U
History of the Battle Against the Titans Part 1
According to the oldest confirmed record,
the Titans first appeared 107 years ago.
The majority of humanity was devoured.
Currently Available Information
U
History of the Battle Against the Titans Part  2
Humanity tried to oppose the Titans using cannons,
but due to the Titans' superior vitality,
there was nothing they could do to stop them.
The remaining Titans are on their way!
We're going over the wall!
We'll retreat as soon as we get Eren back.
Armin! How's Eren?
He's burning up unbelievably!
We need to hurry... and climb the wall.
A part of his body is almost fused.
No matter how much I pull, I can't get him out!
We'll have to cut him out.
Please wait!
Eren! Armin!
Mikasa?
That's...
The Wings of Freedom.
Hey, brats.
What the hell is going on here?
After that,
the Scouting Legion and the Garrison soldiers worked swiftly,
and Wall Rose once again repelled the advancing Titans.
It took an entire day to eliminate the Titans that had gathered in Trost.
During that time, the fixed cannons spewed fire without a break.
Most of the Titans that had gathered near the wall were killed by explosive shells,
and the Scouting Legion took care of the remaining few.
In the process, a four-meter class Titan and a seven-meter class Titan were successfully captured alive.
However,
207 soldiers were either dead or missing,
and another 897 were injured.
Humanity had indeed defeated Titans for the first time in history,
but far too many lives had been lost to feel happy about it.
Hey...
Aren't you... Marco?
Trainee, do you know his name?
I was wondering where he was.
But... how could he...
Impossible.
Marco... what happened?
Someone...
Did anyone see how he died?
What's his name?
If you know, answer me quickly.
Do you get it, Trainee?
It's already been two days since the gate was sealed,
but we're still not done with recovering the corpses.
There's a risk of an epidemic at this rate.
We have to prevent a second disaster.
We don't have time to grieve over dead comrades just yet.
Got it?
From the 104th Trainee Corps,
leader of the 19th squad, Marco Bodt.
Marco, eh?
Glad we found out who he is.
Back to work.
What is this?
It's what a Titan threw up.
They don't have digestive systems,
so once they're full, they just throw up like that.
No way...
Dammit.
We won't be able tell who's who if it's like this.
I'm sorry.
There's no point apologizing.
We need to cremate them soon.
Do you have any questions?
The leader of the Scouting Legion Operations team, Commander Erwin,
and Private First-class, Levi.
Umm...
Where...
am I?
As you can see, it's an underground jail.
The Military Police have put you in their custody for now.
We only just received permission to meet you.
That key is—!
Yeah. It was within your belongings.
I'll return it later.
Your parents' house,
Dr. Jaeger's basement in the Shiganshina district.
The secret of the Titans is there.
Is that right?
Yes, most likely.
That's what my father said.
You have amnesia and your father is missing, huh?
Well that's pretty convenient.
Levi.
We've already established that he has no reason to lie, right?
There are lots of things we don't understand,
but I think that the best course of action is to find out what you want to do.
What... I want to do?
I order to investigate your parents' house,
we will need to recapture Shiganshina and Wall Maria.
We need to adopt extreme methods to quickly seal the destroyed gate.
We will need your Titan power.
The Titans control our destinies after all.
The Colossal Titan and the Armored Titan...
They are probably the same as you.
You're intentions are the key.
It is the key to saving humanity from this despair.
I...
I'll kill them!
From this world...
Every single one of them!
We don't have all day, trash.
What do you want to do?
I want to join the Scouting Legion,
and, for now, just kill some Titans!
Oh? Not bad.
Erwin, I'll take responsibility for him.
Tell that to the higher-ups.
It's not like I trust him.
If he betrays us or goes wild,
I'll kill him immediately.
The higher ups won't complain either.
After all, I'm the only one who can do this.
I'll acknowledge your entry into the Scouting Legion.
Next Time
A promise taken for granted.
Trampled feelings.
An anger hidden deep inside.
In a delusional state,
Eren recalls everything that happened since that day.
Since That Day