In the year 850,
the wall was destroyed by the sudden reappearance of the Colossal Titan,
and humanity faced yet another invasion of Titans.
One by one, our soldiers fell before the Titans.
And then...
Eren! Hurry...!
Eren also fell prey to the Titans.
Man, Mikasa's amazing...
How does she move that fast?
No! She's definitely not as calm as usual!
I have to do everything I can to win!
I have to do everything I can to live!
What appeared before a cornered Mikasa
was a mysterious Titan that attacked other Titans.
Translation
Tobu
Translation Check
No Name
Editing
Tokyoblade
Timing
Floris257
AFX Logo
KakashiCopyNinja
OP / ED
Char Custom
K-timing
Vevlaa
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Typeset
Floris257
Quality Control
Chippo   ultim  iMark   Kaitou[Kid]
Encode
FixeR
Project Leading
Naruto-kun / Kaitou[Kid]
I Can Hear A Heartbeat
-Defense of Trost District   4 -
U
There!
Your Maneuver Gear can still run!
I also refilled all your blades.
Just...
Leave this one here for me, okay?
At the very least, I want to avoid being eaten alive...
B-But...
Armin.
I'm not leaving you here.
B-But...
You can't carry someone while you're swinging around in an area that's crowded with Titans.
Let's go!
This is useless!
Please, just stop it...
If this keeps up, I'm...
gonna get my friends killed again!
Wait!
Listen to me!
I have a suggestion.
A suggestion?
It's going to take you two to do it.
So you two should decide whether we try it.
Call me crazy, but...
I think we could use that Titan!
Use the Titan?
That thing attacks other Titans.
It doesn't show any interest in us.
So, if we could manage to guide it over to the supply building,
and make it take down the Titans there for us,
we might be able to save everyone!
"Guide it"?
How the hell do you plan to guide that?!
That thing might be fighting instinctively.
Mikasa and Conny, you two need to take down the Titans around it.
When you do, it'll move on to chase after other Titans.
That should naturally bring it in the direction of Headquarters.
You expect us to put ourselves in that much danger based on a guess?
But if it works, we might be able to take out every last Titan at Headquarters in one fell swoop!
It seems worth trying.
Huh?! Are you serious?!
If the other option is to wait for death, I'd rather take a gamble and hope it works out.
I agree to Armin's plan.
You wanna fight the Titans alongside a Titan?!
Yes. Exactly.
If we fail, we're gonna be laughingstocks, aren't we?
But if we succeed, we'll save everyone!
Be ready for anything.
I know. I know!
Am I even qualified for this?
Am I qualified to be in a position of responsibility?
No.
That's wrong.
Now's the time...
While the Titans are clustered together...
This could be our chance!
Now!
Make a break for the Headquarters while we have the chance!
It has to be now!
One way or another, if we run out of gas, we're done for!
Everybody, break through together!
Jean!
Thank you!
We slipped past them thanks to you!
It's because of you!
I've told you before, right?
You've got what it takes to command, Jean!
Is that so? I dunno about that!
Dammit!
How many of us... made it?
Using our comrades' deaths...
How many died... on my command?
You're... from the Supply Troops, aren't you?
Cut it out, Jean!
It's them! They're the ones who sold us out!
Thanks to you guys, more of us died out there for nothing!
The Titans broke into the supply rooms!
There was nothing we could have done!
Doing something about it is supposed to be your job!
Get down!
Shit!
There's too many people gathered in here!
What'll we do?!
Get inside!
Let go of me!
They left us to die!
Where the hell did Mikasa go?!
She already ran outta gas and got eaten!
This is normal.
This is what they call "reality," after all.
Have I been clinging to nothing but dreams and illusions all this time?
I should've known...
This is reality.
If I'd thought about it normally, it would have been easy to see.
Against anything this goddamn huge,
we can never win.
What the—
What... was that?
Mikasa!
That was close!
They're empty! But we did it! We just barely made it here!
Y-You're still alive?!
Way to go, Armin!
Ow! Oww!
Your strategy worked like a charm!
Everybody! That Titan's an Abnormal that keeps killing other Titans!
Plus, it doesn't show any interest in us!
If we make good use of it, we can all get the hell out of here!
Use... a Titan?
Be rescued by a Titan?
That sounds like something out of a drea—
This is no dream.
Abnormal or not, I don't care.
We want that thing rampaging around out there for as long as possible...
Realistically speaking, it's our best possible strategy for living through this.
Currently Available Information
U
3-D Maneuver Gear Mechanics  3
<Fan Section>
Gas is blown straight into the fan to make it rotate.
The pressure of the gas is regulated to manipulate the output power.
Currently Available Information
Titans' Size Comparison Diagram
It's all right.
That Titan is stronger than your average Titan.
As long as it's out there showing off and smashing things up,
this building won't be destroyed.
Hey.
How much do you know about that Titan?
Why care when it just saved us?
You're right. That's the most important thing right now.
We found 'em!
This stuff belonged to the Military Police Brigade!
They've just been gathering dust, but...
Are shotgun pellets really going to work for ammunition?
These guns aren't much to begin with...
Will they do any good against the Titans...?
I think they'll be a lot better than nothing.
As long as there are only seven Titans that are three to four meters tall occupying the storage rooms,
it shouldn't be impossible to blind them, even with the degree of firepower we currently have.
First, we'll use the lift to lower a group of people from the middle of the ceiling.
Next, they'll aim at the seven Titans, and simultaneously fire, blinding them all.
Then, everything will be decided in the moment that follows.
The seven people hidden in the ceiling beams will time their attack to coincide with the shooting,
and will slice into the Titans' vital area.
In other words...
According to this strategy, everything depends on a single attack.
All of our lives will be riding on it.
This strategy requires seven of us to bring down all seven Titans in one simultaneous strike.
I'd like the seven of you with the very best-rated maneuvering skills to do it, but...
Asking you all to carry the weight of all our lives...
It's...
I'm sorry.
No problem.
No matter who does it, if they fail, we all die.
The risk is the same.
But... This plan of mine...
Do you really think it's the best possible strategy?
There's nothing we can do but try it.
We don't have much time either.
We're not likely to come up with anything else.
All we can do now is put all our strength into this!
It's all right. Have some confidence.
Armin, you have a gift for leading us down the right path.
Eren and I have both had our lives saved by that gift.
You... have? When?
We're done getting the lift ready!
The guns, as well! They're all loaded!
You just aren't aware of it. Let's talk about it again later.
Okay.
But, you know...
Can we really bring down the Titans without our 3-D Maneuver Gear?
Sure we can!
Our opponents are Titans that are three to four meters tall.
It'll be easy to aim for their weak spots.
Yeah!
No matter how big they are, you can always go below their head and hit the back of their neck.
It's only one meter long and ten centimeters wide!
Otherwise, you shove it right up their asses!
Those are their only two weak points!
I didn't know that! So that's another trick, huh?
This is my first time hearing about it, too.
Reiner! Those could be your last words, you know?
It's all right...
Their numbers haven't increased.
Proceed with the plan!
Stay calm!
We have to draw them in close enough!
Wait...
We must avoid battling at a disadvantage.
We don't want to lose a single fighter.
This one strike will decide everything!
Wait...
Ready...
FIRE!
Got it!
Everyone?
I... Um...
Attacking you suddenly... f-from behind...
Shit!
That was v-very rude of me...
It's Sasha and Conny!
Hurry and cover 'em!
I... I...
I'M SORRY!
Mikasa! You saved me!
You're not hurt?
Thanks to you!
Then get up, quickly!
Sorry about that...
No problem.
Hey, now.
That was close, Annie.
I'm glad you're not hurt, seriously.
They're all taken out!
Switch to resupplying operations!
We did it!
All right! With this, we're saved!
The Titans aren't coming in either!
Thanks to that Titan rampaging around out there!
I... crumbled in front of that Titan...
How am I gonna face everybody?!
You can fall apart as much as you want later!
Right now, we have to get out of here!
So much for having what it takes to command.
Quit telling me stuff like that.
Please don't get mad at me for saying this, but...
Jean, you're not a strong person.
You can really understand the feelings of weaker people.
Because of that, you've got a knack for accurately sizing up situations,
and knowing clearly what we should do next.
Your instructions were solid, Jean.
That's why I can move on, and am still alive now.
Is everyone ready?
It's breakout time!
Everybody go at once!
Climb the wall!
Meet up with the main forces!
Mikasa?
Mikasa!
If we don't get out of here...
That Titan...
They're eating one of their own?
Can't it regenerate its body...?
If we could somehow unravel the mystery of that Titan...
I thought it might be the key to a solution for our desperate situation, but...
I agree.
If it just gets eaten like that, we won't end up learning a thing.
We'll eliminate the Titans clinging to that one.
We've got to keep it alive for now!
Are you insane, Reiner?!
We're finally on our way out of this situation!
It's just a thought but, what if we could make an ally out of that Titan?
What then?
Don't you think it would make a more powerful weapon than any cannon?
An "ally"?
Are you serious?
That's...!
The Abnormal that ate Thomas!
Hey...
You were gonna help that?
As expected, it looks like it used up the last of its energy.
Give it up! Let's leave.
There's no way you could make an ally out of that monster.
A Titan is a Titan.
What the hell is it now?
Mikasa!
It's Eren.
They should be chopped off,
but his arm and leg are still there.
Back then, Eren was swallowed by a Titan.
Back then...
What's... going on?
You mean... Eren...
did all this?
Next Time
"I'll exterminate the Titans."
That strong thought transformed Eren into a Titan.
But the Garrison consider him a threat to humanity,
and turn their blades toward him.
The Whereabouts of His Left Arm
-Defense of Trost District  5 -
U