The year was 845.
Due to the sudden appearance of the Colossal Titan and the Armored Titan,
everyday life was completely destroyed along with the wall.
Stop!
Mankind was forced to abandon Wall Maria.
Having lost a fifth of its population and a third of its territory,
mankind was forced back inside the confines of Wall Rose.
However, not all of mankind have bowed before the Titans.
The Garrison concentrate on fortifying the wall's defenses.
As recruits, many of the youth were gaining the knowledge and skills necessary to defeat the Titans.
It was around that time...
Year 850
Meanwhile, in the Trost district. The elite among the Recon Corps were about to set foot into the Titans' domain once more.
Thirty seconds until the gates open!
All soldiers, prepare to move out!
Oh... for God's sake, I'm so irritated.
Hey Levi.
Hell no.
I haven't said anything yet.
"Help me capture a Titan", right?
That'd be a huge pain the the ass for me.
How about you, Mike?
Won't you join?
The boring responses of boring men, as always.
We will now begin our 49th outer wall expedition!
Onwards!
Woohoo!
Hanji!
Oh Titans, I'm coming to see you!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
Fumareta hana no namae mo shirazu ni
Without knowing the name of the trampled flowers
Chi ni ochita tori wa kaze o machiwabiru
The birds that fell to the ground are waiting for the wind
Inotta tokoro de nani mo kawaranai
Praying won't change anything
Ima o kaeru no wa tatakau kakugo da
What will change the depressing situation is how ready you are to fight...
Shikabane fumikoete susumu ishi o warau buta yo
Oh, the pigs sneering at our will to advance as we step over corpses
Kachiku no annei
The livestock may be at peace
kyogi no hanei
in their phony prosperity
shiseru garou no jiyuu o!
but let us be "free" like the dying, starving wolves!
Torawareta kutsujoku wa hangeki no koushi da
The humiliation of being trapped signals our counterattack
Jouheki no sono kanata emono o hofuru jäger
You're a hunter who slaughters the prey beyond the castle walls
Hotobashiru shoudou ni sono mi o yakinagara
While you're consumed by a raging bloodlust,
tasogare ni hi o ugatsu
what pierces the scarlet at dusk is―
guren no yumiya
the crimson bow and arrow
Ilse's Journal
Memoirs of a Recon Soldier
Just hold on a second, Erwin!
I can see why setting up a base
of operations is our top priority for now,
but figuring out the Titans true intentions is the main objective of the Recon Corps!
I'm sure even you know that!
Um, Squad Leader?
You shouldn't talk like that towards the Commander—
Shove it!
To do that, capturing a Titan is of the utmost importance!
Of course I know I'm not being realistic here.
The last time we managed to capture one was over 15 years ago,
and we lost over twenty men doing it.
But if we're afraid to make sacrifices,
then we'll never gain any new information!
Have the troops focus on the rear for now.
Yes, sir.
How many times must I tell you.
We cannot spare any more soldiers for a capture operation.
We've already lost over ten men just to get here.
I know that! But...
- Hanji.
I won't allow it.
H-Hey!
Erwin, wait!
Guess you couldn't convince him after all, Hanji.
It's hard enough to kill those Titans, let alone capturing one.
However many lives we've got, it won't be enough.
Let's say, Oluo...
Let's say that Levi is trying to kill you, kill you for real!
What would you do?
Can you fight and beat him?
No way I could... that's impossible.
Also...
I can't breathe.
Let me tell you how you can win.
You study him.
From his daily routine, to the food he doesn't like,
his taste in women, hell, even how often he goes to the can...
You take note of every little detail about him.
From that, you'll find his Achilles' heel,
and capitalize on it when the moment arises.
If you don't fight like that, you will surely... be killed.
Hanji!
Squad Leader! You're going too far!
Oops, my bad.
Well anyways, that's how it is.
Squad Leader!
Shit...
I almost died there.
That bitch is fucking crazy.
Mentally insane.
By the way, you're a member of the Recon Corps,
so can you stop speaking in that uncivilized way.
The fuck?
Why the hell is it any of your concern?
Petra!
Are you finished replenishing the gas yet?
N-Not yet, Eld!
Just a little longer, sir!
They're in the forest! Let's move!
All soldiers, be on your guard!
Squad Leader!
It's dangerous to go alone!
Erwin, I'm going!
Wait, Hanji!
Levi!
Shit, what a moron.
Whoa.
Found one!
Hi there!
Nice weather we're having, right?
Atta boy.
Hey, by the way...
why not join me for a brisk walk inside of the walls?
How's that sound?
That was close!
Oh my... You okay?
Follow me!
There we go, good boy.
This way, dumbass.
Hey! Don't get in the way!
Good boy, keep on coming!
What?
Hey!
Wait up!
Hey! Where are you going?
The hell's up with that moron?
Running back home?
It's acting really strange, even for an Abnormal.
Yeah.
Its behavioral patterns are unlike any other
that've been reported thus far.
No, isn't it an Abnormal because it doesn't follow the norm.
- Who gives a crap.
We'll kill it here.
Hey! I said wait up!
Is it heading somewhere in particular?
Even if it is an Abnormal, for a Titan to head towards a specific spot...
What?
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Is this the place...
you wanted go to?
That was close!
What? What is it?
I'm listening.
I've got it!
Oluo, wait!
Say what?
You alright?
Captain...
I'll serve under you for as long as I live!
This one could've been,
a precious test subject.
If we could've just captured it,
mankind could've made some progress.
Shut the fuck up, four-eyes!
If you want to be turned into Titan shit, then be my guest.
However, don't put your subordinates in danger!
Titans don't defecate.
They don't have a digestive system, so...
Huh?
Um... Captain?
What is it?
Is that... a Titan's doing?
But... there's no way a Titan would...
What are you talking about?
The emblem of the 34th expedition...
It's a soldier that died a year ago.
I'm getting a name here...
Ilse... Langnar.
Unbelievable, for a Titan to do this.
Levi, what's that?
This is...
Ilse Langnar's military achievement.
Currently Disclosable Information
The Ecology of the Titans - 1
There is currently no information about the origins of the
Titans in historical records, therefore, very little is known about them.
Currently Disclosable Information
The Ecology of the Titans - 2
The only principle behavior of the Titans is to devour humans.
However, from records and studies, it suggests that aim is not
"predatory", rather, it is for "entertainment".
My name is Ilse Langnar.
I participated in the 34th outer wall expedition,
as a part of the west column with the 2nd Brigade.
We encountered Titans on our way back.
I lost both my horse, and my fellow soldiers.
I even abandoned my broken Maneuver Gear.
I am running north.
I have lost my horse in the Titan-infested lands outside the walls.
I cannot flee from the Titans on foot.
I have no comrades to rely on.
As I make my way back home,
I have lost all hope of survival.
However, I might still be able to reach the walls without encountering any Titans.
That's right...
I cannot let fear overtake me now.
When I volunteered for the Recon Corps, this situation is one I've always been prepared for.
For I am mankind's wings that do not fear death.
As a Recon soldier,
even with my last breath, I will keep on fighting until the bitter end.
I have no weapons, but I can still fight!
I will write down every moment on this journal,
and I will put my all into what I can do right now.
I will not be defeated.
I will not... be defeated.
I've encountered a Titan.
It's a 7, no wait, a 6-meter class.
It won't eat me right away... is it an Abnormal?
I will now meet my end.
This is the end.
I've been selfish all along.
I haven't even given anything back to my parents.
I feel sick.
It ends here...
Ymir's...
people.
It... just spoke.
A Titan actually spoke.
Impossible.
Mistress Ymir.
Welcome.
It's words were.
"Ymir's people".
"Mistress Ymir".
"Welcome".
There's no doubt in my mind.
This Titan has changed its expression.
It assumed a position showing respect towards me.
I can't believe it.
For the first time in history, a human is conversing with a Titan.
W-Who...
are you beings?
I ask it about their existence.
It groans...
No answer.
Where are you from?
I ask it about their origin.
I get no response.
Why do you eat us?
I ask it about their objective.
Why do you eat us?!
You don't even need food to live!
So why?!
You're all a bunch of useless sacks of flesh!
So just disappear from this world already!
What's happening?!
Why?
What's...
No!
It's caught me! It has a large mouth, lots of teeth, but not sharp, warm breath. It's...
Dear Erwin Smith,
I am writing this letter to propose
the resumption of Titan capturing
operations within the Recon Corps.
If you have read the diary enclosed, then it is obvious that it suggests only one thing:
That we are still ignorant about the Titans.
The Titan that Ilse Langnar encountered spoke meaningful words,
and assumed a position showing respect.
Furthermore, it did not eat Ilse, but instead stored her remains inside the tree.
Obviously, this is the first time this has ever been recorded in human history.
We have a sworn duty to make use of newfound
information that Ilse gave here life to attain.
We cannot let her effort of trying to unravel more information about the Titans go to waste.
We must carry on from where she left off.
If we obtain any more information, however little it may be,
it will not be in vain.
This will someday
be the key that will help in our counterattack.
That is what I believe.
2nd Squad Leader,
Hanji Zoe.
Um...
Hanji?
So you're stalking me, huh?
It's good to have a hobby, I guess.
About what happened the other day... well...
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't messed up, we could have captured it.
If we'd succeeded, then we could've gained some valuable information.
If it's for that reason, then my life isn't worth—
No...
I'm the one who should apologize.
I almost got you killed.
I'm sorry.
But never say that your life isn't worth anything again.
Do you understand?
Oops.
Y-You okay?
Oluo, what are you doing?!
Oh yeah...
Erwin has given us the go-ahead.
Is that so.
Woohoo!
20 days later...
Squad Leader Hanji Zoe, with the support of Captain Levi's Special Ops Squad,
succeeded in the first capture of a Titan since the fall of Wall Maria.
During that operation,
a new capture method proposed by Hanji was used,
all without a single casualty.
Sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart is
Inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It’s something more fragile than life itself
Nando demo sutete wa mitsuke
No matter how many times you throw it away, you still find it
Yasuraka ni saa nemure
So rest in peace now
Myakuutsu shoudou ni negai wa okasare
Your wish is violated by your pulsing urge
Wasurete shimau hodo mata omoidasu yo
and as much as you forget about it, you recall it again
Kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful and cruel world
Mada ikiteiru koto "naze" to tou bakari de
We only ask “why” we’re still alive…
Aa boku-tachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
Ah, what are we going to protect
Nani wo mamoru no darou mou risei nado
with our strength and weakness? If reason
Nai naraba
no longer exists