[Script Info]
Title:滑头鬼之孙
Original Script:四魂制作组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Chinese,SIMHEI,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,5,5,8,1
Style: Staff,Microsoft YaHei,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00804000,&H004D2600,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,5,5,8,1
Style: Title,PMingLiU,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,30,1
Style: OP-ED-JP,Microsoft YaHei,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00800040,&H00FF0080,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,5,5,10,1
Style: OP-ED-Ch,Microsoft YaHei,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00A00000,&H00FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,5,5,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.70,0:01:56.70,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}本字幕由四魂制作组(snm.5d6d.com)制作\N仅供交流试看 如喜欢本作品请支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.70,0:01:56.70,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2\fad(130,130)}翻译：mushishi；时间：問答無用；后期：铁碎牙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.74,0:00:28.62,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明日を照らすよSunshine 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.77,0:00:35.65,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}窓から射込む...扉開いて 
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.58,0:00:48.00,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Stop! `cause you got me thinking that I`m a little quicker 
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.01,0:00:50.58,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Go! Maybe the rhythm`s off, but I will never let you 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.59,0:00:53.16,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Know! I wish that you could see it for yourself 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.25,0:00:55.37,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}It`s not, it`s not, just stop, hey y`all! やだ！ 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.45,0:00:57.60,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}I never thought that I would take over it all 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.93,0:00:59.96,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And now I know that there`s no way I could fall 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.09,0:01:02.36,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s on and on and off and on 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.49,0:01:04.02,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And no one gets away 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.20,0:01:08.99,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕の夢は 何処に在るのか？ 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.06,0:01:13.68,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}影も形も見えなくて 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.84,0:01:18.60,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追いかけていた 守るべきもの 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.73,0:01:23.76,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}There`s a sunshine in my mind 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.80,0:01:31.27,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明日を照らすよSunshineどこまでも続く 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.35,0:01:35.95,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}目の前に広がるヒカリの先へ 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.11,0:01:38.26,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}未来のSunshine 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.36,0:01:40.78,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}輝くSunshine 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.90,0:01:42.81,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s hard, just take a chance 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.89,0:01:44.11,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}信じて 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.30,0:01:48.87,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明日も晴れるかな？ 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.74,0:00:28.62,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}照耀明日的阳光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.77,0:00:35.65,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}从窗口透进来...打开门扉吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.58,0:00:48.00,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Stop! `cause you got me thinking that I`m a little quicker
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.01,0:00:50.58,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Go! Maybe the rhythm`s off, but I will never let you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.59,0:00:53.16,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Know! I wish that you could see it for yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.25,0:00:55.37,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}It`s not, it`s not, just stop, hey y`all! やだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.45,0:00:57.60,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}I never thought that I would take over it all
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.93,0:00:59.96,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And now I know that there`s no way I could fall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.09,0:01:02.36,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s on and on and off and on
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.49,0:01:04.02,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And no one gets away 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.20,0:01:08.99,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我的梦想在何方？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.06,0:01:13.68,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}无迹可寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.84,0:01:18.60,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追寻着守护之物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.73,0:01:23.76,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}There`s a sunshine in my mind
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.80,0:01:31.27,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}照耀明日的阳光连绵不绝
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.35,0:01:35.95,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}奔向眼前放射的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.11,0:01:38.26,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}未来的阳光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.36,0:01:40.78,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}闪耀的阳光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.90,0:01:42.81,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s hard, just take a chance
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.89,0:01:44.11,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}请坚信
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.30,0:01:48.87,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明天也是晴天吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.44,0:22:24.19,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}宵闇に紛れ 摘み去られた花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.28,0:22:33.00,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ひとつの希望も 傷付けさせない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.35,0:22:41.86,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怖がる心を試すように 竜巻が嘲笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:51.27,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}揺れる吊り橋 繋いだ手と手 歴史を駆け抜ける
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.83,0:23:03.08,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}まっすぐ光る眼差し 教えてくれた 立ち向かう勇気
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.49,0:23:13.53,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}生きとし生けるすべて キミの時代に 奏でるSymphony
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.65,0:23:19.40,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Be Yourself 信じて まだ見ぬ至上の地
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.51,0:23:26.62,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}キミはキミのままで そう Go Your Way!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.44,0:22:24.19,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}伴随着黄昏的坠落之花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.28,0:22:33.00,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}守护好唯一的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.35,0:22:41.86,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}宛如试探恐惧的心灵 龙卷风在嘲笑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:51.27,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}摇晃的吊桥 紧握的手 超越了历史
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.83,0:23:03.08,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}闪耀着直率的目光 给予了我前进的勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.49,0:23:13.53,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}活着的万物在你的时代演奏Symphony
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.65,0:23:19.40,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Be Yourself 自信 虽未达至顶点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.51,0:23:26.62,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你仍然是你 是的 Go Your Way!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.85,0:00:06.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自古以来 人们就对妖怪心存畏惧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.77,0:00:12.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而走在那众妖之前 统领着百鬼夜行的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.28,0:00:16.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们称其为妖怪的总大将
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.48,0:00:18.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抑或是如此称呼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.07,0:00:21.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魑魅魍魉之主
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.63,0:00:23.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑头鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.66,0:02:27.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶去为玉章大人效力 为玉章大人效力
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.99,0:02:40.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉章虽然已经说了不会袭击我的朋友以及町里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.56,0:02:44.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但妖气却越来越盛 不能大意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.75,0:02:48.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些家伙打算做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.55,0:02:53.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此 但太遗憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.00,0:02:59.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的网页里明明有这么多人声称目击了妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.18,0:03:02.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却从没亲眼看见过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.40,0:03:09.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是个幸福的人啊 我们倒是被折腾得够呛了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.02,0:03:11.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪还真是让人头疼 是不是啊加奈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.06,0:03:18.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 对于赌上一切都要证明妖怪是存在的我来说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.52,0:03:21.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要亲眼看见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.52,0:03:23.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吧 岛同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.12,0:03:24.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.48,0:03:29.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这个周末清十字团务必要到奴良家里去合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.16,0:03:32.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就算了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.62,0:03:35.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也PASS
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.92,0:03:37.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.58,0:03:44.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 现在正是清十字团的关键时期
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.28,0:03:46.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也给奴良添麻烦了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.92,0:03:48.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良同学 真是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.99,0:03:50.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愿意的话就要说出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.06,0:03:53.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愿意吗 奴良同学不愿意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.37,0:03:54.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.74,0:04:08.09,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,300)}三七分的酒杯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.06,0:04:12.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好臭啊 一股纳豆臭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.45,0:04:15.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是当然的啊 因为我是纳豆小僧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.30,0:04:16.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.56,0:04:18.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放过我吧 狸猫兄
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.53,0:04:22.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 传说中的宝物？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.63,0:04:23.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.14,0:04:25.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千真万确吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.61,0:04:31.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 唯有我所宠爱的玉章得到了传说中的宝物
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.14,0:04:34.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 传说中的宝物是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.99,0:04:39.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是魔王的小槌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.12,0:04:43.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.01,0:04:45.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.86,0:04:54.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是自玉章得到宝物那天起 他就变了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.63,0:04:57.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成了不把同伴当同伴看的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.61,0:05:04.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.37,0:05:11.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于到了我们四国八十八鬼夜行登上舞台的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.53,0:05:15.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前进吧 与这把刀一起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.35,0:05:19.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.51,0:05:21.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.45,0:05:25.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是魔王的小槌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.62,0:05:32.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯有被选中的玉章大人才是我们四国八十八鬼夜行之主
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.53,0:05:55.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这股妖气 毫无疑问四国妖怪已经集结了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.60,0:06:00.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅是七人同行 还率领了其他很多同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.76,0:06:02.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是来真的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.94,0:06:09.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内有组里不团结 外有四国八十八鬼夜行的进攻
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.77,0:06:14.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是内忧外患啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.59,0:06:18.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人会发动总攻
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.76,0:06:22.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须振作起来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.32,0:06:27.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在爷爷不在 必须由我来保护奴良组
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.81,0:06:30.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是爷爷的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.46,0:06:34.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑头鬼的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.65,0:06:39.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猩影？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.14,0:06:44.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰丽姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.82,0:06:51.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我本不打算在妖怪的世界里生活
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.51,0:06:58.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为能巧妙地混入人类社会 轻轻松松活下去也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.08,0:07:02.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 由于老爸的遭遇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.23,0:07:08.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉体内的妖怪之血沸腾起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.78,0:07:11.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.07,0:07:14.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这算什么少主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.08,0:07:18.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不准我为老爸报仇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.37,0:07:22.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 少主也没有替我报仇的打算
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.62,0:07:26.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去 我就要控制不住自己的沸腾之血了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.89,0:07:29.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猩影…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.35,0:07:38.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了你们 多数土地神已被杀害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.75,0:07:41.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良组现在的战斗力已在我们的掌握之中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.01,0:07:47.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 奴良陆生已没有能力来抵抗我们的总攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.22,0:07:52.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉章 我只是个杂碎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.65,0:07:55.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经做得很好了 犬神
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.60,0:07:59.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是探明奴良组的战斗力功不可没的杂碎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.24,0:08:03.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我还没闹够啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.34,0:08:08.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别着急犬神 总攻击就要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.06,0:08:40.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪女 怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.05,0:08:44.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为何 心绪不宁的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.50,0:08:46.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.05,0:08:52.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处弥漫着奇怪的妖气 无法安心入睡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.93,0:09:01.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是传闻中的大厦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.00,0:09:09.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸 我来为你报仇
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.40,0:09:30.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只身一人来到敌阵之中 到底是何人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.51,0:09:34.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是奴良组的地盘 你们这些外来的报上名来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.68,0:09:39.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身材高大 胆识过人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.89,0:09:41.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音从哪里来的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.13,0:09:46.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就懒得问你名字了 反正你马上就要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.39,0:10:11.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一天到晚只知道盆栽 还真是悠闲 你还是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.11,0:10:16.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这简直就像个人类的老头嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.41,0:10:20.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的老头吗 这倒不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.96,0:10:26.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猩影 你知道我为何会追随奴良组吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.37,0:10:30.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很钦佩总大将
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.75,0:10:36.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我力气比他大 但我却赢不了他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.74,0:10:42.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那位大人不仅是个真正的妖怪而且懂得人心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.67,0:10:44.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.36,0:10:48.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天你会明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.49,0:10:52.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就以你的所见来决定自己的方向吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.96,0:10:56.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.18,0:10:59.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸 对不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.37,0:11:05.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没死啊 你还真是顽强嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.35,0:11:10.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你粉身碎骨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.77,0:11:22.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.73,0:11:26.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是奴良组的地盘 不会让你为所欲为的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.67,0:11:27.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.79,0:11:34.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别追 手洗鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.76,0:11:36.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉章大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.25,0:11:44.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都等到最终决战来解决
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.50,0:11:57.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猩影
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.32,0:11:59.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少主
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.18,0:12:01.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.28,0:12:04.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.89,0:12:08.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他闯入了四国妖怪的阵营
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.62,0:12:10.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤身一人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.52,0:12:18.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.16,0:12:21.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.18,0:12:24.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪我优柔寡断
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.54,0:12:25.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.49,0:12:29.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是猩影现在能说话他也会这样讲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.81,0:12:32.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他虽然受了伤 但他会怪别人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.52,0:12:35.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁的家里出了事就由当家的解决
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.68,0:12:38.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不过是这样实行了罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.08,0:12:40.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我要怎么做才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.01,0:12:45.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狒狒是和爷爷喝过交杯酒的义兄弟 也是我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.14,0:12:49.47,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他的儿子猩影也是我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.10,0:12:51.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我却…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.63,0:12:54.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就去战斗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.26,0:12:58.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你自己的百鬼夜行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.74,0:13:04.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们和总大将还有你的父亲都喝过交杯酒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.78,0:13:09.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基于这份忠诚 我们接受你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.14,0:13:15.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的情况是陆生大人还不足以成为总大将
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.41,0:13:16.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.58,0:13:20.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们和陆生大人的关系是以总大将为中心的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.12,0:13:22.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说是对等的五五分
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.03,0:13:26.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们并不是陆生大人的百鬼夜行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.58,0:13:30.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我必须组建我自己的百鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.03,0:13:35.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 就像和我一样 你要自己和别人喝交杯酒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.76,0:13:39.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是五五对分 而是七三分这样的老大与小弟的分法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.46,0:13:41.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大与小弟的分法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.19,0:13:42.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.12,0:13:45.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自己率领的百鬼夜行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.26,0:13:51.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我只能在晚上觉醒成为妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.18,0:13:55.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不认为大家会追随这样的我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.08,0:13:57.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.20,0:14:02.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.13,0:14:04.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔还是让我看看你的毅力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.05,0:14:09.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也…也不希望像现在这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.61,0:14:11.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.13,0:14:16.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好犀利的眼神啊 陆生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.94,0:14:20.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管白天还是夜晚 你仍旧是你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.99,0:14:24.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的百鬼夜行是不管白天还是夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.09,0:14:29.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会有听命于你的家伙 就像我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.14,0:14:39.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陆生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.87,0:14:42.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 都这时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.86,0:14:45.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.63,0:15:05.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.15,0:15:08.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷 我也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.25,0:15:11.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩子别跟着来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.35,0:15:13.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.89,0:15:18.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓妖怪就是使用妖术 飞翔于天空
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.77,0:15:24.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时都能隐形现身 精通剑术 武功高强 能改变身形
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.22,0:15:27.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超越常人想象之物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.47,0:15:31.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还太小 什么都不会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.02,0:15:36.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是滑头鬼的孙子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.54,0:15:40.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是滑头鬼的孙子 所以你应该什么都会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.18,0:15:43.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全靠你自己努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.66,0:15:47.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.52,0:15:50.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是因为我是滑头鬼的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.90,0:15:54.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要凭自己的力量不让大家受到伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.48,0:15:56.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.51,0:16:03.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少主
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.46,0:16:07.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.05,0:16:10.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸩大人都告诉我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.38,0:16:13.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一天我可是等了好久了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.17,0:16:15.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小僧也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.02,0:16:18.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是翘首以盼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.20,0:16:42.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发誓从此之后 接受陆生大人的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.17,0:16:45.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一生信任和追随陆生大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.98,0:16:46.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.57,0:16:47.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.41,0:16:47.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.71,0:16:54.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请陆生大人不论何时 都能贯彻自己的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.84,0:16:59.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是道路艰险 我们一定和您一起开拓
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.99,0:17:00.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.03,0:17:39.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照 雪女
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.45,0:17:45.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.99,0:17:47.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.85,0:18:30.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于要率领百鬼了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.69,0:18:32.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再犹豫了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.45,0:18:36.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为人类的你能做得了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.01,0:18:40.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为像你一样的人太难了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.46,0:18:45.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你强大而令人恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.16,0:18:51.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我不会一切都继承你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.81,0:18:55.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我既想保护人类也想保护妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.14,0:18:57.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一点我是绝不会让步的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.20,0:19:11.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人类的事就交给你 妖怪的事就由我处理
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.79,0:19:19.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天 我要在你经常坐的那条树枝上看看这个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.78,0:19:23.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你这个屁孩来说还早得很
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.38,0:19:25.47,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已不是小孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.79,0:19:28.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你是小屁孩你就是小屁孩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.29,0:19:44.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猩影…你不能乱动
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.17,0:19:47.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦 你这大少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.39,0:19:51.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猩影
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.33,0:19:53.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.64,0:20:01.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再硬闯四国妖怪的阵地
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.07,0:20:03.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一次我会一起去的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.51,0:20:14.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人办不到的事交给百鬼夜行办的话一定能成功
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.73,0:20:16.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.37,0:20:22.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别着急 对方只不过是只笨狸猫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.80,0:20:27.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别为了那种家伙丢了自己的命
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.23,0:20:31.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.44,0:20:35.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 是家人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.41,0:20:42.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老爸的仇人 那只狸猫的皮就由你来剥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.82,0:20:45.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在背后支持你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.44,0:20:49.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少主
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.65,0:20:50.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.99,0:20:57.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就开始百鬼夜行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.86,0:20:59.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家出动
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.49,0:21:16.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然现在还只是很小的百鬼夜行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.00,0:21:19.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天会成为一股强大的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.09,0:21:22.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊 陆生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.07,0:21:27.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸 我已用自己的眼睛决定好了将来的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.29,0:21:35.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 犬神
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.98,0:21:41.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是属?我的时代的黎明
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:46.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要咬断他的头
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.67,0:21:47.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.15,0:21:50.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪大战开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.80,0:23:30.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岛是日本足球队的队员？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.77,0:23:31.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,U-14
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.89,0:23:34.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么要来找妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.31,0:23:35.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.64,0:23:37.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去踢足球啊 去踢足球
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.58,0:23:39.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回 滑头鬼之孙
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.69,0:23:40.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黎明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
