[Script Info]
Title:Another 12
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: opjp,微软雅黑,23,&H20EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H322F2F2F,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,5,1
Style: opcn,微软雅黑,22,&H20EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H322F2F2F,&H20000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,5,134
Style: edjp,微软雅黑,20,&H32FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H322F2F2F,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,3,30,10,10,1
Style: edcn,微软雅黑,20,&H32FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H322F2F2F,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,7,10,30,10,1
Style: title,华文中宋,22,&H00F4F4F4,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,4,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,黑体,16,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.98,0:00:12.34,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}睜開暗夜籠罩的眼簾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.34,0:00:15.83,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}莫畏懼那午夜凶影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.25,0:00:23.37,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}宛如從漆黑靈柩之中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.41,0:00:31.73,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誕生的人偶一般
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.43,0:00:36.73,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}身體凍得鮮紅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.66,0:00:45.34,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}將心置於黑暗之中供養
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.62,0:00:48.74,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你是否能看見我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.74,0:00:52.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}是否能感到所牽之手變得冰冷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.04,0:00:55.17,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}請踮起染血的腳尖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.17,0:00:59.09,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}緊皺眉頭  看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.22,0:01:03.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}相互毀滅吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.54,0:01:06.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}迎接那充滿無限延伸謎題的結局
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.64,0:01:10.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}就像被奪去羽翼與雙足後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.18,0:01:13.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在虛空中腐朽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.64,0:01:16.87,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}還有另一個我存在於這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.98,0:01:22.26,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}疼愛著某人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.64,0:01:28.83,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}請告訴我  孰虛孰實
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.98,0:00:12.34,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}夜ヲ覆ウ目蓋開ケ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.34,0:00:15.83,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}凶キ影ヲ恐レルナカレ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.25,0:00:23.37,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}仄くらき柩から
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.41,0:00:31.73,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}産み堕とされた人形のように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.43,0:00:36.73,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}躰は赤く凍え
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.66,0:00:45.34,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}心は闇にあやされ育つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.62,0:00:48.74,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に僕が見えるかい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.74,0:00:52.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}つなぐ手の冷たさに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.04,0:00:55.17,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}鮮血の爪立てる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.17,0:00:59.09,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眉寄せてごらんよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.22,0:01:03.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}壊し合おう　先に続く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.54,0:01:06.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}謎に満ちる結末を
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.64,0:01:10.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽も脚ももがれたまま
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.18,0:01:13.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}虚空のなか朽ち果てるより
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.64,0:01:16.87,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうひとり僕がいて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.98,0:01:22.26,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誰かを痛いほど愛しているんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.64,0:01:28.83,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}さぁどっちが幻だろうね
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.37,0:24:29.82,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}色褪せていくフィルムのように
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.14,0:24:47.64,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}確かな現在もいずれ霞んで
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.23,0:25:05.98,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}何でもなく　笑いあった　刹那の時間と光
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.04,0:25:15.62,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}繋がっていく記憶を底に
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.95,0:25:25.75,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}誰かが見つけるためあると
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.92,0:25:33.63,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}信じている　今でも
Comment: 0,0:01:11.80,0:01:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.37,0:24:29.82,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}如膠片般漸漸褪色
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.14,0:24:47.64,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}眼下的歷歷在目  終將化為雲煙
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.23,0:25:05.98,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}別無他意地相視而笑  剎那間時間與光
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.04,0:25:15.62,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}就此相互輝映  將記憶埋藏於深處
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.95,0:25:25.75,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}為了有誰能將其發現
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.92,0:25:33.63,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}{\be5}我至今仍堅信著
Comment: 0,0:00:50.00,0:00:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.14,0:03:05.14,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(546,300)}-死者-
Comment: 0,0:01:20.00,0:01:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------ANIME-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.15,0:01:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了  快逃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.11,0:02:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.78,0:02:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想死！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.74,0:02:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不太正常呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.95,0:01:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎麼回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.09,0:03:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.81,0:03:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說大家都因為疑神疑鬼…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.98,0:03:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.29,0:03:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有其他人逃出來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.19,0:03:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.73,0:03:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出血已經止住了  沒什麼大礙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.75,0:03:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們待在這裡不要離開  聽到嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.34,0:04:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松井同學
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.86,0:04:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.75,0:04:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,榊原同學  你還記得她嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.36,0:04:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.45,0:04:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然…不是她嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.27,0:04:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼果然…你在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.78,0:04:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杉浦同學懷疑是見崎同學
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.45,0:04:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我懷疑你才是死者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.53,0:04:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年是從5月開始的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.44,0:04:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那5月份增加的人才是死者  難道不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.16,0:04:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.95,0:04:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年是從4月開始的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.75,0:04:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種胡言亂語誰會相信
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.92,0:05:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風見同學…為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.02,0:05:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差點被敕使河原殺掉時明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.05,0:05:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須讓死者回歸死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.70,0:05:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然自己會死
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.05,0:05:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因為這…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.92,0:05:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少囉嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.94,0:05:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你不轉學過來  由加利就不會死了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.19,0:05:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木同學…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.86,0:05:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你不去接近不存在的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.83,0:05:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死者就回歸死…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.16,0:05:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.49,0:05:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恒一同學怎麼可能是死者
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.41,0:05:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風見同學  你殺了兩個同學吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.43,0:05:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活著也沒用了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.27,0:05:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來讓你解脫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.70,0:05:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去由加利那裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.24,0:06:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再做自相殘殺這種傻事了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.57,0:06:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡說些漂亮話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.29,0:06:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕死亡而臨陣脫逃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.66,0:06:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成為旁觀者的你沒有資格這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.03,0:06:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的確是逃跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.56,0:06:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我還能救眼前這些死得不明不白的學生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.59,0:06:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁觀者的你什麼都做不了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.77,0:06:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼都成不了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.84,0:06:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能推動事態的只有身處險境的當事人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.11,0:06:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,榊原同學也到外面去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.52,0:06:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風見
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.19,0:06:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  風見
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.89,0:06:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.20,0:06:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開什麼玩笑啊  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.68,0:07:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.31,0:07:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋！混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.17,0:07:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎還在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.64,0:07:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.87,0:07:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在的話就回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.03,0:07:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.88,0:08:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  快住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.44,0:08:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不殺了她的話  大家都會死的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.80,0:08:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恒一同學也會死的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.42,0:08:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.51,0:08:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎不是死者
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.85,0:08:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果殺了她還不能停止災難的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.09,0:08:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就認了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.16,0:09:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一來…就能停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.38,0:09:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.63,0:09:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.77,0:09:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.87,0:09:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我是想保護你  為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.60,0:09:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼想死的話
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.79,0:09:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把你們一起殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.10,0:10:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥個笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.41,0:10:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.41,0:10:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.64,0:10:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.18,0:10:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是夜見北的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.66,0:10:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我剛從東京過來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.64,0:10:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.84,0:10:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有哪裡疼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.38,0:10:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.56,0:10:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為重要的人過世了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.18,0:10:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.28,0:10:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就和我一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.35,0:11:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年半前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.28,0:11:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被空罐砸到了  還記得嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.96,0:11:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.88,0:11:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.63,0:11:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是說謊也好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.70,0:11:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我說你還記得呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.11,0:11:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤澤同學…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.75,0:12:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.36,0:12:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.57,0:12:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  還能用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.92,0:12:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了  要打通啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.57,0:12:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,榊原同學
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.62,0:12:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎  你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.61,0:12:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.21,0:12:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.41,0:12:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後院
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.49,0:12:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒受傷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.48,0:12:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.44,0:12:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過暫時走不開
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.55,0:13:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上過來  這就來  你就在那…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.24,0:13:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好別來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.20,0:13:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.80,0:13:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,榊原同學還是別來的好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.03,0:13:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我問你為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.11,0:13:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.51,0:13:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須得阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.90,0:13:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎…難道…你要將誰給…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.40,0:13:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你或許會後悔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.72,0:13:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.33,0:13:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.62,0:13:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.25,0:13:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能過來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.04,0:13:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點去救她
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.91,0:13:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能救她
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.45,0:13:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顏色  因為能看見死亡的顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.15,0:13:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是剛剛知道的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.83,0:14:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前就知道了  但沒說出口
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.76,0:14:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.14,0:14:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  我不親手阻止的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.48,0:14:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.36,0:14:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.70,0:14:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道…難道…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.89,0:14:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙人的吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.92,0:14:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個人是「另一個人」…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.50,0:14:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.40,0:14:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是這個人嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.36,0:14:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三神老師  憐子阿姨是「另一個人」嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.37,0:14:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恒一
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.37,0:14:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來夜見北心得之四
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.40,0:14:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公私要分明
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.29,0:14:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在校園裡不能叫我憐子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.62,0:15:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學校裡我也算是副班主任的三神老師
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.30,0:15:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.74,0:15:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這所學校其他班級有副班主任？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.54,0:15:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.17,0:15:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有  學校裡有副班主任的只有三年三班
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.00,0:15:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年教室的書桌是夠用的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.45,0:15:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而災難4月就開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.28,0:15:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得是為什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.34,0:15:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺一個書桌的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.23,0:15:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是辦公室
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.95,0:15:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說謊  她在說謊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.61,0:15:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,榊原同學  讓開
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.95,0:16:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.70,0:16:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓死者回歸死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.39,0:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恒一…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.09,0:16:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  憐子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.24,0:16:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.15,0:16:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了嗎  這樣就行了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.05,0:16:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣真的就行了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.95,0:16:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒弄錯嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.91,0:16:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬一弄錯人的話  我就把憐子阿姨…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.89,0:16:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見崎說過的也好  眼睛的事也好  都是真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.02,0:16:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的能相信嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.97,0:16:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起來了  我看到過…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.80,0:16:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到過的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.44,0:17:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年半前  我看到了三神老師被殺的那一刻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.85,0:17:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打起…打起精神來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.59,0:17:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼  為什麼  小憐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.11,0:17:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概一年半前  是在寵物店呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.74,0:17:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺怎麼樣  一年半後的夜見山
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.88,0:17:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年半前  你被空罐砸到了  還記得嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.42,0:17:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人死後都要辦葬禮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.35,0:17:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,葬禮真是…太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.22,0:18:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太可憐了  理津子  憐子也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.30,0:18:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.78,0:18:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憐子阿姨…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.75,0:18:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永別了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.33,0:18:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憐子阿姨…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.99,0:19:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永別了  媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.03,0:19:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.41,0:19:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸已經不要緊了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.67,0:19:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還可以  不過體育課還是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.28,0:19:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都不記得三神老師的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.20,0:19:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有我們…嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.77,0:19:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點擔心  榊原同學會不會成為第9個犧牲者
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.70,0:19:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了8個人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.33,0:20:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚴格來說  8月的死者一共10名
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.61,0:20:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有兩個是誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.79,0:20:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管理員夫婦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.57,0:20:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是高林同學的外公外婆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.01,0:20:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高林同學死了之後  他們的精神狀態一直不太穩定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.62,0:20:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三神老師是在一年半前的秋天去世的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.82,0:20:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在夜見山河被殺人魔刺殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.63,0:20:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是記不太清楚了  今年的死者是三神老師吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.01,0:20:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話前年因為災難死亡的有7人了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.03,0:20:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  紅叉記號有7處
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.23,0:20:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前年的檔案裡有寫著赤澤的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.19,0:20:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.10,0:20:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是赤澤同學的表哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.06,0:20:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄妹住在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.95,0:20:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開車送你們一程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.31,0:21:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  我們沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.27,0:21:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  回家路上小心點
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.80,0:21:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對…  災難已經結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.42,0:21:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼時候知道憐子阿姨  三神老師是「另一個人」的？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.14,0:21:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什麼時候呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.39,0:21:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘記了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.73,0:21:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼不告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.07,0:21:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴你了也無可奈何
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.42,0:21:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且也沒辦法對榊原同學開口
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.16,0:21:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三神老師  叫憐子阿姨的  是你重要的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.93,0:21:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去一趟那邊的遊樂園吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.50,0:21:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.42,0:21:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡的摩天輪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.30,0:21:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不坐那個
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.92,0:22:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.68,0:22:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前我從醫院給你打電話
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.68,0:22:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打到手機上卻怎麼也打不通
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.92,0:22:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個之後被我扔河裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.79,0:22:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.97,0:22:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人討厭的機器  沒必要一直和外界聯繫著
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.09,0:22:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  馬上就會給我買新的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.58,0:22:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,買好新手機後  可以偶爾給你打個電話嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.34,0:22:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾的話可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.15,0:22:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  這個從望月同學那兒拿到的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.30,0:22:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憐子阿姨  拍在照片上了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.85,0:22:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.67,0:22:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎誰都看不見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.88,0:22:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連望月也沒看見憐子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.83,0:22:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.48,0:23:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顏色呢  憐子阿姨的顏色是什麼樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.74,0:23:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看見死的顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.93,0:23:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這之後的未來  我們會漸漸遺忘吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.21,0:23:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合宿的事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.12,0:23:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4月開始的事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.30,0:23:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圍繞著三神憐子發生的各種事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.09,0:23:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.75,0:23:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那麼不想忘記？想一直記著？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.35,0:24:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都結束了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.35,0:25:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這便是停止災難的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.56,0:25:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼理解是你們的事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.38,0:25:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一定要三思後再去著手實行
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.00,0:25:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔細考慮清楚  和周圍的朋友們商量好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.12,0:25:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了不讓自己後悔
