Over a century ago, mankind faced a new enemy.
The difference of power between mankind and their newfound enemy was overwhelming.
Soon, mankind was driven to the brink of extinction.
The surviving humans built three walls: the Maria, the Rose, and the Sina.
They then lived the next century in peace, under their protection.
However...
No one remembers the names of the trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next wind before they try again
Chiriochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore those pigs who ridicule you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for having to will to step over dead bodies and move on
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock strengthens this false reality
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into your fists and fight the oppression
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Kobushi da
Far beyond the confining walls, you'll slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your burning bow and gash through the twilight
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
That day
Fall of Shiganshina (pt 2)
Until that time a wretched soul and parted.
From God was I, and wholly avaricious.
Now, as thou seest, I here am punished for it.
What avarice doth is here made manifest.
In the purgation of these souls converted,
and no more bitter pain the Mountain hath.
Stop! Let go!
What more, O Avarice, canst thou do to us,
since thou my blood so to thyself hast drawn,
it careth not for its own proper flesh?
What more, O Avarice—
Eren? What?
We could've saved Mom!
Why the hell would you do that?!
Cut it out.
Eren!
Eren...
You couldn't help your mother because you're weak.
I...
I couldn't face the Titan
because I was scared!
I'm sorry.
This is familiar...
Hurry to the inner gates!
Use the ships to escape!
Hurry up if you don't want to be eaten!
The small, closed-off areas surrounding the walls, such as Shiganshina, were used as baits to attract the Titans,
fulfillling their roles of lowering costs of defense and military.
As a result of this design,
the people of Shiganshina could escape the assault of the Titans by traversing only one gate.
Toss all luggage! We might even fit one more if you do that!
Armin, sit down.
But Eren and Mikasa aren't here yet.
They're there.
Eren...
Now isn't a good time to talk to them.
Those poor souls. You can tell
what happened by looking at them.
Don't just stand there! Hurry up!
What are you waiting for?!
Hurry up! They're coming!
This can't be happening...
God, please save us...
Hey, what the hell are you guys doing?!
This ship is full! We're leaving!
Please, let us on! Even just my child!
I'm sorry, but we can't do that!
Go!
Let us on!
Let us get on!
You fool! What are you aiming at?!
We can't hit moving targets with these!
Who the hell cares?! Just hurry and load the next round!
I can't!
The gate is closing!
No... They're leaving us behind!
Hey!
Don't close it yet! Just wait a little longer!
We've still got people out there!
If they break through this gate, we'll lose much more than just this small district!
Mankind will be pushed back to the next wall!
That doesn't mean it's okay to just sacrifice all those people!
Hurry up and close it!
The Titans are coming!
Hurry up and close the gate!
Stop!
Hey!
What...
the hell is it doing?
Fire!
What...
It's not working!
Shit! Run!
Hurry!
The Titans are coming!
Close the gate!
Hurry! Close the gate!
The gate's...
Currently Disclosable Information
Map of human activity [1/2]
This map from the source material illustrates
the size of the human activity area.
No information is available in regards to the exterior of Wall Maria.
Currently Disclosable Information
Map of human activity [2/2]
The altitude of the human activity area
increases near the center.
The area is rich in water, minerals, natural gas,
and other resources.
Within a few hours after Wall Maria had fallen in the southern district of Shiganshina,
the news of it spread through the human territories like wildfire.
Is it true that Shiganshina was invaded by the Titans?
South of Wall Rose
Trost District
Unbelievable. How could the wall fall after lasting an entire century?
The truth is out there.
A ship carrying refugees is already here!
It's reported to have over 500 people onboard.
The question is whether Shiganshina was all we lost.
But there is no way they could invade Wall Maria...
Anyway, let's contact the center and wait for orders.
We can't handle such an emergency by ourselves.
Excuse me!
We just received word!
Wall Maria has fallen and the Titans have invaded the area beyond!
This is the end...
It's over...
The Titans will eat us all...
It's over?
I'll never be able to go home again.
Why?!
Why was I so immature and argued until the very end?!
Mom is gone...
She's gone!
Why?
Because you're weak.
I... Us humans are weak.
Because we're weak, we can do nothing but cry?
I'll erase their existence from this world...
Eren?
What's the matter, Eren?
I'm going to kill them all.
Not even a single one of them will be left...!
Eren...
That year, the Central Government decided to withdraw all human activity inside Wall Rose.
The Titans devoured 10,000 people.
Eren! Carla! Mikasa!
I pray for your safety...
Eren...!
Eren!
Dad! Please stop, Dad!
What are you trying to do?!
Just give me your hand!
No!
You've been acting all weird since Mom died!
Let go of me, Dad!
You're no good!
What are you talking about?!
Don't forget the key!
You must make it there!
But until then—!
Eren, are you okay?
You were crying in your sleep.
It felt like I just met Dad.
No, it was just a dream.
I see...
Let's go. They're handing out rations.
This place used to be the food reserves.
The people who came by ships have now gathered here.
Hey, stop cutting in line!
Shut up!
I haven't eaten anything since yesterday!
We will still struggle for our survival.
Eren! Mikasa!
Armin?
Look! I made it!
Grandpa got these for us kids!
Thanks.
What's the matter with him?
That's how it goes.
There's probably not enough food for everyone.
This is an entire day's worth.
There are just too many refugees.
There's always been a food shortage,
and you know how people always look down on those who live in the outskirts.
Why do we have to give our food to outsiders?
I mean, the Titans broke through the wall anyway.
They should've eaten more of them.
Eren!
This will just make the food shortage worse.
What the hell are you doing, you brat?!
You don't know what you're talking about!
You've never seen it happen with your own eyes!
How the Titans eat people...
Shut up!
We're sorry!
He's just ticked off because he's hungry.
That's why he's acting like a brat.
We're really sorry!
Whatever...
You would've been dead without us.
You kids should learn to be more grateful.
Yes!
Dammit...
I'd rather die than leech off people like him...
I'll be back inside Wall Maria to kill off all the Titans.
Eren, you're not serious, right?
I've never been more serious!
I'm not like those people who only act tough when protected by the wall!
I don't need this crap!
Eren, what are you doing?!
Doesn't it piss you off?
We can't do anything against the Titans because we live off of such pity!
It's impossible!
Nothing can defeat them.
Our only choice is to live inside the walls.
If you do anything rash, you'll die the same way my parents did!
So that's why you're sucking up to those people?!
Do you have no shame?
That's all we can do right now!
That's just an excuse!
Just continue living like livestock, you weak piece of shit!
Mikasa?
If Armin's weak, then so are you and I.
We couldn't even escape the Titans or leave the city by ourselves.
Even the food we eat is from someone else.
There's absolutely no chance of us
weaklings taking down even one Titan.
What's important is staying alive, just as your mother said.
Mikasa?
Eat. Eat and stay alive.
I won't let you starve to death.
A few days later, the refugees were all sent to cultivate land and to secure food.
But that couldn't prevent the food shortage.
In the following year of 846,
the Central Government launched a campaign to retake Wall Maria using the refugees.
There were 250 thousand of them.
Almost a fifth of the total population.
However, only about a hundred survived.
With their sacrifice, the food shortage has
improved, albeit a little, for those who survived.
The Titans are to blame.
If only we could defeat them,
we would regain our place in this world.
Armin, I'm applying for military training next year.
I'll become strong enough to fight them.
Me too.
Armin?!
Me too!
I'll join you too.
Mikasa? You don't have to!
You said survival is the most important thing.
Yes, and I will be there ensuring your safety.
All right, we'll all join.
You are now officially members of the training unit no. 104!
Unfortunately for you, I, Keith Shardis, will be in charge.
I'm not here to give you a warm welcome.
All of you are now merely livestock, waiting to be eaten by the Titans.
You're even worse than livestock!
For the next three years, I'll train you useless shits.
I'll teach you how to fight the Titans!
When you face a Titan in three years, will you still be just food?
Or will you become a glorious wall to protect these walls?
Or a mighty champion of mankind who will destroy the Titans?
The choice lies in your hands.
Yeah, don't worry.
I'll kill every last one of them.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It is more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, sleep in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful and cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves
naze to tou bakari de
why it was we who survived
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic hold true no longer
A failure as a soldier,
Eren vowed revenge against the Titans as he began his training,
but he had to face the bitter reality as he kept failing even the most basic of all exercises.
A Dull Light in Despair
Restoration of Mankind (pt 1)