Episode 9:    "Leila's Crash Course"
I am Noir Stalgia.
In a hidden dungeon,
my master bestowed upon me the Creation skill.
In order to save my master who is trapped,
Leila
I am accumulating LP needed to use Creation.
Noir-kun, the basic kata are important,
but in real combat things won't be this pretty.
R-Right.
Sorry, do I smell of sweat?
No, you smell like greenery...
No way, you're kidding!
Next, the throwing techniques.
Try grabbing me however you can.
Yes, sensei! I'll be in your care!
You're so stiff.
Just go for it.
Then...
Ahh! Noir-san!
You! You are an adventurer from Lahmu, aren't you?
Noir-san belongs to Odin,
you're not poaching him!
It's not like I'm...
But if you talk like that, I'm not backing down.
Noir-san, which do you prefer?!
Both are fine...
Flirting with girls is the most efficient way to accumulate LP.
I'm doing this to save Master!