Episode 10:
"Luna's Deposit Account"
I am Noir Stalgia.
In a hidden dungeon,
my master bestowed upon me the Creation skill.
In order to save my master who is trapped,
Luna
I am accumulating LP needed to use Creation.
Luna-san, please pull yourself together!
Can I get treatment yet?
I'm terribly sorry for making you see such an unsightly scene.
Please forget about it.
Luna-san, don't overdo it.
Should I grant you an increased mana reserve skill?
I don't want to owe Noru-dono more than I already have.
I know, how about we create a Luna Deposit Account?
Luna Deposit Account?
We'll accumulate LP,
and 30% of it will go towards the skills I need.
Luna Deposit Account
Noir-dono, you can use the rest however you wish.
You can have a higher percentage.
For the sake of saving up LP,
I want you to put me to good use!
P-Put you to good use...
Come, anything is fine!
Noir-dono, come on!
If you say so...
~Ahh~ No way... So suddenly...
Does it hurt?
N-Not... at all!
Flirting with girls is the most efficient way to accumulate LP.
I'm doing this to save Master!
If I keep getting tormented like that,
what will become of me?
Noir-dono, we've just discovered
another one of your preferences.