Episode 11:        "Pretty Girls Onigiri"
I am Noir Stalgia.
In a hidden dungeon,
my master bestowed upon me the Creation skill.
In order to save my master who is trapped,
I am accumulating LP needed to use Creation.
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!
Noir, good job! The store is a great success, right?
Yep, thanks to everyone's help.
It's Onii-sama and Alice's very own store.
It's natural.
Uh... It's everyone's store, isn't it?
Today was really exhausting though.
Is there anything I can do to help?
For example... Like a hug.
Alice-chan?!
We're family. It's just natural skinship.
I thought of it first!
First come, first served.
Th-Then...
Can I get a pretty girls onigiri?
A pretty girls onigiri?
Squeeze
Th-This is...
A New Sensation!
Squeeze
Flirting with girls is the most efficient way to accumulate LP.
I'm doing this to save Master!
Thank you very muuuuuch!
Hot! Hot!
TN: Hokka Hokka (Hot! Hot!) is a shout associated with tasty rice dishes,
there is a famous bento take-out chain Hokka Hokka Tei (Hot Hot Shop).