A date...
with me?
I'm kind of shocked.
What are you talking about, Shin?
Can't we?
There should still be
a full day for the DEM raid.
That's true, but you wouldn't need to
conduct training right away, would you?
It's not about training!
You see, it is only now,
before the upcoming battle,
that I'd like to ask you out on a date.
Have you told everyone about this?
I haven't.
Why would you take me
on a date, though?
So you wouldn't date me?
I didn't say that I wouldn't.
But if you want to date someone,
there must be someone else beside me.
I can't do that.
You are the only person
I'd want to date right now, Reine.
Let's set the schedule.
Where would you take me for a date?
As far as my eyes can see,
colors abound
Scenes of the past, unravel, unwound
Paradox tightens,
the resolve we've found
Sinking into tomorrows,
out of bounds
If I open these hands,
once clenched tight
I'll grasp at hopes,
long lost from sight
Tears have dried,
facing the darkest night
Even as you gaze at a future bright
Finally, the light, almost within sight
No words needed,
in silence, take flight
For all the answers, here,
in our hands alight
I see.
Reine is your best friend, after all.
I think it's shocking for you
to suddenly be told this story.
But...
Thanks. It must be
tough for you too, right?
Thanks for telling me this, though.
Kotori...
Now, let's plan countermeasures
before Reine notices.
Yeah. You're right.
Anyway, we need to think about
what your date with Reine
is going to be like by morning.
At the same time, we need to work
on the operation against DEM.
You're right.
And also...
Oh? Is it about the spirits?
Yeah.
For them, I believe Reine was a reliable
and trustworthy older sister figure.
If they knew that
she had betrayed them...
Yes, I know, but they
have to get over it.
(Origami Tobiichi's - Incoming Call)
Origami?
I've heard about the thing.
What?
The spirits have been informed
of the situation.
We will help you to plan the date.
Wait! Hold on!
How on earth could you know
about this already?
Shido.
Check your second shirt button.
Huh?
Whoa!
I've got the whole situation figured out!
We asked Origami.
I'm surprised, but
it isn't the time to be upset.
I don't even know what's going on,
but the situation is getting hotter.
It's not that I hate it, though!
Hmph! As expected of
Reine Murasame!
I'd never thought she'd deceive
the vigorous Kaguya Yamai!
Petition. Let us help you.
Okay. Then we'll meet
in the briefing room.
To disguise our intentions
in case we run into Reine,
make sure to move one at a time.
Kotori, can you give me a minute?
What?
I've got something to do.
We need to talk.
I know you're there, Kurumi.
It's you, huh?
Oh, dear, it's very unusual of you.
I can't believe you called me, Shido.
Are you the only one here right now?
Is the real Kurumi listening
to our conversation?
You're asking me
some strange questions.
There are no other alter ego,
or even real me here.
If there's a story you don't want
my real self to hear,
that's completely okay.
I see.
I don't know if it's safe
to tell the real Kurumi
what I'm about to tell you.
So...
Could you help me make a decision?
On 20 February,
the main body of Kurumi...
...will die.
You speak as if you have
seen it all, huh?
Yes, you guessed it.
Can you tell me who's the killer?
Even if Ellen Mathers were to
be our opponent later on,
we would not be so easy
to defeat, you know?
It's Mio Takamiya.
The Spirit of Origin
is going to kill Kurumi.
On the battlefield of the future,
Mio suddenly appeared out of Kurumi...
I believe Mio should
already be inside Kurumi now.
I get it now.
I appreciate it.
Certainly, this is not information
that can be handled carelessly.
What do you think?
Can you tell Kurumi about this
without Mio realizing?
Maybe...
The only question is
how to deal with it afterward...
I know, right?
I wish there was
something I could do, but...
Don't look so gloomy, please.
Sure, it's a desperate situation,
but thanks to you
I have a choice now.
Shido.
Has the future me fulfilled my duty?
Yeah. You were amazing.
I see.
R-Reine?! What are you doing?
Doing my job, obviously.
I thought I'd get
tomorrow's work done, too.
And I've finished it.
Oh really?
You've been working hard, then.
What about you, Tohka?
Why are you still awake at this hour?
Well, uhh, you know...
If you're looking for evening meals,
go to the canteen or the rest area.
But our time is regulated,
so be moderate.
Don't forget to brush
your teeth before sleep.
Y-Yeah, I'll be paying attention.
I know you can't sleep, but rest well.
After all, we must protect Shin
from the DEM at all costs.
Reine.
Hmm?
Reine, do you love Shido?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Come on, just answer it. Please.
Well, yeah.
I love him.
I see.
Me too.
I mean...
I might just be overthinking it.
Hello Shido. How's the
bone-conduction headset working?
I can hear it well. It feels a bit
different from usual, though.
If we use an intercom,
Reine will find it out, obviously.
But with this, you don't have to worry
about being noticed.
She should be there by now, get ready.
Got you.
Hey. Did I make you wait?
R-Reine...
It's time.
Let's get started!
All right!
Let's start our date!
To be honest, I still can't believe it.
I can't believe that Reine
is actually the Phantom!
I feel the same way, you know.
But we have to accept the facts.
But it's not so depressing, actually.
According to the boy, it's true that Reine
feels friendship towards us, isn't it?
Exactly.
The point is that if Shido makes
Reine fall in love and seals her,
everything will be fine.
What's wrong, Shin?
Did I surprise you that much?
Uhm, well, uhh...
(1. Sorry, I was admiring you, Reine.)
(2. Your hair is different
from usual. It's lovely.)
(3. How do you want me
to take off that dress?)
All hands, select!
-Yeah!
-Let's go!
(1. Sorry, I was admiring you, Reine.)
(2. Your hair is different
from usual. It's lovely.)
(3. How do you want me
to take off that dress?)
Number one, huh?
It's pretty much in order.
Yes. I think that silence makes
people feel insecure.
But I thought she'd
be happy to hear him say this.
What's with that caring?
Are you a goddess?
I might seem weird
for choosing this option,
thinking he should
look at this part first.
Well, this should convince Reine!
Hmm. But Muku thinks
the number two is not so bad.
Well, it is what it is.
Certainly! God dwells in the details.
The ability to notice
small changes is important.
But!
Addition.
Some people might perceive even minor
changes in hairstyle as not quite right.
Perhaps it's best to start with a safety
measure and see how things go.
And what about those three over there?
Oh, obviously I chose number three!
If a seemingly innocent boy
like him suddenly caught her off guard,
she'd be totally aroused, wouldn't she?
Exactly! Reine is a mature woman,
so she'd totally appreciate
this level of wit!
I mean,
our future depends on this,
could you please take this seriously?
I know.
That's why I chose the option that would
make me happiest if someone said it to me.
Shido.
It's number one.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Because I had never seen you
wearing such an outfit before,
I was, well...
captivated by you, Reine.
Really?
I see.
Thank you.
You look good in that outfit, too.
All right, where are we going today?
It seems like quite
a heavy load you're carrying.
It's still a secret.
I want to surprise you, Reine.
Will you trust me and come along?
Yes, of course.
Shall we go now―
Is there anything wrong?
I guess this was technically a date, huh?
Indeed. Though I didn't mean
it to be just 'technically'.
Yup.
If so, then...
Shall we go?
Yes!
Affection level stats...
It's a strange waveform, isn't it?
She's overflowing with affection, almost
like he could seal it away right now.
And yet, there's no indication
of any sealable response.
It feels like she's keeping a distance
despite harboring affection.
It's like warmly watching them
on stage from the wings.
It's like a motherly feeling, I guess?
Indeed, quite aptly put.
Regardless,
it seems it remains
a challenging issue.
This is...
Reine's affinity has increased!
It seems the commander's
strategy has paid off!
It's not just my idea, though.
Last night, I stayed up late with all
spirits to plan this, and it's paid off.
A day trip to
a hot spring on a holiday,
indeed, that's an enticing choice.
After all, Analyst Murasame works
the hardest within the Fraxinus.
Moreover, she also works as
a teacher at Raizen High School.
And for decades,
she has continued to work
towards the revival of Shinji Takamiya.
Even for spirits,
it's only natural to be exhausted.
Well, Reine always had dark circles
under her eyes, didn't she?
I always thought that
her work was always tough.
Yeah, she probably didn't get
much sleep every day.
Not just her body,
but her mind must be exhausted too.
And I suppose what Reine needs is...
...relaxation!
She can relieve all that
accumulated fatigue and weariness
with various relaxation facilities!
(1. Relax in the spacious communal bath.)
(2. Unwind in your own private outdoor bath.)
(3. Refresh with a massage.)
All hands, select!
- Yes!
(1. Relax in the spacious communal bath.
2. Unwind in your own private outdoor bath.)
(3. Refresh with a massage.)
Hmm...
It's number two, huh?
Well, the idea of Shido and Reine
bathing together is,
well, a bit awkward, isn't it?
Yes, I think it's better if the two of them
can have a good conversation together.
It's okay. I'm calm,
I'm calm, I'm calm.
Wait, why should you
say it three times?
Besides, I have experience being alone
with Shido in the bath.
I'm not the type to lose my calmness
over something like this.
Wait! Weren't you the one who was waiting
in ambush without his knowledge back then?
Hmph. When it comes to bathing,
we Yamai can't be ignored.
Agreement.
Making Shido a sandwich by
squeezing him between me and Kaguya was...
a beautiful memory.
Since they've come all
the way to a hot spring inn
let them enjoy
some naked bonding time!
In a bath this size,
there's plenty of room
for Darling and Reine
to squeeze in a bit!
Isn't this the world's best
complete erotic bento box?!
Shido. It's number two.
Roger that.
Shin.
May I go in?
Uhm, yes, please.
Huh?!
Oh my goodness!
What?!
What on earth is going on?!
Analyst Murasame's body...
I mean, I can't see the important
walkthrough screen!
Oh my God!
Restore it right away!
Our goal is for the spirits
to feel love and affection.
After sealing the spiritual power,
it would be wise for us not to do anything
that might make Reine uncomfortable.
-No!
Kannazuki, you're calm, huh?
Oh.
Yes. I am not so much
interested in big breasts.
Oh, I see.
It's just the two of us,
so it should be fine, right?
Huh?
Geez...
You've got pretty enormous ones.
Uhm...
Reine,
when did you start working at Ratatoskr?
Probably since five or six years ago.
Around the same time when
Kotori was appointed
as the commander.
I see.
Well, uhh...
Thank you so much.
What for?
Well, I mean...
You've been supporting Kotori all along.
I haven't done much.
Even without me,
she would surely
have become a great commander.
Well, I won't deny that Kotori's
ability is exceptional...
But what did you do before that?
I was just an ordinary student.
My thesis was recognized,
and that's how I was scouted by Ratatoskr.
Did you have someone
you liked or something?
There was only one person.
Is that person―
It's not fair that I'm
the only one talking, huh?
Would you let me hear your story, too?
Eh?!
Uhm, okay...
I've been curious
to hear your story, too.
Do you remember anything
before being taken in
by the Itsuka family?
To be honest,
it seems like I don't have
very clear memories.
The thing I remember...
The feeling of being held
by warm hands,
and the warmth of embrace, followed by
a sense of loss as those hands vanish.
I'm sure that...
it was from my mother.
Do you resent your mother
for abandoning you?
What?!
Well, I don't harbor
any resentment.
There must have been
some circumstances.
She didn't abandon me out of choice.
Besides, I remember.
How gentle those hands
were when they held me.
I see...
Eek!
There, there.
Hold on!
Reine?!
A little wouldn't hurt, right?
I may not be able to replace her, but...
Uhm...
Ellen, I'm sorry for the suddenness,
but I've decided to expedite our plans.
The situation has changed.
No, it seems like it's about
to change from now on.
What do you mean, Ike?
Oh my, I'm truly fortunate.
I've never felt such a fateful connection
to the Demon King in my hand,
Beelzebub, the Omniscient.
Does that mean...
Beelzebub has discovered something new?
That's right.
It seems we suffered
a painful defeat once.
In a future we're not aware of.
But this time,
we can make the first move.
For now, prepare the power plant.
We'll also need to
gather some talismans.
Then, let's summon the Spirit of Origin.
Now, Ellen.
Let's change the future together.
What is it that you want to show, Shin?
We're almost there.
I'm sure you'll like it.
Here we are.
You can open your eyes now.
This is...
The place I wanted to show you, Reine.
It's beautiful, right?
Yeah...
It's beautiful.
So beautiful.
(Episode 9: "The 'Second' Date")
It's all gone by so naturally
Seeking out the simple happiness
The dry wind that asks
A flower fluttering in the air
One day, I'll keep it a secret
Those faint and vivid shadows
I'm still here and breathing
With the pain that never ceases
I'm still here
Waiting for you
We shall live in this world
With those simple happiness
("The Battlefield That Shouldn't Exist")
The final battle with Westcott.
Who will grasp the future,
DEM or Ratatoskr?
Next, Episode 10,
"The Battlefield That Shouldn't Exist."
The three siblings, united.