All ships, fall back!
Keep your distance to avoid being hit
by the light and press on the attack!
Maria, where are Shido and Tohka?
I do not know yet.
The footage is distorted
because of that object.
Moreover, another angel-like object
appeared on the ground.
Please hasten the analysis.
Now that Reinyan is gone,
I guess I'm the only one available...
I'll try to do something
with spirit power!
Shido...
As far as my eyes can see,
colors abound
Scenes of the past, unravel, unwound
Paradox tightens,
the resolve we've found
Sinking into tomorrows,
out of bounds
If I open these hands,
once clenched tight
I'll grasp at hopes,
long lost from sight
Tears have dried,
facing the darkest night
Even as you gaze at a future bright
Finally, the light, almost within sight
No words needed,
in silence, take flight
For all the answers, here,
in our hands alight
Captain...
We're almost there!
Anyway, if we can get to that ship
called Fraxinus or whatever that is...
Huh?
This is...
You are First Lieutenant Kusakabe, right?
I have heard the story from Tobiichi.
W-Who are you?
I am Hinako Shiizaki,
a member of the Fraxinus crew.
We have moved you all aboard
the ship with the transporter.
Now,
please bring Artemisia
and her squad over here.
O-Okay...
They are my dear friends.
Please take care of them.
We can't guarantee that,
but we'll do our best.
Welcome to Fraxinus.
I'm Kotori Itsuka, the commander.
I am Ryoko Kusakabe,
a former AST member of the JGSDF.
Wait...
Y-You are the commander?
Oh, what a nostalgic response!
We've grown accustomed to it,
but it's just not normal, you know?
That a middle school girl
is the commander.
Ahem.
Excuse me.
Please forgive my foolishness for trying
to judge your ability based on age and
appearance, even if only for a moment.
I appreciate you being flexible.
But I'm sorry to disappoint you,
I don't think we can afford
to have a welcome party.
Please don't worry about it.
We understand the situation.
Thanks.
Artemisia's recovery is completed.
Kannazuki,
our preparation's ready, right?
We're going through.
Yeah, I'm on it, Commander.
Wha...
What?!
Captain Kannazuki!
What are you doing here?!
Ah, long time no see, Kusakabe.
Captain...
...Kannazuki?
Huh?
He was the captain of the AST
when I was just assigned to it!
He was the top ace of the troop,
by far and away the best.
Wow, so he is...
Isn't he kind of cool?
Kannazuki, you used to do that, huh?
I thought the commander had picked
you up from the side of the road...
Commander Itsuka,
this man is dangerous!
He is a pervert who dreams of getting his
ass kicked by a middle school-aged girl!
During his tenure,
he started the "Association to Protect
Junior High School Girls" by himself,
and was reported as a
suspicious person while watching over
local middle school students
on their commute to school!
Commander, you are in his strike zone!
That's rude!
Lately, I like to get stomped
by the heels as well!
The modest but smoldering goodness of...
Y-Yahoo!
We don't have time for this!
Maria breaks through
the front DEM fleet.
We'll launch an attack on Mio.
Copy that.
Authorizing activation of Gungnir.
Why are you sleeping so carefree?
Ratatoskr is not paying you
to take a nap, you know?
Ah!
Thank you so much.
Here we go, Maria!
For the spirits!
And above all, for the reward
from the Commander!
Captain...
Was that guy really our top ace?
He really was.
But...
To have taken the
"walking problem generator,"
"The man whose technique is a treasure
but his fetish should be reported,"
Kyohei Kannazuki, this far...
That commander's no ordinary woman...!
Launching Yggdrafolium,
first to fifteenth.
It will deflect
the enemy ship in front of us.
After passing through it,
provide support for the spirits.
Analysis complete!
What on earth is this!
What's wrong, Nia?
What's wrong with that Angel?
It's way beyond the level of overkill!
Every living thing exposed to that
light is dead without exception,
and all objects are destroyed.
The lifespan, durability limits, and so on
of anything is instantly reduced to zero...
In a word, it's like
"absolute death beam"?
If I drew something like this in a comic
it would definitely be rejected.
I mean, how are you going to beat it?
As for the other thing,
it's kind of...
That one area is like
a completely different world.
If we could get a little closer, we might
be able to see what's going on inside...
Kotori.
Jettison the compartment
where the unconscious
and non-combatants
who were boarded earlier,
I suggest we jettison it to Ulmus.
Maria...
Of course, I have no intention of losing.
It's just a risk diversification.
Thank you, Maria.
Thanks for your suggestion.
No. It's a given that AI's processing
speed is faster than human's.
Captain Kusakabe, it's as you heard.
Would you mind guarding the section
where we're going to launch?
Do you mean...
Alright, Roger that.
Godspeed.
Captain, you are a wonderful person.
I'd love to have you under my command.
Now, I'm sorry, everyone.
But you're going to join me to the hell.
If anyone wants to retreat,
feel free to join them now.
What are you saying, Commander?
We've come this far, we're willing
to go all the way with you.
In the first place, it's too dangerous to
leave you and vice commander alone.
Absolutely.
Alright, then.
Let's go. I love you, everyone.
Right!
We forced our way through
the enemy fleet territory.
Kotori, get the main gun ready.
We have confirmed the inside
of the space in question!
In the center of it is Analyst Murasame...
no, it's Mio Takamiya!
Tohka and Tobiichi
are fighting against her!
What about everyone else?
Around them... Yoshino, Kaguya,
Yuzuru, Mukuro are collapsed!
There are no vital signs!
Our target, Mio Takamiya...
Gungnir...
Fire!
What's wrong?
You're not going to come?
If you won't come,
then I'll come to you.
Origami!
I know!
Sandalphon!
Einherjar!
Reine...
Or... should I call you Mio now?
I'm fine with both.
Reine... was it all a lie?
You who helped me...
and kept supporting me...
even when you called me
your best friend!
Was it all a lie, all of it?
It's not a lie.
I cared for the spirits
and I liked everyone in Fraxinus.
And I still consider you
to be my best friend, even now.
It's just...
I would even devour
my best friend to get Shin back.
That's all.
There's... no way...
What does... that mean...
Raphael!
Nibelcole.
Leave it to us, Father!
It's no use!
What?!
How is it? It's simple,
but it's not a bad move, right?
You've been doing
whatever you want all this time.
You're going to take responsibility!
Metatron!
Huh, what? Did you just get
obliterated by your own attack?
Do you think you're no match for us
so you blow yourself up?
So, what should we do, Father?
Hmm... Well...
Huh?!
What?! What's wrong with me
that I dare to attack Father?!
Is it rebellion?
Am I being rebellious?
Wha... You!
I can't believe you attacked
Father dressed as me!
Were you transformed into Nibelcole
with the power of Haniel?
It was a smart move,
but also very predictable.
My Demon King is Beelzebub, which is
able to know everything in the world.
Of course, I've already researched
what kind of power each spirit has.
It's time to close the curtain.
I have to get the remaining
Spiritual Power before I encounter Deus...
In order to create a new world.
A new... world?
Yes. I, Elliot, Ellen, and Karen...
are not artificial magicians.
We are descendants of
a pure sorcerer called Magus.
One day, humans who feared our power
burned down our village
and killed all of our people.
So I will override this world
with the power of Deus.
To exact revenge on mankind...
Would it be easier to convince you
if that is the reason?
What did you say?
To tell you the truth,
it's not that big of a reason.
In my case, my standards for feeling
"pleasure" and "discomfort"
were a little different from others.
That's all there is to it.
The rest is no different than
any other human being.
I'm just striving to achieve my goals
and my curiosity as I wish.
In that regard,
I am a very ordinary person...
Well, this has gotten long-winded...
Farewell, Shido Itsuka.
And to you, too,
Shinji Takamiya.
W-What?!
Natsumi?!
Are you okay, Darling?
Dangerous.
That was a close one!
Thanks for saving me.
What is going on
with the battle right now?
We've been out of communication
with everyone...
I mean, isn't that the enemy general?
I'll fill you in later!
The Spirit of Origin has appeared!
We'll beat that guy as soon as possible
and assist everyone!
Wha... Spirit of Origin?
That's something we need to rush!
I will take it a step higher
for Darling and everyone else!
Oh? Diva and Witch, huh?
I'm happy to see that.
I can get two Sephiras
from the two of you.
What should we do, Darling?
Shido will take out Nibelcole
while we beat the master?
No. To beat him, we'll have to make
a move beyond his anticipation...
Otherwise, we must launch attacks
that are predictable but unavoidable.
Both of you can enhance me
with Gabriel's performance.
That's all I need.
Darling...
You must have some idea, huh?
All right, take care!
Whatever you're doing, it's useless!
We'll put all three of you down and
make you kneel before our father!
Sandalphon!
Halvanhelev!
Father!
I possess omniscient power
and unlimited knowledge.
I think you still underestimated
the meaning of that.
Right!
If it's you,
I'm sure you'll block that attack.
Surely, if you've got Beelzebub,
Angel's power is the first thing
you'd look into, of course.
Since I'm the one who uses it
and not the original owner,
it is less powerful.
But you see,
did you know this from Beelzebub?
Did you look into it?
Say, the omniscient Westcott!
What?
Roaring Flash...
...Blast Wave!
Darling!
Shido!
Looks like you've got me...
Is this the end of the line?
It's surprising how easy it went.
Geez... I was so surprised.
Yeah... frankly, I thought
you were going to kill him.
Yeah... I'd like to kill him.
In fact, I made the last attack
because I didn't care if he died.
The last attack...
Roaring Flash or something like...
Ah, ahem!
I don't know how to say it.
It's just... I'm sure
it's not good to kill him.
I don't want to end up
like these guys...
I feel bad for Shinji, though.
Darling...
Well, that's fine, too. I guess.
Are you sure?
I don't think you'll ever get
another opportunity like this...
Shut up! The loser doesn't get
a say in the matter!
You sound just like Elliot.
That's too bad.
I've always been interested
in the sensation of death...
Wha...
Huh?
Miku! Natsumi!
Shin...
Mio!
Everyone is...
All of the Sephiras
have been collected...
Along with their lives.
Now we'll be together forever...
Shin.
(Episode 7: "The World Tree Falls")
It's all gone by so naturally
Seeking out the simple happiness
The dry wind that asks
A flower fluttering in the air
One day, I'll keep it a secret
Those faint and vivid shadows
I'm still here and breathing
With the pain that never ceases
I'm still here
Waiting for you
We shall live in this world
With those simple happiness
("Those Who Put a Finger on the Trigger.")
Shido fell into despair
by the deaths of his friends.
And who appeared at the last moment?
Next, Episode 8:
"Those Who Put a Finger on the Trigger."
Fight on and wipe away your tears, Shido!