There really are trees in the middle of the desert
With so many water fruits,
I can solve the water crisis and
be exempt from my demotion.
Does this little fruit really hold that much water?
Yes, I heard that it was compressed inside with magic.
Magic… again.
This queer topic
always makes me feel my presense being denied.
It's very annoying.
You still don't believe in magic?
Be careful of divine retribution.
I seem to smell strong magic and meat here.
It smells so good.
Hey, stop it.
What you just said is called a flag.
An earthquake?
Behold! Here is divine retribution from Zenarith!
Now, quickly apologize to me.
Alice,
I have a sense of foreboding.
Everyone get onto the buggy.
Get ready to make a run.
Sa… Sand King!
This is the first time I see it! It's so huge!
So these fruits are…
A part of that the Sand King's body,
which is an organ for storing water, right?
Is it really alright for us to take them?
Alice
I've had enough of this planet. I want to go home.
Don't say such heartless stuff, partner.
This planet is interesting.
Wha… What are we going to do?
It's going to catch up with us.
Alice, can you drive faster?
Don't worry Six.
Later I will let out a signal.
Everyone will jump out of the car at that time.
You're kidding, right?
What about the water fruits?
Jump now!
The water fruits…
There's still one left.
But it's far from enough.
Did the mission fail?
That's not important.
How do we get back home?
Episode 9 Carnivorous Female Chimera
CROSSING THE DESERT DAY ONE
The scorching sun shines mercilessly onto our bodies.
In order to return to the Grace Kingdom,
we have to travel through the Tezan Desert.
It's hot.
You're too noisy.
Your complaining will only make it feel hotter.
That's because of your clothes.
Why don't you take off your black armor.
It can help regulate my temperature.
Wha… You're so sly.
At least share half of the armor with me.
This armor is tailored for me.
If you think it unbearable, why don't you strip off?
If you two continue arguing, you will get hungry soon.
Only one day after jumping off the car has Grimm fainted out.
Six, exchange your remaining points for a tent.
If you don't, we are going to perish here.
You're right.
After all, we can use this for water.
Captain, I want to eat something.
This is the biggest problem.
At worst, we'll have to eat any monsters that we bump into.
It's time for getting survival,
not for being picky.
We will eat anything that we run into.
Understand?
No! I can't do it!
I really can't!
I really can't eat an orc!
Captain, you're the one who said so.
Stop being picky.
Yes… Stop being pathetic.
Rose, open his mouth!
Let me feed him.
Alice, save me!
They are forcing me to step over my bottom line!
Don't worry, I've checked its properties.
It's not poisonous so you can eat it safely.
I can't eat an intelligent creature!
Come, let me feed you.
Don't give me its head!
Give me something else instead!
Six, things will become worse if we don't find a solution.
So, I need you to do something.
Let's hear it.
Please take off Snow's panties.
Are you kidding me?
Alice, get a grip!
We can only rely on you now!
I understand, partner.
I will do it as your wish.
Don't do it!
Have you driven crazy by the heat?
That's right, stop kidding.
Have you forgotten something?
As long as I commit evil deeds, my points will increase.
If we have points,
I can exchange them for food or even a new buggy.
Why didn't I think of this earlier?
Since it's so hot, let me help you undress.
Go to hell!
Please do not do this in such a cramped place.
Wait until there are not any other options left.
I think we have already run out of options.
Additionally, both Snow and I have already experienced
skin-ship, like rubbing her breast and removing her panties.
Shut up!
Why don't you choose to take off others' panties?
Do it to Rose.
It's the same thing
Just let me rub your breast and remove your panties.
That's impossible.
Six.
Villainy points added.
Six, you…
really surprise me.
Cap… Captain, you're nasty.
No… You misunderstand.
It's Alice…
CROSSING THE DESERT DAY FOUR
It's the fourth day on our torturous journey through the desert.
There is not even a town appearing in our sight.
The daylight is scorching.
So we've decided to move at night.
Because of this, we have not seen any monsters.
However, our food supply has become a problem.
Harassing an unconscious person won't increase the points.
CROSSING THE DESERT DAY SIX
Maybe I can eat an orc now.
I've proposed to loan some points as the last resort
But no one agreed,
even though I succeeded before.
It must be because of Astaroth.
I swear, once I return back to the Earth, I'll use her to get some points.
There is something wrong with Rose.
She seems to want to tell me something.
She often stares at Grimm who remains motionless.
Rose is the kindest person in our team.
She must be worried about her good friend.
By the way, I am hungry.
CROSSING THE DESERT DAY SEVEN
I am starving!
I want to drink cold beer!
Also, let me be alone. Just five minutes are enough.
That's weird.
The points do not increase.
Are you being happy?
The system doesn't consider this an evil act,
which means you're actually happy that I flipped your skirt…
She almost killed me
Rose did not stop our quarrel as usual.
Instead…
Her eyes were full of anticipation.
That expression looks familiar to me.
I remember that.
This is the same way those mutant arachnid woman look at me.
When they are exposed to extreme conditions,
their instinct to breed will kick in and they will…
go into heat.
So that's it.
Rose has that look
because she's in heat.
Rose, don't worry.
I know your feeling.
It's because we only have one tent.
As a man, the lack of privacy is really hard to endure.
However, putting aside Grimm and Snow,
is it proper to do that with a pure-hearted child?
No, I can't do that.
As one of a combatant,
I can't do it to Rose.
So…
I can only do something
that's even worse than flipping her skirt?
We are in an emergency now.
I want to…
strip you naked!
Alright!
I've had enough of you.
Bring it on!
Listen, Snow.
If you make some sacrifices,
you can fill your stomach and be happy,
and I will also be extremely happy for other reasons.
This is a mutually beneficial trade.
Even if this is an emergency, I know you're bluffing.
But…
You don't want to die as well, right?
Don't you want to have a meal?
I do.
I'm not talking to you at the moment.
How about it, Snow?
If you agree, I will also give you rare equipment.
I will even smuggle or do anything you ask.
I can even pay your sword loan.
Why are you still hesitant?
You had not hesitated to sell your body to that old man, Engel.
I… I was blinded by greed then.
and Engel has a sense of responsibility.
But…
he…
I hate the word "responsibility".
You are wasting my effort, you idiot.
I'll never…
Are you alright?
Grimm has brought us enough burden.
Now even she also faints out…
Six, here is your chance.
Do it while she is still conscious.
That's not proper.
You coward.
It's because of your cowardliness that you is still just an underling now.
Bu… But forcing myself on an unconscious woman
is a line I will never cross.
Captain,
I can't stand it anymore.
Ro… Rose?
When I see you two, I feel…
Is it alright?
Wa… Wait!
It's not your time to stand out.
Let me do that to Snow first. She won't weigh on my conscience.
But I can't bear it…
I understand.
If you insist…
I'm sorry that I put you on the spot.
It's just so surprising.
Please don't say that.
I'm also clear that this is a forbidden line.
That's right.
We are teammates.
If we cross that line, it might affect adversely our assignments.
However, we are in a dire situation.
And, there is no one around us.
It is our instinct.
Don't feel ashamed about it.
Instinct…
So it's okay to follow the instinct in an emergency.
That's right. It's one of three original desires of mankind.
Yes.
I don't have any other options.
But I'm really surprised.
I'm not aware that you're such a carnivore.
Captain, do you hate carnivores?
No, I like them instead.
Even if I say so, I will not obediently let you eat me.
I won't be able to get any villainy points if it is consensual.
It is the law of nature, right?
If so, I won't feel guilty about it.
Guilty?
Please take the fight seriously, Captain.
What? Are you asking me to take the initiative?
I'm okay with that…
It's more exciting, but…
And I really want to give my all for you.
So please do whatever you want.
Do whatever I want?
I initially wanted to be gentle with you, but since you said that…
Sorry, I can't hold it back anymore.
Wa… Wait a minute.
Let me clean my body with a wet towel first.
Those are the basic manners.
Let's begin right now.
I always think
Captain, you smell really good.
I smell really good?
You're unusually open today.
I think that is too hasty,
but since you like that…
Yes, I will try my best not to cause any pain.
There's no turning back, what's left is for me to start.
There's something I'm curious about.
We're busy!
What are you doing?
Doing "it" with her, of course.
Yes, I'll "eat" Captain.
I don't think you two are on the same page.
I'll do it with Rose. Can't you see it?
Meaning I'll fight with Captain?
What do you mean?
Are you going to play big for the first time?
We will eat the loser according to the law of nature, right?
Do you mean sexually?
I mean eating you literally.
Are you kidding me?
This is not funny!
Why do you suddenly get angry, Captain?
Didn't you say this is one of the three original desires of mankind?
And it's reasonable to follow it.
I did say it.
It's an emergency so I have no need to feel ashamed about it.
You misunderstand what I said.
Hearing you said that you don't hate our species, I am really happy.
It's so hard to communicate with her.
Is this so-called cultural gap?
Captain, you smell very good.
What you said is the same as earlier,
but my heart is racing for another reason.
My grandpa once said that
if you fall in love with someone, you will want to be part of him.
Your grandpa is right, but you also totally misunderstand him.
I'd better leave you two young people alone.
Come on!
It seems that I have to fight with you.
That's right.
We are destined to have this fight since our birth.
I am Rose, the Combat Chimera of Grace Kingdom's Guerilla Force.
Here I come!
I am Combat Agent Six of the Kisaragi Corporation.
I will use you to earn more points.
We should be able to survive with so many points.
Massive amount of villainy points added.
I want to go back to Earth.
Didn't you enjoy yourself yesterday?
Idiot, I didn't cross the line, alright?
I risked my life to sexually harass her. It's not worth it at all.
I haven't had meat for a long time…
Combat Chimeras are truly formidable.
She could fight against me, even though I used my all effort.
That's interesting.
It is more reasonable to investigate the ruins on this planet.
There is a town appearing.
However, the mission has failed.
The mission…
I've completely forgotten about it.
Toris has joined hands with the Demon Army.
They are preparing for invasion.
I understand.
Are you trying to make me work for you?
You should pay a big price for that.
Have you forgotten that you are the culprit of the situation?
I've forgotten everything about that past.
That's astounding, Six.
That just happened last week.
I ask you to take responsibility for your failure to get water fruits.
I hate the word "responsibility".
You're indeed a scum.
Since we're lacking water, prolonging the war goes against us.
Therefore, I have an assignment for you.
This map's intended as your reward for completing the Toris assignment.
There are 2,000 soldiers of the Demon Army investigating the ruins.
Heine and Russell?
Yes, they want to kill the Sand King by the ancient weaponry.
I need you to stop the Demon Army from obtaining the ancient weaponry.
I just need to destroy them, right?
Hold on.
Why don't we…
seize the weapon?
I want to drink hot tea.
I also want tea, as well as food.
Do it yourself.
Defeating the heroes
is exhausting.
Six, tea…
(NEXT EPISODE KISARAGI LEADERS, WILL DELIVER!)
If Six were here,
even though he had fought in the Sahara Deserts for a month,
he would quickly make a cup of tea for me.
You treated him like that?
And you want us to run your errands?
Six is surprisingly nice.
What did he write in his report?
Is he still fine?
I can't read anything at the moment.
Disappointed.
Let's take a rest first.
Agreed.
Aren't you forgetting something?
We will have a party after we wake up, right?