It's unfair to always leave me alone.
I also want to explore the ruins.
We're not going there for fun.
The Toris kingdom and Demon Army are both attacking us,
so we have to split our forces.
The enemies are intruding here and here,
And the knights will deal with the Toris Imperial Army,
while you tackle the Demon Army.
Are you serious?
Even if Tiger Man is a kaijin,
it's unreasonable to send him to face an army alone, isn't it?
You seem to want to declare, "Lolicons must die!"
That's exactly what I think.
However, I believe you're able to do that.
Look at this map.
Aren't you the King of the Jungle, Tiger Man?
What's this?
So, the ambush spot is in the jungle.
In this case, I can beat them up at ease.
That's amazing, Tiger Man.
Even your disgusting voice sounds cool.
I'm flattered.
When the knights and Tiger Man fight against the enemies,
we'll head to Toris again.
If we succeed in stealing the ancient weapon,
we can threaten them to negotiate with us.
We're an evil organization.
Let's capitalize on them and take all the benefits.
Yeah!
Episode 11 How to Make an Evil Leader Cry
There's a war coming soon,
and you want to go to Toris now?
It's the right time to go there.
At the moment,
there are only the Demon Army's executives at the ruins.
Captain, why did you do that to the prince?
Sometimes, I think you're an idiot.
You're the same. Though you look innocent,
sometimes you are mean.
And you even want to eat me.
What are you talking about?
No matter how hungry I am, I won't eat you.
What?
We even had a fight.
Did you forget that night?
My debts…
Six.
Someone has been crying all this time.
It's annoying, do something about it.
Captain, what happened that night?
-I need money.
-I'm asking you, Captain.
-I need to pay my debts!
-What on earth happened that night?
-It's just a pay cut.
-Are you listening to me?
-What can we do?
-What did we do?
Look at me,
-I spent all my salary on the first week.
-Tell me what happened.
-Nonetheless, I am still enjoying my life.
-Captain…
-Life is not all about money.
-Captain!
That's because I give you an allowance, right?
You accept an allowance from a child?
As an adult, don't you feel ashamed?
I'm comforting you.
How can you criticize me?
Annoying.
Snow,
If you help finish this mission, I will give you an allowance as well.
If we can obtain the ancient weapon in the ruins,
I will give you a bonus worth three months of your salary.
Alice!
We're going to infiltrate the ruins where the Demon Army's executives are.
Don't be reckless like before.
I understand, Alice.
I will definitely be useful.
You are the most pitiful person I've ever seen.
Shut up.
How can you criticize me while you also receive allowance from Alice?
Money is the most important thing.
As long as it's about money, I can even sacrifice
my colleagues, friends, and even parents whom I've never met.
I'm sorry to interrupt your shameless declaration,
but please stop calling me so intimately.
Should we invite her to join the Kisaragi Corporation?
I think she has the genes of a villain.
I don't think so.
She's more of a despicable subordinate like you.
With the bonus, I can have my second frost sword.
She tends to easily succumb to temptation.
That's true.
But I'm different.
I have a good rest.
Be quiet, you idiot.
It seems like we cannot take this ancient civilization lightly.
Six, the ancient weapon may be a big surprise.
Maybe it will go out of control and attack us?
I know that
because I've watched a lot of animations that have the same results.
Yes, it might even explode automatically.
Since they are still camping here,
it means we have reached on time.
I'm exhausted.
As hard as much we fight, the enemies seem to be endless.
There're also countless traps.
But there are only inches from our goal.
I think we will reach it tomorrow.
Russell, have a rest first.
You've used a lot of mana, right?
Don't worry, I'm still energetic.
We combat chimeras have endless mana.
As long as I've plenty of food, I can fight all day long.
Well.
For the fight tomorrow, fill your stomach and take a good rest tonight.
Can you stop treating me like a child?
It seems that they are exhausted from exploring the ruins.
Yes, what should we do now?
Captain,
if we want to sneak into the ruins, we must act faster.
If possible, I advise to complete our investigation at night.
Otherwise, you won't be able to see
the contribution of my power.
I don't remember what contribution your power has made recently.
What did you say?
You can remind me of that.
Hold it!
I am Grimm, the archbishop!
You always count on me in a pinch!
Calm down, Grimm.
They certainly don't expect us to arrive at Toris that quickly.
I totally agree.
That's right.
Therefore, I want to propose an underhand tactic.
Underhand tactic!
Their vigilance must be relaxed now.
So, we shouldn't investigate the ruins first.
Instead, we sneak in…
Kill them…
Don't mimic her.
Snow, aren't you a knight of justice?
That's right.
Are you corrupted by Captain?
What else can we do?
Two Demon Army executives are we faced with.
Six, Alice,
You should understand me, shouldn't you?
Are you looking down on me?
Kisaragi Corporation's combatants will never use such underhand tactics.
What?
I agree, Six.
That's how a Kisaragi Corporation combat agent should act.
Wait a minute.
I'm just following your lead.
She said she's following our lead.
How can she look down on us?
That's right.
Six, let's make it clear to her.
We are going to rest here tonight.
Tomorrow, we are going to tail them.
We will leave all the traps and guards to them.
When they are exhausted after reaching the end,
we will launch our attack.
Rather than conducting a raid tonight,
why don't we let them clear the way for us?
Good point.
Six, you are making a good example.
Different from the outside, the scene here is like a science fiction.
It seems that there is a huge gap between the planet's civilizations.
It should be a well-developed, ancient civilization.
After all,
they could create an amazing creature like that girl.
Rose, what's wrong?
Nothing, I…
The ruins I had visited before should be a different one,
but this place looks quite familiar.
Interesting.
Let's catch up to them first.
Snow, what are you doing?
This is a relic from an ancient ruin.
It should be valuable.
-But we are on a mission now.
-Can we leave her alone?
But I've told her,
-I will award her a bonus if we succeed.
-Alright.
These are robots, right?
They've fallen into disrepair over the years.
But you're right.
I guess they are used for security.
Wait for me, Six.
If I bring these back, I can…
Hey, let's go.
We have to catch up to Heine.
You can come back later.
Alice, you should come and…
This is interesting.
What are the power source for…
Listen up to me!
I felt as if I had played with these children before…
Heine, they're coming again.
This a new type of guard.
These are endless.
Leave it to me.
I will incinerate them with my flame.
I am tired of camping.
I can't wait to get back to the Demon City.
For a combat chimera like me,
I feel at home here.
But I understand your feeling.
You're a demon used to the modern city.
Don't be cocky.
They are so intimate.
Let's go.
Is it a trap?
Russell, are you alright?
Are you hurt?
Thanks to your protection, I'm fine.
You yourself are hurt?
Don't move. Let me heal it.
You have no need to do that. I'm a tough chimera.
I will be troubled if you get hurt.
It is the wish of all demons to destroy the Sand King.
And the only one capable of defeating it
is you.
Heine.
I see.
I won't die before I complete the mission.
I won't let you die even if you complete it.
After all, you're still a child.
It's my responsibility as an adult to protect children.
You treat me like a child again.
Alright, just wait.
I will also protect you when you're in danger.
Okay, I'm waiting.
Hey, I'm serious about it.
They are totally unaware of our presence.
Grimm,
Grimm, are you drowsy?
What's the matter, Captain?
Even if there is no sunlight here,
it doesn't mean that I cannot be sleepy.
Hey.
Are you able to put a curse on them secretly?
If we can restrict their power by your curse,
it must be much easier for us to handle them.
Good idea.
However, the curse could only be effective when I say it loudly.
Captain, I can't bear to fight with them now.
They are working so hard…
It's not the right time to feel sorry for your enemies.
It's about a war that determines the fate of the country.
Failure is absolutely not allowed.
But…
Bonus.
I'm a knight.
Since it's about my country, I have to fight.
Rose, get a hold of yourself.
I will give you tons of tasty food once we get back.
Captain, don't think I'm willing to do anything for food.
Except for this time.
These people are hopeless.
CHIMERA FRIEND?
Here is the end, Heine.
The place where our target is.
Is this your secret weapon against the Sand King?
It's impressive.
Yep.
This was originally intended to annihilate those monkeys from the earth.
We can use it to eliminate the Sand King,
as well as those irritating humans.
You are talking about it again.
Are humans so annoying?
Yes.
This is the wish of my creator.
Heine, don't you hate them as well?
I heard that you were tortured by them.
That's the nature of war.
If you keep those painful experiences in mind…
No,
I hate them.
I must kill that man.
I see.
Are you talking about that man you met in Toris?
If I catch him, I will leave him to you.
Thanks a lot.
However, if we activate it,
the war will be over.
Alright, Russell. I can't wait anymore.
Do you need my help?
No, just stay there.
It seems to be in operation.
Now…
Here I am…
Russell, Demon Army executive,
has been defeated!
Russell!
Hey, put your hands on the air.
Why are you here?
Unfortunately, this ancient ruin is now ours.
If you resist,
don't blame me for harming him.
You're so…
Wait a minute.
Are you following us here?
And take away the fruit of our efforts?
You are right.
We walked idly while you cleared the path for us.
How shameless you are!
We have gone through days of efforts to get here.
Despicable man!
Even as a man, you have conscience, don't you?
Indeed, but we are from an evil organization.
That's not the point, Miss Heine.
Who do you refer to
when you said you must kill him?
It's not you.
Six.
What? I'm busy now…
He stops breathing.
-Russell!
-Really?
It's a fatal attack.
-You're amazing, Six.
-Russell!
Russell!
Did I kill a kid?
Alice, can you save him?
I can try by injecting him with a stimulant.
If it doesn't work, just give up.
Good morning.
What happened?
I almost killed you by accidence.
However, since we won,
we are kind enough to treat you.
So it's you who attacked me.
How could he say that?
It's him who frantically tried to save him, isn't it?
He even declared himself as the winner.
Even Zenarith will be shocked.
You saved me because you want to steal the ancient weapon, right?
Correct.
Don't think that I care about your life.
I know it's strange to hear it from a demon's mouth.
but aren't you ashamed of your behaviour?
Cut the crap. Activate it now.
Then, teach us how to control it.
Snow, I think I've become a villain.
Don't say that to me.
This is for the country.
Yes, it's for the country.
Snow, say it while looking into my eyes.
It's simple to activate it.
Actually, anyone who is related to this facility can control it.
You are obedient.
Six, what was that?
Darn it.
It seems it's too late to stop it.
Six, destroy it.
Halt!
If you make any move, this woman's life will be in danger.
What's wrong?
My companions are avoiding me as well.
Russell, can you handle the situation alone?
No problem, I can easily defeat them.
You can send my words to the Demon City now.
This scene…
Tell them that I'm going to eliminate the Sand King and all humans.
Listen, Six.
We're even this time.
Next time we meet…
I won't let you…
Darn it, I didn't stop her.
Well done, Six.
You've obtained a treasure.
That bastard, Six.
At least let me finish my words.
What's wrong?
No!
Villainy points added.
You…
Retreat!
Stop! You monkeys who humiliated Heine.
I will crush you.
You're so noisy.
Do you want Heine's undergarment?
You rascal!
I'll leave it to you.
Here you go!
Idiot!
We are not like that…
You!
Captain, what should we do now?
He is much more powerful than us…
But how does he get out here?
There's no room for that giant to leave.
The ancient people are not stupid.
They should have made an entrance for it.
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, since he is going to chase after us,
let's prolong the time here.
That's right.
That giant does not have a supply line.
I don't think it can operate indefinitely.
Here you are. I've been awaiting for a long time.
Go back!
The ruins are not strong enough to withstand my attacks.
You can't rely on it to escape from me.
Wait for me to crush all of you
like insects!
FINAL EPISODE
PLEASE STAY TUNED