We're just one step away from world dominance.
We have gone through the massive rebellion led by the heroes
Cheers
KISARAGI CORPORATION APPRECIATION DINNER
Isn't this too careless?
After all, everyone has survived the intense battle.
It's normal for them to want to slack off.
It's a reward only for tonight.
I understand as well,
but we are slacking off at the moment,
while Six is working hard on the other side.
You're so rigid like usual.
Relax for a moment.
Look.
If all of us executives work endlessly,
how are you going to persuade our subordinates to rest?
Fine,
we rest for tonight.
Yes, now you should enjoy as well.
Ho…hold it.
Let's get rid of these clothes and swim!
First of all, let's race for 1,000 meters.
We are all women, so there's no need to feel embarrassed.
Unless you want to swim naked?
Wait… Don't say such stupid things.
Villainy points added.
Episode 10 Kisaragi Leaders Will Be Livestreamed!
I'm back.
I've placed that weird mummy girl on the altar,
she will probably revive on the next day.
Good job.
Once Grimm revives, we will head toward the Toris Ruins
Before we do that, remember to make preparations.
Yes, before that, I should make some complaints to Astaroth.
Did you do something wrong again?
It's not us but them, Tiger Man.
It's their fault for prohibiting us from loaning villainy points.
I almost died in the desert.
Six, about this…
You have mail!
It's from Lilith.
To all Kisaragi Corporation employees,
Don't miss the arrival of this special livestream.
That's all.
Lilith is doing something silly again, right?
It's Belial.
-You can identify her just like that?
-It's my victory.
It's a close win.
It's nice to have a swim sometimes.
-It's true, right? Let's compete once more.
-Six
-No, let's compete 10 more times.
-We can't turn the camera angle.
Hey, we're going to fight the executives of the Demon Army tomorrow,
and you're having a night pool party now? Are you looking down on me?
HOT! IDEAL BOSS POLL
Everyone seems to be exhilarated down there.
It must be the company's routine poll.
Aren't they bored with it yet?
Yeah…
I've no idea who started this silly project.
I remembered that it was Six who started it.
Lilith?
Here, this is for you.
Thank you.
In the past, Six caught the heart of a mantis woman and an arachnid woman.
Both of them forced Six to decide on them.
That guy is really popular among weird women.
That's right.
Then Six said,
"You're both so charming that I can't make up my mind."
That's right, he is always hesitant.
Tha…That's right.
Then, he suddenly put forward with a popularity contest,
and involved everyone in it.
Well, it ended up being a tie,
and the mantis woman and arachnid woman got along with each other
Now, they are a very powerful pair.
That guy looked as if he don't care
but in reality, he was surprisingly aware of his surroundings.
Is that right?
Did that guy really think that much?
Damn. They are having fun all by themselves on Earth.
What's with the temperature difference between here and Earth?
So, that's what she's trying to do.
I understand what Lilith is planning to do.
She gather all the audiences and then…
You must subscribe to the channel before you can continue watching.
it will become this.
No way, Lilith…
Damn, I can only subscribe now.
And there are a bunch of these silly men.
Lilith is very smart.
Subscribe.
What's this?
Is she really thinking about giving fanservice?
If that's true, I will be very upset.
I would rather watch a zashiki-warashi kaijin give fanservice.
Do you want to bet who's going to be number one?
I'll pass.
I've already decided not to gamble.
Obviously, I will bet on myself.
You're always at the last place every year.
Are you really you're going to do it?
Are you so sure you will win?
Have you forgotten who I am?
That's right. I'm the head genius scientist in the Kisaragi Corporation.
Black Lilith.
Did she bribe the combatants?
Lilith is such a big spender, how can she afford to bribe anyone?
I bet she threatens them.
I hear what you're saying.
If nothing goes wrong, you'll win as you're popular with the combatants.
Look, the early results are…
I feel embarrassed when you say that.
You're very considerate to the combatants as well.
Anyone who noticed will know.
I…I've also issued a lot of strict orders,
and I'm not interested in the poll.
I'm very interested though.
After all, everyone is working hard for us.
Although, half of them are just voting for fun,
I'm still very curious if my subordinates trust me at all.
Well, yes.
If you put it this way, this project has its uses too.
Here, have another one.
Th…Thank you.
Even if you don't say so, you're very concerned about who Six voted for.
Th…That's not true at all.
I'm not…
Damn.
Useless Lilith actually did something good this time.
Is this live stream synchronized with our world?
She is the senior member of the organization, but she can't act at will.
If this matter gets exposed, I wonder what will happen to Lilith.
I am already looking forward to it.
There's no one around us, so you don't have to hide it.
That's right.
We have already seen through it.
You should be frank about it.
Of course, I do care about who he voted for.
But, I can't hold back that feeling.
From the time he attended the interview, he is a big idiot.
But he continuously calls out my name while following me,
supporting me all the way.
Even though his salary is meager, he never complains about it.
I think that he has lots of complaints about it.
He won't disobey even when I send him on dangerous missions.
He was upset that he was sent to that planet, wasn't he?
Yes, he complains about it and acts reluctantly.
Sorry, I'm blind to that.
But does that matter?
We've known each other since the founding of the Kisaragi Corporation.
So I naturally hold some feelings about him.
That's great.
Take this opportunity to let out all your inner voice.
Wait…
Hold on for a second, Astaroth.
Please save your words until you and Six are alone…
Why do you say that all of a sudden?
Here comes the climax. Don't spoil it!
However, I can't be distracted with Six.
We're just a tiny step away from world domination.
When we succeed, I will fire all the…
Stop! You can't say that!
I'm the supreme leader of the Kisaragi Corporation,
Freezing Astaroth.
In order to protect the jobs of 5 million combatants
and their future.
This is…
Villainy points added.
ZASHIKI-WARASHI KAIJIN
LIVESTREAM ENDED.
Lilith,
quickly think how to comfort Astaroth.
Aren't you a self-proclaimed genius?
The word "self-proclaimed" is so harsh…
It can't be helped.
The reason why Astaroth becomes like this,
is because Six had heard all her embarrassing confessions.
If that's the case, then we only need him to say something nice to her.
Combat Agent Six.
You've heard what we said just now.
Now, say something to Astaroth.
Peek.
I've recorded the livestream.
I will watch it once everyday.
-No! -Villainy points added.
You idiot!
What should we do? What are we going to do?
Do…Don't panic!
Look at the results of the poll.
Let's check the ranking on the Ideal Boss poll.
That's right.
Just now, Astaroth was talking halfway about
protecting the jobs of 5 million combatants
and their future.
Th…That's right.
Perhaps it's because she is drunk,
that she is able to make such an embarrassing statement.
Don't say it. I beg you don't say it.
Villainy points added.
What are you saying?
Alright, come up now.
Astaroth, let me tell you something.
After your speech,
there will definitely be more combatants who vote for you.
You will certainly become number one.
I would rather give up on being number one,
than to go through such embarrassment.
Alright,
let's go and have a look.
BLACK LILITH FREEZING
ASTAROTH FLAMING BELIAL
Lilith has gained the lead.
Lilith.
You shouldn't use violence because of your defeat.
You sounded so confident when you bet with me just now.
And you remain the number one now, so I'm certain you're chea…
You're ruining our relationship by suspecting me without any evidence.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for showing you something undesirable, Six.
Actually, I also think that Lilith is chea…
It's impossible that I'm cheating.
Do you really think you can get away with this?
Now, longlasting competition among us has finally come to an end.
Alright, Belial. Stop dawdling.
Get me, the great winner, some cola.
What's wrong?
Lilith's votes…
have exceeded the overall numbers of combatants.
What?
You little…
It, as I thought, was hacked.
I've already punished the culprit.
Please deduct the votes Lilith added.
Forget it. I don't care about the ranking at all.
This is fine too.
Ideal boss ranking.
Whenever we start this useless project,
I will remember the first time we met.
To be honest, every time this event starts,
I will vote for Astaroth…
I beg you
I will treat you to a meal next time.
Look, what do you think?
Thank you.
Alright, give you another one.
I've done a lot of things behind the scene.
I've already said I don't care about being number one,
but you kept on doing these by yourself.
You're so stubborn.
Are you upset by it?
No.
Actually, I am somewhat happy.
I didn't expect to become number one.
Thank you.
No, I didn't do anything this time.
But I feel happy when you said that.
What's the matter, Six?
Well…
Lilith has become number one again.
Stop being so obnoxious.
Wa…Wait. It's an accident.
What are you saying?
I'm a genius.
Actually, I've a second plan.
I have to say first that it's not cheating this time.
However,
the number of votes has exceeded the total amount of combatants.
So this does not count as cheating?
I've recruited more combatants
just for this poll.
7 days break per week, monthly salary of 500,000yen
hired without interview,
Their job is simply to write "Black Lilith"
on the ballot paper for the Ideal Boss poll.
This is how I recruit all these people easily.
I've always thought about this.
You're definitely denser than Six and me.
We're already thinking about retrenching.
How are you going to pay the salary of all these people?
We can just produce bad debts.
We're an evil organization.
We can deal with these little things by producing bad debts.
How can disposable employees like combatants
have high salary?
That's enough about it.
You've proclaimed yourselves as an evil organization,
but in the end, you're just too good for your own good.
But I don't hate you.
Seriously,
I will be considerate and withdraw this time.
No, even if you try to flatter us,
you won't get away with this.
You still want to escape
even after you created such a big mess?
Alright, I understand.
How about deducting it from my salary for this month?
That is far from enough!
But I don't have any choice.
I'm a standard bishoujo.
I don't have a seductive body like yours.
As a standard bishoujo, I can never be like you,
wearing seductive clothes to earn votes.
Hold it.
Alright.
It's all my fault.
As a member of an evil organization, what's wrong for doing something evil?
Villainy points added.
I can't believe Lilith has gotten number one.
Did you vote for her?
That's impossible. I'm not a lolicon.
Dismiss the combatants Lilith hired with Kisaragi Corporation coupons.
Lilith will bear all the costs.
Tell them that it's a mistake in the adverts.
Delete all the videos uploaded on NicoTube as well.
The poll…
The result means nothing to me.
But I still want to ask a question.
What's the matter?
I understand your character very well,
and I don't think I still need to ask you about it.
But just in case…
I want to hear it from you directly.
That is…
Who did you vote for?
Who did I vote for?
Of course, that's…
Hero Alert!
A lot of heroes are detected near the location of the appreciation dinner!
All combatants and kaijins! Prepare for battle!
Curses. Why am I always interrupted at a crucial moment?
The timing of this attack is too good.
Our appreciation dinner is supposed to be top secret.
How did they know?
Isn't it because of Lilith livestreaming the event to the whole world?
Come on, obnoxious heroes.
I will subjugate all of you.
Let's have a talk after all of this.
What's the matter?
Executives, the type of attackers is dreadful.
There's a lot of locust type heroes.
Take a hold on yourself.
Lilith.
You said you will subjugate the heroes, right?
Combat Agent Six.
After this battle ends,
I will ask you who you voted for again.
Astaroth, you've just raised a death flag.
Curses. How can I be afraid of locust type heroes?
My kaijins are much stronger.
I've made a lot of mistakes tonight.
I will redeem myself by defeating all the heroes.
You'd better remember what you've said.
Alright, everyone!
The appreciation dinner is over!
It's now a victory celebration for defeating the heroes!
It's quite troublesome on your side as well.
Attention.
I will announce now to all personnels in the planet invasion team.
From this moment on,
we will prove that the Kisaragi Corporation is the strongest organization.
Therefore,
you're not allowed to be defeated by the Demon Army.
Astaroth
THE BATTLE HAD STARTED
PLEASE CONTACT US VIA EMAIL
The way she ends it is good,
but since she doesn't want me to lose, at least lend me some points.
I have to move out tomorrow morning.
They are busy with fighting heroes.
You should give up that thought for tonight.
Given that you are in trouble, why don't you turn to Alice?
You can count on my intelligence.
I've already thought of a tactic to defeat the Demon Army.
Really?
You're great, Alice.
You're indeed very smart.
That's because I have good functionality.
We have to wake up early tomorrow. Go to sleep now.
Alright, I'm going now. Good night.
NEXT EPISODE
HOW TO MAKE AN EVIL SUBORDINATE CRY
I didn't expect that there is a tactic.
PLEASE STAY TUNED
It's Alice after all.
After all, I'm the one who suggest not to lend any points to Six.
If we lend him some points,
I'm afraid he will never be able to return to Earth.
I will apply for a loan if we face an emergency
and have him indebted to me.
I…
I didn't hear anything.