Y'know, the scientific name for
gorillas is gorilla gorilla!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! So what
about virtual gorillas?
They don't need one, you horsey bastard!
Hey, hey!
Wow, look at all the books.
Oh, Hamlet.
"To be or not to be? That is the question."
What brought all that on?
It's a famous line written by Shakespeare.
You see it come up online a lot nowadays.
Oh, I know him!
"Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?"
That guy, right?
Right! He's an incredibly
famous poet and playwright.
Siroet! Can I bring you
home with me tonight?
Okey-dokey!
There's no time for this, everyone!
We must get ready for the opening!
Wh-What did you say?!
It's nearly time for the title call!
Uh... we know.
I'm...  uh, no, I am ready as well!
Let us sally forth, then,
unto the title call!
Ready and...
Virtual-san is...
Looking!
Yeah!
What the heck?
Virtual-san is looking!
Everyone, we've been slacking off lately!
At this rate, we'll never be
able to conquer the galaxy!
Which is why I've been thinking...
I want to hear Kaede-chan's plan!
To destroy the planets of every Vtuber,
we need to infiltrate them!
So this is what I've come up with...
We need to master mimicry,
so we can impersonate other people!
I see! We make others
think we're someone else,
and once their guard is down, defeat them!
Excellent idea, chief!
I'm not that good at impressions, though.
Ryo-kun is the one who is!
I'm not that good at it, either.
Mirai Akari-chan!
Hello! Mirai Akari here!
Nekomiya Hinata-chan.
Yahoo guys, how you doing?
Nekomiya Hinata here.
Tanaka Hime-chan!
Hao! I'm Tanaka Hime! Yay!
Peanuts-kun.
This is really solid ground.
Ryo-kun, you're incredible!
You can infiltrate enemy
territory on your own, Ryo!
What about the rest of you?
You seem like you might have a few, Haruto.
I don't really...
A certain person who says
this is a one-way street!
Can I help you with something, Kihara-kun?
Someone hard to notice that plays basketball!
I'm a shadow.
Not bad, Harutrash!
Now it's my turn!
It's that person who barfs people up!
So many mini-pink idiots! What even is this?!
Miria-chan, that's less an impersonation
and more of a shocking trick!
Not to mention useless when
it comes to infiltrating!
Okay, I'm going to go last with something
I think might be good for infiltrating.
It's a housewife who gets caught
shoplifting on reality TV!
Why would that help!?
Well, I wasn't planning on shoplifting,
but before I knew it, it was in of my purse.
Can you just let me go? I'll pay for it.
I told you, I wasn't shoplifting!
Hey, I think the chief might have
taken too well to her role!
Miria-chan, you can stop throwing up!
Please, just don't tell
my husband about this!
The Game Club's galactic conquest continues!
Virtual Grandmother!
"Uogokoro areba mizugokoro."
Grandma
Today's Phrase:
Uogokoro Areba
Mizugokoro
That's the phrase.
It refers to how being shown good will
can encourage someone to do the same.
I thought I'd talk a bit about Valentine's Day
and White Day this week.
Valentine's Day started becoming a fixture
in Japan in the latter half of the 1970s.
And White Day in the first half of the 1980s.
The specifics about the dates weren't
really commonly known at the time,
so it took them a while to
actually take a hold, culturally.
There are all kinds of interesting
chocolates out there now, aren't there?
You know, like glasses or bats!
Like, chocolate bats...
I think it'd be wonderful if this program
was a chance to be immortalized
in chocolate myself.
A life-sized chocolate Kobayashi Sachiko!
We'll call it...
Godivava.
Grandma
Everyone's
Virtual-san
Pen Name: Lost Alien Akuhato
We want to see your characters!
Check out the Virtualsan - Looking
official website for details!
My homeland, the Ugarid Nebula,
was destroyed by invaders,
and I have come to Earth as a refugee,
the Alien Akuhato.
Everyone's
Virtual-san
Virtual-san is looking! Yeah!
Hello, everybody!
You keeping it virtual out there?
Because it's time for Virtual Radio!
We've got another great virtual
song to introduce today!
This one...
...is a cute and pop magical number,
where the "Hello! Hello!" calls are so catchy,
they'll leave you with a spring in your step!
It's a super pop and sexy
virtual cutie cool song!
Let's throw it on now! This is
Mirai Akari's "Mirai to Mirai."
"Mirai to Mirai"
By: Mirai Akari
That's a nice virtual song!
That was "Mirai to Mirai" by Mirai Akari.
See you next time! Keep it V!
Virtual-san is looking.
Hello.
There!
There! There! There!
Hello... Hello... Hello... Hello...
Huh? G-Gori-chan?
Hello!
I can't reach that far!
Fuji Aoi!
Fuji Aoi Park
Hello.
Big trouble, big trouble!
Big trouble, Akari-chan!
Akari-chan, there's big trouble!
What is it, Hime?
Akari-san, we've got ever such big trouble!
Well, what's going on?
Someone with the pen name "Ochabba-kun"
is in trouble! They've got problems!
Hurry, take it! Read it, read it now!
Okay, fork it over, come on!
"Hello, Akari-san." Hello!
H'lo.
"I loaned my friend a
video game a while ago,
and it's now been three months
with no sign of them returning it."
"Do you think they intend on keeping it?"
"They might have just forgotten about it,
so I have trouble bringing up, because I
don't want them to think I'm accusing them."
Problem: A loaned game isn't being returned
This is an awkward one!
True enough...
Did he swipe it?
But three months is a weird
amount of time, y'know?
Yeah, three months!
I mean, the game might
take that long to finish!
True, if it's a longer one!
Right, right!
And you're friends, so it's hard
to really come down hard on it.
Right, totally!
What to do?
This is a hard one!
Huh?
Mirai-san?
Mirai-san!
Hikari
Yami
The best thing is to wait patiently.
I mean, there are other games to play!
You need to dox people like this.
Get some proof they swiped
your game and let 'er rip!
But they're friends! Could you please not?
Well, you take it from here, Akari.
Hello?
Hello! Mirai-san!
Sorry! I'm back!
Welcome home.
Not sure what that was about.
Must be rough!
Well, pen name Ochabba-kun,
I'm gonna get to the bottom line.
Is this it?!
She's going to show her bottom! Line?
You need to have your friend
become a Let's Player!
Let's Plays?!
Right!
You set things up for them,
so that they can become
a famous Let's Player!
Their handle can be "1BRO."
1BRO? But they're not brothers!
What the heck? What the
heck's that about, then?
Then how about "Ninja"?
Ninja?! That's one lonely ninja!
Then, after they're famous,
you set things up so that their stream is
going to show their LINE window instead!
Then you capture an image of
a LINE message where you say,
"Ever since you swiped that game a year ago,
and my heart and body have been aching!"
and stick it on the stream.
Okay, I'm gonna go check out ○Bro's videos!
Make sure you watch the TLOU one, Tanaka!
"Hey everyone, good morneveningafternoon!"
Big Trouble!
Akari-chan
Hinata-chan Heads to
School
There!
This is bad.
If falling onto the road to
school would be a game over,
and I needed to get from
one side to the other,
maybe the first thing is to
hook onto the stone wall,
then the overhang to get onto
the roof of that building,
and then try a big jump, which should
just barely let me catch the edge.
I think that'd work.
But maybe the safer way is to
just jump from the stone wall.
What a choice.
But y'know, if I can catch
onto the wall on the right,
the rest of the way should be simple!
Well, I wonder, maybe...
I might break some sort
of speedrunning record!
Yeah, it doesn't work that
way in reality, I guess.
Guess I'll head to school.
Hinata-chan Heads to
School
Virtual-san is looking!
And so is Siro!
Trivia
Diner
Oh, it's Kaede-chan and Miria-chan! Welcome!
We are so fed up!
Can we get some trivia about baths, please?
Sure, coming right up!
Trivia, go!
Baths, huh?
"Baths"
You know about putting a towel on your head
when you're soaking in hot water, right?
Well, it turns out it's not just a
tradition about where to put your towel,
but that there's a scientific
basis for doing it!
By putting a wet towel on your
head after gently wringing it out,
the water evaporating from
it will cool your head off!
It helps prevent the kind of dizziness you can
get from soaking in hot water for too long!
By the way, in the Edo period,
there were bathhouses on boats,
which is why another word for bathtub is
"yubune," with the "bune" meaning "boat."
Wow, really?
Your trivia really is
always handy, Siro-chan!
Everyone's
Virtual-san
Pen Name: Domeki Akira
We want to see your characters!
Check out the Virtualsan - Looking
official website for details!
It's nice to meet you, everyone.
My name is Domeki Akira.
Now, I know my name might
mean "hundred-eyed demon,"
but I'm not a youkai,
so there are no eyes on my arm.
Everyone's
Virtual-san
It's 3 PM,
Class President.
When I think about the order
of guests I've had so far,
today's will probably be that 280-year-old.
Mito-Mito-chan!
Hey, an elf!
How mean!
You know it's me, the high-minded elven
beauty from the land of elves, Elu!
Could you give me your legal name, then?
Snow White Paradise El Santo
Flow Wasurena Pure Pri...
Sorry, my fault for asking.
Well, today we're doing the ultimate "would
you rather" committee with Elu-san!
Here's the subject. Which
superpower would you rather have?
A) The power to read people's minds.
B) The power to see the future.
Elu-chan, you're not human in the
first place, so I imagine you
might have some kind of superpower, do you?
Okay, first, discriminate much?
What do you mean?
But y'know, I'd like a power that'd let me
know if my forest was going to burn down.
That's oddly specific.
But which of these options would you prefer?
I guess if I had to pick one,
I'd pick the ability to see the future.
But if you could do that,
you might know if you're
going to die in five minutes,
or that the elf forest is going
to be burned down, right?
But I'd be able to choose my last words,
and make sure I've taken care of business...
Things you wanted to get done?
What specifically would that be?
Huh... I'm not sure.
Maybe eat my favorite food?
Well, one thing would be changing my
LINE name to "Thank you for everything."
That is super morbid!
Okay, it's time.
Today's answer is A, the ability
to read people's minds!
We didn't talk about that at all, though!
If you control people's minds,
you'll never have to worry about a bad future!
Live in the present!
It's 3 PM,
Class President.
Special Announcement
The Sudden Appearance of a City
Overflowing with crowds
Giant Growth
Transformation
The secrets of the opening are about to be revealed!?
Coming Soon!!
Virtual-san is looking!
Unity-chan Wants to
Roll Around
Unity-chan!
Boom!
Ootori Kohaku here!
I'm really athletic, y'know!
My dream is to become
an action star some day!
Here I come!
Secret technique,
Curry Crou-ken!
I'm sorry! I overdid it!
Everyone's
Virtual-san
We want to see your characters!
Check out the Virtualsan - Looking
official website for details!
Pen Name: Akumano Maga
I'm Akumano Maga.
Did you know that demons
don't really have genders?
Maybe I'm what you all call...
An otokonoko. Maybe!
Previously on Kerin Slayer.
Gorillaga!
Gorilla!
Hello!
Want to grab some banana shakes?
Kerin Slayer.
So, what are we here for this time, Hime?
Well, you remember that
dark elf from last time?
And when he mentioned the legendary,
beautiful god elf known throughout the land!
Elu-san?
Yeah!
And this is forest that Elu-san revived by
releasing all of her aura
through an oath and a vow!
Look, Hime!
More Keblins!
Fine, then!
Expecchan Patrol!
That's some crazy magic you've got, again!
Look, Hime, there's another one!
Personal Home Security Patrol!
That's just another way of describing a NEET!
I messed up! And now the Keblins are here!
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Th-That voice...
Yamikumo Kerin!
Yami
Yamikumo
Ke
Keri
Kerin
You guys are here again?
Well, you're not getting away this time.
N-Now hang on, Kerin, you've
got the wrong idea!
The Keblins started attacking us!
Hina, we've got no choice!
After all, we're Kerin Slayers!
It's our job to exterminate dark elves!
Suits me fine.
I'm gonna blow you both up!
It's the ultimate super
maximum magic, Buchitema!
Get out of Elu-san's forest, you two!
We'll have to use our
ultimate combo attack, then!
Let's go, Hina!
I get what you mean, Hime!
In the name of the Girly Girl Empire!
This hand of mine is burning pink!
Its loud roar tells us to grasp success!
Erupting Sekiha Hao Ken!
Blast 'em!
Hao!
Hold it right there!
That voice... could it be?!
Sister!
Can you hear me out, Sister?
What is it, dear horse?
There's this girl I want to tell how I—
Listen, Sister!
What is it?
I think I've put on weight by
snacking at night too much!
Oh man, what am I gonna do?!
You've lost to the sweet temptation
of late night snacks, I see.
Yeah! The more I try to resist, the better
it tastes when I finally eat something!
Let me suggest a snack that should
fulfill that sensation while also
limiting how guilty you feel.
Really?!
It's made from a type of
algae so it's full of
minerals and nutrients:
agar jelly with anmitsu syrup.
It's got a lot of dietary fiber to
suppress carbohydrate absorption,
which should also help relieve your hunger.
I get it!
I'm gonna get my fill of
agar jelly starting today!
May you be virtually blessed.
Jiggly agar jelly!
Sister!
Why, why?! Virtual-san is looking!
Well, we've got a letter here.
It's from pen name "Urban Riemann."
Thanks for writing!
"I'm getting tired of being an officer worker
and thinking about a change in careers."
"What kind of occupation
should I pursue next?"
"By the way, my hobbies are gourmet dining,
reading, and walking."
So he writes, and he's
talking about jobs, right?
Do you all have any kind
of jobs that you like
that show up in anime or manga?
Me, me! Vampire!
Favorite jobs from
anime and manga
Papaya?
Sounds tasty!
No!
I mean, I like papaya.
I said vampire!
Vampires!
Oh, right!
I wanna be, like...
Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh!
A ninja!
I wanna be zipping and zapping all over!
Then I'm gonna be king of the pirates.
Sounds good!
I think I'd like to be a mage.
Mito-mito, you give me more
of a sage vibe than a mage.
I suppose that'd work, too.
I think Akari-chan would make a good
gadabout, since her costume is so cute...
For real?
What's a gadabout do, anyway?
Well, they have really high luck stats.
Luck shats?
Shats?
No!
Akari-chan...
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
You're so bad, Akari-san.
I thought she was talking
about high level shats!
I did, too!
I think I'd be a white wizard.
That's perfect!
I'd wanna get healed by you!
I think I'd want to be a gambler,
something that's kind of cool!
We've got a millionaire!
Suzuki plays hard! You know?
So what kind of job should Urban Riemann,
who sent in the letter, get?
What kind of job should
Urban Riemann get?
His hobbies are gourmet dining,
reading, and walking.
Dining, reading, and walking?
Is there a job where you eat?
Sounds good to me!
Like a professional speed eater?
Oh, I love those contests!
But what if he loses weight doing it?
He could be a big eater who's skinny?
Would that be a good fit for TV?
Maybe?
For walking, he could walk
around while eating.
But that's a recipe for
smacking into something.
Smackeroonie!
Say that again, Tanaka?
Sma... don't wanna.
Don't try and make me say that sorta thing!
She caught on... well done.
Well, that's it for this
week, so until next week...
Virtual-san is looking!
Weatheroid Type A Airi (Ponko)
Good evening everybody!
I'm Type A Airi, the weatheroid!
I warned everybody about the cold
weather coming up the other day
and ended up catching a cold myself!
It's still possible, even
when you're an android!
My nose won't stop dripping oil!
Are any of you feeling under the weather?
When you're feeling sick in virtual town,
it's called restarting.
So next time you're feeling bad,
try restarting, and hang in there!
Next time, it's "PP Dance Festival."
Next Time
"PP Dance Festival"
Virtual-san will be looking next week, too!