I'm gonna be joining you in
the intro today, all right?
Sure, sure thing! That'll be 5,000
yen for your participation fee!
You mean I don't get an appearance fee,
you horsey bastard?!
Sure don't!
Okay, girls, gather around!
Fiberoptic
Virtual
Student
Dorm
Coming!
Hey, Hinata?
What, Akari... chan?
You've been half-asleep all day today!
Hinata-san, you need to get up!
Sleepy...
Aw, she went back to sleep. What do we do?
It's cute, but...
Tweet us at
#virtualsan
Hinata-chan! Enemies! You're under fire!
Huh?! Enemies!
Nice, Siro-chan!
Hurry up, it's already time!
Quickly, everyone, gather around!
Okay, okay, coming!
Okay, here we go!
Ready and...
Virtual-san is looking!
I seriously thought we were dead last week.
Really! Let's save our ability to turn into
titans as a secret weapon for the Game Club.
Even if it was momentary,
for you to be able to instill the fear of
death into us... Very impressive, Chief.
Come on, guys, stop praising me!
It's not praise, Kaede-chan.
More importantly, Chief,
this week I've come up with a plan.
Let's hear it!
It is called...
The Super Shadow Clone Technique, believe it!
Super Shadow Clone Technique
Haru-kun, I think a certain ninja
might get mad at us over that.
Ryo! I've finally managed to
concoct a legendary chemical mix.
By drinking it, shockingly,
you will be able to create clones!
Amazing! And that'll give us more firepower?
Shadoclon-C
Precisely!
Should we find the need, we can create
multiple clones of the titan-sized Chief,
which will let us conquer any planet!
And this drink will do that?
You pink fool! How dare you?!
Harutrash, this tastes funny.
My body feels really hot...
You okay, Miria-chan?
It's me, Miria!
What?!
Miria-chan's the cutest in the world!
So many Miria-chans! Cute!
Miria Super Shadow Clone Technique!
Look at all the Miria-chans!
It's me, Miria!
It's me, Miria.
Uh, Haru-kun, what are
we gonna do about this?
That pink fool! Such a nuisance!
Wow, it's like I'm surrounded
by Clefairies and Jigglypuffs!
Now really isn't the time, Chief!
It's me, Miria!
Don't take this personally, you pink fool.
Ryo! Chief! Get your masks ready!
It's time to turn this pink
horde into space debris!
It's me, Miria...
We're saved... but Miria-chan just...
Miria-chan is so cute!
Miria-chan?!
That must be the original pink fool!
By some miracle, she remained
on the space ship.
I think I'm the third.
The Game Club's galactic conquest continues!
Virtual Grandmother!
Nisshin Geppo.
It's a phrase that describes the steady,
ongoing, daily, monthly march of progress.
Grandma
Humanity's science has evolved
steadily with the passing of time.
Can any of you imagine
life without a smartphone?
Grandma
Nisshin
Geppo
There was a time where regular
contact with someone outside
of the home wasn't as easy as it is now.
One particular way this was difficult
was when it came to meetings.
Without an accurate time and
location for meeting someone,
it was easy to miss them.
When you did, in the old days,
you'd then have to call
that person's home and leave
a message with their family.
And then in the same fashion,
the other person would
have to call home and ask, "Did I
get a call from So-and-So?" to check.
Thinking back on it now, it was
a huge pain in the butt, yes.
Oh, one second.
Grandma
Hello? Mikawa Ken-chan?
Nisshin
Geppo
Sorry.
This dog won't shut up.
Sorry about that!
Oh, the other day was so much fun...
Grandma
Nisshin
Geppo
Virtual-san is looking.
Bang!
I thought we were finished!
It's such a relief that we survived!
It really was...
This segment is called
Let's Go! To Class
I'm so hungry.
Hinata-chan, didn't you eat breakfast?
Breakfast? Come to think of it, no.
You really ought to, for health reasons!
But you're so busy in the morning,
it's hard to find the time.
I can't wait until lunch. This sucks...
What?! What is it!? What the—?!
That scared me!
Where did that shaking come from?
Hey, am I the only one who's really cold?
You're right! It suddenly got cold!
Could it be... Hey, is this...?
The North Pole?!
Wh-Why are we at the North Pole?!
H-Hey, look! That must be the North Wind!
It's got a face?!
The wind is so cold! I'm freezing!
Too cold! Close the window!
I'd love to, but the window is gone!
M-Mouth n-numb... t-too
c-c-cold to t-t-talk...
We're going to freeze to death at this rate!
I-I know, if we want to forget about this
cold, we should start by eating something!
Is now really the time?
Well, y'know, when you've had something
to eat, you've got more energy, right?
Just imagine it!
Yourself, on a full stomach...
I get it! We're trying to trick our brains!
Okay, everybody, imagine you're
eating your favorite thing!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Too cold!
Cyber shaved ice! Served hot!
That's just... water!
Come on, think of something hotter!
Steaming hot oden!
That just reminds me of a certain
trio and their reactions!
Not the point! Isn't there
anything else to warm us up?
Oh, I know!
Ra...
Ra?
Oh, ramen?
You mean ramen, right, Akari-chan?
Akari-chan? Didn't you mean ramen?
I'm right, aren't I?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Akari's spiritual pressure is gone.
Everyone's frozen!
Don't leave me behind!
I can't enjoy life without
the rest of you, you jerks!
To Be Continued
Virtual-san is looking!
I'm gonna get serious now. Eyes open.
Y'know what, Gori-chan? I started
doing yoga the other day.
That sounds lovely.
You should try it out, too!
Start by breathing through your nose.
Like that.
Right, right, just like that.
Yoga.
Huh? Gori-chan?
Gori-chan when did you—?
Yoga.
Again?
Amazing! You can teleport, Gori-chan?
Yoga.
Sonic Banana.
Hello, hello, hello...
Fuji Aoi!
Fuji Aoi Park
Hello.
Big trouble, big trouble!
Big trouble, Akari-chan!
Akari-chan, there's big trouble!
What is it, Hime?!
Mirai-san! We've got really big trouble!
What, what is it?!
Someone with the pen name
"Miho-chan" is in trouble!
Here, read it!
Okay.
"Hello, Mirai-san." Hello there!
"My best friend and I like the same guy."
"She suddenly opened up to me about it on
the way home from school the other day."
"I was so shocked! Instead of telling her
I liked him too, I ended up cheering her on!"
You can do it!
"What should I do?"
Oh, what to do?!
Problem: Liking the Same Person as Your Best Friend
That's totally nutso!
Sounds like trouble.
I think the problem is Miho-chan made it
sound like she's rooting for her friend.
But she's not ready to give
up on the person she likes!
Yeah, that sounds like it.
Huh? Hey! Mirai-san?
Mirai-san! Mirai-san—?!
Hikari
Yami
Seriously, just jump into
bed with this dude you like.
Hey! Could you please stop trying to
take that approach with everything?
But it's the fastest way.
I think the best thing would be
to talk it over, as friends!
Just be honest and...
God, you're annoying.
You handle it, then, Akari. Seeya.
Wait a second!
You can do it, Akari!
Hello? Hello?! Mirai-san!
Sorry, I was thinking too hard there!
Good morning.
Well, pen name Miho-chan,
I'm gonna get to the bottom line.
Is this it?! She's going
to show her bottom! Line?
First, you wait until P.E., and then
swipe your best friend's phone!
You swipe her phone?!
Yep! Then, you hit up the guy you like
on LINE from your friend's phone!
W-With what?
You send him a stamp with a
coin swinging back and forth!
Are you...
"You are falling more and
more in love with Miho-chan."
Then you send him a stamp
with the voice that says that!
It's digital hypnotism!
Three... two... one...
Sorry, I like Miho-chan
And there you go!
Wow, awesome!
But wait, if it's gonna have voice,
it needs to be an authorized stamp.
So Miho-chan needs to contact the
LINE developers and get permission!
You can do it, Miho-chan!
(With your application!)
All right, I'm gonna head
over to the LINE people!
Take care of it, then! See you next time!
All right! All right, then...
Big Trouble!
Akari-chan
Hinata-chan Heads to
School
I need some items! Gotta find them!
This is bad.
The game's already halfway over,
but all I have is the 4x scope.
I'm gonna want the 8x scope if
I intend to survive to the end.
The most likely spots for it
are big apartment buildings,
the military base,
and the hospital.
But when I factor in the safety zone...
Right! The hospital, then!
Time to head out and grab that 8x scope!
Pick it up...
Nope, can't do it.
It's way too much of a drag to
move like this in real life.
Better head to school.
Hinata-chan Heads to
School
Hao! Virtual-san is looking!
Trivia
Diner
Oh, it's Mirai Akari-chan! Welcome!
I am so fed up!
Can I get some trivia about Mount Fuji?
Sure, coming right up!
Trivia, go!
Mount Fuji...
Do you guys know the altitude of it's summit?
Everyone thinks it's 3,776 meters, right?
Well, that might be what it says on the
books, but it's not actually the case!
In the records from 120 years ago,
it was 3,778 meters, but then
with each subsequent survey...
It went to 3,776 meters, to
3,775 meters, to 3,774.9 meters!
It's shrinking a little
bit every time they check!
Trivia
Diner
It seems the truth is that nobody
really knows how tall Mount Fuji is!
And when you're hiking on Mount Fuji,
the drinks you get from the ninth
vending machine on the trail cost 500 yen.
Your trivia really is
always handy, Siro-chan!
Everyone's
Virtual-san
We want to see your characters!
Check out the Virtualsan - Looking
official website for details!
Pen Name: Akeura Uru
I'm Akeura Uru, the virtual ghost.
I'll always be here,
so I'd love it if you came by to see me.
Well,
bye-bye.
Everyone's
Virtual-san
It's 3 PM,
Class President.
I need to hurry before she
lights anything on fire!
Kaede-chan!
Where's the elf forest I've gotta burn down?!
Nowhere near here, Kaede-chan,
so don't light anything on fire!
Oh, dang, guess I was almost an arsonist.
I'm glad I made it in time...
Today, you're joining me for the ultimate
decision committee, Kaede-chan.
Right.
Here's today's subject.
If you could only have one,
which would you like?
A) A reset button that would
let you redo your mistakes.
B) The mentality of a streamer
who can laugh off their mistakes.
Uh, A seems kinda OP?
You think so?
Yeah, I mean, you can have do-overs, right?
Then if you had a reset button,
what would you like to redo?
Well, one time a bird pooped on me,
and I went to school without noticing.
Wait, where was it on you?
My shoulder.
Your shoulder?
Yeah!
Oh, it's a black uniform, too,
so I bet it stood out.
Yeah, I thought, "Something
reeks!" the whole time.
That sucks.
Y'know, Mito-chan, you've got that black hair,
so if any fell on you it'd be super obvious.
If it fell on my head?
So are you saying that since you've got
white hair, Kaede-chan, nobody would notice,
so we might as well cover you in it now?
Nope!
Just cake it on there, everywhere...
That'd get me banned.
When would you have used it, Mito-chan?
Well, I was trying to come across as
a refined student council president,
and since then I've been called a girl who
can do anything other than be refined.
So I'd like to go back to my early
days and try harder not to slip up.
What do you think?
Eh, I wouldn't bother.
Why not?!
Oh, it's 3 PM now.
So the answer is B, the mentality of a
streamer who can laugh off their mistakes.
But I liked A better.
Shut up!
As a Vtuber, your glory only awaits
at the end of a long, haggard road!
It's 3 PM,
Class President.
Unity-chan Wants to
Roll Around
Unity-chan!
25 Second
Introduction
Challenge
N-Nice to meet you!
I'm Otori Kohaku, and I'm 17 years old!
Everyone calls me Unity-chan!
As for why...
I wonder why?
Oh, right, I love curry croquettes!
I'm actually a little upset
I don't have any right now.
We have some curry croquettes for you.
Really?! Thank you!
I love curry croquettes!
The taste of curry with the crunchiness
of a croquette, and it's all so warm—
And cut!
Wait, we're done?
Virtual-san is looking!
Everyone's
Virtual-san
Pen Name: Kazekiriha P
We want to see your characters!
Check out the Virtualsan - Looking
official website for details!
Pen Name: Cherry Land Employee
Pen Name: Seren
Pen Name: Himari
Pen Name: En
Pen Name: Kuroyan-chan
Pen Name: Origami-san
Kerin Slayer.
Hey, Hime, are there really dark
elves in a cave like this?
One of the villagers said he
saw one leaving this cave.
Did you ask Villager B, too?
B was walking into a wall,
so I left him alone.
Well, it'd be dangerous if
they were so close to a town.
Right, so we have to do something about it!
Hime, wait!
There it is!
It's a Keblin!
Dummy! It noticed us!
This is bad!
This is really bad!
Ninnomono!
That was amazing, Hina-chan!
How'd you manage that?!
It kinda felt like it'd work out!
Look, there's another one!
Okay...
Nin! Nin!
You suck!
The Keblins are coming!
Help!
Let go! Quit trying to take Hime's pants off!
What are you all doing?!
Th-That voice...
Kerin!
What do you think you're doing to my Keblins?
We're Kerin Slayers!
We're here to take you down!
Bring it on, then!
Time to blow it all up!
This is bad!
It's the extra-special heavy-duty
mega magic, Blowemway!
You should've never stepped foot into Gunma.
Hina, get back!
Hime, don't!
I don't care if this is the end.
So please, with everything I have...
Hina, come on!
Haoken!
Blast 'em!
Hold it right there.
Who are you?
Sister!
This week, Sister, I hope you'll hear me out.
What is it, dear horse?
There's a girl I really want to confess—
Listen, Sister!
What is it?
I cheated on my calligraphy submission,
and it won!
Now I feel super guilty!
What should I do?
The best thing to do to avoid any unfortunate
outcomes is to simply stay quiet about it.
Wait, I should stay quiet?
If you were honest about it, it'd upset your
teacher and the other students, wouldn't it?
True.
The best thing is to practice
your penmanship in preparation
for the next time you need
to put it on display.
Great idea, Sister!
I'll head home and practice now!
May you be virtually blessed.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Sister!
Sister!
Virtual-san is looking! Elu elu!
Okay, we've got a letter here!
From pen name "Robasuke-san"!
Thanks for writing!
Thank you!
"Watching all of your videos
always helps me feel better."
"So, I have a question for you:
what do you do to feel better?"
And that's what he wants to know!
I see...
Good question.
Subject:
What Makes You Feel Better?
So what is it, everybody?
I like... Where's Waldo? books.
Seriously?!
Akari Feels Better by
Reading Where's Waldo?
It doesn't get on your nerves?!
I look for Waldo, and then I go to bed.
I get how it helps you clear your mind.
I think if I couldn't find him,
he'd show up in my dreams!
What about the rest of you?
Lately, I've developed the habit
of going to karaoke by myself.
Class Rep Feels Better
with Solo Karaoke
Sounds nice!
Sing the stress away!
That's right.
When I sing in a group, I get so embarrassed
that I do it while sitting down.
I can't bring myself to stand.
Is it really so different?
Oh, but of course it is!
Isn't standing while singing embarrassing?
I get you! I totally, totally get you!
I dance like crazy, though.
Impressive.
That's what I'd expect...
So do you keep singing if one of the
people who works there comes in?
I sit right down.
I turn and point the mic at them!
That's amazing!
Kinda like, "Sing along!"
After I order my drinks, I don't
start singing until they bring them.
I totally get you!
I'm too embarrassed.
You just take the covers off the microphones.
I know the feeling!
Just peel the vinyl off!
And then just play with
the screen you log on.
I see, I see...
What were we talking about?
Healing, we were talking about healing!
We weren't discussing common karaoke habits.
Karaoke habits!
I like to sharpen knives.
Shiro Feels Better
After Sharpening
Knives
Because I like to cook,
so something about sharpening a
knife really helps me calm down.
Wow...
That's terrifying!
I'm serious! Try it out.
What about the rest of you?
Like, an activity you do to relax.
What about you, Hinata?
Oh, come think of it... what is it?
It's not like Siro-chan's, but... sounds?
Like, environmental sounds.
And maybe battlefield sounds.
Like, "Crack!" and, "Boom!"
The sounds of echoing gunfire.
Environmental sounds...
What kind of environment is that?!
Hina Feels Better with
Environmental Sounds
Oh, wait a second.
Hina-chan, what about you?
What makes you feel better?
Quit trying to get out of it!
Was that what I was doing?
I wonder... maybe petting animals?
So cute!
They're warm, after all! There's
something soothing about that!
True enough.
Wanting to feel human warmth...
Well some people want to feel cat warmth!
Cat warmth!
You're not gonna go, "I'm not a cat!"?
I'm not a cat!
Thank you very much!
And so, the best top of feeling better is...
Well, what is it?
It is, "Feeling better with animals!"
Best top of Feeling Better
Is with Animals
Makes sense.
Are we sure about that?
You just can't say no to animals!
They're fluffy and cute!
Wait, what about Waldo?
Waldo, huh?
You've got specific tastes.
I mean, Waldo's an animal, too!
He is?!
What kind of animal?
A homo sapien, I think.
I thought he was a prisoner.
Well, with that, that
wraps it up for this week!
So, until next week...
Virtual-san is looking!
How you guys doing? It's me,
Fukuyamaster, the Vtuber.
Fukuyamaster
I wanna ask, what do you do when you're
alone and can't sleep at night?
It's best to count sheep when
you've got a bit of insomnia.
One sheep... Two sheep...
Three sheep, four sheep...
Well? Feeling sleepy yet?
But it's not bed time!
Next time, it's
"Gorilla Rampages, Normies Explode."
Next Time:
"Gorilla Rampages, Normies Explode"
Virtual-san will still be looking next week.