So, Kyouno...
What're you planning to do?
Umm... I don't know?
Unbelievable. It's your last summer of high school.
Most students have their whole career already planned out by now.
You, on the other hand, haven't even decided whether you want to go to college or get a job.
When you put it that way... I guess you're right.
You guess? You know...
This is your future we're talking about.
I know.
In fact, I've been giving it a lot of thought.
Yeah, right. You're not fooling anybody.
Uh-oh...
Well...
After that performance you gave us, I can't hold it against you if you feel a little burnt out.
Oh, not at all.
The Jersey Club is always in tip-top shape!
People usually retire from their club in their senior year.
Once a Kamo Girls' Jersey Club member, always a Jersey Club member!
One, two, three!
Two, two, three!
Three, two, three!
Career plans, eh...
ano koro watashitachi wa (tobenai puropera de)
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't carry us
sora no mou hanbun miage (hadashi de hashitteta yo ne)
We ran with bare feet with our eyes fixed on the other side of the sky
watashitachi wa itsudemo
We always live
kanchigai da to ka
in a world full of conviction
jishin de ikiteru
and misunderstandings
daiji na takaramono ne
I wish I could store these
shimaeru you ni kokoro
precious feelings in my heart
kitto mienaku natteru yo
I'll get over it
guru guru mawase
Spin the wheel of fate
kono mahou no tsue de
With this magic staff,
namida to sunny day mazerun da
I'll blend tears and sunny days
samishigariyasan
Oh, lonely girl
yume wa kanau yo
I'm sure your dream will come true
itsu datte issho da yo watashitachi
and we will be together forever
Welcome Back to Kamogawa!
Are you ready, milady?
Yes.
We will now initiate the third Vox Particle Control Experiment.
Stage One.
Connecting the Nerve Cutter to the Consciousness Strata.
Stage Two. Activating Mind Probe.
Penetrating straight into the Fourth Layer of the Consciousness Strata.
Bio-telepathic wave pulse is in sync.
Biometrics pattern, range beta to theta, is orange.
What is the concentration of Vox particles?
It's stalling at around 200.
Still far from the breaking point.
Let us move on to Stage Three.
Commencing Stage Three.
Mind probe now penetrating the Sixth Layer, into the Ego Borderline Stratum.
The cell structure in her Consciousness Bubble is becoming unstable.
Any further stimulus may cause irremediable damage to her psyche.
Pull the probe back to the Fifth Layer...
No, keep going.
King Dizelmine?
This could inflict severe damage to Lady Lan's subconscious...
We don't have enough data yet.
As you wish, your highness.
Control, report.
It's an enemy attack!
Armed forces from De Metrio are approaching!
The enemy crafts have activated their weapons systems.
They are attacking!
Lympha, standing by for takeoff.
Lan, we are abandoning this station.
Brother?!
We are ready for takeoff.
Jam enemy com systems and deploy!
This facility is useless to us now that Villagiulio has discovered it.
I understand.
In that case, I will cover your escape.
Dizelmine!
Thank you for your patience!
Here's your Oraga Bowl lunch special!
Please enjoy!
Madoka, I can handle the rest.
Can you go help out the guys at the seaside cafe?
It's gonna get busy there soon.
Sure thing, Uncle.
On my way.
I better start thinking about what's really best for her future.
Seaside Branch
Welcome.
What a hottie...
Izo!
BWH lunches: slightly better than the competition!
Here are your Offshore lunch specials. Thank you for waiting!
Array, you're so cute!
Did you notice the customers over on the deck?
Yeah, they're from Le Garite.
Just leave 'em alone.
It's not so uncommon to see them around these days.
You guys seem pretty busy.
Kyouno!
My uncle asked me to give you guys a hand.
You're very welcome to, Kyouno!
The guys come around when you're here.
Array only attracts the strange ones.
We've got a few who come all the way from Tokyo to see him.
I don't choose the customers.
Everyone is welcome.
You know, you three are really starting to embrace your roles.
Someone's drowning!
Oh no!
I'm coming!
She's okay now.
Success!
Madoka!
Madoka, you're on the ball, as always.
One never retires from the Jersey Club.
More like the School Swimsuit Club.
Either way, it's pretty unusual.
Unusual?
Anyway, I still can't get over the fact that your uncle opened up a beach cafe.
There was some talk about it a while ago.
But until last year, it would've been impossible with just my uncle and myself to run the business.
He should stick to easy dishes like curry and ramen noodles here.
My uncle takes pride in his cooking.
Did things change this year then?
Yup. He found an awesome part-time chef.
You mean Izocchi? But he's an alien.
Not the sort of skill you'd expect from him.
We decided to let those three run the place,
and it worked out great.
Well, Kirikiri and Array aren't bad looking...
It's not Kirikiri. It's Kirius!
Whatever.
A lot of students from our school have become regulars.
Take a look.
Damn it, this isn't a host club.
Is it any wonder this place is popular?
All three are from outer space.
Does that even matter?
Of course.
I mean, it's sort of romantic.
I dunno, they don't come across as the romantic type to me.
Besides, more and more people from Le Garite have been coming over.
That's the real reason for your last-minute college change, isn't it?
Oh really?
You've always wanted to study astronomy, right?
Now, I'm interested in diplomacy.
Diplomacy?
Yes. From now on, we'll be dealing with people from Earth, Le Garite and more.
So I thought that if I became a diplomat,
I'd be able to visit all kinds of planets.
Wow... That sounds pretty awesome.
It's still just a dream, though.
Compared to that, my career plan is pretty down-to-earth.
You're planning to find a job in Tokyo, right?
No no...
I'm eyeing the Kamogawa Fisheries Cooperative now.
Fisheries Cooperative?
You're going to use Koujirou's personal connections?
That too.
But this place is perfect for surfing.
Plus, Kamogawa's become the center of the world lately.
It's gathering more interest than Tokyo at the moment.
Madoka...
Will Lan and Muginami ever return to Kamogawa?
I guess that wasn't the best choice of topic, huh.
They're both busy.
I bet they'll show up out of the blue, one day.
You're right.
It hasn't even been a year. I'm sure they'll come back.
I wonder if Lan's learned how to swim?
t
Hey, Muginami!
Hey, Lan!
I wonder if they're doing okay...
No, no! I have lots to do tomorrow.
Time for bed!
All sections, confirm anchor stabilization,
then turn in your checklists to the bridge.
Jim, please report to HQ that we have reached Kamogawa.
Roger.
We will hold an Intergalactic Conference on Pharos.
It will take place in Kamogawa!
I want you to head there immediately.
So we're back here again...
Morning! Let's make this another great day, guys!
What's wrong?
Pharos?
They must've arrived late last night.
So you didn't know about this, Kyouno?
No, I didn't.
What about you? Did Asteria not tell you anything?
That girl has forgotten we even exist.
I wonder if something happened.
Maybe they're on summer vacation.
Madoka...
Lan?
Woof.
Lan!
Welcome back!
You're looking good. Did you grow out your hair?
My aide evens it out for me every day.
Spoken like a true princess!
You haven't changed at all, Madoka.
Actually, she wasn't quite herself until you came back.
It's been a long time, Mr. Hiroshi.
Is this for me?
Of course! Eat up.
Thank you.
Is it good?
Yes, delicious.
What's wrong?
Did you put wasabi in it, Uncle?
Huh? Why would I?
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
How is everyone in Kamogawa?
Huh?
Oh yeah, they're all fine.
And Youko?
She's in Madagascar.
Madagascar?
It's faint, but I'm getting Vox particle readings.
There's no mistaking it.
It's a fossilized Lagrange Flower.
I see... So she's there to investigate the Voxes.
What about you? Is your older brother doing well?
Yes.
Yeah? That's great!
We'll have to throw you a "welcome back" party!
Madoka...
Huh?
Will you hear me out?
Lan?
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Damn it! I can't hear them.
What are they talking about?
Why would Le Garite's princess come here, and why now?
Izo!
Vox Lympha?!
Let's go!
I'd like to order please.
Water please!
Right away!
Damn it! If only Kirius and Izo would hurry and get back here!
I wish I could say it's good to have you and Kyouno back on board...
...but barging in unannounced in your
Vox was a surprise to say the least.
I'm here by special ordnance from King Dizelmine of Le Garite.
This is an unofficial visit, but one of utmost importance.
Then you came fully aware that Pharos was heading to Kamogawa.
Lan...?
Madoka, please pilot Aura one more time.
Huh?
But...
Aura shut itself down after its last battle.
You know this very well.
Yes, I understand. But...
Our need is dire!
Lan...
In order to maintain our military power, we tried to reboot Aura.
We conducted many tests with Madoka's help,
but they've all been unsuccessful.
Well, even if they had worked, there was nothing for me to do.
You're wrong!
Lan?
The connection you shared with Vox Aura runs deep.
It's a bond that cannot be easily broken!
You think so?
I know she'll move if you get in, Madoka.
I already tried several times.
But if you say so, I'll try it again.
So what do I do... comrade?
Comrade...
Tadokoro speaking.
What?
We have a lot of guests today.
The unidentified craft will soon enter our air defense identification zone.
Does it belong to the Le Garite?
We made an inquiry, but the reply we received did not match any of Le Garite's.
Order all ships to Defcon 2 status.
The unidentified craft is quickly approaching.
No!
Could this be...?
What's going on? Snap out of it and report!
P-Pardon me!
According to our IFF systems,
the unidentified craft is Vox Ignis. It's Muginami!
Muginami?!
Lan, Muginami has returned too!
She's running interference again...
Wait, Lan!
Hey, Lan!
What's going on?!
Lan...?
Don't worry. I will protect you, Madoka.
Huh?
That girl...
Muginami is planning to kill you.
Let's go, Orca.
Muginami is... planning to what?
Orca...
So Lan is here, after all.
Muginami!
So you intend to have Madoka pilot the Vox no matter what?
Fine!
I'll destroy you first, Lan!
Lord Villagiulio, Muginami has left the main force and has headed for Earth onboard Vox Ignis.
What?
I believe she intends to go after Kyouno Madoka by herself.
Oh, brother...
I guess she's not cut out for De Metrio's regular army after all.
What shall we do, sir?
She chose to carry out the dirty work in my name.
What do you want me to do?
Have her court-martialed and executed?
But we can't just ignore her...
Let her be.
Otherwise, we'd be no different from Dizelmine.
Tell everyone that Muginami went to Earth under my orders.
Yes, sir.
My goodness...
They're way too gentle. Each and every one of them.
Move! Please, Midori!
Lympha, Ignis... Still engaged in battle.
Lan... Muginami...
I don't get it. Why?
Why are you two fighting?
This is crazy!
Midori...
We've rested more than enough, don't you think?
It's time to get up.
It's already a new semester!
Time to wake up,
sleepyhead!
Owww!
Midori!
Aura has activated!
What?!
Don't you dare start a fight without me!
jaajibu damashii jaajibu damashii
The Jersey Club spirit! The Jersey Club spirit!
hottokenai hello and let's genki damashii
I won't leave you alone, hello and let's be cheery!
tadashii ka dou ka wa ato de
Who cares what's correct right now
mazu tonikaku koudou
First things first
me no mae ni nayami oku seijun
I just saw a glimpse of your innocence
kakaeru kimi wo mitsuketa yo isshun
as you deal with a billion issues
damatte misugosenai shuusei
I won't just leave you be, I'll fix you up!
utsumuki kagen senaka chousei hora
I'll adjust that hunching back of yours
tonikaku sesuji jibun nobashite mite
Just stand up straight on your own
tsukareteru ne
You look tired
hai, kamogawa enajii
Here, have some Kamogawa Energy
daijoubu
It's all right
zenbu nonda tte ii yo
It's good to drink it all
nihon nonda tte ii yo
It's good to drink two
atashi no bun nante ki ni shinaide
You don't have to save any for me
nande soko made shite kureru yo tte
You ask me why I do so much for you
kimatteru jan sonna no
Isn't that obvious?
kimi no yume ga mabushii kara
I do it because your dreams are wonderful!
jaajibu damashii jaajibu damashii
The Jersey Club spirit! The Jersey Club spirit!
suketto shitai hello and let's honki damashii
I want to help you, hello and let's get serious!
Hey, why are you two fighting? This isn't right!
Wait, I got it! Are you fighting over a Killer Whale plushie?
No.
You're not? Wait, I got it!
Is it over Muginami's flattering cape?
No!
It's not? What?!
Then what else is there that the two of you would be fighting over?
Oh wait, I got it!
That's not it, either!
Mayhem on Kamogawa Beach