[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: OP,方正粗圆_GBK,49,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hc88f8f8f,0,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,3,1,2,12,10,10,1
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,60,&H00ffffff,&H00ffffff,&H002f2f2f,&H002f2f2f,0,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,3,1,2,12,10,10,1
Style: SGS,华文琥珀,49,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hc88f8f8f,0,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,3,1,2,12,10,10,1
Style: Notes,方正粗圆_GBK,45,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hc88f8f8f,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,10,10,10,134
Style: Staff,方正准圆_GBK,50,&H00ffffff,&H00ffffff,&H002f2f2f,&H002f2f2f,0,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,3,1,2,12,10,10,1
Style: ED,方正粗圆_GBK,49,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&Hc88f8f8f,0,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,3,1,2,12,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------------------------Title & Staff
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------------------------OP & ED
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------------------------Dialogue
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.61,0:00:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}心描き出す地図上の未知なるフロンティア
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.61,0:00:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}心里描绘着 地图上的未知区域
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.47,0:00:30.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}扉開いたら道は続いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.47,0:00:30.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}敞开心扉 路途继续着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.32,0:00:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}埃巻き上げて 君の街へ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.32,0:00:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}喧扬起尘土 奔向你的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.24,0:00:43.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}空と大地が重なるルートで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.24,0:00:43.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}驰骋在天地的交界线上
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.99,0:00:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}走る南風に乗って
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.99,0:00:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}乘上飞驰的南风
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.78,0:00:50.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}蒼く染まる風を切って
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.78,0:00:50.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}穿越蔚蓝色的清风
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.69,0:00:56.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}心ごと駆けだしているんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.69,0:00:56.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}心情雀跃不已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.62,0:01:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}真昼の月を追い越して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.62,0:01:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}追逐正午的明月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.36,0:01:04.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}昨日とは違う世界へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.36,0:01:04.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}向着与昨日不同的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.36,0:01:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}どこまでも走り抜けてく あの風のように
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.36,0:01:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}就像风一样 无论何处都能到达
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.16,0:01:18.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}あの風のように
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.16,0:01:18.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}就像那风一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.85,0:01:19.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1100,620)\i(1)\c&HE8A344&}{\fs55}{\t(100,2300,\fs50)}S G S  曙 光 社
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.05,0:01:29.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻译&校对：香蕉皮  南风     润稿：LIHE333    时间：午夜时分    压制: λ-Driver    后期：小怡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.05,0:01:29.80,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\be1\an8\fs(45)}本字幕仅供交流试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版。\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，曙光字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.05,0:01:38.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复公告
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.95,0:01:41.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才北京府召开了记者会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.95,0:01:44.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提出 如果事件在6点前无任何解决迹象的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.85,0:01:48.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事态将向不可收拾的方向发展
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.35,0:01:54.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,针对这一发言 南XX XX民众联合的蒋总社长
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.35,0:01:57.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,申明此事与来历不明的AS的恐怖袭击…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.65,0:01:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.95,0:02:01.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的时限是早上6点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.05,0:02:03.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下只有90分钟时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.15,0:02:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失败了就玩完了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.75,0:02:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香港会成为火海
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.75,0:02:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光这样还不算完
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.65,0:02:15.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 脸蛋还这么漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.15,0:02:17.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对女人真甜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.55,0:02:21.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没找到玉芳吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.35,0:02:23.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备都齐全了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.35,0:02:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就看着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.35,0:02:33.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 姐姐 我是玉兰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.35,0:02:36.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在被一群可怕的男人包围了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.85,0:02:38.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.65,0:02:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.35,0:02:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 啊 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.85,0:02:43.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.15,0:02:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～姐姐救我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.35,0:02:51.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛 不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.55,0:03:00.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对于南北双方来说 都是不希望发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.65,0:03:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且对于Venom破坏事件的调查完全没收获
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.35,0:03:08.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是同一个犯人所为吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.05,0:03:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是到底是谁为了什么而让南北两军战斗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.35,0:03:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狩人社长 有客人…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.45,0:03:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是很急要见你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.75,0:03:25.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替我回绝掉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:26.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在什么时候 你也…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.95,0:03:27.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.95,0:03:29.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让开
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.05,0:03:30.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.95,0:03:32.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说让我见他!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.45,0:03:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿富汗人?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.25,0:03:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.35,0:03:40.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要说哪里有阿拉伯人居住的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.75,0:03:42.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.95,0:03:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是「卡修姆」吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.05,0:03:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个乳臭未干的小鬼头
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.25,0:03:56.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想玷污「巴达富夏之虎」的威名吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.05,0:03:57.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我管你这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.35,0:03:58.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有话就说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.35,0:04:05.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个中国女孩叫我把这个给你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.05,0:04:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿了就快点滚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.25,0:04:41.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狙击点有5个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.85,0:05:09.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是相良宗介是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.75,0:05:10.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.85,0:05:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公园的出口有出租车等你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.95,0:05:14.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐上去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.65,0:05:20.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁雇佣你的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.25,0:05:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和现在发生的事件有什么关系？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.15,0:05:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.85,0:05:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道了又怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.05,0:05:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相良宗介
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.15,0:05:51.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你背后大楼的2楼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.15,0:05:56.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人在最里面的房间等你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.75,0:05:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.25,0:06:01.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这里的地址牌你就知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.05,0:06:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九…龙…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.15,0:07:09.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 3个月不见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.35,0:07:12.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到你我真开心 卡修姆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.65,0:07:14.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九龙?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.15,0:07:17.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像很惊讶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.05,0:07:20.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我活着就这么不可思议吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.65,0:07:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…在那个时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.05,0:07:26.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该死了…是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.15,0:07:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记了可不好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.25,0:07:32.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的机体也是搭载有λ-Driver的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.45,0:07:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了那个即使自爆也可以保护驾驶员
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.55,0:07:40.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也把我伤成这个样子了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.45,0:07:45.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看我都绑成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.85,0:07:48.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用得着这么急吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.25,0:07:50.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的目的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.15,0:07:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啥 只是想和你聊聊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.15,0:07:55.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡说!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.35,0:07:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.75,0:08:02.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你所见
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.05,0:08:03.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的时间没多少了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.45,0:08:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才在这个城里到处搞破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.25,0:08:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想把那个白色AS和你引来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.05,0:08:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把给你的信息散步到城市各处
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.45,0:08:20.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去在阿富汗从事游击队中有名的战术家马吉德
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.85,0:08:23.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的外号是「巴达富夏之虎」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.45,0:08:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这个男人那里获得名字的暗杀者「卡修姆」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.85,0:08:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以巴达富夏的虎之子就是指你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.95,0:08:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈米达恩是你过去曾经开电器店的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.25,0:08:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要留言「去找尖沙嘴的哈米达恩」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.65,0:08:42.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就会去找塔阿富汗人开的电器店
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.15,0:08:47.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是全世界只有你才能看懂的留言啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.15,0:08:49.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.85,0:08:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你会带着一帮伙伴一起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.05,0:08:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么就你一个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.85,0:08:56.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是发生什么了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.95,0:08:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.85,0:09:03.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系也该差不多闹僵了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.35,0:09:03.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.55,0:09:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和Mithril
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.75,0:09:09.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那种自称正义使者的那种部队里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.15,0:09:11.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁都会感到压抑的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.35,0:09:15.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其像你这样的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.65,0:09:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.65,0:09:26.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说你背后的那个组织的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.75,0:09:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌啊 工作就这么重要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.95,0:09:34.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.65,0:09:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.05,0:09:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Amalgam
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.65,0:09:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是雇佣我的组织的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.85,0:09:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,组织的目的是最新武器的研发和实战测试
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.15,0:09:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此策划地域纠纷争
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.45,0:09:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各国的高层机关里都渗透着大量Amalgam的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.85,0:09:59.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是些制造冷战和维持军需的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.05,0:10:01.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论东方还是西方都很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.65,0:10:05.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次骚乱也和这个组织有关吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.85,0:10:07.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次倒是我自己策划的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.75,0:10:14.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在Amalgam因为找不到我们而心急如焚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.35,0:10:17.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Venom
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.75,0:10:19.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 玉芳 吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.95,0:10:21.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差不多要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.75,0:10:24.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 多谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.45,0:10:26.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.75,0:10:36.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过去曾抚养过玉兰和玉芳这对双胞胎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.55,0:10:39.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和你一样的小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.85,0:10:42.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在比狗还忠诚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.85,0:10:45.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次骚乱就是我命令她们去做的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.25,0:10:51.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是玉芳今天晚上会在和Mithril的战斗中死亡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.25,0:10:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则就会被Amalgam的执行部队杀死
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.35,0:10:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,执行部队
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.05,0:10:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是帮可怕的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.45,0:11:03.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指挥官又是个实力很强的疯子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.55,0:11:07.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭你的同伴的实力是打不过他们的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.55,0:11:10.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦遇上肯定会被全灭的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.15,0:11:12.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.25,0:11:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在上层区域
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.85,0:11:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.15,0:11:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去收拾小猫咪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.45,0:11:20.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是Amalgam吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.05,0:11:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个组织里有被称为Whisper的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.05,0:11:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,YES
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.25,0:11:27.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经成为主要成员之一了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.65,0:11:30.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有Whisper的话为什么还要抓千鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.95,0:11:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不需要了不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.75,0:11:34.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不完全啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.05,0:11:39.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Whisper所拥有的知识好像各自不同
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.55,0:11:44.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的可以解决像λ-Driver那样复杂的技术理论问题
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.05,0:11:48.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的只能解决潜水艇的技术问题
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.65,0:11:51.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 如果发现新的Whisper后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.95,0:11:55.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要确定他有哪方面的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.35,0:11:59.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半年前 对那个女孩进行的试验就是为了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.05,0:12:04.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果证明千鸟要就是Whisper
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.15,0:12:08.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.65,0:12:10.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Amalgam的据点在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.85,0:12:12.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,组织主要人员呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.65,0:12:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想说了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.55,0:12:19.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就很无聊了 还说这无关的主题…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.75,0:12:24.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 你以为我想活下去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.05,0:12:30.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.05,0:12:33.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求我?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.25,0:12:37.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…真的是那个「卡修姆」吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.25,0:12:37.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.45,0:12:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回想起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.45,0:12:42.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5年前我们第一次相遇的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.15,0:12:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么样的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.75,0:12:48.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候我还是佣兵的教官
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.65,0:12:51.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是和苏联战斗的游击队
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.75,0:12:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是伙伴但也不是敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.95,0:12:58.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在还记得很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.75,0:13:01.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候的你眼神非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.25,0:13:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不肯定也不否定生命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.95,0:13:08.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有烦恼 迷茫 痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.35,0:13:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就和圣人一般的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.25,0:13:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那应该被称为美丽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.05,0:13:17.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.35,0:13:21.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是和谐 没有任何矛盾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.25,0:13:26.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半年前和你再会的时候你还是有着那副美丽的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.55,0:13:30.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼中简直没有人类的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.15,0:13:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这样的你杀死真的不错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.95,0:13:36.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经是这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.45,0:13:38.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这些
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.15,0:13:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可 现在你这副脸是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.85,0:13:45.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Venom出现
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.35,0:13:47.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在上层区域
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.95,0:13:51.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给ARX-7装备紧急启动推进器
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.35,0:13:55.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配备近距离霰弹枪并在升降机上待机
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.15,0:13:57.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舰长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.45,0:14:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Arbalest的使用应该被禁止了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.55,0:14:02.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起码能成为诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.45,0:14:04.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微减轻点大家的危险
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.45,0:14:07.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…相良中士还没…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.55,0:14:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.45,0:14:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为相良中士放弃了任务
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.55,0:14:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指望那个AS和那个男人明显是错误的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.45,0:14:19.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非如此
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.15,0:14:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是学校里的社团活动
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.85,0:14:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 你现在准备对我说教吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.15,0:14:27.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.15,0:14:29.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯独这次我不能不说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.35,0:14:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太过重于私人感情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.95,0:14:34.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连上级部门的命令都歪曲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.95,0:14:36.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,组织和军纪该如何处理
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.35,0:14:42.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且对于一名放弃任务的士兵给以特别待遇更是不妥当的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.85,0:14:48.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的好 那么总是给这位士兵难以想像的重任的人是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.15,0:14:51.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.25,0:14:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.45,0:14:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是的吧 你说说看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.25,0:14:56.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6个月前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.45,0:14:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那个机场
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.75,0:15:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不顾自身安危 把珍贵的情报带回来的人是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.35,0:15:04.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4个月前在及其恶劣的环境下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.55,0:15:08.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对敌人 挺身而出并击毁敌人的人是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.65,0:15:10.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在阿富汗的深山里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.25,0:15:12.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在同伴接二连三被杀死的情况下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.65,0:15:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将被夺走的核弹头抢回来的人 是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.45,0:15:20.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3月前保护这艘潜艇的人 是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.15,0:15:22.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁 你说说看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.15,0:15:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相良中士
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.05,0:15:26.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.15,0:15:29.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使这样你也要指责他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.35,0:15:31.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认定他就是胆小鬼了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.25,0:15:33.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.95,0:15:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你希望的话 我承认
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.15,0:15:39.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢他
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.45,0:15:42.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这和私人感情无关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.25,0:15:44.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定还会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.75,0:15:47.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会丢下我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.85,0:15:49.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论现在如何糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.45,0:15:51.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定还会重新振作起来回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.25,0:15:55.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的本质是无法改变的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.95,0:15:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很坚强而且温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.95,0:16:00.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚强而且温柔…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.75,0:16:04.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舰长 你认为我会认同这…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.05,0:16:06.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.05,0:16:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怀疑的是我的判断
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.05,0:16:13.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理查德·马迪卡斯中校
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.45,0:16:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信我吗 还是不信任我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.15,0:16:19.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止作为舰长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.75,0:16:22.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守护这艘潜艇的我 泰蕾莎·塔斯特罗莎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.75,0:16:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 你选择吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.35,0:16:38.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变坚强了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.75,0:16:43.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命 长官
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.95,0:16:47.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给ARX-7装备紧急启动推进器
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.65,0:16:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配备近距离霰弹枪并在升降机上待机
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.55,0:16:55.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给ARX-7装备紧急启动推进器
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.45,0:16:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配备近距离霰弹枪并在升降机上待机
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.15,0:16:59.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.05,0:17:05.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 我希望大家都平安归来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.95,0:17:09.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无线电自己接通了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.65,0:17:12.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁故意让我们听到的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.15,0:17:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.15,0:17:18.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 泰蕾莎竟然会和副舰长吵起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.25,0:17:21.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说希望大家平安归来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.05,0:17:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家怎么想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.75,0:17:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然肯定是要这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.45,0:17:29.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让我们的公主伤心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.45,0:17:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都这样担心我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.55,0:17:33.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也只能老实的感动了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.15,0:17:35.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真符合她的风格啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.65,0:17:36.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,效果很好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.35,0:17:39.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终时间是0600
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.95,0:17:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是专业的话就不要辜负这份期望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.85,0:17:42.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会失误
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.25,0:17:44.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也不要失误
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.25,0:17:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就成万事俱备了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.95,0:17:47.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.85,0:17:48.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.55,0:18:21.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸色真难看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.25,0:18:24.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在烦恼吗 在犹豫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.55,0:18:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那圣人般的你去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.85,0:18:30.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太让我失望了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.35,0:18:32.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在心中充满了矛盾
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.45,0:18:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连被杀死的价值都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.75,0:18:34.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.15,0:18:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明和我是同类 现在却想做个普通人了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.35,0:18:41.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听了都想吐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.45,0:18:42.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都叫你闭嘴了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.65,0:18:44.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我就要说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.85,0:18:49.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mithril和那个学校的人把你变得无聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.55,0:18:53.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被那些屁一样的家伙束缚住 变得没劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.15,0:18:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才不是说你不冷静了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.65,0:18:59.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是因为他们的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.75,0:19:01.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓的人道主义啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.25,0:19:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再也见不到那个杀人圣者 卡修姆了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.85,0:19:08.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被他们欺负了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.75,0:19:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.85,0:19:12.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱者会寄生在强者身上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.85,0:19:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装着一副温柔可靠的同伴的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.95,0:19:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把强者的力量连骨头都一起榨干
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.45,0:19:21.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老实说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.95,0:19:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和软弱的家伙混一起开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.35,0:19:27.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.45,0:19:31.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问你和软弱的家伙混一起开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.55,0:19:33.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都叫你闭嘴了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.65,0:19:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连杀我的气魄都没了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.15,0:19:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就要挂了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.35,0:19:47.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在死之前要找人陪葬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.35,0:19:53.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我刚才命令玉芳把香港变成火海那样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.45,0:19:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外那个玉兰
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.45,0:20:02.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命令她去杀掉使你堕落的最大癌细胞了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.65,0:20:03.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,癌细胞?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.65,0:20:05.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人啊 卡修姆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.85,0:20:07.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没收到消息吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.25,0:20:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是收到点消息了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.85,0:20:14.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个可爱的制服被弄的一塌糊涂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.45,0:20:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过最后没有求饶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.65,0:20:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后的话就是「对不起」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.85,0:20:22.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是对谁说的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.75,0:20:24.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人感动流泪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.45,0:20:26.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.15,0:20:27.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.35,0:20:33.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来想让你在这里看她的照片 瞧瞧你绝望的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.05,0:20:35.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过先忍耐会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.85,0:20:40.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 卡修姆会受不了打击的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.75,0:20:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东京的女人…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.85,0:20:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经来不及了…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.25,0:20:50.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 太可怜了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.65,0:20:53.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小要明明是好女孩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.95,0:20:54.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九龙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.15,0:20:57.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就是我杀的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.35,0:20:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来把 恨我吧 恨我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.85,0:21:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡修姆
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.35,0:22:04.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}きっと君は今日の日も
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.35,0:22:04.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}你今天一定也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.40,0:22:10.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}真っ直ぐ明日を見てる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.40,0:22:10.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}直视着明天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.41,0:22:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}風が吹くあの丘に咲いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.41,0:22:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}仿佛在那微风吹过的山丘上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.12,0:22:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}向日葵のように
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.12,0:22:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}绽放的向日葵
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.66,0:22:31.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}どんなに遠く離れていても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.66,0:22:31.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}即使相离再遥远
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.72,0:22:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}この歌声が君に届くように
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.72,0:22:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}也要把这歌声传递给你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.67,0:22:43.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}涙がずっと止まらない夜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.67,0:22:43.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}在这满脸泪痕的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.70,0:22:49.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}君の窓を照らす月になりたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.70,0:22:49.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}希望成为照亮你窗前的月光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.04,0:23:03.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}また必ず会えると そう思うから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.04,0:23:03.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}一定会再相见的 我这么相信着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.95,0:23:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九龙…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.05,0:23:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这个宿敌看穿了我的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.55,0:23:23.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶魔在向我招手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.95,0:23:25.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被精心算计的最终诅咒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.65,0:23:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回 最终话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.45,0:23:29.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「继续的日子」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.55,0:23:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能击溃绝望的只有那猛烈的一击
