Starting this moment, we will
start our attack on them!
We will resurrect Shion and others!
Great Rimuru.
Mnn?
I believe we should decide on a password
to confirm whether you still have you
sanity after becoming a Demon Lord.
Password?
Yes. For example...
"Shion's cooking is shit."
I will ask your opinion on Shion's cooking,
and you should answer "It's shit."
What kind of password is that?!
Shion would hate it!
That is why.
In hope she would get angry
and wake up to complain.
I-I see...
Got it.
Nnn?
Let's make this a success.
Yes.
Let's give a name to a nameless flower
So that it won't freeze
from the coldness of solitude
If it's as frail as it is beautiful
Then it's not as fragile anymore
Like how you paint color
on a transparent body
Beyond the page of the chapter
It's welcoming you with a smile
Whenever, as much as it takes
Let's start a new world
We're Storyteller
All the love, hope, envy
Even the song of despair we sing today
It will all be a seed and bloom,
into a strong person
Why does salvation
born from someone's tear
That's just sad
Ideal and fantasy,
all mixed up by youthful impulse
My real self, is now reborn!
(Episode 36: The Unleashed)
What happened?
What about everyone?
Did I manage to evolve?
Yes.
Evolution to Demon Lord;
Harvest Festival was a success.
I see...
Great Rimuru?
Are you awake now?
Good morning, Great Rimuru.
Good morning, Shion.
I'm glad you got back alive.
Yes! All thanks to you, Great Rimuru.
Listen, don't make me worry anymore.
It's an order.
Understood.
Never again.
- Great Rimuru?
- He's finally awake?
Great Rimuru!
As you can see, we all have been
resurrected in one piece!
We all, without a single soul left
behind, have returned!
Good.
Nnn?
You all somehow look...
...somewhat different?
Report.
Gifts were distributed to all creatures
within your genealogy,
leading all of them to evolve further.
I see.
And also, do you sound much more fluent now?
No.
I have always been like this.
Ergo, it's just your imagination.
I see, so it's all just in my head. Hahaha!
Like hell that is! You are speaking
more fluently now!
Report.
To tell the truth, the Unique Skill Great Sage
has evolved into Ultimate Skill Raphael.
Raphael?
Named after an angel, now that's cool.
There is no longer anything I can't answer.
I-I see...
I will be counting on you.
You are more fluent now, aren't you?
No. It's your imagination.
So you're really pushing that
idea through, huh?
By the way, Great Rimuru.
Just to make sure.
Let me confirm whether you still have
your sanity after evolving into a Demon Lord.
Eeh?
Shion's cooking is?
Eh?!
What is it about my cooking, Great Rimuru?
There is no way I can say it's shit
in this situation!
Great Rimuru, please answer me.
To see if you still have your sanity!
Benimaru!
Lord of Wisdom, Raphael!
It's your turn now!
Find me the best way to deceive Shion
with your marvelous wisdom!
Answer. The answer to that question...
The answer is?
...doesn't exist.
You piece of crap! Didn't you say there's
no question you can't answer a minute ago?!
So what is it about my cooking?
Ermm, well...
I bet he wanted to eat it.
He looked like he really missed your
food when you're still dead.
He trapped me!
You do? I will gladly cook you food!
Let me provide suggestion.
Raphael!
Would that be okay?
I see! As I expect from Lord of Wisdom!
Ah, yes, Benimaru.
I do remember the password
that you decided.
You told me that when you ask me about
Shion's cooking, I should answer with "It's shit."
That's what you told me, right?
Yes, none other than you!
G-Great Rimuru!
I remember it perfectly!
The password that you decided!
With this, you now know
I still have my sanity, right?
W-Wait, Shion.
G-Great Rimuru has only just awoken.
I'm sure he's still in a state of confusion.
Understood
Sir Benimaru... no, Benimaru.
I serve Great Rimuru directly,
so I do not need to refer
to you with honorifics anymore.
However, I will gladly feed you my cooking
until your stomach ready to burst.
Why did you do that?!
Just do your best not to die, okay?
It's easier said than done.
Well, I have been testing some of her food,
so I've developed Poison Resistance lately.
Poison Resistance?!
I might die for real this time.
Well...
You reap what you sow.
Ah, that's right.
This is not the time to do this.
We still have problems to deal with.
Problems?
It happens during the past
three days you fell asleep.
I have been sleeping for three days?!
Yes.
Something serious has happened in
the Animal Kingdom of Eurazania.
My name is Milim Nava, a Demon Lord!
I hereby declare all agreements made between
myself and other demon lords are now void.
And I declare war to Beastmaster,
Demon Lord Carrion!
A war you say?!
The war will be in one week from now.
You better prepare yourself!
Wait Milim!
What the heck are you thinking?!
Did she say war, General?
You better let me have the first row.
Suphia, wait.
You don't know how much power
demon lord Milim has.
The entire Animal King's Brigade could
take her on and be wiped in mere seconds!
Phobio, you have seen Milim's power,
so I believe in your judgment.
So who do you think is stronger?
Milim or myself?
If I'm forced to give an answer...
Demon lord Milim does live up
to her title as The Destroyer.
I see. So you're saying
she's stronger than me?
Ah, no, I have certainly not--
To run from an enemy because of their strength
is not something a demon lord would do.
And here I get the chance to fight
the legendary demon lord.
There is no way I would throw
away this opportunity so easily.
Get in contact with that slime and have
our people take shelter in Jura.
This place won't be safe once Milim
and myself start our fight.
Also, I will be the only one fighting Milim.
Eh? But...
Let me fight too!
Great Carrion, we--
Silence! I am the only one who is capable
of fighting the demon lord Milim Nava!
The rest of you should devote yourself
to protecting our people.
I forbid you from joining this battle!
Yes, sir!
Trust me. I will win.
I don't hate you, Milim.
We could've been a great friend.
It's a real shame.
Milim's declaration of war.
That was ten days ago.
And finally, three days go.
So, Milim. Why are you doing this?
You're not telling me someone
is controlling you, aren't you?
If so, it's quite a shame.
I wish I could defeat you at your full strength
and prove once for all that I am the strongest!
Behold! This is my unique skill,
Royal Beast Form!
I am the king of the demonic beasts,
the Beastmaster Carrion!
Now, Milim.
I have to say this, but now that I have shown
you this form, I will have to ask you to leave.
I won't hold back.
This is the end!
Prepare to disappear from this world!
Beast Roar!
Destroyer, Milim Nava.
So that's your true combat form, yes?
It was fun. It has been a while
since my left hand went numb like this.
I'll show you my trump card.
Drago-Nova!
She's on a whole different level...
But... could she possibly be...
Could possibly be what?
I would love it if you tell me.
The Sky Queen, Frey!
Correct.
You too?
Oh my, me too as in what?
Could you perhaps tell me more about it?
So Eurazania has been destroyed?
Yes.
I saw it with my very own eyes.
Our people have evacuated in advance,
so they're all safe.
Have you got the refugees
the place to stay and food to eat?
Yes! I apologize for not confirming with
you beforehand, but all have been done.
I see. As I expect of you.
We appreciate your help.
But still... demon lord Frey is
working with Milim?
It's rare for demon lords to work together.
Furthermore, I thought Milim is the type who hate
working with others based on her personality.
Yeah, it is pretty odd.
I also don't think Milim would do
something underhanded like that.
And about that...
Demon lord Frey was not heading to her
domain nor Milim's domain.
Nnn? So you're saying...
The direction she goes to...
...was demon lord Clayman's domain.
- What?
I... I have to go for a moment--
Suphia, wait.
If you're going for revenge,
we should do it together.
Well, hang on.
If my guess is correct,
Carrion is still alive.
There's no way Milim would let
anyone cut her fight off like that.
There must be something behind it.
Which is why you guys mustn’t
do anything reckless.
If we don't work together, we might
end up destroying the chance we got.
Understood.
-Yes.
-Got it.
Is demon lord Clayman pulling the strings?
Worst case scenario, we would have
to deal with three demon lords at once.
Well then, what should we do now...
What's wrong?
I'm glad that you are awake, My Master.
Nnn? Yeah...
Allow me to express my joy at seeing
you becoming a full-fledged demon lord.
Ummnn...
Who are you again?
S-Surely you jest...
Those words hurt my demon heart
more than anything else could.
He looks like a pretty high-level demon.
But I don't know this guy.
This person right here is the demon you
summoned by sacrificing the Falmuth knights.
Ah, I see. So you're still here, huh?
S-Still...?
I heard about how much you
helped out. Thank you!
No, it was hardly worthy of your praise.
And as for--
Sorry for keeping you for so long.
You can go home now.
Go... home...?
Yeah.
Nn? What's wrong?
Please, do not say such a thing.
As I had asked you before, I wish you to
bestow me the honor to join as your follower!
You want to be my follower?
No matter how you look at it,
this guy is not some ordinary
greater demon at all.
He should be something with a higher rank.
Hey, Ranga.
Did I really summoned this guy?
You certainly did.
I see.
Okay then...
I can't give you much,
but are you okay with that?
To be able to serve you is all the joy I need.
All right then.
I thank you, My Master!
Quit with that "My Master" thingy,
it doesn't feel right.
You can call me Rimuru. Just Rimuru.
Rimuru.
Such a sweet tone that name has.
Great Rimuru it shall be, then.
So what's your name?
Being a nameless demon is enough for me.
You don't have a name?
I will give you a name as your reward then!
Oh my, that is the greatest gift I could have!
Let's see... you're a demon, so
a demon-like name would be great.
Ah, then your name will be Diablo!
Diablo...
It flat-out means "demon,"
but there is a sport-car with that name,
so it shouldn't be a problem.
May you live up to that name
and serve me well.
It took around half of my magicule.
It took 30% of my magicule when I give
that Greater Demon Beretta his name.
So this one took less than I expected.
Report.
Now that you have evolved, you
have a much higher magicule stores.
Therefore, you can't compare
it simply like that.
How much do I have now?
Ten times more than before.
Seems like this guy will evolve
into some real monster.
Oooh!
He looks strong.
Diablo. It is now my name.
My heart is now filled with great delight,
Great Rimuru.
I promise to serve you will all my heart
and body from today forward.
Nice to have you.
So, it appears to me you have
something in your mind right now.
If you don't mind,
please let me hear about it.
It's nothing big... well, it is, I guess.
It's about the future.
As in?
We got too many troubles at once.
Demon lord Clayman's scheme.
The clean up for Falmuth kingdom.
And dealing with the Western Holy Church
that sees monsters as enemies.
I see.
Report.
I believe there is no need to worry
about the Western Holy Church.
Why is that?
The Analysis and Assessment of
the Unlimited Imprisonment that sealed
the individual Veldora will
be completed shortly.
Eh?! We can seriously
release Veldora now?!
Yes, seriously.
It was supposed to take a few hundred years.
Raphael really is something, huh.
Releasing Veldora is believed to provide suitable
restraint on the nearby Western countries.
True, the Church wouldn't be able to
do anything reckless when that happens.
Wait, you are speaking much
more fluently now!
No. It is your imagination.
Ah, fine.
Anyway, that sure opens up
our path to solution.
Okay, I think we can work this out.
Oh, has an idea come to your mind?
I've decided to become a demon lord,
in both name and deed!
As I expected of you, Great Rimuru.
I, Diablo, pledge my eternal loyalty to you.
Hmph! If so, then I, Ranga,
am My Lord's most loyal servant!
I got it, okay?
With that's settled, Ranga.
I will head off for a moment.
Tell everyone else to prepare a party.
Yes, sir!
Soei, are you here?
Here.
-Immediately...
-We will look for info about Clayman.
Oooh, no need for me to even say it.
That's a guy who can do his job, alright.
Okay, I'm going now.
After transforming into a demon lord,
all of my skill are now
united by my ultimate skill Raphael,
making it much easier to use.
My Gluttony has also evolved
into Beelzebub.
That means I now have two
ultimate skills under my belt.
This place sure takes me back.
It has been two years since then.
Report.
Analysis and Assessment of
Unlimited Imprisonment is complete.
I can finally fulfill my promise.
I will free you now, Veldora.
I grew taller?
Raphael, make a Body Double of me,
I'll make it as the vessel for Veldora.
Enhanced Replication activate.
Seems like I do look older.
It's supposed to be me, but man,
I look beautiful.
Okay, time to do this.
Please work.
Report. The soul corridor between Master and
the individual Veldora has been established.
I, the Storm Dragon
Veldora Tempest, have returned!
Anyone who opposes me will die!
I'm used to losing things
I said it like it's someone else's problem
It's a blurry realism
Because it's not about me
The nameless sadness disappears,
warped in a legato-like dream
Will we feel better if we hug each other?
The life which I repeat is a joined miracle
Don't forget me, pass your voice to me
If I were to live for someone's sake
I wish that someone is you
(I'll tell you one more story)
If I can redo this world once again
I will paint that story with love
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
I will tell you one more story
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you