Well then, let's move on to the main topic.
Ramiris?!
What's up all of the sudden?
I heard all about it!
This country, Tempest, will be destroyed!
Wha--
What did you say?!
Yes, destro--
H-Hey! What are you doing?!
I can't break free even with all my power!
Great Rimuru, how would you like me to dispose of this pesky insect?
What? What is it with you?!
That thing is more or less a Demon Lord, though.
Y-You're not just some ordinary guy, are you?!
Umm, Mr. Rimuru...
Who is that spirit...?
Well, she's Ramiris, my acquaintance.
She might not look the part, but she's apparently a Demon Lord.
Demon Lord...
Despite how I look,
I'm actually revered as the strongest of the Ten Great Demon Lords!
Oooh?
Hey, you. Why aren't you more surprised?
I am Ramiris of the Labyrinth, in flesh!
How can you be so dry like that?
Well, the Storm Dragon's revival is already a big enough surprise for me.
I don't think anything could surprise me at this point.
Huh? Storm Dragon?
You're telling me Veldora has been revived?
No way! I am the one who beat Veldora in a single punch!
He was nothing but all talk.
Besides, his era is over now.
What you should fear is me, not that puny "Breeze Dragon"!
-Veldora. -Hmm?
Sorry, but can you deal with this kid for me?
Veldora?
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Fate repeats all over again
The voices of my heart say
Time is not enough, it's over
Belief that makes me who I am
Light doesn't fade away
Made my mind up now, it's better
Yeah I know it's not an easy road
Lured by your hands
Even if it rains don't be swayed
Being same as always
Want to feel my destiny
Open my eyes to be braver
Get up now Get up now stronger
I believe in myself
Stand up now Stand up now shouting
I'll never run away
I might lose control
It's a perfect world
Destroy all of it, in the end it's for our good
Let me shout like flames
(Episode 39: Ramiris's Report)
Well then, once again, let me bring up the main topic.
The narrative we will reveal to the public will be as follows.
I will declare myself a Demon Lord, but conceal the fact that I have awakened.
The greedy king of Falmuth, Edmaris, led his army towards Tempest,
starting a war, and got defeated as result.
Rather than getting destroyed by a Demon Lord alone,
saying they got defeated in war makes it easier to swallow for other nations.
And the fallen Falmuth soldiers unwittingly opened up the dreadful seal,
unleashing the sleeping Evil Dragon, the Storm Dragon Veldora.
What is it?
To oppose Veldora, the Champion Youm and I joined hand.
After many losses, we successfully negotiated and calmed his anger.
And ended the conflict by agreeing to worship him as our guardian.
We will justify my ascend as a Demon Lord, put all the blame on Falmuth Kingdom,
and portray our actions as justice.
Just think about it.
People fear what they do not understand, and will never willfully accept it.
Even if the monster who destroyed an army of 20,000 is standing for peace,
no one would believe it.
But if we claim the Storm Dragon is behind those deaths,
the masses will find it easier to grasp.
The Storm Dragon is a 'Catastrophe,' a mastermind of chaos, after all.
You're quite a smart man for calling me a mastermind!
That's not what he meant!
I also support this narrative.
Rather than my daughter being resented for causing the birth of a new Demon Lord,
it's better for her to be credited
for introducing a Demon Lord that enabled negotiations with the Storm Dragon.
And that's not the only merit of this.
This might also fool other Demon Lords into thinking that Veldora is the only threat.
If so, it'll be easier for me to make my move.
Furthermore, if people know that we've got the authority to negotiate with Veldora,
it'll keep a lot of nations from trying to mess with us, don't you think?
If anyone is opposed to this, please speak up.
Especially Veldora, since I would have you take all the blame for my sins.
There is no problem.
I've decided to share your karma.
So just make use of the name Storm Dragon all you want.
All right. Thank you.
It is understandable!
In that case, we can continue negotiating with other nations the same way as before.
Brilliantly done, Great Rimuru.
A truly ingenious plan!
No, it was King Gazel's idea.
I only compile everyone's opinion together.
We thank you, King Gazel.
This means we can expect Sir Rimuru's aid when we make our move.
I see.
So we can simply focus solely on Clayman.
If we lose, then it will just prove that I'm incompetent.
All right.
That will be the narrative we're going for my transformation into a Demon Lord.
Everyone agrees?
Well then, with that in mind, I would like to decide on our next move.
Youm.
Huh?
Yes.
I would like to support Champion Youm as the new King of Falmuth
and build a new nation for its people.
What did you say? Youm will?
First, we will release King Edmaris,
and force him to pay reparations for invading our country.
But I highly doubt that king will even oblige to pay reparations.
That's the point.
The reparation is merely the trigger.
Our real goal is to start a civil war within Falmuth Kingdom.
We will destroy and rebuild it as a new nation.
With the Champion Youm as its new king.
Thankfully, he's popular among the citizens.
Eeeh?
Very well.
I have no objection in the proposal itself.
Do you have the resolve to feel for your people, shoulder their pain,
and stand before them?!
How is it?
Hell do I know?
I'm not here to become a king because I want to.
But people trust me with this role,
and if I turn it down, how can I call myself a man?
I just don't want to tell myself I can't do it and give up before I even try.
And I also want to impress the woman I love.
Idiot.
If I'm doing this, I'll give it my all!
This guy is certainly an idiot.
But that's how he does things.
Dwarven King, I can guarantee you this.
This guy is undoubtedly an idiot.
Don't call me idiot over and over--
But he's not irresponsible.
I promise until the day he can become like a King of Champion such as you,
I, Grucius, will be on his side and watch over him!
So do I!
Very well.
If you need anything, you may rely on me.
I must say, you found quite an interesting man here.
Seeing how he seeks the throne to impress the woman he loves.
Nice going, Grucius.
I wasn't expecting you to declare betraying Great Carrion like that in front of us.
W-Well, that's not my intention...
Youm, what we seek from your nation is agricultural production.
Instead of competing with other nations in a common field,
you will find it easier to coexist if you take a dip into the unexplored market.
Count me in on that, too, Youm.
We can discuss the detail later.
Understood, Mister.
Just count on me.
Agriculture is fully developed in Falmuth, I'm sure it will work out.
Then as a representative of Blumund, I have a proposal.
Proposal?
I feel like we have something to offer in this plan.
Oh?
Blumund has an intimate relationship with Marquis Muller and Count Hellman in Falmuth.
How about we negotiate with them and have them join our side on this matter?
I believe they can provide reliable support when Youm takes his post as a king.
That would be great, but...
Even as a Guildmaster, is it really okay for you to decide that here?
Please understand that right now I'm standing here as part of the government.
Not as a Guildmaster,
but as an secretary Supervisor of Blumund's intelligence department.
And you're saying we can trust those nobles?
Marquis Muller is actually a distant relative of Blumund royal family.
And Count Hellman owed a great dept of gratitude towards Marquis Muller.
It is unlikely he would betray him.
I see.
But is it really okay for you to reveal that secret right here?
It's okay.
And I'm sure you're well aware of this already.
The Spymaster of Dwargon are just as skilled as our intelligence department.
All right, got it.
Fuze, can you contact Marquis Muller and Count Hellman for us in secret?
Yeah, just leave it to me.
Youm, you heard him right?
Yeah, you can count on me.
Okay, that should be all about Youm and the throne.
Let's make the Champion's triumph as brilliant as it can be!
The leaders of nations expressing their minds without doubting one another.
I feel like a fool for being on alert with you all.
C'mon, Papa.
Allow me to ask you.
Do you really trust this monster Rimuru?
What do you mean by that?
Even if monsters band together and decide to start a country,
there should be no reason for Blumund to officially recognize them.
Let alone developing the diplomacy with them.
So what I'm saying is this.
If it were me, I would only engage in trade
and see how the Western Holy Church moves.
Enjoy all the profit and give them confidential reports.
If there's any problem, just leave the matters to them.
Isn't that how a small nation usually handle matters?
Argh, all right, all right! I understand!
Well then, allow me to be straight with you.
Yes, of course, I had the same opinion as you, Archduke Erald.
I stated the same to my superior before Mr. Rimuru first arrived at Blumund.
But he rejected the idea, fearing the possibility of war.
Build a mutual friendship and find a way to coexist.
That was the conclusion the higher-ups in our government made.
A nation such as yours and the Dwarven Kingdom is big and powerful.
So I'm sure you have all sorts of choices available.
But for us weak nations, one misstep could speak our doom.
If we're going to entrust our fate to someone,
it's better to trust the monster lord than relying on Western Holy Church's help.
Anyway, that's basically it.
And you came here to save Mister Rimuru.
Was that also the decision of your superior?
Exactly.
Since we've ratified a security treaty,
I've been ordered to follow it to the letter.
Well, even if the government broke its promise, I would still come here.
I'm a free man.
Why did I even take this job?
Anyway, I've been appointed to Blumund's intelligence department.
You can say my luck ran out from that point on.
And that superior of yours is...
None other than His Majesty, the King of Blumund himself.
I apologize, Sir Fuze.
But thanks to you, I now finally understand Blumund's intentions.
I already trust Rimuru since the start, so there is nothing to doubt.
You may say that Gazel,
but deciding whether to form a pact with a nation of monsters is not that easy.
I'm having a new-found respect for King of Blumund.
Hmph, enough with the act.
You already made your decision, that's why you're here in the first place.
So, Master Strategist Erald.
What's your conclusion?
I have indeed made my own conclusion.
But before I answer you that.
May I ask one more question?
Papa, come on!
Stop acting all stuck-up and just answer already!
Whoa, Princess, that's not good!
Yeah! Archduke is trying his hardest to look cool for you, okay?!
So much for master strategist.
Let me hear it, Erald.
A Demon Lord aura!
I see, tremendous indeed.
Well then, Demon Lord Rimuru.
Let me ask you.
How do you intent to wield your power as Demon Lord?
Eh?
Really? Just something that easy?
Easy?
The answer is simple.
I want to make a world that's easy to live in as I pictured.
A bountiful world where as many people as possible can be content with.
You really think you can make such a fantasy-like dream come true?
That's what this power is for.
An ideal with no power to back it up is nonsense,
and a power without ideals are pointless, right?
Hilarious!
This is hilarious, Demon Lord Rimuru!
'O Demon Lord versed in karma.
I think I now understand why you managed to awaken yourself.
My pardons, Demon Lord Rimuru.
As the envoy of the Sorcerous Dynasty of Thalion,
I hereby request the establishment of formal relations with Jura Tempest Federation.
I hope to hear a positive reply from you.
Papa!
-P-Princess! -Wait!
I was also hoping to build a positive relationship with you.
I will gladly accept the offer.
Thus, Tempest successfully established a relation with Sorcerous Dynasty of Thalion.
After Blumund and Dwargon, that makes it our third allied human nation.
-Okay, Benimaru. -Yes!
Our enemy is Clayman. Let's crush him!
I've been waiting for that order!
Yes, I'm all ready!
And for The Three Beastketeers and the rest of the Brigade.
All of us are now under your command.
Yeah, you can count on us.
Rimuru, are you sure you can win this?
We will win.
He has angered me.
You sure make it sound easy.
Clayman is a Demon Lord who has many Majin under his control.
He is not someone to take lightly.
That doesn't matter.
War is not about quantity but quality.
Good grief.
I can already hear the sound of my common sense crumbling apart.
With that, the long meeting between humans and monsters comes to an end.
Once again, we take another big step in making our ideal come true.
I heard all about it.
You're planning to invade Eurazania next?
Yeah.
Milim obliterated the capital, but that country has a large population.
There are still many humans staying within several scattered settlements.
They would make just the right sacrifice for my awakening.
Don't you think so?
So he's planning to kill everyone including the non-combatants?
Sounds like he's forcing it.
Aren't you a little to hasty, Clayman?
By the way, do you really have to make a move right before the big event Walpurgis?
And isn't there also a non-aggression treaty between Demon Lords?
Yeah, that's not problem.
My "ringleader" Mjurran was killed by that slime.
That is a threat aimed towards me and my Demon Lord's seat.
And turned out the one who instigated that was Carrion.
That's how I intent to frame it.
I see.
It would make sense if the other side was the one who betrayed first--
Lil' Mjurran was killed?!
Yeah, I heard the whole thing via Marionette Heart.
And the heart I was holding onto turned into ashes.
I see.
She was a good girl though.
You sure are kind.
Tear told me the other day.
That you must treat tools with care.
Laplace, it was you who taught her that, right?
Which is why I must hold those who broke my tools accountable for it.
Hey, Clayman.
Did you really plan all these yourself?
The only ones who can command me are Great Kazaream
and 'that person' who we are indebted to.
You know that better than anyone else, don't you?
I see.
That's all, then.
I'll take my leave now.
But let me give you one last piece of advice as a friend.
Don't be overconfident in your control over Demon Lord Milim.
That one has been existing for longer than even our President Kazaream.
She's one of the ancient Demon Lords.
Whatever you do, don't let your guard down.
See ya.
Is he trying to say I'm being influenced by someone?!
How annoying!
The more you got hurt
That seed of hope
You plant on both of your hand
Will surely bloom someday
Whatever it is, it doesn't have to last forever
As long as it makes you smile
To find the meaning behind that fleeting moment
Let's go on a journey
Together
I ride on that momentary whirlwind
Above the shadow you cast
Reincarnate
The full bloom flower will paint color on this dreary world
If you were reincarnated
I'd be with you wherever you go
Our souls are connected
I'll always by your side
Next time, "The Congress Dances."