Wonderfully done, Great Rimuru.
It was one truly magnificent spell.
Yes! It was great!
Fascinating!
Rimuru! How about I go there
and beat the enemy instead?
Just hold it.
We want to keep you a secret until
Walpurgis begins, remember?
If you go there, people will know
it's you right off the bat.
That's right! It just slipped off my head!
Don't forget it like that!
Anyway, don't do anything
unnecessarily, you hear me?
Benimaru and others headed to
the Animal Kingdom of Eurazania
to fight Clayman's army.
At the same time, Gazel returns to Dwargon.
And Erald returns to Thalion.
Meanwhile, Youm and his friends
head to take over Falmuth.
I shall return immediately,
so rest assured.
You can take your time.
I shall return immediately,
so rest assured.
We're talking about taking over
a nation here, it won't be that easy.
All right!
We should prepare now!
For Walpurgis!
(Fate repeats all over again)
Fate repeats all over again
(The voices of my heart say)
The voices of my heart say
(依然還是不夠啊 itʼs over)
Time is not enough, it's over
Belief that makes me who I am
(Belief that makes me who I am)
(Light doesnʼt fade away)
Light doesn't fade away
(我已經下定決心 itʼs better)
Made my mind up now, it's better
Yeah I know it's not an easy road
(Yeah I know itʼs not an easy road)
(朝呼喚的方向前進)
Lured by your hands
(Even if it rains donʼt be swayed)
Even if it rains don't be swayed
Being same as always
(順從內心自我)
Want to feel my destiny
(渴望感受命運)
(就在此刻覺醒吧勇者)
Open my eyes to be braver
Get up now Get up now stronger
(Get up now Get up now stronger)
(I believe in myself)
I believe in myself
Stand up now Stand up now shouting
(Stand up now Stand up now shouting)
(Iʼll never run away)
I'll never run away
(I might lose control…)
I might lose control
It's a perfect world
(請為了我們 照亮這個世界吧)
Destroy all of it,
in the end it's for our good
(Let me shout like flames)
Let me shout like flames
There's no one there?
(Episode 42: The Demon Lords)
(第42話 魔王們)
Yes, the Animal Kingdom of Eurazania
is completely empty.
(第42話 魔王們)
How come?
Oh well.
Search the whole area thoroughly.
Smoke them out.
Yes, sir.
And one more thing.
One of our men heard an interesting
story from a passing merchant.
Interesting story?
Yes.
He said the Storm Dragon
Veldora has been revived.
Veldora...
According to him, the Falmuth army
fell victim to Veldora's rampage.
So it's the Storm Dragon's fault?
Yes.
And apparently, the Storm Dragon had
lost most of his energy upon his revival.
I see.
So that's why I lost contact with
Pirone and my Marionettes in Falmuth.
It was all because of Veldora's revival.
There was no way a mere slime
could destroy Falmuth's army.
And it should be easy for me to kill
the Evil Dragon at his current state.
Not only that, I may even be able
to add him to my cache of pawns...
Yamza, good job on the report.
Continue on with your job.
Yes, sir!
To think I was so close
to fall into his bluff.
Still, truth is not something that
one can hide so easily.
You mere slime who swaggers
about under the Evil Dragon.
Consider this an honor.
I shall crush you
with my very own hands.
Don't be overconfident in your control
over Demon Lord Milim.
Whatever you do,
don't let your guard down.
Don't worry, Laplace.
I will win.
Hey, Frey! What a good weather
we're having today!
Or maybe it's a little hot?
Aaah! It's so hot today!
Milim...
You seem to be in a great mood.
Did something nice happen to you?
You could tell?! Well, you see...
Take a look at these!
Oh my, it looks great on you.
Where'd you get those?
You wanna know?!
What should I do?
Well, I won't mind telling you.
But what should I do?
Troublesome girl as always.
We're friends, aren't we?
It should be okay for you to tell me.
Really? Oh Frey, we sure are friends!
All right! I will tell you! You see--
And like that, my besties Rimuru
gave me these as a present.
Ah, besties means best friends
among best friends!
I see, I'm happy for you.
Ah, that's right. Milim.
As your friend, I also have a present for you.
Would you take it?
Ooh, a pendant? I can have it?
But...
I won't give you these knuckles!
It's okay, Milim.
Consider it a symbol of our friendship.
I want to have my gratitude,
so I would love it if you could
wear it every once in a while.
If that's the case, then leave it to me.
Let me put this on for you.
It tickles!
Don't move, okay?
Would that be all, Clayman?
Good work.
The forbidden spell, Demon Marionette
has been activated with no problem.
Now I finally obtained
the ultimate puppet!
This is what you get for picking on me
and calling me a young upstart!
Pathetic, isn't it, Milim?
I advice you to stop that.
This isn't the sort of weak curse that'll
undo itself after a punch or two.
Don't you resent her as well for
being so bossy around us?
Isn't that why
you joined me on my plan?
Or is it not?
It's not.
I'm just fulfilling my promise to you.
Cut it with that innocent act.
This thing is now nothing
more than a mere puppet.
There is no need to hold back!
So that's your true nature.
What a pathetic man.
So Clayman, it seems like
you don't know about this.
But Milim has a self-defense mechanism.
Huh?
Self-defense mechanism?
It's called Stampede.
I heard it will put her in
an uncontrollable state.
I don't mind you die on your own,
but I don't want to
be caught in the mess.
What an annoying
Demon Lord to the core.
Very well.
I can still use her to strengthen
my clout in our rank.
And you're my accomplice.
I'll expect you work for me.
Oh my, aren't we supposed
to be equal on this matter?
Fool!
I'm the one who came out with this plan!
You're already one of my pawns.
Or what?
You want to fight Milim?
Is that supposed to be a threat?
You can take it any way you like.
If you don't want to die,
you better not anger me.
All right.
Good. Just don't think about doing
anything to betray me, okay?
As long as you listen to my requests,
I'll guarantee your position
as the ruler of the sky.
Miss Frey, the Sky Queen.
That man could not see
the true essence of things.
On the day of the new moon,
the night of Walpurgis.
Clayman, it seems like you
won't be alive for much longer.
Lord of Darkness.
To Demon Lord Guy Crimson.
Demon Lord Leon Cromwell has arrived.
Long time no see.
My friend, the Platinum Devil.
Demon Lord Cromwell.
Or do you prefer me to call
you Platinum Saber instead?
Call me whatever.
Have you been well?
I'm glad you responded to my call.
Let me thank you.
Stop it! I told you
I don't swing that way!
You're as cold as usual!
If you wish, I can become a girl
and let you sleep with me.
Silence.
Oh well, let's move somewhere else.
So, what did you call me here for?
As you know, the banquet of Demon Lords,
Walpurgis will be held soon.
I was thinking to implore
you to attend this time.
It sure is rare for you to force
anything upon me like that.
I will have you come even if
I have to owe you a favor.
The reason being?
Cautious as usual, aren't you?
Fine, I will explain.
The proponent this time is Clayman.
The little one.
But oddly enough, Milim's name
was on the list of endorsers.
Milim is one of the oldest and strongest
Demon Lords, up there with me.
She wouldn't lift a finger
for the likes of Clayman.
Which means...
The report of Carrion's death
might not be entirely true?
Oh, you know, don't you?
Clayman overstepped his boundaries.
He tried to harass me without leaving
any evidence behind.
I won't let him pass this time.
Setting Carrion's case aside, if Milim
is taking action then it's a bad news.
This might be just
another game for Milim,
but I don't want anyone tipping
the balance of power among the Demon Lords.
It'll just give me more work.
Do you think Milim is being
controlled by Clayman?
Thinking about Milim will get you nowhere.
A genius like me can't read
the behavior of a moron.
You can consider it one of few
weaknesses that I have.
Since you seem to be
interested in the matter,
does that mean you will
participate this time, Leon?
Yes, I intend to.
I'm not interested in a friendly meeting,
but it seems like I have no choice.
Oh, then I'm glad.
And here I was thinking of letting you
sleep with me for a night if you refuse--
I refuse.
So cold.
You're just so cold.
Do you know anything about
this Rimuru guy?
The way Clayman puts it,
he's just a self-styled Demon Lord.
But if he has the strength to back it up,
I have no problem with it.
So you're saying he's qualified
to be a Demon Lord?
Since Ramiris has taken a liking in him,
I figured he might be
quite an interesting guy.
Ramiris?
I can't stand that spirit.
She makes fun of me
every time we meet.
I've thought about strangling
her to death countless times.
You better not.
If you kill Ramiris,
I will be your enemy.
Figured.
I wasn't serious.
It's not like I can win against
you in a fight, anyway.
Nnn? I wouldn't be so sure.
I say you'd kill me in
one in a million tries.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not interested in a fight
I'm not guaranteed to win.
Don't be so modest.
You're strong enough for even having
the possibility of killing me, Leon.
Hmph, that goes without saying.
You and Milim are simply
on a different level from us.
And speaking of that.
I heard the Storm Dragon Veldora
has awoken recently.
Oh my?
I am very interested in
the topic you're having there.
Almost forgot you're also here.
One of the four remaining dragons.
The White Ice Dragon, Velzard.
The Ice Empress.
Oh my, forgetting me already?
Cold as always, aren't you?
But I'm glad to see your face here.
Is it so? Then it is also a pleasure
to my eye to see your face.
You two never did get
along with each other.
Leon, are you feeling jealous
towards my partner?
Nonsense.
So, Sir Leon.
You're saying my younger brother
Veldora has awoken?
I stopped sensing his presence
around two years ago,
so I assumed he had met his end.
Are you certain?
No mistake.
If so, then why that Evil Dragon
hasn't done anything?
Has he weakened to the point
he couldn't replenish energy on his own?
Then who would've undone his seal?
As the spy reports it,
Clayman's scheme was the cause.
Clayman, huh...
Seems like he manipulated
Falmuth from the shadow
in an attempt to destroy
the nation Rimuru had built.
You sure know much, Leon.
Of course I do.
I'm a former human, unlike you.
And apparently, Veldora was sleeping
right around the battlefield.
Just before he disappeared for good,
he was exposed to vast amounts
of blood and thus awakened.
The Falmuth's troops were subsequently
massacred by his rage,
and Rimuru survived
through the ordeal.
Or so I heard.
So that's what happened, huh?
Then did his seal get undone by accident?
Who knows, I can't tell you that much.
I see.
Then there is a chance that
the hero's seal was incomplete.
That might be the case, but
I also came up with a hypothesis.
Hypothesis?
It's weird that his presence
just disappeared out of nowhere.
But what if someone transported him
alongside the seal into a
subspace of their making?
Interesting!
Then someone must've undone
the seal for him!
That means that someone would
have a power equal to us!
It's still just a possibility.
And Leon, you're thinking that person
might be Rimuru, aren't you?
Precisely.
I see.
Then we really need to
ascertain this person.
Clayman's scheme and
Milim's suspicious action.
How Rimuru turned into a Demon Lord.
Veldora's revival.
If all of these are connected...
Then we must be up for a spectacle
in Walpurgis this time.
If so, then why is Veldora
acting so obedient?
He seems to have weakened.
His presence is so weak now,
it's nothing like what he was before.
But it is strange that
he didn't go into more rampage.
Running amok was like
the only source of joy for him.
Anyhow, I don't care about that.
If you two want to get Veldora on
your side, then do as you pleased.
You're leaving already?
Yeah. That's all you need from me, right?
Just hold on, there's no need to rush.
Have you made any progress in
your true goal; targeted summoning?
Not quite yet.
There were hindrance.
Hindrance?
One guy had apparently saved the lives
of some kids who were close to their death.
Before I could take them in.
Oh?
Seems like that guy got angry about nations
summoning children from the otherworld.
He may start applying pressure
to each of the nations.
So that's the end of that experiment.
Then why don't you just
get rid of that hindrance?
It should be easy for you.
That hindrance is the exact Rimuru
we were just discussing.
What did you say?!
Is that really just a coincidence?
Interesting, don't you think?
That's why I also want
to see him in person.
I see, now I'm more interested than ever.
Milim might be thinking the same
thing as me right now.
She's a moron, but she's also
quite sharp in some places.
Perhaps.
Well, tonight's Walpurgis could
be a rather raucous occasion.
No doubt about it.
By the way, who is this collaborator
of yours providing your information?
He seems to be a human from the Empire,
I don't know much about him.
He call himself a merchant.
Can you trust him?
Trust?
Why should I?
I'm just making use of him.
If you're fine with that,
then I don't have anything to say.
But don't let your guard down.
I'm not letting you die on your own.
You're worried about me?
How rare.
Rest assured, Guy.
I have no intention of dying
before I accomplish my goal.
That's reassuring.
Is that goal of yours
really that important?
Yeah.
It is something that I would
prioritize over anything in this world.
I see, that makes me jealous.
Don't feed me with that lie.
But I'll accept your warning.
See you in Walpurgis.
See ya.
What an impatient guy.
But that's just like him.
But it's pretty uncharacteristic
of him to be so rash like that.
Should I investigate for him?
Stop it.
Meddling with Leon's affair
will just offend him.
I don't want my friend to hate me.
We can just help him
when he asks for it.
Understood.
Looks like this Walpurgis
will be a fun one.
Do you want to come, too?
Let's see...
No, I don't think I will.
Perhaps if my brother were there,
but otherwise,
I have no interest in the Demon Lords.
I see.
Then keep the lights on for me.
Yes.
Well then, excuse me.
Interesting.
It has been several hundred years
since I feel so excited.
I can feel a big wave of change will come.
For Walpurgis!
The more you got hurt
(在過去留下多少傷痕)
(就撒下多少種子吧)
That seed of hope
You plant on both of your hand
(那些雙手灑下的希望之種)
Will surely bloom someday
(何時會發芽呢)
(不管是永恆或甚麼都無關緊要)
Whatever it is,
it doesn't have to last forever
(只要你能微笑)
As long as it makes you smile
(我為尋找在剎那間四散的意義)
To find the meaning behind
that fleeting moment
(決定踏上旅程)
Let's go on a journey
(一同前行吧)
Together
(在那你所留下的黑影上)
I ride on that momentary whirlwind
(乘著一瞬之間的塵捲風)
Above the shadow you cast
(Reincarnate 艷麗綻放的花朵)
Reincarnate
The full bloom flower will paint
color on this dreary world
(將為這枯燥無趣的世界帶來色彩)
(If you were reincarnated)
If you were reincarnated
(Iʼd be with you wherever you go)
I'd be with you wherever you go
(Our souls are connected)
Our souls are connected
(Iʼll always by your side)
I'll always by your side
Next time, "The Starting Signal."