Die!
Dead End Rainbow!
Awaken, Gluttony!
Understood. Order accepted.
Executing at once.
Let's give a name to a nameless flower
So that it won't freeze
from the coldness of solitude
If it's as frail as it is beautiful
Then it's not as fragile anymore
Like how you paint color
on a transparent body
Beyond the page of the chapter
It's welcoming you with a smile
Whenever, as much as it takes
Let's start a new world
We're Storyteller
All the love, hope, envy
Even the song of despair we sing today
It will all be a seed and bloom,
into a strong person
Why does salvation
born from someone's tear
That's just sad
Ideal and fantasy,
all mixed up by youthful impulse
My real self, is now reborn!
(Episode 31: Despair)
Unbelievable.
I see.
You copy the characteristic of
monsters and items you devoured
to create a form
that is specialized in combat.
Which is that.
And seeing that you didn't die
from Dead End Rainbow...
...it means you don't have a soul at all.
If so...
Astral Bind!
You won't stop with just that?
Elemental Summon!
Here I give my prayer to the One.
For I seek the power of the holy spirits.
Listen to my wish!
Exhaust everything!
Disintegration!
I have avenged you, Ms. Shizu.
I thought I'm dead.
I finally can get out!
Are you okay, My Lord?
My Lord!
I'm fine! I'm fine, okay!
That was really a close call, I must say.
This is not good. She's strong!
The end.
You did pretty well moving that
much in this barrier.
To tell you the truth,
I underestimated you.
But you can't win against me.
Because you will kill me in
one more hit?
Not even I thought the situation
would be this desperate.
But I will keep on struggling
until the end.
I'm not kind enough to let myself
get killed by you so easily!
Report. Using the unique skill De-generate,
the higher-level elemental Ifrit
has been separated into a pure elemental.
Okay.
Defeat my enemy!
O' Ifrit, the high-level fire elemental!
I immediately made a body double
and went into hiding.
It was the right choice to hide.
But still, that darn Hinata.
She's crazy strong.
I would've lost even without that barrier.
With that Disintegration thing.
Maybe I can dodge that,
but the chance would be very slim.
I wonder can Milim withstand that.
I should ask her later.
But still, that girl Hinata.
How dare she!
She didn't listen to anything I say
and attacked me ruthlessly like that!
I don't really understand, but it should not
be an exaggeration to say that it's your win.
Right? You think so too, Ranga?
Well, if she insists,
I won't mind calling it a draw.
I don't really understand, but it should not
be an exaggeration to say that it's your big win.
Anyway, let's go home now.
I'm worried about everyone.
Back to Tempest!
Yes, sir!
What's wrong?
Report. Unable to locate target location.
Huh?
It is believed that Tempest is isolated
by some kind of barrier.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Can we teleport somewhere near Tempest?
Searching.
Location found.
Great, let's go!
I will go and break it with my attack.
No, I will go there once again.
But still...
Oooh! Great Rimuru!
Great Rimuru.
Glad to see you safe and sound.
Yeah...
Wait!
You're looking much worse than me, Soei!
This means nothing.
Ah, Great Rimuru.
Here, take this.
What is happening in Tempest?
We're not really sure.
I'm worried about my underling
back in town. I can't contact them.
The town seems to be covered
by a barrier.
As I thought.
Sir Soei was injured in his attempt to
cross the barrier that's covering the town.
Silence, Soka.
I am fine.
Understood.
If even Soei can't break it,
then it must be really strong.
Who did this?
I fear it might be an attack from
the human nation, Falmuth kingdom.
We have confirmed that there
are some movement in their army.
A large crowd is heading towards Tempest.
Let's head to the town now!
So this is the barrier?!
Great Sage, analyze it.
Report.
The effect of certain Great Magic
from inside, the Anti-Magic Area,
and the Barrier from outside have
caused a reduction in magicule density.
Reduction in magicule density?
Is it the same thing
as Hinata's Holy Field?
No.
It runs on the same principle,
but has weaker purification effect.
Assumed to be an inferior version.
The effects can be resisted
with Multilayer Barrier.
A Great Magic from inside and
Holy Magic from outside.
A double barrier, huh.
Just who did this and for what purpose?
Soei, I will hold down the one
who cast the Great Magic.
You guy look for those who
cast this barrier.
- Understood
- Yes, sir.
However, I forbid you from
engaging them in combat.
Confirm their identity and strength.
So how would we contact you?
I'm sure we can do Thought Communication
with this even through the barrier.
I see.
Okay, go!
Yes, sir!
Ranga, get into my shadow.
You wait here, Gabiru.
Be careful!
Yeah.
It's weak, but there are
some magicule left.
How awful...
All the kids were safe thanks to you.
Thank you so much for protecting them.
Thank you so much!
No need for thanks.
I'm sure Sir Gabiru would've
done the same.
We're just doing what's normal.
I hope Sir Gabiru is safe.
It's Great Rimuru!
Great Rimuru, you came.
Great Rimuru!
It's wonderful to see you back.
I'm so glad you're safe.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Not at all!
What happened?
About that...
Mister, glad you're safe.
Kaijin...
Great Rimuru, we have a lot of things
to report and discuss with you,
so please head to the meeting room.
Kaijin, what's that over there?
Well, it is...
We just got a little trouble, that's all!
Stop changing the topic.
What's happening in the plaza?
What was that?
Is it Benimaru?
You're going to protect that woman, too?
I'm sorry but I have no time for this.
Get out of here at once!
No way I'd hand her to you
when you lose your calm like that.
What?
I'm not 'calm' you say?
If I'm not calm, I would've
already burnt you into ashes.
Just give up and--
Sorry, but I will protect
this woman no matter what!
I told you to get down!
But... I'm... still...!
If you continue to resist, I will really...!
Stop it, Benimaru!
Great Rimuru.
Explain this to me.
It's about this barrier.
It prevents us from using our magic
and lowers our strength.
And because of that,
many of our people--
B-Benimaru!
Let's discuss that later.
Regardless, the magic that weakened us
were cast by that woman.
We wanted to capture the caster, but...
Youm got in our way, so we were
forced to engage in combat.
Mister Rimuru!
I'm sorry!
I have no intention to betray you.
I just wanted to save Mjurran.
Mjurran?
That's enough.
You should abandon me.
Don't say that.
You don't have to get yourself
involved in this.
I told you to not say that!
Lord... Rimuru...
I'm fully aware that it's not the place
for a guest like me to speak...
But even so,
can you at least hear her out?
Okay.
No. Youm, Grucius.
I have no right to be protected by you two.
Mjurran!
This town has lost so many
because of me.
I'm the one who caused that tragedy.
Tragedy?
What do you mean by that?
You will know once you see it.
What is this?
Just what... happened?
Are everyone here...
...dead?
Those humans were merciless.
Humans?
As you wished, we accepted
the humans and let them in.
But as the result of that...
Shut your mouth.
Shut it.
I'm deeply sorry.
My words...
My words has...
There are three rules.
I'd like you to uphold them,
at the very least.
First, no attacking humans.
Second, no fighting amongst yourselves.
Third, no belittling other races.
That's all.
All because they followed my order...
This wouldn't have happened if
I hadn't activated the great magic.
This woman did what?
Report.
Great Magic Anti-Magic Area
can not weaken its targets by itself.
In terms of cause,
it's believed to be more relevant to
the humans that Soei is investigating.
That's right.
I must calm down.
This woman tried to anger me
so that I would kill her?
All to protect Youm and Grucius.
Mjurran, was it?
I want more detail about this.
Join us to the meeting room.
Great Rimuru.
If you don't mind, may I join
this meeting as well?
I believe I can provide some valuable
outside perspective regarding this incident.
You are...
So you came.
That would be a great help.
Mjöllmile.
I listen to the report regarding what
happened to Tempest.
The mysterious attackers.
And the Falmuth's knights...
Hakuro wouldn't have lost
if he hadn't been weakened.
Hakuro lost?!
He was seriously injured,
but he's still alive.
Along with injured Gobta, the two are
currently being treated by Princess Shuna.
I see.
And before leaving, the Falmuth
knights left their warning.
This town is contaminated by monsters!
As the protector of the law of humanity,
we won't acknowledge the existence
of a country of monsters!
Therefore we shall discuss this
with the Western Holy Church
to decide our treatment of this country.
We will return in one week time.
Led by the wise and noble
King Edmaris himself!
We are willing to accept your
unconditional surrender.
If you do not, then in the name of
the One God, we will eradicate all of you!
It's a farce.
Yes, indeed it was.
Your town is a hindrance.
That's why we're going to crush it.
Western Holy Church and Falmuth Kingdom
are conspiring against us from the start.
The Church must've wanted to crush a country
of monsters like ours considering their belief.
But if that's the case, what about
Falmuth kingdom?
Great Rimuru, may I?
At this point, a brand-new trade route
that runs through Tempest has been born
and it has already begun to change
the way merchants distribute their goods.
And so?
Trade route is important.
You can profit a lot
from just imposing tariffs.
Falmuth kingdom is known as
the gateway to the western nations.
They gain a lot from the trades.
If Tempest prospers,
Falmuth will suffer economical loss.
Yes.
A very big loss at that.
I see.
So I have unknowingly
stepped on a tiger's tail.
Mjöllmile.
Yes.
The current condition of Tempest
and the upcoming Falmuth's attack.
Can you deliver the news to
Blumund kingdom immediately?
Of course.
We shall appeal Tempest's rightfulness.
I'm counting on you.
I shall prepare for it now.
Well then, Mjurran.
Can you explain to us why you
decided to meddle with our nation?
Mjurran.
It's okay. I have nothing more to hide.
I'm Mjurran.
Demon Lord Clayman's subordinate.
Eh?!
Demon Lord?!
I see.
So Clayman is the one pulling the string...
I'm used to losing things
I said it like it's someone else's problem
It's a blurry realism
Because it's not about me
The nameless sadness disappears,
warped in a legato-like dream
Will we feel better if we hug each other?
The life which I repeat is a joined miracle
Don't forget me, pass your voice to me
If I were to live for someone's sake
I wish that someone is you
(I'll tell you one more story)
If I can redo this world once again
I will paint that story with love
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
I will tell you one more story
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
Next time, "Hope."