I, the Storm Dragon
Veldora Tempest, have returned!
Anyone who opposes me will die!
Hey, old man.
How did you know that line?
I got bored so I analyzed your memory
and read this thing you call manga!
And also!
My shogi skill is now equal to that of a Meijin.
And since I'm a dragon,
you can even say that I'm Ryuo level!
(Ryuo; Dragon King)
I see, glad that you enjoyed
your time in my stomach.
I just got revived,
aren't you being a bit too cold?
But it was way faster than I expected.
Let me thank you, Rimuru Tempest!
My sworn friend!
Sworn friend? That's old, man.
That's right, did you
receive a Gift as well?
Glad you asked!
Thanks to you, my Unique Skill Inquirer
now became Ultimate skill Faust!
This is the power that embodies
my restless pursuit of knowledge--
As I thought.
My Great Sage also evolved into
Ultimate Skill Raphael, after all.
Yes.
And by analyzing Veldora's residue,
you have obtained Ultimate Skill Veldora.
Also,
after using Unique Skill Unlimited Imprisonment
as a base for ability rearrangement,
Ultimate Skill Uriel has
been successfully acquired.
So now I have a total of four
Ultimate Skills?!
Indeed you have.
So with that in mind,
I'm now invincible!
You can just relax and let me help you out!
O-Okay...
Fate repeats all over again
The voices of my heart say
Time is not enough, it's over
Belief that makes me who I am
Light doesn't fade away
Made my mind up now, it's better
Yeah I know it's not an easy road
Lured by your hands
Even if it rains don't be swayed
Being same as always
Want to feel my destiny
Open my eyes to be braver
Get up now Get up now stronger
I believe in myself
Stand up now Stand up now shouting
I'll never run away
I might lose control
It's a perfect world
Destroy all of it,
in the end it's for our good
Let me shout like flames
(Episode 37: The Visitors)
The outside world
after several hundred years.
The air is delicious!
Say, can you tone down
your enormous aura a little?
You'll scare off those in the town.
Very well, I will try.
Imagine like piling it up inside.
I see, I can do "that."
"That"?
He's releasing his aura like crazy...
How is it?
Oh, looks good.
Your aura is pretty small now.
I learn this from the holy sculpture!
It contains all the world's knowledge!
He must've tried something
he read from a manga.
Hey everyone! Sorry for the wait!
Oh, Great Rimuru! Are you okay?
We were really worried!
There was a sudden sign that
the Storm Dragon Veldora has been revived!
I'm actually going to explain that now.
But before that,
let me introduce this guy to you.
This guy is Veldora!
He's a little shy guy,
but please get along with him!
Eh?
Hey there! I'm not a shy guy in the slightest!
It's simply that there aren't many
people who could actually reach me alive!
Ms. Treyni!
Our guardian deity, Lord Veldora.
We congratulate you on your revival.
Oh, Dryads, it's been a while.
You did well looking after my forest!
Your thanks are more than we deserve.
You've kindly taken us in after we got
separated from the spirit queen.
It is a favor that cannot
be so easily repaid.
Don't mind it.
Eh?! He's the real Storm Dragon?!
You got to be kidding me.
I'll be counting on you to
help out Rimuru from now on.
Because I will stay here with him as well.
Hey, what do you mean by that?!
E-Excuse me...!
What is it?
May we humbly ask what's your
relationship with Great Rimuru?
You want to know?
Indeed, if you kindly!
Very well.
Rimuru is my confidant,
another half of my soul,
and a sworn friend!
Sworn friend!
Stop it! Now you're embarrassing me!
Amazing! So not only he's acquaintance
with Lady Milim but also Lord Veldora?!
Great Rimuru has always been
amazing since the beginning!
It's like anything goes at this point.
It's only natural for My Lord!
Indeed it is.
Incidentally, what is that appearance,
Lord Veldora?
This is a medium Rimuru made for me!
What do you think? Cool, isn't it?
Yes, it is very cool.
You think so? You think so?!
Now it all makes sense!
When you first showed up in front of us,
it was right after Lord Veldora disappeared.
I kept it a secret.
I thought it would take over a hundred
years until I can release Veldora,
and who knows what others
would do if they know about it.
Indeed.
Great Rimuru!
We're already done with
the preparation for the banquet.
Okay.
Everyone!
A lot of things happened,
but let's all forget about it today
and eat, drink, and have fun!
Let's celebrate the fact
that we are all alive right now!
Everyone partied hard that night
like they're in a festival.
We celebrated Veldora's revival
and reunion with those we once lost.
I received a blow!
Then I rotate my body and
deliver a punch from behind!
It's almost done!
Why am I here too?
Please taste Shion's cooking
together with me.
Don't get me involved!
It might miraculously tastes delicious!
Miracle don't happen that easily!
Sorry for the wait!
Enjoy!
Please don't hold back and enjoy!
Shion, do you understand
the definition of cooking?
Of course I do, Great Rimuru!
What do you think?
It looks delicious, right?
Why the onion is not peeled
and still has its roots
and the tomato still has
its stem as well!
Pull them, cut them, peel them,
there are a lot you should do with it!
Well, if I try to process the ingredients...
I might end up cutting it
alongside the building.
Huh? Not the cooking table
but the building?!
Yes.
My sword Gorikimaru can cut really well,
but it's a bit too long.
So you cooked with that?!
Yes!
When I was little,
I thought nothing is impossible.
But it seems like I've mistaken.
Why are you looking so calm?!
Sword is not a cooking utensil,
do you understand?!
Can't you use a kitchen knife
or at least a regular knife?
Gorikimaru is my one and only tool.
Cheating is not an option.
Oh, I see.
And I was thinking to give you
a kitchen knife as a present later.
I've been mistaken!
It's all my misunderstanding!
Gorikimaru said he's okay
with a little bit of cheating!
I see, well, then use kitchen
knife to cook next time, okay?
Yes!
This cooking... well, not sure
if you can even call it one.
If you eat this every day, of course
you'd develop poison resistance.
I've evolved into a Demon Lord!
I shouldn't die just from eating
someone's cooking!
Delicious!
Why does it taste this delicious
despite how terrible it looks?!
Wh-What is happening?!
Actually, when I came back to life,
I acquired a new skill with the Gift I receive.
Hah?!
A Unique Skill called Master Chef!
Master....
...Chef?
With this skill, whatever I cook
will taste just as I want it to be.
I-I see, thank goodness.
Don't you think so, Benimaru?
Yes.
Now I can go through this without dying.
Well then, let's eat!
Yes!
It looks terrible, but it does taste good.
-Good.
-Yes, yes it is!
It looks terrible, though!
Feel free to ask for seconds!
-We have enough!
-Eh?!
We learned something important that day.
That look of the food is also important.
Everyone, I'm sure you already know him,
but let me introduce him once again.
This man is Diablo, he saved
me when I was in trouble.
He's a newcomer,
but he's quite strong and dependable.
So I'll have him work
as my second secretary.
I wish you all can get along with him.
I'll greatly appreciate your further
guidance and encouragement.
Everyone, nice to be with you.
Teach him the ropes for me.
Understood.
-And Gabiru.
-Yes!
The development division is
in your care starting today.
It'll only be for the time being,
but now you're an executive.
-Eh?!
-I'll be counting on you.
I promise you that I, Gabiru, shall
give it my all to fulfill my duty!
Good.
So now I would like to tell
you guys my plan going forward.
It also has to do with the
Three Beastketeers and Youm,
so I want you guys to listen too.
We will follow whatever you say, Mister.
It has something to do with
rescuing Great Carrion, I believe?
I had decided to become a Demon Lord.
Yes!
Like I said, a Demon Lord.
Demon Lord...
And you've became one.
No, I mean I'm planning to announce
to the world that I'm also a Demon Lord.
Oh, so you mean you want to pick
a fight with the other Demon Lords?
Yes, precisely!
To other Demon Lords,
but to be precise...
Clayman.
I see.
So you're planning to take
his Demon Lord position.
Interesting.
That's right.
The one behind this whole thing
is Demon Lord Clayman.
I have no intention to forgive Clayman.
So I told everyone my plan.
The clean-up of Falmuth Kingdom.
The need to check
the Western Holy Church's movement.
And the Demon Lord Clayman's rescue we
promised with people from Animal Kingdom.
-Rigurd.
-Yes!
You handle the negotiation
with the western countries.
My pleasure!
Just leave it to me, Great Rimuru!
-Benimaru.
-Yes!
Compile a report of
everyone's evolution changes.
To crush Clayman with full force,
we need to know how much power we have.
Understood, Great Rimuru.
-Shion.
-Yes!
Go interrogate the POWs.
Leave it to me, Great Rimuru.
Listen, don't overdo it, okay?
Rest assured.
That would be great, though...
Youm, Mjurran.
Yes?
Help Shion for me.
Get as much inside information
about Falmuth from them.
Let's snatch their country!
Just leave it to me, Mister.
It'll be my country, after all.
The Three Beastketeers, I like to
request your cooperation, as well.
It will be our greatest pleasure,
Lord of the Jura forest.
Just say anything,
we will follow every of your command.
Okay.
Take a rest and build your strength
for the decisive battle to come!
-Yes, sir.
-Yeah!
Mr. Rimuru!
We've arrived in accordance with
the Blumund and Tempest security treaty!
Fuze!
I saw many have fallen
throughout the town.
Darn Falmuth, how dare they...!
Eh? Well, they're not lying dead,
they're just sleeping--
It's not much but I brought
in 50 fully armed men.
All of them are fully prepared.
It seems like Falmuth's
main army hasn't arrived.
The king of Blumund promised me
that he'll send his knights--
Ah, Fuze, please pause for a moment.
Oh, my apology.
-Do you already have a strategy planned?
-Well, actually...
A strategy...
Well, rather than a strategy...
Is it something to keep secret from us?
It's not about that.
You see, Fuze.
We appreciate your help,
but it's already over.
Huh? Over? What do you mean?
What just ended?
Umm, I'm not sure how to say this.
In short, to put it simply,
I killed all of them already.
Killed what?
The entire Falmuth army!
All of them are already dead! Hahaha!
I understand what you feel.
Why don't you go to the hot spring
and rest for now? Okay?
Take the soldiers to the inn
and have them relax.
They went all the trouble to come here,
so be kind to them.
-Yes!
-C'mon, let's go.
W-Wait, can we at least talk a bit--
Nn? Another visitor?
Visitor?
Not to mention...
Report. 30 mounted troops
approaching confirmed.
They are led by
the king of Armed Nation of Dwargon.
Individual Gazel Dwargon confirmed.
-Hey, Ms. Raphael.
-Yes?
It's a pain to hear reports every time
someone comes, can you please just brief it?
Brief it?
Just tell me when something
hostile approaches, okay?
Understood.
It's been a while, Rimuru.
I heard you've become a Demon Lord.
Yeah, a lot happened.
To be frank, it's a hassle.
But we're doing a meeting to
discuss what to do from now on.
Perfect timing.
Let me participate in that meeting.
What?
Since when?! My Universal Detect
didn't detect them?!
Report.
No clear hostility was detected
from that group.
Ah, because I said it
was a pain a while ago.
Hmph.
I'm sorry! I'll be counting on
your report from now on as well!
Okay, Ms. Raphael?
Who are you people?
Well, well, if this isn't
the underground dweller.
Nonetheless, the emperor himself.
This is surprising.
To find a coward like you trying
to side with a Demon Lord.
Ah, it's you.
The descendant of silly elves,
obsessed with high places.
What makes you leave your homeland
embraced by the sacred tree?
No.
That body...
If I guess correctly...
Yeah, it's artificial human.
Created with a homunculus.
One ought to be cautious when
trying to approach a Demon Lord.
Oh, a successful homunculus
indistinguishable from a human.
Maybe I should ask them to
teach me how to make one.
They're envoys from
the Sorcerous Dynasty of Thalion.
You're still the same as always, Elalude.
Same goes for you, Gazel.
So, this person over here...
Ah!
Hello, nice to meet you.
I'm Rimuru, the lord of this forest.
Let's get along--
So it's you?!
You bastard! Are you the Demon Lord
who bewitched my daughter?!
Nn? Eh? Eh?!
You better be prepared!
'O flame, burn, explode, rage.
Gather and burst, tyrannize everything--
Hey, what is this old man
doing all of the sudden!?
Report. That is a high-level
fire explosion magic formula.
Why is he doing that so suddenly?!
'O flame, burn, explode, rage.
Gather and burst, tyrannize everything--
You giant moron!
Hey, Papa! What are you here for?!
Ah, Eren-chan! You're safe!
Of course I'm safe!
I came here out of my own will!
Well... Sorry about that.
I got a report that my daughter was
kidnapped by a Demon Lord,
so I couldn't resist but to
hurry my way here.
Could't resist my ass.
You're as overly doting as ever, Elalude.
I'm not overly doting.
Eren-chan is cute, so it can't be helped.
In general, that's what you call...
No, whatever I say to you,
it's pointless.
Mr. Rimuru, this person is my father,
the archduke of the Sorcerous
Dynasty of Thalion. Elalude Grimwalt.
Lord of the Great Forest of Jura
and the leader of monsters.
Like what my daughter Elyune just told you,
My name is Elalude Grimwalt.
Please call me Elalude.
I knew her parents are noble,
but not even I expect it'd
be someone this important.
So did you come all the way
here just to inquire about Eren?
Of course not.
Thought so.
I want to ascertain with my own eyes.
Just what kind of person is the one
who my daughter has grown so fond of.
And if you don't mind,
I'll also join your meeting today.
Why do people like them keep
coming up here like this?
With that, the important meeting to determine
Tempest's next movement begins.
The more you got hurt
That seed of hope
You plant on both of your hand
Will surely bloom someday
Whatever it is,
it doesn't have to last forever
As long it makes you smile
To find the meaning behind
that fleeting moment
Let's go on an journey
Together
I ride on that momentary whirlwind
Above the shadow you cast
Reincarnate
The full bloom flower will paint
color on this dreary world
If you were reincarnated
I'd be with you wherever you go
Our souls are connected
I'll always by your side
Next time, "Man-and-Monster Summit."