Tempest successfully established relation with the Sorcerous Dynasty of Thalion.
After Blumund and Dwargon,
that makes it our third allied human nation.
With that, the long meeting between humans and monsters comes to an end...
...or so we thought.
Come to think of it, what made she come here anyway?
If I remember correctly...
It's the golem I made as a replacement for the one I destroyed, isn't it?
Congratulation on your evolution to a Demon Lord.
Thanks. Good to see you doing well.
Thank you for your kind words.
Please keep listening to Ramiris, unless she starts giving crazy orders.
Understood.
I promise I will not betray your expectation.
By the way, what brings you two here?
Lady Ramiris, now is not the time to laze around.
We must inform Lord Rimuru of the news.
Shut up, I'm very busy right now.
Please recall your goal coming here.
I told you! I just had a fateful encounter!
I must find out which suitor will the heroine choose in this wonderful book they call manga!
Hey, Ramiris!
If you don't want me to spoil it for you,
tell me why you came here already!
Yes, sir!
I'll say it one more time.
This country...
Tempest will be destroyed!
Fate repeats all over again
The voices of my heart say
Time is not enough, it's over
Belief that makes me who I am
Light doesn't fade away
Made my mind up now, it's better
Yeah I know it's not an easy road
Lured by your hands
Even if it rains don't be swayed
Being same as always
Want to feel my destiny
Open my eyes to be braver
Get up now Get up now stronger
I believe in myself
Stand up now Stand up now shouting
I'll never run away
I might lose control
It's a perfect world
Destroy all of it, in the end it's for our good
Let me shout like flames
(Episode 40: The Congress Dances)
Shocked? (Episode 40: The Congress Dances)
No, we're already done with that. (Episode 40: The Congress Dances)
That said, I don't want Tempest to be destroyed.
That's why I came all the way here to tell you that.
You better thank me!
But why will we be destroyed, anyway?
Stop panicking and calm down!
Listen, there is an order to things, okay?
We're not really panicking, though.
It was Demon Lord Clayman's proposal.
Clayman?!
To launch the Walpurgis!
So what is Walpurgis?
The banquet of the Demon Lords.
A special meeting of all the Demon Lords!
That is Walpurgis.
I've read about it in the old books.
Once, all the Demon Lords came together and waged an epic battle.
Battle?
The Western Holy Church named the day of their meeting as Walpurgis.
So Demon Lords gathered to declare war on something?
No! Do I look like I have that much free time?
Why would I want wars and other annoying stuff like that?
You looked like you have a lot of free time, though.
Just to be clear, we had Walpurgis every once in a while.
It's basically a place for the Demon Lords to come together
for a tea and talk about what happened lately.
It's not like we always talk about war or anything like that.
Then why would Tempest be destroyed over a tea party?
That's not it.
The problem is not the meeting itself, but the topic.
Topic?
We launch Walpurgis when at least three Demon Lords agree to hold one.
This time two people agreed to Clayman's Walpurgis request.
Frey and Milim.
Milim?
Frey...
The topic is "New force has been born in the Great Forest of Jura."
"And their leader assumed the title of Demon Lord."
So you declared yourself a Demon Lord?
I did not regret it one bit.
Well, it's not weird coming from you.
I'm sure you'll face a lot of trouble, but with all the power you've got,
it should work out for you.
So Clayman's goal is to punish me for it?
In our line of work, we don't really care who wants to punish who.
Line of work?
There is a more pressing matter for Walpurgis this time.
It is about Demon Lord Carrion's betrayal.
What do you mean by that?
Who are you people?
They're the Three Beastketeers, warriors who serve Carrion.
Anyway, don't complain to me. I'm not the one saying it.
So what betrayal did they claim that Great Carrion has committed?
He broke the non-aggression treaty on the Great Forest of Jura
and told you that this Majin named Mjurran is actually Clayman's underling, right?
So he's saying I killed Mjurran?
Is he trying to suppress the Forest of Jura?
How can you be so calm? This is a big deal!
I heard Milim took Carrion down
and Clayman already dispatched his Majin army!
Dispatched? So he already made his move?
Clayman is shrewder than I thought.
I told you! This is nothing to be so calm about!
Calm down.
I didn't even kill Mjurran to begin with.
What do you mean?
Clayman is saying some nonsense.
Can you prove that?
Umm, Demon Lord Ramiris.
I am the Majin servant who was allegedly killed.
Eh?
I am Mjurran.
Huh?
Now I get it!
Clayman is the real culprit, isn't he?!
Clayman, how dare he tried to fool me!
But no one can deceive me, the Detective Ramiris!
I am older and smarter than I look! That is me, the Queen of Spirits!
In the name of my grandma!
Say something! Who are you calling grandma, that's rude!
She clearly got influenced by something.
Say, Ramiris. I want to ask you something.
What? Just ask Detective Ramiris and she'll crack the case!
Clayman took the bait I set with Mjurran's fake death and made his move.
How do you think the other Demon Lords will react to this?
Huh? How should I know?
They told me what we'll talk about during the party, that's all.
So when is this Walpurgis? Do you know the exact date and time?
Let's see...
One... two... three days from now, on the night of the new moon.
So soon.
It's gonna be hard to crush Clayman in just three days.
That means the showdown will have to wait until after Walpurgis.
So why'd you come all the way here to tell us?
Well, if you get killed...
Who knows what will happen to my precious Beretta?
Thank you very much for worrying about me.
I've decided to take your side, that's why I'm here!
I'm also gonna build an entrance to my labyrinth here. It's okay, right?
No, it's not okay!
What's the big deal? Don't mind the small stuff!
I mind it and you should too!
Well, back to reading.
Hey!
In the end, it seemed the meeting will continue.
So we decided to take a rest first.
That tickles!
Stop it!
I can wash myself!
There's nothing to hold back, Lady Ramiris.
Yes! Please let us help you wash your body!
Is there any place that itches?
Let me wash you this time.
Trya came too?
Sounds like they're having so much fun over there.
I should've gone there instead.
This sure feels good.
Yeah, it heals my body and soul.
Actually, can you even feel this with your homonculus body?
Lil' Eren! How is the bath?!
What a shy girl.
By the way, Sir Rimuru.
What is it?
I believe having a direct highway connecting our nations
would make it easier for travel.
What do you think?
Is he asking us to make the highway?
Don't you think you're asking a bit too much, Erald?
Didn't he also left the highway work to Dwarf Kingdom on us?
I'm okay with Sir Rimuru telling me that, but I don't want to hear that from you!
Precisely!
Let's see. I understand where you're coming from.
I'm fine with taking on the work to build the highway.
However.
Yes?
I want you to handle the highway maintenance and inn management.
And of course, I'll be taking toll taxes on top of the expenses for it.
I see.
That is reasonable demand.
Then I request a chance to negotiate on the toll tax once every several years.
Okay, let's go with that!
So casual!
Good grief, brazen to say the least.
I told you I don't want to hear that from you!
Then it's decided!
Won't the water make you rust?
That should be everyone.
Oh you! What are you doing? What's the meaning of this?!
What do you mean?
The Dryads are giving me really good treatment!
What's the meaning of this?!
Isn't that great?
It is great!
Really great!
So Rimuru! I've decided to live here!
Hey, don't decide that on your own!
Remember, the Dryads are busy managing things in the forest.
They don't live with you anymore, and they can't spend all day taking care of you.
Stingy! Stingy! Stingy!
What's the big deal?
If anything happens, this strong gal Ramiris will help you out of it!
Are you serious?
Lord Rimuru, we promise to take care of Lord Ramiris.
We do hope you will think about it in a positive light.
If you would be so kind.
All right. I will think about it.
Really?!
Rimuru my boy! That's what I'm talking about!
Well then, please enjoy the food.
We can talk while we eat.
Here you go.
Delicious.
This is exquisite!
Bon appetit!
I'm sure everyone is already tired from all the meeting,
but please bear with it.
By the way, Shion.
I heard you already questioned the POWs.
Did they give anything useful?
Of course they did, Great Rimuru!
Well...
Questioning? Interrogation?
Either way, they did tell us some stuff, Mister Rimuru.
Yes, they did.
But that was no questioning.
I'm not sure if you can even call it an interrogation.
First off, Ed...
Ednoyol?
-Ed... -You mean King Edmaris?
Yes. King Edmaris had apparently made contact with a merchant.
That merchant brought him stuff like silken fabrics from our nation
and whetted his appetite for conquest.
He feared that trade would drift over to our nation in the future,
which led to his actions in this incident.
Do you know who this merchant is?
Some black-market dealer?
We still don't know. I apologize.
That's fine.
And what about the Western Holy Church?
Ah yes!
We've identified the mastermind!
His name was...
Erm, the core of it all is...
Niconico Pul...
According to Archbishop Reyhiem,
The core of it all was Cardinal Nicolaus Speltus.
Yes!
The Cardinal was planning to destroy this nation as an "enemy of god."
So he said.
I see.
Archbishop Reyhiem wanted the glory for defeating the enemy of god,
so he could earn extra clout against the central authorities?
If they were still planning at the time,
then maybe we can still negotiate with the Western Holy Church.
How about I give them some nudge?
Dwargon will also advertize our lively trade relationship with Tempest.
Then Thalion will officially declare their relations with Tempest to the world.
If we can get the attention of other nations,
I'm sure the Western Holy Church will have a hard time making a move.
Yes, I'll be counting on you.
Just leave it to me.
Thank you for the food!
Well then.
So Youm will take those three prisoners out
and make it look like a triumphal return.
Wait.
King Edmaris, Archbishop Reyhiem...
Who's the remaining one?
That terribly frightened man?
The last man survived, huh.
If I had to guess, it's the captain of the knights, Folgen perhaps?
It was you who caught him, right?
What kind of guy was he?
Do you think it'll be okay if we let him out?
He was nothing but a minnow, incapable of being a problem at all.
He does appear to be quite well-versed in magic for a human.
So he's a magician?
If so, maybe not Folgen, then.
What is his name?
Ramen!
Ramen, huh.
Come to think of it, I haven't had ramen in years.
Was there a magician named Ramen in Falmuth?
Speaking of magic, there's also that Majin Razen in Falmuth.
Eh?
The Champion Razen?
He's a man we must not forget in this matter.
Eh?
The man known as the guardian of Falmuth and among the most intelligent of Majin.
The man who mastered the way of magic.
I've always wanted a chance to fight him.
Well, I'm sure we'd win in close-quarter combat.
But he's surely not a human to be taken lightly.
Shion, are you certain the man we have is named Ramen?
W-Well, probably...
But he's just a young man!
He was one of the people who attacked this town!
Certainly not the magician everyone is talking about!
What's happening?
Report.
It is possible to switch bodies using spiritual magic-type technique.
Eh? Then that means this Ramen guy...
E-Ermm...
It's Razen.
The prisoner's name.
Bingo.
So you captured the Champion who supported Falmuth for centuries...
He was one of the rare humans who was equal or superior to me as a wizard.
And he took down such a man with ease?
He is powerful, no doubt.
All right, Youm.
Y-Yeah?
I want you to take King Edmaris, Archbishop Reyhiem, and Razen
and do something with them for me.
So take Diablo with you.
We will start a war against Clayman.
And I'll have Veldora stay here to protect the town.
So I was wondering who should I have to support Youm.
You're perfect fit!
I'm counting on you.
Understood, Great Rimuru.
This job might take several years, so I hope you can be patient.
Not a problem, sir.
I shall go and finish it as soon as possible.
You sure are confident, we're talking about destroying a country here.
But it is precisely why I can leave it to him with confidence.
Well then, about our upcoming war against Clayman.
Thanks to Ramiris's report, we now know that he's targeting me.
Wonderfully done, Lady Ramiris!
Soei.
Yes, sir.
Tell me about Clayman's army.
His army...
Their numbers are roughly 30,000.
They're currently organizing their forces at Milim's domain.
30,000 huh.
It's still a manageable number.
The one leading the army doesn't seem to be Clayman himself, however.
Oh?
In terms of magicule capacity, the one with the highest amount would be...
Is this guy the commander?
He's Yamza, the Middle Finger.
Middle Finger?
Yes.
The especially strong ones among Clayman's subordinate are known as the Five Fingers.
Yamza, the Middle Finger.
Adalman, the Pointer Finger.
Nine-Head, the Thumb.
Pirone, the Little Finger.
I used to be the Ring Finger.
Clayman had granted him a magic sword with the power to freeze its target.
Which made him known as the Frozen Swordmage.
The Frozen Swordmage...
He's a cruel, unfair, and merciless man.
But a regrettably talented one.
He willingly swore his loyalty to Clayman,
and we never did get on well for that.
He's the strongest Majin among the Five Fingers.
I see.
But it doesn't seem like we need to be wary of him.
Clayman is a cautious man.
He must've known that the Animal Kingdom's Brigade gathered in this town.
If he wants to fight us, this force is too weak.
It is odd indeed.
Yeah, that's right.
Could Clayman be aiming at something besides this town?
I see. That might be true.
We all thought he would be aiming for Tempest next.
But if that's not the case...
The Animal Kingdom?
So they're marching for Eurazania?!
But Milim already took down the capital.
There is nothing but refugees left in the surrounding town and village.
What would his goal be?
Answer.
It is predicted that Demon Lord Clayman
seeks to awaken himself to become a True Demon Lord.
However, his method is crude and based on imprecise theory.
He is likely aiming to hunt down all remaining life
in the Animal Kingdom of Eurazania.
He's likely aiming to awaken himself into a True Demon Lord
by killing the remaining refugees.
Clayman must've known that us Three Beastketeers and main Carrion's army
are taking refuge in this town.
So it's the perfect opportunity to trample The Animal Kingdom.
We believe Clayman's army will arrive at Eurazania in two days.
Dammit! We won't make it in time even if we head there now!
So he took the first step ahead of us.
Clayman...
The more you got hurt
That seed of hope
You plant on both of your hand
Will surely bloom someday
Whatever it is, it doesn't have to last forever
As long as it makes you smile
To find the meaning behind that fleeting moment
Let's go on a journey
Together
I ride on that momentary whirlwind
Above the shadow you cast
Reincarnate
The full bloom flower will paint color on this dreary world
If you were reincarnated
I'd be with you wherever you go
Our souls are connected
I'll always by your side
Next time, "The Eve of Battle."