[Script Info]
Title:11 eyes 05 BD
Original Script:sumisora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14C93241,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPMaruMoji-W3,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00004080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCN,華康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00004080,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,8,1
Style: EDJP,DFPMaruMoji-W3,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: EDCN,華康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,8,1
Style: TITLE,宋体,28,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,85,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,5,1
Style: Fs,黑体,30,&H003B50E1,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,90,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: POS,方正卡通_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00004080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,8,1
Style: staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,5,1
Style: las,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------OP------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.78,0:00:44.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}歪んだ覚醒の中で　赤き夜が目を醒ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.39,0:00:53.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}黒き闇永遠の眠り　月影に怯えてる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.96,0:01:03.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}炎が包み込んでく　世界を焼き尽くしても
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.92,0:01:08.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈りだけは絶やさずに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.15,0:01:14.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}友と交わした明日のため
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.61,0:01:20.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}溢れる涙　連声に響け
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.39,0:01:24.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}忘却の剣へと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.92,0:01:34.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}刹那さに溺れてゆく魂　浮遊して往く光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.50,0:01:38.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}空を切り裂いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.04,0:01:47.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}此の世界　希望を抱いて逝こう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.78,0:00:44.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如若赤夜蘇生於扭曲的覺醒之中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.39,0:00:53.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}黑暗與永眠  都在月影下畏縮不前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.96,0:01:03.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}就算火炎席捲世間  燃盡一切
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.92,0:01:08.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}唯有祈願始終不斷
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.15,0:01:14.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}為了與摯友相約的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.61,0:01:20.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}潸然淚聲  響徹連城
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.39,0:01:24.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}向著忘卻之劍
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.92,0:01:34.37,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}為時間短暫而墮落的靈魂  浮游的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.50,0:01:38.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}斬破蒼天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.04,0:01:47.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在這世界之中  懷抱希望而前
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------ED-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.37,0:22:55.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}世界を崩すPieceはとても軽く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.74,0:23:05.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}日々を過す片隅　ずっと潜んでる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.33,0:23:14.15,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}差し出された諸刃に映るのは今は悲しげな君の瞳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.51,0:23:21.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}護るものはただ一つだけ...そう君さ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.98,0:23:31.61,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}溢れ出す　想いを放った贖罪の夜も愛しくなる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.72,0:23:40.04,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}どんな深い闇も僕らを一つに結ぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.18,0:23:45.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奮い立て　二度と振り向かず
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.32,0:23:49.69,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕らその明日のため
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.98,0:23:56.25,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}I Believe...　ぎゅっと抱きしめた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.61,0:24:02.36,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}まだ見えぬその真実
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.37,0:22:55.74,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}毀滅世界的因子靜靜地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.74,0:23:05.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}潛藏在  歲月的角落間
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.33,0:23:14.15,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雙刃劍映出的  是你此刻憂傷的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.51,0:23:21.11,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想要守護的唯有一物  就是你的笑顏
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.98,0:23:31.61,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}將滿溢的相思傳達  贖罪的夜晚也變得惹人愛憐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.72,0:23:40.04,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}無論黑暗有多麼深邃  我們都一體同心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.18,0:23:45.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不再回頭  不再見那顫抖的雙手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.32,0:23:49.69,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}為了我們的明天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.98,0:23:56.25,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因為我相信  那在我懷中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.61,0:24:02.36,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}還未知曉的真實
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-------------TEXT--------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:04.73,las,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,200)\pos(323,210)}赤夜——它唐突地降臨了。
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.21,0:00:08.52,las,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,200)\pos(323,210)}既是現實又是虛幻，不同時空的闇世界。
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.05,0:00:12.31,las,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,200)\pos(323,210)}墮落於其中的少年少女被稱為"碎片"，並受到異型的黑騎士襲擊他們。
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.80,0:00:16.02,las,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,200)\pos(323,210)}為什麼會是他們，到底發生了什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.64,0:00:19.40,las,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,0)\pos(323,210)}在惡夢的盡頭，會有答案嗎——？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.58,0:02:27.59,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)}為了朋友和明日
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.54,0:02:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想保護結花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.32,0:02:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想保護…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.89,0:02:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.30,0:02:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好啦  結花她…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.65,0:02:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.27,0:02:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貧血？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.48,0:02:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  只是貧血而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.25,0:02:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.54,0:02:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了沒事的  可香央里她…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.00,0:02:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說你是在教室裡昏倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.22,0:02:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不過沒什麼大礙了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.04,0:02:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微睡一會兒就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.73,0:02:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起這個來  我更擔心驅君你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.43,0:02:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.79,0:02:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那素描簿…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.89,0:03:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那東西到底意味著什麼  到時候自然就會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.60,0:03:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算再怎麼在意也沒辦法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.31,0:03:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在意？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.19,0:03:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.09,0:03:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別對我說謊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.65,0:03:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結花…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.93,0:03:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.97,0:03:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼親熱  不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.58,0:03:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那  那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.93,0:03:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽得人背上癢癢  真是受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.31,0:03:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一點兒都不可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.38,0:03:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.81,0:04:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.29,0:04:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.27,0:04:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒看見前面…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.57,0:04:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賢久前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.75,0:04:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿一包走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.40,0:04:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.39,0:04:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的沒事了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.38,0:04:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  沒問題啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.54,0:04:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水奈瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.79,0:04:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事  彩子老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.35,0:04:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說你是睡眠不足  原因是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.13,0:05:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  算啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.96,0:05:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟你也是個花季少女嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.61,0:05:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過  不好好睡的話可不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.44,0:05:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.32,0:05:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  要是又睡不著了的話  就叫人給你唱搖籃曲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.89,0:05:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？搖籃曲？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.15,0:05:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行嗎  皐月？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.14,0:05:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我唱？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.52,0:05:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電話上唱就好啦  就唱給她聽嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.60,0:05:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我…搖籃曲什麼的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.50,0:05:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一開始是有點不好意思  不過很快就會習慣了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.75,0:05:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前也是這樣的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.22,0:05:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.88,0:05:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彩子老師也唱…  搖籃曲？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.08,0:05:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  很奇怪嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.95,0:05:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.16,0:05:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是給誰唱呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.47,0:05:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.64,0:05:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家小孩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.90,0:05:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你家小孩？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.91,0:05:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師  有小孩呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.42,0:05:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們不也見過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.67,0:05:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那個一點都不可愛的不良少年
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.32,0:05:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大嬸  老規矩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.17,0:06:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們吃驚個什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.59,0:06:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.27,0:06:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  感覺不太搭調？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.05,0:06:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.11,0:06:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也難怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.69,0:06:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為不是親生的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.68,0:06:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要說的話  我就算是養母吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.14,0:06:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,養母…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.60,0:06:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久以前啊  我可是個有點我行我素的摩托車愛好者哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.65,0:06:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我行我素的…  愛好者？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.71,0:06:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  女飆車族嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.22,0:06:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也算…簡單說來就是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.10,0:06:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是  那一夜也發生了很多事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.68,0:06:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被條子追著…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.84,0:06:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.48,0:06:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.47,0:07:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是所謂的流浪兒童吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.51,0:07:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說是小孩  但還是拼命地想活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.25,0:07:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但孩子畢竟還是孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.04,0:07:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時候  我突然想到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.62,0:07:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰來保護這孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.14,0:07:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來那時我也是年少輕狂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.20,0:08:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在可真後悔當初撿了那樣一個包袱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.91,0:08:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流浪兒童…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.55,0:08:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟在孤兒院長大的我們一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.52,0:08:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.64,0:08:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  你們也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.53,0:08:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們就回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.68,0:08:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要叫他給你唱搖籃曲哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.78,0:08:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.07,0:08:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  結花
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.56,0:08:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會給我唱的吧  驅君？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.68,0:08:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  那個嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.89,0:08:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我站住  站住  站住…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.31,0:08:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.13,0:08:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.56,0:08:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別怕嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.24,0:08:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷路的乖貓貓
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.36,0:09:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匡  不注意的話可會很危險的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.87,0:09:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  剛一說就…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.07,0:09:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心  這可是個暴力小貓
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.32,0:09:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵  喵  喵…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.83,0:09:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.43,0:09:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.30,0:09:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.22,0:09:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼消失了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.67,0:09:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般人我不告訴他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.98,0:09:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰來保護這孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.63,0:09:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草壁前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.07,0:09:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.63,0:09:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀  正好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.36,0:10:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天放學以後  也要拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.70,0:10:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劍術啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.18,0:10:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天呢  在那之前  我要給你們介紹一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.20,0:10:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.46,0:10:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  前輩你說過的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.53,0:10:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  她似乎終於下定決心要見你們了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.11,0:10:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君  練劍就等你們見完了面再開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.90,0:10:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那放學之後  考現學部見
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.37,0:10:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  辛苦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.31,0:10:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為  為什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.02,0:10:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  忘記說了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.75,0:10:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賢久前輩從今天起  就成為我們考現學部的一員了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.88,0:10:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.49,0:10:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過是你跟我說能夠隨便山吃海喝  我才來的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.96,0:10:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抹布  抹布  抹布…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.17,0:10:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.37,0:10:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.38,0:11:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.32,0:11:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.34,0:11:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我來晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.25,0:11:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生了什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.71,0:11:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.86,0:11:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得了啦  不得了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.38,0:11:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  現在我向大家介紹一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.27,0:11:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3年級B班的橘菊理同學
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.05,0:11:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊理姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.46,0:11:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.83,0:11:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊  她跟皐月君你的姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.12,0:11:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.01,0:11:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經在無意間見到過了好幾次  每次都心裡七上八下的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.94,0:11:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為長得一模一樣嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.74,0:11:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊理同學她不會說話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.70,0:12:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳朵能聽見聲音  所以別人說的還是能懂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.36,0:12:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要對話的時候  就只能筆談
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.79,0:12:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我想大家應該很快就能適應的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.42,0:12:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.01,0:12:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.49,0:12:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫廣原雪子  請多多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.08,0:12:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊前輩  好豐滿的胸部  真好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.50,0:12:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.58,0:12:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  對啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.14,0:12:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fa do sete o furese en tora
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.31,0:12:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚇了一跳？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.67,0:12:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可還真是嚇了一跳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.46,0:12:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什麼啊  剛才那話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.83,0:12:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的是Fa do sete o furese en tora
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.95,0:12:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外語？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.17,0:12:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的故鄉德拉斯貝尼亞的話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.57,0:12:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是  為了朋友和明日
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.12,0:12:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.03,0:13:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你硬要問怎麼樣  也…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.49,0:13:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是口號了啦  我們的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.02,0:13:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口號？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.17,0:13:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用在「要加油哦」這樣的時候啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.13,0:13:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得還是有的好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.00,0:13:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.23,0:13:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒準還挺不錯的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.05,0:13:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是的說  為了朋友和明日
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.73,0:13:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  好  挺不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.97,0:13:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是的說  就是的說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.57,0:13:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊理前輩  覺得好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.56,0:13:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感謝啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.95,0:13:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是敗給了雪子你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.36,0:13:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了朋友和明日…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.55,0:13:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.09,0:13:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅前輩你也中意嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.78,0:13:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那就大家一起喊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.67,0:13:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備好了嗎  一二…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.26,0:13:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.35,0:13:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼口號啊  又不是三歲小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.23,0:13:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  賢久前輩居然害羞啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.91,0:13:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把他給拉回來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.00,0:13:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別管他啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.75,0:14:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.08,0:14:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.60,0:14:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙不是我們的戰友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.35,0:14:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.47,0:14:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊理學姐她名字跟姐姐一樣  的確讓人有點吃驚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.48,0:14:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過總算不是一個人  放心了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.43,0:14:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在想什麼呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.64,0:14:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了朋友和明日…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.01,0:14:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  明天什麼的  我從來就沒有好好想過
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.80,0:14:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺心裡一緊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.53,0:14:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.33,0:14:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一句很響亮的話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.90,0:14:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了朋友和明日
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.05,0:14:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久沒有見過了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.19,0:14:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久沒有見過  驅君的笑容了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.57,0:14:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得  好高興
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.88,0:14:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結花…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.44,0:15:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.18,0:15:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.85,0:15:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼東西啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.43,0:15:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牆？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.42,0:15:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只針對我嗎…？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.23,0:15:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊理學姐呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.08,0:15:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼一說  是去廁所了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.87,0:15:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去看看就來
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.89,0:15:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草壁前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.67,0:15:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還請指導我練劍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.13,0:15:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君  今天已經很晚了啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.30,0:16:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你過去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.98,0:16:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這兒練？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.14,0:16:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此為止
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.37,0:16:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你腳下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.28,0:16:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什麼時候…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.07,0:16:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踩到了就會滑倒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.61,0:16:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,架勢一旦崩潰  就全盤皆輸了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.15,0:16:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面對敵人  你不過就是隻無頭蒼蠅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.40,0:16:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是現在  迄今為止  你都是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.51,0:16:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「想要保護結花」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.79,0:16:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這信念就橫亙在你的眼前  於是你便不顧周圍的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.36,0:16:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你首先得冷靜下來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.31,0:16:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是之後一切的先決條件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.45,0:16:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心浮氣躁的人  與勝利無緣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.72,0:17:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.02,0:17:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  我們回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.92,0:17:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.34,0:17:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我把那些碎片消滅乾淨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.82,0:17:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得逃出去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.06,0:17:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.36,0:17:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碎片們  我要把你們剁成肉醬
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.64,0:17:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.46,0:17:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.76,0:18:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑哪裡去了呢  菊理前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.62,0:18:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會出事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.04,0:18:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賢久前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.17,0:18:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開門之前可得先敲門哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.16,0:18:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡可是…  女廁所哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.77,0:18:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.00,0:18:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就憑你能打倒我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.32,0:18:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.97,0:18:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連我一根寒毛也傷不到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.42,0:19:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.04,0:19:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就睜大眼睛好好看著  你想要保護的人的下場吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.41,0:19:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後好好感受一下自己的無力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.54,0:19:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…  不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.09,0:19:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別過來…  別…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.38,0:19:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.59,0:19:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你無論怎樣都想先去投胎的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.07,0:19:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就成全你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.28,0:19:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量差距太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.57,0:19:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從正面進攻不可能贏  只會被幹掉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.66,0:19:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…  到底該怎麼做  才能…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.81,0:19:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.68,0:19:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小烏丸天國
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.33,0:19:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你首先得冷靜下來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.56,0:20:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心浮氣躁之人  與勝利無緣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.84,0:20:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  不能慌
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.28,0:20:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須得冷靜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.13,0:20:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？廢物  放馬過來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.03,0:20:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚇破了膽  變得不正常了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.83,0:20:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.44,0:20:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將感情化為力量  只想著這一點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.05,0:20:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將感情…  化為力量…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.77,0:20:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會保護好結花的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.34,0:20:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.53,0:20:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.36,0:20:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然躲過去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.97,0:20:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才那是？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.49,0:20:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此  是這麼一回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.70,0:20:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛…  難不成…  沒這種可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.12,0:21:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種低賤的人類  是沒有可能覺醒的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.67,0:21:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.66,0:21:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的鎧甲…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.76,0:21:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.69,0:21:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這回是伊拉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.28,0:21:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.96,0:21:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.87,0:21:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉澤特  你剛才說什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.41,0:22:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.27,0:22:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅…  驅君…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.14,0:22:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.79,0:22:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.45,0:22:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.85,0:22:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.13,0:22:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說話呀  驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.16,0:22:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驅君
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.88,0:24:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於覺醒了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.55,0:24:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顫抖吧  為自己的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.53,0:24:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那瞳眸給予了你一切的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.78,0:24:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也會奪走你一切的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.38,0:24:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你深愛的世界  深愛的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.17,0:24:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…  你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.18,0:24:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾名維拉德  毀滅之國的王
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.22,0:24:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被劫之眼魅惑之人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.22,0:24:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(265,325)\fs17}AION
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.67,0:24:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.98,0:24:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亂我心者
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.10,0:24:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在惡夢的盡頭
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.55,0:24:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會有答案嗎
