H-Hey.
Nyaruko, I love you!
Nyaruko, I love you! I love you!
Marry me now!
Wha... Wha... Wha...
What?!
Allow me to explain.
Currently, Nyaruko and Mahiro-san are in each other's bodies.
Nyaruko! I love you!
I want to make you mine!
Your silver antenna, your green eyes, everything!
When you crawl up to me,
not even the Twelve Zodiac Temples or the Budokai can scare me!
I can go anywhere if I have you!
If you want me to wear nothing but glasses and an apron,
I'd be happy to—
Ludon Mesa...
Yasaka-kun got rejected pretty hard.
Um, you two.
Could you do that someplace where it won't disrupt your teacher?
Nyaruko-san
Haiyore!
Translation Check
ElyasRay
Timing         Naruto-kun
Editing                 HeavenlyArmed
OP / ED
Silikine      Chojenoe
K-time chout
Karaoke FX
Naruto-kun
Typesetting
Quality Control
ScarletDevil                   SoulSpeed
Encoder
mike332
I don't want to live like this anymore.
There's nothing to be depressed about.
Our future is bright!
Boy, I will not forgive you for confessing your feelings to Nyaruko.
Hey, I'm not the one who confessed.
Let's see... Nyaruko-chan confessed in Mahiro-kun's body.
So if Mahiro-kun apologized in Nyaruko-chan's body, then...
Huh? Wait, what?
This is getting complicated.
It's Isuka! I mean...
Kurei!
I'm worn out to exhaustion.
It's like all my exhaustion has blended together.
I am bayoe~n.
You're what?
Did the extremists get you?
Now I know how people who skip work
for a major RPG release feel.
What?
Even if you decide you'll just play until the next save point,
you end up grinding levels and
staying up until the next morning.
Hey.
The Ruler of Super Time-Space
This is delicious!
I didn't eat or drink anything
while I was absorbed in video games,
so this tastes especially good!
Anyway, what happened to the device
that will return us to our original bodies?
It's currently recharging.
It won't be fully charged until tonight.
We have to stay this way a bit longer, then.
What kind of meat is this?
Which Mahiro-kun am I supposed to love?
Meat! Delicious meat! More meat!
This is fantastic!
That depends on what sort of play you like.
What a difficult question.
I'm not playing any dirty games.
With such an amazing cuisine,
it's a shame the Earth's going to be erased.
Hey,
what did you just say?
In the future I'm from,
Earth does not exist anymore.
The Space Confederation declared Earth a dangerous planet
and destroyed it.
What?!
Why would they do that to Earth?
Even in the Yith's massive database,
there's hardly any record of it.
But...
Now, now. As long as I'm around,
whether they drop a colony or a small planet on us,
I'll blast them away, so don't worry!
I can only worry...
We're going to Yoichi-san's residence?
Yeah, it's rare for him to miss a day like this,
so I thought I should check up on him.
But if I go like this, it'll be all kinds of complicated.
He was absent today, wasn't he?
Huh, ho, hum.
What are you saying?
I just thought the extremists might have
exchanged their consciousness with someone else.
For example, Yoichi-san.
No way a coincidence like that would happen.
I know, right?
Of course.
But when an unremarkable character suddenly falls into the spotlight,
there must be something going on.
Stop. I was really worried, but I didn't say anything.
Yoichi-san is not home.
Why did you follow us?
Kuuko-san was telling me about RPG strategies.
If you walk clockwise with your left hand against the wall,
you will not fall into pit traps.
However, this only works in the
original version, not the remake.
Now I can finally reach the last boss!
Don't you have something better to do?
Huh? What is that?
My Yith Searcher is picking something up!
Yoichi!
He ran!
That's the extremist!
Important characters must be picked up in the first part.
Let's chase him!
Yoichi!
Don't come any closer!
Don't you care what happens to this body?
My name is Isurugi.
I have come to this ancient Earth as a soldier of Yith!
Watch as our greatest wish comes to fruition.
Look.
This device will exchange the minds
of the Earthlings and the Yith!
With this, all of Earth's
entertainment will belong to the Yith!
Creators who excite video sharing sites,
popular artists within illustration communities, all will be ours!
You can't be serious!
I will never allow it!
Stop! That's my body!
Then, Mahiro-san, are you willing
to stain your own fists with blood?
Hasuta, Kuuko, take care of him.
Got it, Mahiro-kun!
This is a good opportunity to make Nyaruko owe me one.
Cthugha and Hastur.
However, I have made my own preparations!
Space CQC jammer!
He blocked our Space CQC.
It is a jammer, after all.
Now I have nothing to fear from you.
I thought this might happen.
That's why I prepared a Space CQC jammer canceler!
They are back.
I have prepared something for that!
Space CQC jammer canceler breaker!
They disappeared again.
Bring it on!
Space CQC jammer canceler breaker eraser!
There they are.
This isn't over yet!
Space CQC jammer canceler breaker eraser confiner!
Space CQC jammer canceler
breaker eraser confiner obstructor!
Space CQC jammer canceler breaker eraser confiner obstructor buster!
Space CQC jammer canceler breaker
eraser confiner obstructor buster closer!
What are you, kids?
I'm out of cartridges!
It seems my Space CQC jammer canceler et cetera has won.
The time has come.
This isn't good.
The Yith's destiny will now become history!
The mind exchange is complete.
Now Earth's entertainment belongs to the Yith.
Comrades!
Isn't it a fine time to invade?
What do you think you're talking about?
Our minds haven't been transplanted.
Hey, wait! That's Yoichi's body!
But it was completed according to the plan...
Isurugi, Isurugi!
That voice!
The chief— no, Mr. President!
President?
Who's that?
The leader and founder of the extremist organization.
I completed the mind exchange device according to your orders,
but it does not seem to have worked.
No, this is fine.
Everything is going according to plan.
What?
According to plan...
you will all...
...die!
Yoichi!
Mr. President?
You created an Earthling annihilation device.
The president of the extremists is only a guise.
I am actually
an agent of the Space Confederation organization.
Space Child Guardian!
Space Child Guardian?
That's right. Foolish humans, lay down and die.
Why are you doing this to Earth?
We are destroying Earth because...
Because?
Because of space wholesomeness laws!
ce Wholesomeness L
Space Wholesomeness Laws
What?
We cannot turn a blind eye to Earth's
anime, manga, and other entertainment.
Elements hidden by light and fog
are visible in the special features,
and figures can be undressed
at their owner's discretion.
Hey...
According to space wholesomeness laws,
Earth's entertainment has been recognized as
an agent promoting sex crimes throughout space.
The entire planet must be punished!
You can't just decide that!
Child Guardian exists...
to protect the future of children and to ensure my retirement into a high profile position!
Looks like you've revealed your true motive.
We have the law on our side!
Kuuko, Hasuta!
The Earth belongs to Mahiro-kun and his friends!
I won't let you kill them!
My and Nyaruko's love nest is here.
Are you talking about my house?
Twinkle.
Isn't the Space CQC jammer active?
Sometimes an alien must fight,
even when she knows she will lose.
Fools! You must really want to die!
How dare you deceive me?!
You have fulfilled your purpose!
Now die already!
Yoichi!
This is Nyaruko's body, after all.
Even though it's me inside, it still moves reasonably well.
Lawless scum!
Wait!
I'm not an Earthling!
Fool! This is what you deserve!
Hey...
Wake up, Nyaruko.
Why are you sleeping?
The entertainment you treasure so much is in trouble.
You said you'd protect my personal life, too.
And yet... this is the state you're in?
Standing in your shoes, I finally understand.
Protecting someone must have been difficult.
I'm sorry for being so mean to you.
Come on...
Wake up, Nyaruko!
Smooch yeah!
I did it! I tasted every last bit of it!
It was...
Super soft!
Your tongue! You put your tongue in, didn't you?!
Why are you alive, anyway?
Because of this.
A black crystal?
It's like a protective charm.
Don't just conveniently drag up old foreshadowing devices like that!
If you were okay, why didn't you wake up right away?
While listening to you confess your feelings,
I started getting hot...
and I ended up giving you a cruel angel's kiss.
That's the kind of bad influence on minors I'm talking about!
Recharge complete!
Sorry it took so long!
Thanks for waiting!
I'm back in my body!
Nyaruko!
Yes!
I'm the chaos that
always crawls up to you with a smile, Nyarlathotep!
You!
Transform.
Why? Your Space CQC should be sealed!
All obstacles are meaningless in the face of our love!
What do you think you're saying?
The truth is, even if I can't use Space CQC,
I can still use my Space CQC enhancer.
You're just pulling stuff out of thin air now...
Such convenient construes are the enemy of the system!
What did you say?
Impossible.
The Space Child Guardian is protected by the law!
Laws are made to be broken!
Um, hello? Planetary defense organization...
Now dance the Rondo Towards Destruction!
That's one case completed!
It's over.
The punchline was terrible again, too.
So, what are you guys going to do?
I will take Isurugi back to the future.
I will leave the rest to the higher ups.
We'll be good as long as we get Yoichi and Kurei back.
Of course you will.
However, I will erase Tamao-san's memory.
See you later.
Den-den-dendrobium bye-bye.
Are they gone?
They must be.
Now that the obstacles are gone...
we can pick up where we left off.
Owie-yith!
I should have saved. There are monsters.
Isuka?
Oh, no! I am just a cute little stuffed animal and...
Wait...
Why do you remember me, Tamao-san?
I thought I erased your memory.
But I remember you.
I'm so clumsy.
I thought you went home.
Well, I wanted to see what happened next in the game.
I mean, I wanted to thank you.
Thank me?
Thank you for everything.
Thanks to you, I was able to solve the case.
I don't remember much, but you're welcome.
You're not mad I borrowed your body?
Having an alien stay in your body is a valuable experience.
Tamao-san, you're such a good person,
but I have to erase all your memories.
I see. Even though we became friends...
I learned a lot about you while I was borrowing your body.
Your worries, and the person you cannot admit you love...
Stop!
You know all of that?
Yes. And I was with him the whole time, so...
Don't tell anyone!
Understood!
I will carry your secret with me into the future!
Tamao-san, I will be cheering for you from the distant future.
It will be all right.
I'm sure something good will happen to you soon.
Good morning, Yasaka-kun.
Morning, Yoichi.
Thank goodness,
my life is back to normal.
Hey, I thought she rejected him.
Why are they still coming to school together?
It's not back to normal!
Yasaka Mahiro, could you come to the faculty office
and explain to me what happened yesterday?
If you just say you're under a lot of stress, it won't be a big deal.
My quiet, ordinary life...
Where did it go?
Kurei Tamao here!
I'm Yoichi Takehiko!
It seems three cute little sisters are going to come rolling in.
Oh? Why do I feel like I'm going to be the star?
No, it's just your imagination.
Besides, nothing's coming our way.
You're right.
The next episode is "Lost Girl From The Stars."
I wish you would listen to Yasaka-kun.