I worked as a salaryman
for a toxic company,
until I reincarnated...
in a crazy world where everything is
dropped by monsters in dungeons.
In my new life, I'm level 1,
but I have a unique skill
that puts all of my drop rates at rank S.
And today I'm facing off against
a really scary monster and...
Emily?!
MY UNIQUE SKILL MAKES ME OP EVEN AT LEVEL 1
KILL ALL THE LITTLE BLACK THINGS
Yoda?!
Don't underestimate my skill!
It's over...
Yes, it is!
What a cheeky low-level.
- Thank you!
- That was amazing!
What a man!
You're the town hero!
I got a weapon that shouldn't
exist in this world
from a stray, a monster that's
not supposed to drop anything.
LUCK, DEXTERITY, SPEED, WILL,
INTELLIGENCE, VITALITY, STRENGTH, MP, HP
I'm still at level 1,
RYOTA: LEVEL, STATUS
but thanks to the seeds I find here,
my abilities are steadily improving.
NIHONIUM LEVEL 2
Okay...
Let's see if this thing's
gonna be of any use.
Yeah, it's definitely a gun.
It works on monsters
just the way it should.
I wonder how I'm supposed
to get more bullets.
Will they drop from strays, too?
I'll have to use them
sparingly until I know.
Yoda!
Your weapon is amazing, Yoda.
I've never seen anything like it.
Yeah, and my strength is
at rank B now because of it.
Let's check out the next level later.
Sure!
As my stats increase,
so does the range of places I can go.
It feels good knowing
there's something I can do!
She's not coming.
So she isn't.
Well, I guess Eve has stuff to do, too.
She can't just show up every day.
We'll save these carrots for her,
just in case.
Yeah. She might still
show up at the house.
Anyway, the lunches you make
are still the best, Emily!
Have some tea, too.
Thanks.
How I put this...
It's so relaxing.
Have you been down here before?
No.
I only know the names
of the monsters here and what they drop.
The monsters are cockroslimes,
and they drop pumpkins.
Slimes again?
But I look forward to meals
made with pumpkins.
So those are cockroslimes?
I bet girls would run away
screaming from these.
I mean, they look just like cockroa—
E-Emily, I don't think you
needed to go that hard...
What are you talking about, Yoda?
The tragedy will only grow
more widespread if I don't.
Not relaxing anymore!
I can't allow any to escape.
Um... Emily?
Hey, a drop.
I did it!
Well, we killed the cockroslimes.
Let's go up and get more carrots.
Okay!
We gotta get out of here, fast.
I don't want to see
that scary version of Emily again.
For every one you see...
you have to assume there are
thirty more you can't see!
Yoda... I might never regain my humanity!
Don't be hasty!
Let me do it!
Just let me take care of everything here!
I'm begging you!
Please let me take care of this!
I can't miss a single shot!
Have I ever concentrated so intently
on anything in all my life?
No... I haven't.
They're so big!
You've done it again, Yoda!
Yeah, but we can't take all these upstairs.
Those things will spawn again
if we stay here.
Do you want to kill them again?
O-Okay, just calm down for a minute...
Low-Level, I'm here for today's carrots.
Help yourself.
I-I'm saved...
Thank you as always!
We'll bring some more later.
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Aw, man.
I guess some animal got to them.
We can't sell these.
They're here...
But how?! We're outside the dungeon!
I have lived my entire life
for this moment.
You're getting a little intense there!
I'll do it! I'll kill them, okay?!
Give her back!
Give me my Emily back!
I did it. I killed them all.
I'm sorry.
I guess I turn into someone else
when I see those things.
It's not your fault, Emily.
You didn't know?
If you leave dropped items behind
where there are no people around,
monsters spawn around them.
I think Emily told me something like that
when the gorilla showed up,
but it didn't even register.
Yeah, and they ruined
the last of our pumpkins.
Sorry. I know you were waiting for them.
No problem.
We're still open, anyway.
We will be closing soon, though.
- So it's possible to force strays to spawn?
- Um, Ryota, if you don't mind...
- That means...
Would you like to g-g-go out for dinner?
I found a great restaurant,
- and I thought—
- Thanks, Erza!
I'll be back!
What?!
Once I get an idea,
I have to act on it right away.
I got this carrot in Telulu earlier.
Is this gonna work?
You took the bait?!
Hey! That carrot—
This carrot is for a rabbit!
Even if Heaven and Earth switch places,
I won't give it up!
It's the longest sentence I've heard
you say, and it was to say that?!
Starting over...
Good thing I got so many of these.
I can't believe she took
nine out of ten, though...
Here we go!
It worked!
They say strays don't drop anything,
but for me...
Hang on...
What if I did this with those guys?
Boing.
Emily!
NIHONIUM LEVEL 1
RYOTA'S MAX HP INCREASED BY 0.
Ryota's max HP increased by 0.
No matter how many times I try,
they just vanish.
Turning monsters with no drops
into strays, then killing them...
With my unique skill,
something interesting
is about to happen...
RYOTA'S MAX HP INCREASED BY 0.
Ryota's max HP increased by 0.
Since my HP's already maxed out,
I thought I'd be able to carry the seeds back
without consuming them...
But I guess that won't work.
I'll just meet up with Emily in Telulu
and work hard to hunt down
today's supply of drops.
Damn! It'll turn into a stray!
No, actually, that's fine!
Huh?
Monsters disappear
if they leave a dungeon.
We'd have strays all over
the place otherwise.
So that's how it works.
Even within a dungeon, they disappear
if they enter a different floor.
That's why there's only one type
of monster on each floor.
I see.
You're a very talented adventurer,
but there's a surprising
amount you don't know.
Still, I think the contrast is...
k-kind of charming... or...
Thanks, Erza!
Huh?!
I'll be back!
Darn it!
Ryota, you jerk!
If my guess is right,
this should work.
There's one!
Just like before...
I have just a moment before it disappears.
If I kill it within that moment...
It worked!
If I kill it outside its floor,
it should count as a stray!
Ryota acquired a freezing bullet.
A freezing bullet?
This is incredible!
Depending on how I use them,
I could do a lot with these!
Now, Emily!
Got it!
Freeze it in place,
then hit it with a powerful attack.
It's a combo often used in games,
and it looks like we can do it here, too.
Yoda, that was amazing.
What was...
What was that, exactly?
Just what it looked like.
A bullet that freezes whatever it hits.
It takes time to get them, though,
so I can't fire a lot in succession.
They're quite valuable.
Yeah. So I'll stick with the regular bullets
unless it's an emergency.
You can just finish off the ones I miss.
Understood!
Looks like it's rained recently.
Watch your step.
Same to you.
I will.
Get it up here already!
Don't be crazy!
- You fool!
- Are they fighting?
Say what?!
Excuse me.
We'd like to get past.
Oh, you'll do.
Pull that cargo up for me.
This fool will pay you.
What?!
What in the...
Cargo?
Do you mean that?
Uh... If someone could drop
a rope to climb down,
I could probably get it,
though it wouldn't be easy...
Don't!
It's been quite a while since it fell.
It might turn into a stray, then!
That thing's loaded with drops
from some troublesome monsters.
We have to burn it up with magic
while we still can.
No!
Hey, watch it!
That perfume will sell for a fortune!
Do you have any idea how many adventurers
I hired to collect that much of it?!
Do you think I care?!
Besides, you're the one who dropped it!
The rain made you slip and lose it!
Well, you... are fired!
Huh?!
That's one very powerful old man!
I was too late.
What's that?
A monster called a Femini.
It doesn't have its own body.
It possesses a human and uses it
as a nursery to propagate itself.
That's not good!
It worked!
Take him and run!
Huh?
Hey! What are you gonna do?!
If I don't do something, Femini are
gonna pop out in all directions.
If I go down there and become a nursery,
I can buy time while you gather
an army in town.
But what will happen to you?
As the one hired to serve as
the escort on this mission,
I must take responsible for this accident!
Oh, boy, you've done it now.
The client's furious, y'know.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Gotta start all over now, huh?
You're not gonna get any sleep
for five days, but good luck!
Yes, sir.
Man, I could never survive that.
U-Uh...
It was my mistake,
so the responsibility is mine.
You have your own work to do, senior Sato.
I really did want to help.
But in the end,
all I could think about was myself.
What are you doing?!
Run away now!
No! Let me help!
It's not like that anymore.
The whole reason
I'm gaining more abilities
is for times like these!
Emily! Are you okay?!
Just like before...
I did it right!
Thank you. You saved us.
EMILY: LEVEL, STATUS
HP, MP, STRENGTH, VITALITY,
Your level went way up!
INTELLIGENCE, WILL, SPEED, DEXTERITY
It sure did! I could feel it!
I guess Femini are really strong monsters.
If you take out
that many of them at once,
of course your level's gonna go up.
It's all thanks to you.
If I stay with you,
I'm sure more good things will happen.
Nah, I'm the one...
who felt the same.
Oh, you are, too?
So we're the same!