[Script Info]
;===== Toaru_Kagaku_no_Railgun 科學超電磁砲 作品ASS字幕外掛發佈訊息 =====
;字幕由HKG字幕組製作
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈 謝謝
;參與製作人員
;翻譯：AgTom
;時間：怕輸  okayu
;特效：怕輸  天河明人
;後期&BDRip：ZilcH
;========================================================================
Script Type: V4.00+
ScriptType: V4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.000
WrapStyle: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00808080,&H50FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3.5,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default2,ZhunYuan,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00808080,&H50FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default3,ZhunYuan,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00808080,&H50FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,1,8,30,30,8,1
Style: jp,ms Gothic,25,&H00FCFCFC,&H000000FF,&H00454545,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,20,20,8,1
Style: title,DFNMingXBold-B5,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: JP2,ms Gothic,23,&H00FCFCFC,&H000000FF,&H00454545,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,20,20,8,1
Style: LOGO1,新宋体,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: LOGO2,新宋体,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,75,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: LOGO3,新宋体,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,60,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

;Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================OP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.74,0:01:47.64,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}響き合う　願いが今、覚醒めてく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.88,0:01:50.57,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}譲れない未来のために
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.67,0:01:54.83,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}巡り逢う　運命を超えたその先に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.85,0:01:59.80,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}この想い輝くから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.21,0:02:03.33,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ここじゃない未来に
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.55,0:02:06.83,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想い託してみては
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.96,0:02:13.82,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}強さの本当の意味を捜し続けてた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.98,0:02:17.09,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ありのままの痛みを
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.26,0:02:20.53,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}受け入れるその意味を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.73,0:02:26.85,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}明日へ走り続ける君に知った
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.86,0:02:30.78,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}巡りゆく　景色が今、流れてく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.89,0:02:33.65,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}手繰り寄せた世界の先
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.68,0:02:37.85,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}降り注ぐ　シグナルを躰で感じて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.86,0:02:40.60,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}解き放つ今全てを
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.61,0:02:41.92,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Just truth in my heart
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.93,0:02:44.62,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}いつだって迷わないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.63,0:02:47.41,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}消せない想いがあるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.41,0:02:51.59,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}解き明かす　真実から　瞳を逸らさずに
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.61,0:02:54.92,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}I'll reach the next stage to realize all
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.05,0:02:58.93,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}確かな絆信じて
;Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.03,0:00:52.03,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================Logo
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(250,430)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5\fs50}{\shad0}{\1c&H4D81DF\fs50}囧\N　{\1c&H455EDC\fs50}\N齒{\1c&H3035CE\fs50}\N輪{\1c&4028D1}\N{\fs55\b0}の
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,250)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5}{\shad0}{\fs25}{\1c&H4D81DF}爆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,275)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5}{\shad0}{\fs25}{\1c&H5B76CC}肝
Dialogue: 2,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(191,307)\fnDFNMingXBold-B5}{\shad0}{\fs65}真
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(225,275)}{\shad0}{\1c&H2e41e2}{\fs90}{\frz90}▆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(202,355)}{\shad0}{\1c&4028D1}{\fs85}H
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(199,403)}{\shad0}{\1c&341FD7}{\fs105}K
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.69,0:01:51.60,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(193,465)}{\shad0}{\1c&341FD7}{\fs130}G
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.26,0:01:51.60,LOGO3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(170,360)\fad(250,0)}{\shad0}{\frz90}{\fs20}{\1c&341FD7}hkgfansub
;Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================ED
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.74,0:22:21.86,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}狙いさだめた　指先がさす
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.87,0:22:26.81,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}運命は絶望？　それとも希望？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.05,0:22:33.27,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}ゆらぎの中で　受信してゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.28,0:22:35.53,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}悲しみにも負けない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.54,0:22:38.23,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}勇気だけをください
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.42,0:22:44.27,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}大切なもの　守るため
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.42,0:22:49.79,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}「強さ」はあると信じてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.80,0:22:55.53,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}Saving our future 一緒に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:23:01.19,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}明日へのドア開いた空へ飛び立とう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.35,0:23:07.02,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}とある世界の果てで
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.14,0:23:12.83,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}駆け抜けてくReal Force
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.05,0:23:19.77,jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\b1}光を放って！
;Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,=============================================================Main

Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.53,0:00:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 鐵裝老師
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.05,0:00:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都放暑假了 還這麼辛勞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.19,0:00:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 有些活兒還沒做完
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.29,0:00:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.33,0:00:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.06,0:00:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 已經到這點啦 糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.77,0:00:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天那邊也有活兒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.67,0:00:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 那我先告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.83,0:00:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.44,0:00:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.61,0:00:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 現在不是幹這事的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:00:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.23,0:01:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要多小心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.43,0:01:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.04,0:01:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.10,0:01:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這回遲大到啦——！

Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.77,0:03:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起我來晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.81,0:03:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚得也太離譜了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.60,0:03:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.71,0:03:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了暑假 學生們容易心野
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.12,0:03:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光靠風紀委員來維持風紀太困難了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.01,0:03:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們才會像現在這樣出來巡邏
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.98,0:03:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連你都心野的話 那可怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.10,0:03:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.94,0:03:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.46,0:03:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我是黃泉川
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.83,0:03:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搶劫？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.85,0:03:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.01,0:03:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用工作彌補自己的失敗吧 明白沒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.24,0:03:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.45,0:03:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黃 黃泉川老師
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.84,0:03:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要過來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.27,0:03:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敢靠近來 就宰了她
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.94,0:03:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用管我 快制服犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.08,0:03:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.79,0:03:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.83,0:03:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.94,0:03:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.89,0:03:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的要下手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.42,0:03:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Excellent！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.10,0:03:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狀態極好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.03,0:03:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何等粗野
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.45,0:04:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 能打出高分不是很厲害嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.76,0:04:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺行的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.79,0:04:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 我不會輸的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.78,0:04:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 救出人質以後就鬆懈了 才會有這下場吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.99,0:04:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是也用不著連我也一起打...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.57,0:04:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Excellent！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.69,0:04:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.78,0:04:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記錄更新？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.19,0:04:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐天好強
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.19,0:04:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多到清校時間了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.63,0:04:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.49,0:04:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.79,0:04:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用工作挽回失敗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.57,0:04:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明 明白
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.36,0:04:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一拳我要動真格了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.54,0:04:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 就是說剛才那拳還沒算動真格咯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.52,0:04:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算搞錯了 也請不要用腳踢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.85,0:04:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 原來還有這麼一招啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.76,0:04:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能作弊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.72,0:04:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你們幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.52,0:04:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快就到清校時間了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.51,0:04:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.17,0:04:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.39,0:04:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不就是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.51,0:04:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當時的...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.28,0:05:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當時真是受你照顧了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.69,0:05:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才要謝謝你們呢 救了我一命
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.95,0:05:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問 你是不是瘦了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.27,0:05:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與其說瘦了 不如說是憔悴了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.51,0:05:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.97,0:05:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為你應該保養一下皮膚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.19,0:05:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警備員也夠辛苦的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.90,0:05:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.59,0:05:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如這樣吧 抽這個一拳 給自己解解壓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.67,0:05:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我還在上班啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.46,0:05:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定對皮膚也有好處哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.09,0:05:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那就試一下吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.86,0:05:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼被人家牽著鼻子走了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.70,0:05:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你們快回家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.71,0:05:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 當時那個魔鬼老師
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.91,0:05:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你也是 已經到清校時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.29,0:05:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.26,0:05:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？是鴻野江
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.77,0:05:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你熟人？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.88,0:05:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們的同學
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.32,0:05:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不是很熟
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.64,0:05:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺很難接近呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.88,0:06:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燙燙燙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.09,0:06:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺激傷口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.92,0:06:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐵裝 你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.54,0:06:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 只是熱水刺激到擦傷的地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.61,0:06:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是問你這個
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.30,0:06:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最近有點怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.65,0:06:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你今天又遲到 又被挾持 還被學生牽著鼻子走
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.16,0:06:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.46,0:06:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來你作為警備員的表現就已經說不上好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.74,0:06:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是鬆懈了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.90,0:06:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.23,0:06:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼說 幹完一天活兒 來泡個澡真是夠爽的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.61,0:06:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.17,0:06:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小萌老師也是這麼認為的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.31,0:06:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 來碟雞胗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.15,0:06:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.48,0:07:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一如既往的豪放啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.78,0:07:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐵裝綴里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.92,0:07:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.32,0:07:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好了 你的缺點就是太軟弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.75,0:07:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺起胸膛做人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.20,0:07:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.42,0:07:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該強硬的時候就要硬起來 硬起來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.89,0:07:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是 該硬時就要硬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.57,0:07:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.50,0:07:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 來碟烤豬肝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.36,0:07:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.82,0:07:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要硬起來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.53,0:07:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得加油了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.12,0:07:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我們從A地區巡邏到D地區
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.59,0:07:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分頭行動吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.33,0:07:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吧 鐵裝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.51,0:07:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.24,0:07:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃...這邊是北...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.62,0:08:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟媽媽是在哪裡走散的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.46,0:08:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 諸事不順啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.98,0:08:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.58,0:08:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.55,0:08:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你 馬上就到清校時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.01,0:08:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.26,0:08:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 說你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.70,0:08:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激掌9 好懷念啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.70,0:08:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到這麼老的遊戲都會出現在學園都市
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.11,0:08:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前我經常玩的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.95,0:08:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到頭來 10都沒出來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.94,0:08:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不是說這個的時候 你快回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.97,0:08:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.15,0:09:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 來碗燉豬手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.94,0:09:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.23,0:09:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 要點越南煎餅和竹筍刺身
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.39,0:09:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.10,0:09:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 鐵裝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.77,0:09:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.82,0:09:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有煩惱的話 我可以聽你傾訴 說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.97,0:09:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 有戀愛煩惱嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.70,0:09:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也說不上是煩惱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.14,0:09:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那為什麼老是幹蠢事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.44,0:09:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.91,0:09:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 俗話說「人生苦短 戀愛吧 少女」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.48,0:09:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 鐵裝 你有什麼興趣愛好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.14,0:09:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.86,0:10:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不是愛好也行 偶爾也做點自己喜歡的事嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.73,0:10:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.66,0:10:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天能將女人變成獵人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.29,0:10:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散散心吧 什麼事都行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.28,0:10:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放鬆放鬆自己 盡情地去放鬆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.02,0:10:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡情地...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.77,0:10:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有道理呢 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.29,0:10:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.36,0:10:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 來碟田鱉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.36,0:10:22.11,*Default3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田鱉 中國南方以及東南亞一帶著名的食用昆蟲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.23,0:10:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.51,0:10:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 小萌老師 之前我就很想問了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.51,0:10:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.65,0:10:32.93,*title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(431,10)}{\bord0\shad0}{\fad(150,0)}{\fscx92}#17{\fscx98\b0} {\1c&H4D81DF}暑假的綴里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.22,0:10:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這家攤 是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.32,0:10:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要遲到？你到底在幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.09,0:10:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一學期的評定還沒匯總好...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.78,0:10:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？那點事應該在暑假前就已經搞定了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.74,0:10:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.02,0:10:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你沒辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.35,0:10:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你不用來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.92,0:10:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 你今天之內要搞定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.23,0:10:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.38,0:11:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 下次酒會就到你請了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.41,0:11:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的...呃？！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.02,0:11:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞定了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.00,0:11:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都到這點了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.37,0:11:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡的事啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.60,0:11:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太拘泥於放大招了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.70,0:11:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 你要學會善攻能防才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.81,0:11:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半吊子的攻擊 還不如不發呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.45,0:11:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.88,0:11:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前很沉迷的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.60,0:11:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能換我來一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.05,0:11:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎 長按Start鍵的話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.23,0:12:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後再這樣操作
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.27,0:12:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 幹一場
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.02,0:12:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隱藏角色
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.13,0:12:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 不過很沒用的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.64,0:12:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.65,0:12:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡這遊戲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.42,0:12:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡的遊戲的秘籍 還挺讓人期待的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.11,0:12:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且這個角色 也挺可愛的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.08,0:12:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 完全不可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.95,0:12:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣好嗎 你可是警備員啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.50,0:12:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天放假 學校的活兒也幹完了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.28,0:12:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼久了 我也該放鬆一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.34,0:12:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 不知道技巧有沒有生疏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.82,0:12:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 小萌老師
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.48,0:12:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 呃？黃泉川老師發生緊急狀況
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.85,0:12:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好 不過...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.37,0:12:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黃泉川老師她...不過 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.06,0:12:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jamie...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.67,0:13:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 你幫我打吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.56,0:13:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 Jamie線結局超級熱血的 絕對要看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.78,0:13:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黃泉川老師
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.14,0:13:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喝不下了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.07,0:13:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是緊急狀況嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.85,0:13:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這個啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.92,0:13:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這麼早就開喝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.37,0:13:34.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她到底喝了多少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.01,0:13:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們倆輕鬆幹掉了5、6升吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.38,0:13:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐵裝老師 你開心嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.27,0:13:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能開心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.24,0:13:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那今天一天過得怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.76,0:13:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天呢 之前又如何呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.15,0:14:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 也沒有特別開心的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.44,0:14:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且工作這麼忙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.29,0:14:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天都很開心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.92,0:14:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這座城市 有著各種各樣的學生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.87,0:14:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.24,0:14:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然當中還有炸飛我家屋頂的調皮學生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.92,0:14:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？屋頂？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.98,0:14:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.77,0:14:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 我最喜歡我的學生了 包括那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.12,0:14:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐵裝老師你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.44,0:14:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.07,0:14:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就從I地區巡到L地區吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.35,0:14:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分頭行動...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.09,0:14:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就從L地區開始巡邏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.97,0:14:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有幹勁嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.15,0:15:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.82,0:15:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你 是哪裡殺出來的Agathion
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.14,0:15:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 等等 你是哪裡的學生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.53,0:15:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是學生 是修女
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.66,0:15:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說 你掉了的麵包圈被清掃機器人回收了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.59,0:15:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當麻說過 這國家有著「3秒規則」這偉大定規哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.35,0:15:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我覺得大馬路不在規則的適用範圍內吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.61,0:15:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 快還我麵包圈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.46,0:15:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.49,0:15:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 客人？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.75,0:15:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.42,0:15:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全要？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.64,0:15:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.00,0:15:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 那女孩說要把店裡的漢堡包全買下 不肯讓啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.26,0:15:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.71,0:15:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是哪裡的學生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.07,0:15:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧丘女子學院 不過現在是自由身
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.50,0:16:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由身？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.81,0:16:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說 為什麼你要這麼多漢堡包
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.31,0:16:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘不了那味道 所以全都要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.05,0:16:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個嘛...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.14,0:16:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 我果然還是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.47,0:16:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 不能示弱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.40,0:16:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去下一個地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.97,0:16:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.97,0:16:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的鏈墜丟了...吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.82,0:16:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鏈墜？什麼樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.88,0:16:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內有照片的那種
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.71,0:16:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是Locket吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.64,0:16:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Locket？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.90,0:16:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能放照片進去的鏈墜都這麼叫的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.36,0:16:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧 現在的女生都不這麼叫了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.12,0:16:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫鏈墜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.18,0:16:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊對 對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.61,0:16:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 是在這附近掉的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.45,0:16:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估計...是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.08,0:16:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我陪你一起找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.68,0:17:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不見啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.28,0:17:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地 地震
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.24,0:17:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 剛才那是地震？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.88,0:17:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 晃了嗎 你錯覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.65,0:17:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.60,0:17:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.41,0:17:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.61,0:17:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.28,0:17:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來你是哪間學校的...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.77,0:17:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 竟然連一個Locket都找不著
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.59,0:17:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是真的在努力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.69,0:17:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這麼晚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.50,0:17:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她搞什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.84,0:18:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃？使Jamie的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.85,0:18:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不能輸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.96,0:18:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺強的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.78,0:18:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肘擊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.06,0:18:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.37,0:18:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前也被人稱作「大宮Jamie」的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.21,0:18:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贏啦！打平
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.99,0:18:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一場 一定要贏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.08,0:18:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.22,0:18:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這招搞定你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.25,0:19:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,技術果然生疏了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.05,0:19:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 好久都沒試過這麼熱情澎湃了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.15,0:19:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大宮Jamie呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.12,0:19:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 你都聽見了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.23,0:19:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧 後來你真的就為了看Jamie結局一直玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.71,0:19:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難怪那麼猛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.06,0:19:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道會不會出激掌10呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.17,0:19:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會的 那麼老的遊戲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.73,0:19:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出的話 下次我一定能贏你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.54,0:19:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.03,0:19:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我期待著哦 大宮Jamie小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.90,0:19:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都叫你忘記這個名字啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.01,0:20:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到這裡就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.26,0:20:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼呢 都已經過清校時間了 你一個初中生...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.89,0:20:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事 我家就在那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.67,0:20:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.99,0:20:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.89,0:20:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.43,0:20:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞什麼啊 也不聯絡一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.77,0:20:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不來也要跟我們說聲嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.18,0:20:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會擔心的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.70,0:20:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才沒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.15,0:20:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 之前說好了今天要你請客的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.36,0:20:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准說忘了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.60,0:20:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 今天豪氣一點上豬臉皮了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.57,0:20:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.13,0:20:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以趕緊給我過來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.75,0:20:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.52,0:20:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉學了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.88,0:20:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.20,0:21:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在放暑假 太突然了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.24,0:21:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.87,0:21:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他轉去的學校 叫什麼名字來著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.59,0:21:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雜草學院初中部
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.76,0:21:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雜草學院？那是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.90,0:21:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字粗魯也得有個譜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.25,0:21:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雜草的英文不就是Weed嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.40,0:21:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是遊戲廠商Weed作為母體的學校名字
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.80,0:21:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Weed？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.01,0:21:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是以前出「激掌」系列遊戲很有名的那家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.84,0:21:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 那個我好像聽說過
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.78,0:21:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是培養遊戲創作者的學校咯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.44,0:21:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,專業知識還要到高中部才開始講呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.42,0:21:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過為什麼挑Weed呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.45,0:21:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家公司已經衰敗了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.07,0:21:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 那家出的遊戲有很多我都喜歡哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.58,0:21:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初春是狂熱者嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.66,0:21:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.78,0:21:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了 突然笑出來 真噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.10,0:21:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個 到清校時間要準時回去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.91,0:22:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是～
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.29,0:22:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～我要加油
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.15,0:22:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了 太突然了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.46,0:22:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 我們走吧 接下來是E地區了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.14,0:22:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,F吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.07,0:22:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.95,0:00:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,/ED
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.52,0:23:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說到jyan 有猜拳啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.32,0:23:39.99,*title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\b0\shad0\bord1.5}{\1c&H4D81DF}{\fscx92}#18{\fscx98} 羅漢柏園
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.83,0:23:34.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有麻將的將
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.84,0:23:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的前世是冉·阿讓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.84,0:23:37.23,*Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(496,436)}Jean-Valjean
Dialogue: 2,0:23:34.84,0:23:37.23,*Default3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25}冉·阿讓是『悲慘世界』/『孤星淚』的主角
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.03,0:23:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有Jungle呢～


