Gintama
Slip Arc
Diamonds are Unscratchable
GKB48's Request!! Watch this program in a bright room
and at a safe distance from your TV ♥
We would never let you
leave looking so sad.
Why? Because...
We provide dreams to all of space
as the special unit of galactic idols.
That is why.
That's...
Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48?!
Why are they on Earth?
Guys, come to our meet-and-greet and wipe
this bitter taste out of your mouths.
Otherwise your Bitchie will
be so lonely, she'll cry.
I-I can't believe I get to
meet the universe's top idols!
Is this some dream or fantasy?!
I'm going first!
No, I am!
Wait, what? Giant Knobhead Bitches 48?
No way... They're here in Edo?
They are Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48.
On several planets, top idol groups
faced off in a public vote,
and only the centers whose
groups placed at the top—
in other words, only the top of the
top idols from across the galaxy—
formed this top idol group!
How many times are you gonna say "top"?
They're the biggest idols in the galaxy!
They traverse planets, nabbing
the top idol spot on each one,
then move on to their next target.
If that special unit of idols is here in
Edo and showed up in front of Otsu-chan,
that must mean their next target is...
Terakado Tsu.
We got a good look at how
Edo's top idol does sales.
I'm amazed you sit at the
top of the pile like that.
It seems Edo has the weakest idols
of all the planets we've been to.
Let us show you how real idols
do meet-and-greets.
A-Are those...
Line up and come in one by one, guys.
We want to spend quality
time with each of you.
Why have closed spaces if
they're only gonna shake hands?
Challenge accepted. I'll go first.
Taka-chin?
You ran your mouth at Otsu-chan.
If this meet-and-greet ain't up to
scratch, you'll be in real trouble.
Taka-chin!
Sorry, Shin-chan.
I honestly don't understand what you're
trying to do with Otsu-chan right now.
But I believe that you'll
protect her to the end.
I believe that she would
never lose to these hussies!
Taka-chin!
Huh? Seriously?
Is this how it works?
Uh, why is it shaking?
Taka-chin!
Huh? Was he in his undies just now?
I hear weird noises. What is that?
What's going on?
Taka-chin!
He was totally butt-naked!
What're they doing?
Are they really shaking hands?
Taka-chin!
Uh, hold up. What is this?
They're not shaking hands at all. They're
doing something totally different.
Taka-chin!
What is that? Something just came out.
What's going on in there?
What're you guys doing?
Taka-chin!
Now his whole body's covered in pixels!
What happened to him?
Taka-chin!
Taka-chin?
Taka-chin?!
Taka-chin!
Pull yourself together, Taka-chin!
What happened, Taka-chin?!
Once I get home, I'm gonna
burn all my porn mags.
What'd they do to you?!
What'd they do to him?
They clearly just did him!
They totally got down and dirty.
He looks like he released everything he had
pent up. He's basking in the afterglow.
Taka-chin, tell me what happened inside.
Everything turned white.
Crap! Now he's turned completely white!
Once I get home, I'll try being nicer to Mom.
I'll try to find something
good about Kamiji Yusuke.
Hey! People are getting enlightened
in the afterglow one after another!
Wait, are you kidding me?
Seriously? Is this for real?
What, do they shake something
other than hands on their planets?
Are you kidding me? Seriously?
Is this for real?
Calm down, Gin-san!
Our meet-and-greet made
everyone weak in the knees.
Terakado Tsu, we've rendered all
your fans completely spineless.
They're wrapped around our fingers.
This is what real idols are capable of.
What the greatest galactic
idol group is capable of.
What Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48 is capable of.
Uh, idols? You're practically
just pr*******es!
What? How mean!
You know nothing about me!
You know nothing about
what we were doing inside!
If you suspect us that much,
why don't you try it yourself...
Our meet-and-greet.
I'll take the special course, please.
Meet-and-greet.
I can start a tab with you, right?
Like hell!
No... My fans, who've been
behind me all this time...
All hail Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48!
The ones who've supported
me all this time...
In one moment, they all just...
No...
This can't be.
This can't be happening!
Otsu-chan!
H-Hey! How long are you
gonna sleep, you dumbass?!
Wait, Otsu-chan!
We still have a bunch of pillow
sales events lined up after this!
Hey!
She went down far easier than expected.
All hail Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48!
But this isn't enough.
Getting these core idol fans on
our side doesn't mean a thing.
All of Edo must watch as Terakado Tsu
and Booger Diamonds 48 fall to pieces.
They need to know that we, Galaxy Kingdom
Bitches 48, are the greatest idols alive.
Showtime is only just beginning.
I see.
Otsu-chan's still holed up?
She seems to be taking it really hard.
Sorry. It's all our fault
for being so useless.
Oh, no. I made her form a unit to put
her under this exact kind of pressure.
But I can't believe they came
gunning for Otsu at the same time.
She's hit rock bottom, and
she may not climb back up.
Otsu-chan will definitely bounce back!
She'd never lose to those people!
Yeah. Right now, we don't
stand to make any mon—
I mean, make a decent impression,
so give us a chance to turn this around.
Otsu's not alone.
If she's hit rock bottom,
there's still something I,
along with Booger Diamonds 48,
can do to help her.
I want her to remember that.
There's nothing any of you can do.
I mean...
Terakado Tsu Cries
Outside a Love Hotel!!
Producer Carries
BDZ48 Member Home!
You're all down there with her.
There they are!
It's Booger Diamonds 48's
producer, Mr. Sakata!
What was Otsu-chan doing
in front of a love hotel?
Is it true that you're using
your position as producer
to screw around with your agency's idols?
You've got the wrong idea!
I was the one who was with
Otsu-chan! I'm her manager!
We were just talking about work—
So the producer and manager are both
screwing around with their agency's idols?
Did you listen to a word I said?!
Well?
You know they're gonna twist
your words, Shinpachi.
Just get through it by saying
"Whatever. I don't care."
They'll twist that even worse!
We've done nothing wrong.
No need to run or hide.
That's right.
Besides, Gin-chan and I have gone long
past "taking home." We live together.
What do you mean, you live together?
He keeps me at home without pay
and makes me do all kinds of stuff from
morning to night until I can't stand.
Nothing wrong with that.
Everything about that sounds wrong!
Sakata-san, are you a lolicon p**o?
I'm not a p**o! The P stands for producer!
I'm not a lolicon, either!
So you're a p**o P?
Knock it off already, you rotten cue ball!
Did you hear that verbal abuse?
I no longer have any fans cheering me on.
Showbiz really is seedy, huh?
Well, everyone in the entertainment
business is like this.
I don't have anyone on my side.
Should've seen it coming.
Otsu and
Her Manager
Super
Edo Scoop
Otsu-chan's in big trouble,
and it's all our fault!
Tch.
Who woulda thought this would happen right
before the release of the debut single?
We've been had.
The background on this
photograph has been shopped.
In other words, you were used
in a plot to bring Otsu down...
by Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48.
Th-They were behind this?
They're a special squad that has destroyed
top idols on all kinds of planets.
They're not picky about their methods.
They'll pay for this.
Let's expose their tactics and condemn them!
They have tremendous influence
with media across the galaxy.
It'll never see the light of day.
At this point, our only choice is to
upload a shaved-head apology video.
Even if you hate me, the manager,
please don't come to hate Booger Diamonds 48!
What part do you think you're shaving off?!
Or we'll have to put fries
and Shinpachi side-by-side
and upload a video about
which one will rot sooner.
Your brains are what's rotten!
Too late for that too, apparently.
They got the jump on us.
Greetings, earthlings!
We are the special unit of galactic idols,
Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48!
As it turns out, we're going
to make our debut on Earth!
Yay!
Our new single, "A Slut's Badge
of Honor," releases December 10th.
December 10th? The same release date
as Booger Diamonds 48's debut single?
They're even going with a similar title.
With that in mind, we plan to hold
a release event at Oedo Dome.
But since that alone wouldn't
be exciting enough,
we've got some big guests lined up.
Surprise!
We want to invite Edo's top idol,
Terakado Tsu-chan, to this event!
Wha?!
We don't have an appointment yet, but...
Terakado Tsu-san, why don't we face
off to determine Edo's top idol?
Us, Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48,
versus Terakado Tsu's Booger Diamonds 48?
Let's compete to see which of us can
charm more fans in a meet-and-greet.
The winner gets to perform
their new single live.
But the loser has to retire from the
idol industry right then and there.
It's a battle to determine the top idol.
There has to be some risk involved.
Let's settle this, Terakado Tsu-san.
You were once the top idol in all of Edo.
We trust you won't run
away from this challenge.
Up Next
The Making of Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48's "A Slut's Badge of Honor"
Cancel
Th-That was...
Well played.
Now that they've released
this video to the public,
our reputation will be ruined if we refuse.
For someone so cute, she sure can play dirty.
Kingdom Bitches is a fitting name, I say.
The words "idol" and "bitch"
are practically synonyms.
They're several times
better at this than Otsu.
That's a hell of a thing for the
president of an idol agency to say.
But we can't put her idol career on
the line, even if it makes us lose face.
And having lost all her fans,
Otsu stands no chance—
Not all of them.
She still has three fans right here.
Relax. I won't cause any trouble.
An idol digs out her boogers
with her own hands.
And besides, we Booger Diamonds 48
are fully prepared to be the boogers that
make Otsu-chan's diamond shine bright.
You guys...
Until now, Otsu-chan has given
us hopes and dreams as an idol.
Now, it's our turn as fans to return the
favor by giving her hopes and dreams.
Oedo Dome
Hello, everyone!
Thanks for coming to see us today!
We are the idols of the entire universe...
Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48!
And here is the group that
accepted our challenge...
Heya. We are Booger Diamonds 48.
Yeah, right!
Where's Otsu? You're just
three piles of boogers now!
What kinda nostrils did you pop out of?!
We took responsibility for causing a
scandal by shaving our heads down there.
We are the newest members...
Pachie!
Pako!
You call that taking responsibility?!
You've gotta be kidding me.
We're here for Terakado Tsu! We don't
give two hoots about you morons!
Right back at ya. Otsu says she has
no time to waste on knobhead bitches.
But we decided to drop by while
chasing our boogers too far in.
You should be grateful to us.
Say what, you booger brat?
Oh, my! Sparks are already
flying on the stage!
Booger Diamonds 48 and Galaxy
Kingdom Bitches 48...
Will their meet-and-greet with the fans
turn into a World Martial Arts Tournament?
Fine by us.
We don't care if you're a special
unit of galactic idols or whatever.
But if you want to settle things with
force, then we'll gladly play along.
Just know that you won't stand
a chance in hell of winning.
Not when you're against the strongest
combat backing band in the galaxy,
Diamond Vacuum.
Sis!
So they made it.
Whoa! Booger Diamonds 48 had
a real ace up their sleeve!
A group of hotties comparable to
Otsu-chan has taken the stage!
We're saying we'll battle you
in your arena and on your terms.
Get back, before we render
your pretty faces useless.
How dare you frame our producer?
The one sleeping with Producer Sakata is me!
What are you even here for?
I don't know how things ended up
like this, but this too is fate.
No matter in what arena, I refuse
to lose any battles I take part in.
I'll show you the fruits of my training.
What the hell did you guys train for?!
Don't just do whatever the hell you please!
I see.
Otsu ran from us, so you
tried to make up for that
by hastily gathering trash
that's nothing but looks?
Man, I've never felt this insulted before.
Fine. If that's how you want to
play, we'll kill your careers
and crush you so thoroughly that Otsu will
never think about taking the stage again.
Let's determine the greatest idols
in the universe right here and now.
Fight fair and square!
The battle to determine the greatest
idols alive is now underway.
This battle between Galaxy Kingdom
Bitches 48 and Booger Diamonds 48
will be decided by how many fans flock
to their respective meet-and-greets.
Pleased to meet you all!
Whoa, as soon as the bell rings, a
tidal wave of people comes rushing in.
Incredible!
Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48!
It's like they're gobbling up every fan in
the arena! What overwhelming popularity!
Meanwhile, Booger Diamonds 48's
base is tumbleweed central!
They may have a bunch of hotties,
but they're still newly debuted nobodies.
Was it too soon for them to take on
the galaxy's greatest idol group?
Otsu or no Otsu, the outcome was
decided before it even started.
Didn't you realize that?
In truth, this was never a battle to
determine the greatest idols alive.
It's just a public execution.
That so? Either way, you shouldn't
get distracted during a battle.
Don't you get it? This can't
even be called a battle.
You're the one who doesn't get it.
An idol's enemy isn't just in front of her.
Yikes, what's with that line?
It's an idol meet-and-greet, apparently.
Ew, gross.
That's...
A rear ambush by the backing band!
So what if they can shake hands with idols?
Does that really make them happy?
Why are they so desperate?
You're so silly, Otae.
Look at them. They've probably never
held a girl's hand in their lives.
Oh, sorry. They've probably
never talked to one, either.
The backing band unit's barrage of insults
is making the fans lose all desire
to attend the meet-and-greet!
Rude! I have at least talked to girls!
I bet it just went like, "Would
you like that heated?" and "Sure."
There was more! Like,
"I don't need a plastic bag."
You don't call that talking to a girl.
That's cheating! Do you really
think you can mess with our line?
Keep talking. Plotting evil from behind
the idol is what a backing band does.
Don't they know that lining up
here won't resolve a thing?
They're basically lining up to
climb the 13 stairs to the gallows.
Corpses everywhere!
They're massacring the fans in Galaxy
Kingdom Bitches 48's line one after another!
Such futile resistance.
Your sabotaging is only making the
fans distance themselves from you.
What?
You went too far, Tae-chan, Sarutobi.
They had a Plan B with more backing
band members at the back?
Sorry. Are you all right?
Can you stand?
Don't tell me, the first two backing
band members were just a setup?
Forgive them.
They mean no harm. They're just a little shy.
By mercilessly beating down the
fans and then picking them up...
They wanted to talk to you all, but it
seems they didn't know where to begin.
After all, it's the same for us.
W-We've never held a meet-and-greet...
...before today.
Sorry.
In truth, we're the same as you.
If you don't mind...
...could you take our first time?
They brought out the tsundere act?!
Hey, why did my heart just skip a beat?
The girls over there are pretty cute, too!
I think I'll head over there!
Me, too!
Me three!
Whoa, Galaxy Kingdom Bitches
48's line is falling apart!
You were right. Nobodies could never
beat the greatest idols in the universe.
But it looks like this battle
is neither to determine the greatest
idols alive nor a public execution.
I hear it's just a battle to
determine the biggest sluts alive.
You're the ones who started playing dirty.
We'll make you regret it!
Wh-What're those?
Even if we can't win as idols,
Booger Diamonds 48 is invincible
in a battle of the sluts.
Those are... toilet stalls!
Are they using toilet stalls, of all things,
to compete with the bewitching curtains?
H-How vulgar.
A meet-and-greet in such a disgusting
place would never make the fans happy.
Wh-What's with the toilets?
Don't tell me, we'll get to see them
doing all sorts of dirty things?
No way, man.
But they're toilets.
Oh, dear! The fans are beset by confusion!
Hey, Gin-chan! What's the meaning of this?
This is the first I'm hearing of a
meet-and-greet in toilets, Shin-chan.
I-It's not what you think, Sis!
The fans aren't the only ones confused!
You know... This is the first
meet-and-greet for you guys, too.
You're probably feeling
too shy to face the fans.
That's where these come in.
Enter the stalls from beneath the toilets.
Just stick your hands out and wait.
That way, you can deal with any
kind of embarrassment just fine.
All you have to do after
that is shake everything.
You won't see a thing, but it's simple.
Just grab everything that's
held out in front of you.
Consider your hand nothing but toilet paper.
What perverted acts are you
trying to make us perform?!
You hear that?
I'm going over there!
Wow! Even more people are leaving
Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48's line!
Producer Sakata is stealing even more
fans with a terrifying slut plan!
You shitheads!
This is where things get real.
Let's do this. Show them what
real sluts are capable of!
Who're you calling sluts?!
Ger-bleaurgh!
To Be Continued
Preview
Everyone... Thank you so,
so much for everything.
Next time: "An Idol's Badge of Honor."
An Idol's Badge of Honor
Shocked and hurt, Otsu holes up.
Will she end up retiring like this?
In this idol battle without honor and humanity,
who will stand victorious in the end?