Gintama
Slip Arc
Gintama Rumble?
What the heck is this?
Enjoy Gintama Rumble in a bright room and at a safe distance from your TV!!
What do you mean? It's an upcoming game.
Following the success of
the Gintama board game,
Bandai Namco went all-out to
make another game adaptation.
And it's an actual action game this time,
as you can tell from the "Rumble."
It's got tons more money invested
in it than the board game.
What's the point of making an action game
when we don't have any special moves?
Talk about living in denial.
At least it was kinda cute when they
made the board game in desperation.
Hey, quit complaining.
What's even going on with the rights?
Don't you think this is weird, Bamco?
Sugar Content
Our protagonist discussing our
game is weirder, if you ask me.
True, we never really talked about it before.
Regardless of who made games about
us or how badly they bombed,
we pretended not to notice.
Stop being rude, or we'll
never get another game!
Besides, the licensed-game genre has
always been a hotbed of shitty games.
They're not shitty! They're
made with love and affection!
But if we don't produce a hit soon, sponsors
might give up on the whole franchise.
That could lead to a reduction of
cross-media promotions and merch
and ultimately affect even the anime.
Uh, the anime isn't really one to talk.
Talk about reckless, making an action game
while we weren't paying attention.
It'll be in the bargain bin
within a few months, no doubt.
Don't jinx it before the release!
It's gonna sell like hotcakes!
I dunno about other Jump protags,
but as an adult protag, I'm gonna
point out problems when I see them.
You're the biggest problem here!
I've never heard of a protag
meddling in his franchise's merch!
I'm saying I can't just sit back
and let Bamco handle it all.
In this day and age, any protag worth
his salt has to oversee all the merch.
On that note...
The Line Between Godlike Games
and Shitty Games Is Paper-Thin
Bandai Namco
Lab A
Main system successfully infiltrated.
Authenticating
Unlocked
Hacking complete.
Great. Let's fix up Gintama
Rumble by ourselves.
Hey! What do you think you're
doing right before the release?!
We're gonna do all we can to make a game
that has a chance of selling a million.
Yeah, right!
Do you really think we're gonna get away
with sneaking in here and doing whatever?
They've almost finished
making a really fun game!
Gintama Rumble
People with no game dev experience
should keep their noses out of this!
Don't be naïve.
Sure, it might be a fun game.
But I wanna ask Bamco this:
"Do you guys really want to score a hit?"
Gintama Rumble
If they were serious about it,
this is what would happen, obviously.
Like hell!
Don't try to claw your way
into a super-hit series!
There's a ton of them already,
so nobody'll notice if we slip ourselves in.
Can't go wrong Tales-of-ing
basically anything in life.
What the hell is "Tales-of-ing"?
What kinda verb is that?
Ignoring our crude original work is fine.
We're totally up for
Tales-of-ing off of them.
More like Tales of hitching
a ride on their backs!
Talk about riding on
someone else's coattails!
Roger.
You want to be carried one way or another.
Hey, Tama-san!
So switching to a fantasy RPG, basically?
Wait a sec! What about the "Rumble" part?
Gintama Rumble
That's the USP of this game, you know!
That won't be hard to work around. We can
just name the protag Rumble or something.
Who? This will be a Gintama game, right?
Great idea. I really hate game
protags who talk too much.
In order to provide the best immersion,
he should say nothing but
"yes" and "no," like in DQ.
So Gin-san doesn't have
to be the protag here.
The protag has no personality,
only speaks when required,
Tales of Rumble
and his name is Tales of Rumble.
But Rumble's dripping with personality!
Even if he doesn't say a word,
his back tells the whole story!
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Snack Otose
Rumble comes to Edo, joins Odd Jobs,
and rescues the kidnapped
princess with us, is the story.
Who would self-insert
into this rugged old man?
He's clearly the guy who
normally kidnaps the princess!
Hello, Rumble. Welcome to Odd Jobs.
Before you join, I'd like to know your affinity. Is that okay?
Before you join, I'd like to know
your affinity. Is that okay?
I'm S
I'm M
What happened to "yes" and "no"?!
How many things could you
respond to with that?!
All an RPG protag needs to
say is whether he's S or M.
That'd let him choose his
size at the armor shop, too.
Which size armor would you like?
I'm M
Rumble's L-sized, though.
What's the point, then? The leather
armor would be too tight on him!
Also, you recover HP at Starbecks, not
inns, giving the game a modern, hip feel.
The options should come in handy there, too.
Would you like that in short, tall, or grande?
He can't order anything!
The grande and stuff is too trendy
for him! He's freaking out!
Don't worry. HP might be difficult,
but buying rope and candles from the
item shop will let you recover MP.
I'm M
That's Masochist Points!
Why is "M" the only choice
you can make in this game?!
Hey! Who the hell would want
to control such a gross protag?
Relax. It only looks so graphic
because this is a cinematic scene.
Most of the time, he'll be super-deformed.
The protag is practically a corpse?
Games these days are too reliant on FMVs.
Graphics only need to be
detailed in climactic scenes.
The rest of the time, they should be
left up to the player's imagination.
Shinpachi: "Big trouble, Gin-san!"
What do you think you're
leaving to imagination?!
What happened to the body? Are you saying
that's a waste of resources, too?!
Someone kidnapped the princess.
Hey! Why're the glasses
dragging a coffin around?!
Does it mean what I think it means?!
With that, we've got a full party.
Yeah. The four of them will
now begin their adventure.
Gintoki
Kagura
Rumble
Shinpachi
They've practically been wiped out from
the start! Hurry up and visit the church!
A monster appeared.
Look, an enemy.
Rotten Shades (38)
ATK
DEF
WORK
Why is everyone, ally or enemy, a corpse?!
Why is Hasegawa-san a monster?!
That's not Hasegawa-san.
It's Rotten Shades (38).
So Hasegawa-san, then!
Rotten Shades calls for backup...
but no help arrives.
but no help arrives, obviously.
Somebody help him!
Rotten Shades is defeated.
What did he even show up for?
All he's done is embarrass himself!
Rotten Shades gets up and looks at you
like he wants work. Will you give him a job?
"He wants work"?
What's that supposed to mean?
Wait, is he gonna join the party?
You can save the Rotten Shades?
I'm S
Somebody save him!
I don't see a choice to
save Rotten Shades (38)!
Games have gotten too indifferent
to killing and looting, right?
You kill monsters for XP and open
chests in strangers' homes for items.
By giving the players a
choice in this scenario,
we want them to learn how much
people sin in everyday life.
Can we really make kids play a game
where they finish off a half-dead guy?
Our lives are being supported
by countless deaths.
We wanna teach kids that through this game.
So the more Rotten Shades you kill,
the more coffins you'll be dragging around.
We don't need any more corpses!
This is so depressing, it'll only
make people lose motivation to play!
Gintoki
Kagura
Rumble
Shinpachi
We lost HP.
What caused it?
Gintoki
Job: NEET
Looks like I got infected by NEET in
the fight against the Rotten Shades.
Why is NEET a poison-like status effect?
It reduces the motivation stat to zero,
preventing the use of items or heals.
ATK
DEF
MOT
WALK
You also lose the energy to walk,
so HP is gradually lost.
And eventually...
The party is wiped out.
NEET is way too scary!
Of course it is. Being a NEET is terrifying.
You know how a lot of people are goofing
off after finishing their education lately?
We want to show them how
important it is to work.
But you're not. All you're showing
them is an absurd fear of NEETdom!
Enquiries
Don't worry. Those who are up for
the fight will get another chance.
This is Hello Work. We can refer you to a workplace.
What? You come back to life
at Hello Work, not a church?
So long as you never give up,
you can start anew over and over.
Choose your new job.
S, please
M, please
Excuse me! In the end, S and M
are the only jobs I can take!
Choose quickly.
Could you hurry up?
Huh? The staff are acting weird.
It doesn't matter which.
Come on...
Man... This is a pain.
Hello Work is wiped out.
NEET is way too scary!
Why has it infected the
Hello Work staff, too?!
Sometimes, even Hello Work
people don't wanna work.
I wanted to show the player that.
Do you wanna make them work or not?
Edo is wiped out.
At this point, all you can
do is reset and start over.
Who was it that said you can start
anew so long as you don't give up?!
Shaddup!
You think you can auto-revive when
you're wiped out? Life ain't that easy!
Those of us who grew up on Wizardry
had to form another party to go recover
our bodies once we got wiped out.
After all that trouble, we'd take
them to the temple to revive,
but sometimes we'd fail and
lose our characters forever.
Enough with your "back in my day" crap!
There's no way modern kids could
deal with this masochistic design!
That's it. Making them
reset is going too far.
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Snack Otose
We can just make them form a
new party to save us NEETs.
Welcome to Kabuki District, Rumblee.
Rumblee?!
Rumble had a kid sister.
She's come to Kabuki District
in order to save him.
I get it! Twin protags!
I'm impressed by your resolve
to save your NEET brother.
But this town is overrun with NEET now.
Rumblee,
Rumblee, can you really...
can you really...
save your brother?!
MADAO Hazard
MADAO Hazard.
It turned into a completely different game!
Act Two, Tales of Madao Hazard,
is a survival-horror game set in a
Kabuki District taken over by NEETs.
Why have NEETs turned into
a resident evil biohazard?!
The player must cut through
wave after wave of NEETs.
What happened to the girl who
came here to save a NEET?!
The objective is to reach NEET Rumble!
Rumble's totally become the last boss!
Oh, no. Shinpachi's been completely consumed.
What do you mean, "consumed"?
Just how terrifying is the NEET virus?
Shinpachi... Rumble...
Don't give up! There must
be a way to make them work!
Don't give up!
There must be a way to make them work!
How come you two get to be Rumblee's
party members and I don't?!
Fire that thing into their asses.
It'll send them flying all the way to Hello Work.
It'll send them flying all
the way to Hello Work.
Hey! Why's the NEET who caused all this
showing up now like he's here to help?!
However, there's only one work slot open.
Unfortunately, one of the two will be
erased along with the NEET virus.
Unfortunately, one of the two will
be erased along with the NEET virus.
Say what?!
Press A for Shinpachi-kun.
Press B for Rumble.
Now, choose one!
H-How are you supposed to choose—
I'm S
You too?!
In the end, all three NEETs got wiped out!
Can both siblings only speak in S and Ms?!
How the hell were they raised?!
There you have it.
Pretty good.
Like hell it is!
This game has nothing to do
with even the G of Gintama!
And what happened to the stuff about
the kidnapped princess, anyway?!
The princess doesn't exist anymore.
Everyone turned into a NEET.
Just how half-assed is this story?!
Shinpachi-sama...
The kidnapped princess, and the
slain Rumble and friends...
There's one way to recover them all.
Really, Tama-san?
The princess is fine.
Funnily enough, she escaped the NEET
outbreak because she was kidnapped.
She was being held captive
by terrifying monsters
in a world where no living
person can ever set foot.
D-Don't tell me...
Yes. In order to gain tickets to
the afterlife and save the princess,
Rumble and gang risked their lives
and separated their bodies and souls.
Their new forms showed no traces
of the time they spent as MADAOs.
History would come to know them as...
Super MADAO Brothers
Forget recovering anything!
It just made an even bigger mess!
Are you seriously going to start
a third act at this point?
How many coattails are you
people gonna crap on?!
But they've found work as plumbers now,
and the princess will be rescued, too.
Everyone will be saved.
Not Bamco!
Okay, fine. We'll move on to a guy named
Bamco Lord van Damme as the protag and—
Enough!
So we can either go with something like
this or the action game showed before.
Gintama Rumble Pitch
Which should we release, President?
Bandai Namco
I'm S!
Take care.
Uh, something seems off.
Glasses Are a Part of the Soul
Zoff's Eyewear
So, what kind of glasses are you looking for?
Normal ones like these.
I broke them while half-asleep.
All the trendy stores are too expen—wait,
don't take it the wrong way!
It's fine. We place more importance
on visibility than appearance.
Glasses take the place of their
wearer's eyes to see things.
They're a second pair of eyes.
Why don't you try these?
They have a bit of a rock style, though.
Uh, is this really rock?
They're called the Curr Sedd Glasses.
Curr Sedd Glasses?
These will let you see through all the
world's truths clearly and distinctly.
Clearly and distinctly?
Indeed.
All of nature and creation,
clearly and distinctly.
Uh, this goes beyond clearly and distinctly.
I'm clearly and distinctly seeing
things that I shouldn't be seeing.
"Curr Sedd Glasses"?
These are just cursed glasses!
Guardian
Spirit
Guardian spirit.
It started analyzing things!
Guardian spirits are spirits
that follow a person or other
entity and protect them.
Also known as tutelary deities
or guardian angels.
Guardian spirits are spirits
that follow a person or other
entity and protect them.
Also known as tutelary deities
or guardian angels.
-Extract from Vikipedia
It just copy-pasted from Vikipedia?!
Why can I see guardian spirits?
These glasses are no joke!
And I can't unequip these cursed glasses!
That geezer!
What the hell does he think he's sold me?!
He'll pay for this!
Th-The store's gone...
No way.
Was that store itself an
otherworldly eyewear store?
What am I to do?
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Gin-san!
Please help me!
What?
I can't deal with all
this noise so early, man.
What is it? You see something scary?
One word and you're dead.
N-No, it's nothing.
There was a huge one here, too!
Gin-san has one crazy guardian spirit!
What's wrong with you?
Do you wanna be killed?
I-I'm sorry. Please don't kill me.
Seriously, what's gotten into you?
Spirit, nothing! That's practically a monster!
Has this thing always been by Gin-san's
side since the anime started 10 years ago?
I'm busy as shit this morning, y'know.
I have so much to do, even an
extra arm wouldn't be enough.
But you're using six arms!
Your guardian spirit's helping
you with your morning stuff!
You should hurry up and get ready, too.
We're being forced to take part
in the neighborhood sports meet.
Chew well.
What about rice?
Want a normal serving or large?
What're you, a mom?!
And what does this look
like without the glasses?
Oh, the miso soup moved.
A guardian spirit was behind the
moving miso soup phenomenon?
I need to take a dump.
That's how the morning
call of nature worked?!
Huh? Hey, who forgot to flush their poop?!
The unflushed poop was a guardian spirit's?!
I-I had no idea
that they were supporting
our lifestyles this way.
But who knows what'd happen
to me if I exposed this?
Anyway, I can't believe Gin-san
had such a rugged guardian spirit.
No wonder he's so strong.
Is he an ancestor of his, or
some god his family worshiped?
Guardian Spirit Asuraman.
Sakata Gintoki's guardian spirit.
The spirit of Ginnikuman erasers
he got from capsule machines as a kid.
He was a Ginraser spirit?!
What the hell do you mean,
an eraser's spirit?!
He got seven Asuramans,
so he threw away six.
The vengeful malice of the six
formed a spirit that plots to
exact revenge on its host
when it gets the chance.
This is no guardian spirit!
It's just a vengeful ghost!
Toilet
Hey, we're out of toilet paper!
Special ability: making
minor things disappear
with its eraser.
That's some petty revenge!
Shinpachi! Bring me some TP!
I'll kill you if you bring it!!
You there, Shinpachi?!
Hey! TP!
Sorry, Gin-san, but your guardian spirit
has no intention of guarding you.
We're out of toilet paper, Shinpachi!
Wake up, Kagura!
Bring me toilet paper!
Quiet. Forget that, bring me booze.
Who the hell is this dude?!
Hup.
Guardian Spirit Alchu.
Kagura's guardian spirit.
The spirit of a p***mon
that's super popular with kids.
What do you mean, Alchu?
What is it, a ripoff?!
A miraculous monster born
from a collaboration between
a drunkard and the P***chu
stuffed toy Kagura made as
a poor child who wanted to
be part of the P***mon fad.
No! My P***chu!
That drunkard looks familiar!
Actually, the spirit looks
just like him, too!
Swore absolute loyalty to the
shochu that gave birth to him,
stays with it, and protects it
at all times.
He's just an alcoholic!
Kagura! TP!
Oh, shut up.
Gimme a sec. I'll go call Master.
Master, shochu on the rocks.
Not a master bartender!
Wake up, Master.
We're out of shochu, Master.
Who wakes someone up like that?!
Ew, something stinks!
Is that why she always
wakes up in a bad mood?!
Master, get me sake.
Sake, sake. Sake, okay?
Sake, Sakay...
So sleepy...
...kay.
I wanna pee...
Going to the bathroom...
Since alcohol is his primary source
of energy, he's always requesting
more sake from his master.
...kay.
The 'kays were coming from you?!
That wasn't a verbal tic? It was
just the ramblings of a drunkard?!
Hey, somebody in there? Tell me...
...kay.
What the heck? There's no response...
Oh, I forgot about Gin-san.
Guardian Spirit TP Knight
Guardian Spirit TP Knight.
Why are you a spirit now?!
The ill-will over a lack of TP and
nobody bringing it to him brings
this spirit of Sakata Gintoki to life
every morning.
You turn into a spirit over no paper?
You do this crap every morning?!
While wandering to Matsu**to Kiyoshi for
toilet paper, it also walks Sadaharu as
his makeshift guardian spirit.
You were the one walking Sadaharu?!
Take care of him.
My ass! You guys are totally useless!
Kabuki District Sports Meet
Thank you all for taking time out of
your busy schedules to be here today.
Kabuki District Sports Meet
Jeez, why do old men and cabaret
girls have to race one another?
Old men and cabaret girls
would be one thing...
But all I'm seeing is a
great underworld war!
To Be Continued
Guardian Spirits Are Also
a Part of the Soul
You know, this isn't even the
right season for a sports meet!
Taking part in a big sports meet
while listening to Jingle Bells
has its own charm.
But what becomes of Pachi-boy's glasses,
which have turned into
something quite bizarre?