Gintama
Slip Arc
An Idol's Badge of Honor
Oedo Dome
To hell with that. Even a normal
meet-and-greet doesn't sit right with me.
BDZ48's Request!! Watch this program in a bright room
and at a safe distance from your TV ♥
If you're holding a toilet meet-and-greet,
they might as well all work at Yoshiwara.
Is that really the issue here, Tsukuyo-san?
No need to tell me. I've always
been the producer's cum dumpster.
You keep your mouth shut!
Idol or not, as a samurai, I could
never grab something so filthy.
The only things a samurai should grab
are swords, dirt on powerful people,
control of the Yagyu Family and
the right to its inheritance,
stocks, and rice balls.
Don't make rice balls with a hand that
touched all that filth, you celeb samurai!
Besides, shaking hands from a
toilet would be rude to the fans.
We want to treat our fans better.
On that note,
let's have the fans enter the toilet instead.
Treat your fans better!
Also, keeping hygiene in mind,
they can hold Clift's fate in their hands.
A Mad Hand
Appeared
Don't treat fans like the Mad Hands in DQ!
And don't pull on Clift's leg! Quit pulling
our leg by being so useless, Clift!
And despite everything that happened,
let's flush it all away and
call it water under the bridge.
They won't get flushed!
Not even the large option will flush your
evil deeds and Clift's feelings away!
It's the same principle
as the Gintama movies.
The moment we get the fans
inside, we've already won.
After that, the money will flow in even
if the movie's a steady stream of shit.
Enough with the outrageous statements!
Don't put us in the same boat
as your rip-off cabaret club!
H-Hey, what happened in there?
Uh, I think...
I touched something soft
that starts with "cli."
"Cli"? Something soft?!
And then water came bursting out...
Holy water came bursting out?!
I-I'm lining up for Otae-chan!
She seems prim and proper, but is
actually really bold! She's the best!
By some miracle, it caused a
misunderstanding and formed a line!
There, there.
Don't rush, guys. Enter
the toilet in turn, okay?
Well, since a line's formed,
let's just go with it.
Pfft! Don't make me laugh!
What part of that woman is soft?
As you can see, she's a legendary Bigfoot
whose entire body is the Rockies!
Sacchan...
Could you not get all jealous because
nobody's coming to your toilet?
Be a good little monkey and ride
on someone else's back, would you?
Otae...
A monkey on the back is an idiom that means
having a problem, not a literal monkey.
Has your brain turned into a rock, too?
Hey! Boss lady, Sacchan!
And I'm saying you can ride
these filthy men bareback.
Did you hear that, guys?
This is what Otae's really like!
Who the hell are you two fighting?!
What are you saying?
Before being a battle to decide the top idol,
this is a vote-off between
Diamond Vacuum members!
Who the hell cares about that?!
I won't let anyone else be center.
You guys are better off lining up
for me instead of this Jezebel.
Hey, don't you want to meet-and-greet me?
I've got two much softer
things than she does.
Look right here.
On second thought, I'm going for Sacchan!
She may wear glasses, but she's got
a bombshell body! She's the best!
Why, you little bitch!
I'm gonna be the center!
You can spew all the holy water
you want in the wagon, Clift!
No... You need to hold me more gently.
Hey! What the hell are you guys doing?!
If you shake that hard,
you'll crush my two
soft balls!
They're just Brey's golden orbs!
What the hell are you doing?!
This has turned into a meet-and-greet
for DQ48's wagon members!
Where'd you even find them?!
Clift and Brey needed to get rid of
their worries before the final battle!
You two are Booger Diamonds
48's Clift and Brey!
Exactly.
Good job, Clift, Brey.
Consider DQ48's Alena and McRyan.
Do you know why most people pick
Alena out of these two fighters?
That's because unlike McRyan, who is all
alone, Alena has Clift and Brey with her.
No way!
Yes way. They're just
like an idol group, too.
The center Alena's star shines brighter
amidst the darkness that is Clift and Brey.
Which means...
On second thought, Kyubei-chan's the best!
Unlike those two sluts, she's a pure tomboy!
Plus, she's got eyepatch and twin tails moe!
Orthodox really is best!
Go, Alena!
Walk over the corpses of Clift and Brey!
I forgot Alena could spam critical hits.
Don't touch me!
Turns out Alena has the
biggest, Psaro-tier darkness.
You've gotta be kidding me!
What did she even come here for?!
G-Give me some time.
I'm slowly getting used to it.
I think I'll be able to overcome it
once I throw another 1,500 of them.
The fans won't recover from that!
Then why don't you throw Clift 1,500 times?
And Brey, too.
Don't listen to those dark voices!
Spare Clift and Brey already!
Stop it, Kyubei.
Don't push yourself.
Tsukuyo-dono?
If you can't hold hands with men,
then I can just hold your share as well.
But I can't place such a burden on you.
Don't worry. I cast aside my femininity,
but ah'm still a woman of Yoshiwara.
Ah'm prepared to bear the sins of man.
Ah'm moe!
Why are you freaking out over her?!
We still had our ultimate weapon, the
female hero who backs up Alena's party!
She looks like a cool, aloof beauty,
but she's kind enough to look out for others!
Tsukuyo-chan is the best!
This is our chance!
My, aren't we popular, Tsukuyo-san.
You two get back in the wagon right now!
After that popularity poll, you want to
win the Diamond Vacuum vote-off, too?
Popularity Poll Arc (Episodes 182 - 184) November 2009
Of course a Yoshiwara woman would
know all about the casting couch.
You still haven't gotten over
what happened eight years ago?!
But the center always has
the spotlight on her.
So as fellow members, we really need
you to be more careful about things.
Female Hero Sends Clift to the Wagon!!
The Two Disappear Into the Wagon\Where Brey Awaits...
What kinda scandal is that?!
And why are you guys fabricating
stories to bring down your bandmate?!
How will you take responsibility for this?
Sending you to the Hakata wagon won't
be enough. You'll be sent to Indonesia!
Your shitty organization
doesn't exist in Indonesia!
I don't recall any of that,
but I guess it's okay if it'll
get me out of this stupid mess.
It had zero effect on her!
That laid-back attitude of
yours is really annoying!
Want me to cast Thwack on you?!
Be honest! You want to be center too, right?
Look, if you wanna play center
field or whatever base in baseball,
first get nine people to play with!
Don't play dumb with me!
Knock it off! Your ugly infighting
is weirding out the fans!
Oh, wait!
We were kidding! That was
just a comedy opening act!
Come back!
Uh, excuse me. Can I just, like,
take a dump?
Whoa! It's totally sticking out!
We don't need play-by-play for that!
My poop is as loose and sloppy as
Booger Diamonds 48's morals!
Their behavior sticks out
so much in the idol sphere,
both the fans and my poop
scattered all over the place!
Quit telling us about how your dump is going!
Meanwhile, Galaxy Kingdom Bitches
48 are nearly in four digits!
There's no telling what's going on
behind those bewitching curtains,
but the fans are being rendered
spineless one after another!
It's all over, Booger Diamonds 48.
Guess we'll have to do something about
their mystery meet-and-greet after all.
Not yet.
Booger Diamonds 48 isn't finished yet.
Terakado Tsu isn't finished yet!
Not as long as the captain
of the Terakado Tsu Fanclub,
Shimura Shinpachi, is still here.
I'll stop them.
So Kagura-chan, Otsu-chan,
the rest is in your hands.
Captain of the Terakado Tsu
Fanclub, Shimura Shinpachi.
Do you really want a taste
of our meet-and-greet?
Did you forget what happened to
your friends when they tried us?
Otsu-chan...
As long as you keep singing,
your fans won't go anywhere.
Even back when you didn't have any fans,
you still had fun singing on the roadsise.
Someone who was given strength
by watching you is still here.
Just as your voice has cheered
us on when we were sad and hurt,
there's a fan still here who will cheer
you on when you are sad and hurt.
If you've lost everything, you can
just start over from that spot.
If you'll sing, I'll gladly come
see you there again and again...
At that concert hall for just the two of us.
No matter what happens,
I will be Terakado Tsu's first and last fan.
How amusing.
By getting through our meet-and-greet,
you want to stir up the undecided
fans and that cowardly girl?
Well, let's see you try.
Just like you wanted, we'll make
you Terakado Tsu's last ever fan
by enslaving your heart!
Right back at you.
I'm Shimura Shinpachi, captain
of the Terakado Tsu Fanclub.
Here I come!
Sh-Shinpachi!
That was quick!
What's wrong with you? After all that
big talk, you got destroyed in a flash!
You got stripped to your underwear
at an incredible speed!
Even her oldest fan and white knight
is just a rotten virgin nerd.
Our meet-and-greet can entrance anyone in
one shot, no matter whose fan they are.
Now, Terakado Tsu has
not a single fan left...
Once I get home, I'm gonna
throw away all my porn mags.
But as for Otsu-chan's CDs,
I won't throw a single one away.
My antenna? Did he...
Wow, Shimaru has made a successful return!
And what's going on here?
Miss Bitchie is suddenly writhing in pain!
I thought it was strange how one handshake
could turn anyone into a Galaxy
Kingdom Bitches 48 fanatic.
Selling dreams is your job?
That's not it.
What you were showing them was just an
illusion, Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48!
C-Curse you!
Having lost her antenna, Miss Bitchie
has turned into a different person!
Th-That's not all! From behind
the bewitching curtains,
unfamiliar uggo idols are
tumbling out one after another!
Shin-chan's right.
Fans of any other idol would've been fine,
but you ran out of luck when
you picked a fight with us.
Your brainwashing won't work on us.
Because...
We're the universe's greatest fans
of the universe's greatest idol!
Because we're the Terakado
Tsu Fanclub, dynamite!
Taka-chin! Guys!
C-Can you believe it? The Terakado
Tsu Fanclub is back in action!
With their sheer love for Otsu-chan, they
exposed the brainwashing shenanigans!
No way!
Our number one idols in the universe!
The shocking truth is making the
Galaxy Kingdom Bitches fans waver!
Wait, the count went down to zero!
It has been deemed invalid
due to brainwashing!
Booger Diamonds 48 have pulled off
an miraculous last-ditch comeback!
Let it be heard across the universe, men.
Who the universe's greatest idol with
the universe's greatest fans is.
Booger Diamonds 48 Fanclub, let's go!
L-O-V-E Otsu!
L-O-V-E Kagura!
Let's go cheer them on, too.
The fanclub's Booger Diamonds 48
chant echoes across the arena.
Their overwhelming passion
is infecting the now recovered
Galaxy Kingdom Bitches fans!
Wh-What's this noise?!
How dare you expose an idol's hidden
face, that which mustn't be seen!
Mysterious sound waves are being emitted
by all of Galaxy Kingdom Bitches 48.
If you found out, all we have to
do is brainwash you all once again.
Keep dancing within the fantasies that
are idols for the rest of your lives...
That's...
Looks like this is the kind
of handshake you need.
Booger Diamonds 48's Kagura
stops Miss Bitchie!
In these final stages, she's turning
it into an actual fight of hands!
What are you morons doing?
Hurry up and brainwash...
What's this awful noise?
The time has come to show you
the fruits of our training.
Th-That's...
Kagura-chan, leave the backing to us!
Go grab idol stardom with your hands!
It's the backing band!
Diamond Vacuum's overwriting the mystery
sound waves with terrifying dissonance!
Suffering fans,
screaming fanclub,
and groaning backing band.
All of their fates now rest
in the hands of those two!
Is this really a meet-and-greet?
No, this is a battle with their idol careers
on the line! A real meet-and-beat!
Do you really think you
have the right to stop us?
Showing illusions and brainwashing
is something all idols do.
Beneath the surface, idols
are filthy people, too.
They hide that filth with cosmetic
surgery and show off their fake beauty.
They hide that filth by putting on an
act and showing off their fake purity.
The dreams you people are having are
nothing but illusions wrapped in lies!
All we did was perfect those illusions
and make them more beautiful!
And we did it to show you the
dreams that you wanted to see!
You can't call those dreams.
It's just giving up.
Sure, idols dig their nostrils,
take dumps, and have ***, too.
They cause scandals at times and
get down in the dumps at others.
But to make their pathetic selves
stand proud in the spotlight,
they discipline themselves, strive to
improve, and struggle to stand on stage.
You laugh that off as a mere illusion?
Well, you're wrong.
That's not an illusion. It's an ideal.
The dream to crawl toward one's ideal.
That's what idols are all about.
Just like samurai,
they're seekers of the ultimate dream.
Sorry to keep you waiting, menthol.
And what those morons are having
is a real dream they're
pursuing with their idols.
I-It can't be. Why is she here?
Idols really are best in a group.
Our diamond is shining
especially bright right now,
thanks to us massive boogers.
Did they believe that she would come here?
Were we—no, was this entire
event and its ugly battles—
just a massive booger to make the
diamond called Otsu shine brighter?!
You were using us all along?!
Kagura-chan! Guys!
Otsu.
It wasn't for long, but I had
fun being an idol with you.
Let them hear it... Our
Booger Diamonds 48's song.
The song of real idols, which can blow
away all illusions and brainwashing!
Y-You little!
Guys! Don't let some illusion control you!
Take back your dreams!
Listen to our song!
And...
Even if you hate Booger Diamonds 48,
please don't come to hate Terakado Tsu!
Please lend me your ears.
Fellow members who have walked with me,
fans who have cheered me on,
and rivals who have competed with me.
All of you have been my pillar of support.
You are all part of Booger Diamonds 48,
and I dedicate this song to you.
This is An Idol's Badge of Honor.
La la la, idol
Accel, consul, it's dreams that we sell
Idol, idol, idling
Even on the edge, we've got the handling
That scandal back then
Was a summer sentence
I know it's do or die, yes
I could end up doing pillow business
Even that day of the month is safe and secure
Scarlet, blood ruby, an idol's badge of honor
La la la, idol
Foot soldier, loot and plunder, pillow seller
Idol, idol, idling
We can't swerve around aging
Oedo Dome
How ironic it is
that the stage on which an idol
stands to give people dreams
is built on the wrecks of
countless other dreams.
But that's why she shines brightly,
like a lone star in the dark.
She will walk over our dreams
and those of her friends
and continue down this path
of chaos we call idol stardom.
I don't know if you'll be able to
make up for what you've sacrificed.
You just let go of a talent
that could surpass Otsu.
She has the ruthlessness
to take down her enemies,
and the selflessness to cast
herself aside to help her friends.
A diamond covered in boogers,
with two totally contrasting faces.
Gin-san, Kagura-chan!
Wait a second. Aren't you gonna watch?
Yeah. I asked her if she
would like to keep at it,
Damn it, I couldn't make any money again.
but she refused, saying she was
already part of an idol group.
It's too bad, but she's fine that way.
I mean, she shines brightest
in that group of three.
Beyond all the cigarettes,
alcohol, and shaved heads,
the one who filled me
with passion again was...
It was you, you, you
Thenk you.
Knock it off already
Otsu-chan really is cute.
But there's something off about her lately.
Look at what she started doing,
even though she's an idol.
Apparently, she was influenced by
an idol group she really loves.
A group that disbanded right
after making its debut.
What was it called, again?
Booger Diamonds 48.
That's it! The phantom idol
group, Booger Diamonds 48!
It's no phantom.
It remains in my heart
as the idol group of dreams!
Preview
Just to let you know in advance,
this isn't a sales promotion
for our upcoming game.
The Line Between Godlike Games and Shitty Games Is Paper-Thin
We're just messing around.
There you have it,
so keep that in mind, all of you.
Next time, we're again
going with wave, wind,
and standing all the way!