Go! Shock!! Gourmet!! Gourmet!!
Go! Shock!!
Friends who can eat the same dream
Friends who share the same future
With you guys
It’s first-rate gourmet my way!
If we join forces
We’ll be invincible
Come on, let’s show ‘em
Delicious food gives life
So be thankful for everything and
Let’s eat!!
We can’t lose!! We can’t be stopped!!
We ain’t gonna let ‘em have that
We’re gonna win it!! Shock!
Shock! Gourmet king!!
Spiked Punch!! Infinity!!
I’ll punch through with this fist
First-rate gourmet my way!
Let’s gather ‘round the table
For the sake of tomorrow
Let’s go! Go! Gourmet!!
Someone once said...
So plump and soft, you can't
help but say "It's delicious"
about the first-rate rice
that can be harvested
from the rice field growing
on this horse's back...
Delicious Horice!
There are exquisite cherries that
grow just like lily of the valley...
Cherries of the Valley!
The world is in the Gourmet Age...
An age in which people quest for
yet unknown culinary delights!
There are two training ingredients left
on the IGO President, Ichiryu's list.
One is somewhere in the Lost Forest,
the Human World's vastest sea of trees.
I know it's in there,
but the area is so vast that
I can't pinpoint its location.
Fortune-telling Sushi
Monchy
Toriko decided to have Monchy, the
fortune-telling sushi crafstman,
divine the ingredient's exact location,
but first he has to gather
fillings for a Fortune Roll.
We got it!
That's the Madam Fish?! It's huge!
After the Madam Fish, they next
set their sights on capturing
King Vinegar, the king of all
vinegars, on Firewater Island.
You think I can make it with the
Madam Fish and King Vinegar alone?!
King Vinegar
That's not nearly enough fillings!
They continued to gather
fillings for the Fortune Roll.
Toriko and Komatsu set out
to capture the Durian Bomb,
the stinkiest ingredient in the world!
Uh-oh! Oh, boy!
They collapsed a countless number
of times from the tremendous stink,
but were finally able to
obtain the Durian Bomb.
However...
Are we doomed to live as
totally smelly characters?
Too Huge! The Giant Fortune Roll,
Completed with a Pro Wrestling Move!
I-I'm just grateful, right, Komatsu?!
We're not stinky characters anymore!
That's right, Toriko-san! Now
I can finally go back to work!
Who would've figured, the
method to dissipate the stink
of the Durian Bomb is to eat its fruit!
Terry, you steered clear of me too
'til the stink went away, huh?
I thought I'd never get to
touch this soft fur ever again!
By the way, Toriko-san,
after gathering all those materials for the
Fortune Roll, they're still not enough?
Nope!
But we just got one more to go!
What are you, stupid?!
What are we gonna do without
seaweed?! Go get some, dumbass!
Monchy went on about needing
seaweed to wrap the Fortune Roll.
Seaweed?!
Another basic ingredient he doesn't have...
So I thought we'd go to a place I'm familiar
with to get some delicious seaweed.
Get some?
Yeah.
There it is!
That hill!
This scent brings back memories...
It hasn't changed a bit.
You know this place, Toriko-san?
Yep.
An old friend lives here.
Fork Shield!
Knife!
What is this?!
Hey!
I'm no poacher!
That's a fine way to greet me!
I am Akimaru of the Gourmet
Knight Four Seasons Clan.
Please forgive my rash rudeness.
Gourmet Knight?
Then, Toriko-san...
Uh-huh.
Toriko-san! Komatsu-san!
Long time no see!
I was right! Takimaru-san!
Yo, Takimaru!
What's wrong? You suddenly show up here...
What?!
I'm just in the area to get an ingredient.
That aside, Takimaru,
it looks like your cells have evolved
some since the last time I saw you.
You've really developed!
T-Thank you!
But what was that attack about?
An order from your leader?
Of course, it was my order.
Maybe it was a bit too lukewarm
of a greeting for you, though...
You wanna know why?
'Cause you guys are light eaters!
Right, Ai?!
It's been a while, Toriko.
I hear you took good care of
our Takimaru that last time.
I thank you.
Aw, I don't need any thanks.
More importantly...
...you look well.
I'm relieved you're not dead!
Same here!
Don't overestimate Takimaru, Toriko.
Ai...
Takimaru saved your life.
Give him credit for his development.
Among our ranks, he's still green.
I see...
Sorry, I didn't introduce myself.
I'm Yukimaru of the Blue Sky Clan.
I'm Raimaru, also of the Blue Sky Clan.
Kagemaru, Hidden Leaves Clan.
Tsukimaru, Milky Way Clan.
Certainly, you all seem very impressive.
A team made up of the best
and the brightest, huh?
But you're all too skinny!
Are you gettin' enough to eat?!
Hey, knock it off!
We have precepts about humble fare.
Why don't you cut back a little bit?
What's that?! Like I'd ever cut back!
That's right, I'm sure you
live a life of debauchery!
Try fasting once.
Forget it!
I ain't interested in any
Gourmet Knight teachings!
So that's Gourmet Hunter Toriko...
If you don't eat more meat,
you're gonna keel over again!
So it really was true that he and
Aimaru-san are old friends...
Mind your own business!
Our humble fare is healthy for the body!
But this is the most I've
ever seen Aimaru-san speak...
No matter how good it is for the body,
it's pointless if it makes you weak!
By the way, Komatsu-san...
What was that?! Belittling
Gourmet Knights like that
Exactly what ingredient are
you looking for in this area?
will only get you hurt!
Get hurt?! Is that right?!
Seaweed, but I don't know the details...
Seaweed? Oh, maybe it's Eco Seaweed...
Eco Seaweed?
There's a village near here called Eco Land
and there's seaweed you can take from
the shells of turtles that live there.
The area is called the Humble Fare Zone
since there are only simple ingredients,
but that seaweed is outstanding.
If you'd like, I can take you there tomorrow.
You read my mind, Takimaru!
That's exactly why we came
here, so I'm countin' on you!
R-Right!
Hey!
I'm not done talking to you, Toriko!
You should ditch that ill-mannered leader!
Who's got ill manners?!
Hey!
This is good!
Humble fare ain't bad, actually.
Right?!
So, are you ready?
Ready to get GOD...
Of course.
And I've already assembled my Full Course...
Modest Grass
Hors d'Oeuvre: Modest Grass.
Graceful Soup
Soup: Graceful Soup.
Frugal Sardine
Fish: Frugal Sardine.
Love Pork
Meat: Love Pork.
Simple Rice
Main Dish: Simple Rice.
Inexhaustible Potato
Salad: Inexhaustible Potato.
Plum Peach
Dessert: Plum Peach.
Quiet Tea
Drink: Quiet Tea.
Awesome.
All simple, yet every last one
is a wonderful ingredient.
But it seems the competition for GOD isn’t
just between the two of us, Toriko.
Yeah, well...
But no worries there.
Even if it comes to war,
I'm gonna get GOD.
Relax, Toriko.
Even if I get GOD first,
I'll be a nice guy and share it
with you for old times' sake.
Don't talk nonsense, Ai.
I'm gonna get it first.
No, I will.
And then I'll share it, like I said.
I'm gonna share it with you!
You don't get it!
Who do you think you are?!
Who are you?!
What?!
There they go again...
There's no way a blockhead
like you could ever get it!
Toriko-san isn't usually so
quick to get into a fight...
You know, muscles aren't everything!
You ought to try a little temperance!
The same with Aimaru-san...
Temperance?! What the hell is that?!
Well, I guess they can fight like
that because they're so close.
I never ate it, so bring me some!
Let's pay them no mind.
Yeah...
It seems like an idyllic village...
This village doesn't have electricity,
gas, or even running water.
The villagers rely 100% on the
blessings already provided by nature.
So that's why it's called Eco Land, huh?
Living together with nature, naturally...
There's no village that's kinder
to the planet and living beings.
Hey!
Stupid wild rabbits!
Always stealin' my food...!
Morons!
Gimme back my onigiri, dumbasses!
There's somebody who's not kind at all...
Idiots!
What the hell are you lookin' at, jerk?!
Are you stupid?!
N-No, I'm not stupid!
Huh? Monchy-san?
Mayor Nonchy!
It's been a long time!
Takimaru? What's up?!
We came here to get something...
What is it?
Mayor... Nonchy...?
Oh, I see!
So that's what Monchy told you to get!
What a maroon!
Mayor, do you know Monchy-san?
Monchy is Mayor Nonchy's
younger twin brother.
I kind of thought so!
Actually, we're quintuplets.
Really?!
But who cares about that nonsense?!
Come on, tonight, we feast!
Fill yourselves up!
Huh? Mayor...
This house has gas?
What are you, stupid?!
There's no gas in the village!
Then what was that...
An Eco Eco Skunk!
It shares the gas from its farts!
For tap water, I've got
a Reservoir Sea Cucumber!
It comes in handy.
For when I want a simple
fire, I use Fire Moss Balls.
If you wash and dry 'em out, you
can use 'em again and again!
I notice that you also have electricity...
Night is about to fall.
Maybe I'll turn on the power.
Power?
The ingredient that you guys
want is over there, too.
Look! That's a Solar Turtle.
It's a turtle equipped with natural
solar panels on its shell!
It's huge!
All of the private homes in this village
have this power plug.
If you connect it to the
Solar Turtle's tail...
Amazing!
There are small Solar Turtles that
have as much power as batteries
as well as gigantic turtles that
can power up the whole town.
Those are some blessed turtles!
Incidentally, when their power runs out,
the surface of their
shells peels off lightly,
and that is exactly...
...Eco Seaweed!
What beautiful seaweed!
The quality is so high that I can
smell its fresh flavor from here!
However, I ain't gonna give
it to you for free, Toriko.
Actually, the weather's been lousy recently,
so the town's Solar Turtles
can't generate enough power.
At a time like this, Solar Turtles
can be charged up manually.
Manually?!
So this is what you meant?!
It's charging up more and more!
What incredible speed!
It seems like the turtle's perked up, too!
Come on, power up, power
up, power up, power up!
Fully charged!
Hey!
Charge mine, too!
Please!
What?!
There are that many Solar Turtles?!
Fine!
Bring 'em over!
Power up, power up, power up,
power up, power up, power up!
Power up!
Alright!
We got a ton of Eco Seaweed!
You did it, Toriko-san!
With this seaweed, I bet even Monchy
will be happy enough to make it for us!
I think you're right!
Toriko, give that idiot Monchy a message:
"You're an idiot!"
Sure. Thank you, Mayor Nonchy!
Thank you too, Takimaru!
Not at all.
It was fun getting to hang out
with you again, Toriko-san.
Tell Ai I said goodbye, too.
I will.
Alright, let's take this stuff
and be on our way, Komatsu!
Right!
Okay!
You gathered so much stuff, you make
me think you're stupid, Toriko!
It really was tough, Monchy!
Especially the Durian Bomb...
Idiot! This stinks! It really stinks!
But with all this, it should be enough.
Dopes!
We'll need all these as fillings for
the place you want me to divine!
1-2! 1-2!
What's that?
Monchy!
We brought it!
Yeah! Thanks!
C-Cutting board?!
A cutting board... ring?!
Alright, let's see it!
This is gonna be a spectacle!
Okay, guess I'll get started!
Don't tell me... you're
going to make it here?!
Of course, dumbass!
You threw it...
Toriko! The gong!
R-Right!
Let the match begin!
What is this?!
There it is! Monchy Press!
You can't make sushi without it!
That's Monchy! He never neglects the basics!
Really?!
And now I hoist this over my
head! Monchy Hyper Back Drop!
This is sushi preparation?!
Yeah! Awesome preparation!
It's also Monchy's way of expressing
gratitude and love to the ingredients!
Are you an idiot?!
Certainly, it is getting softer,
and the savoriness appears
to be concentrating...
You reek, dumbass!
Toriko, the count!
R-Right! 1...
Stinks!
That was fast!
Monchy Arm Lock!
I don't think that does anything...
Seaweed Roll Suplex!
That was close!
You can't let your identity be revealed?!
Okay!
What are you, stupid?!
This is...
...Monchy's Fortune Roll!
It's too huge!
I hope Toriko-san and Komatsu-san
safely make it to their training ingredient.
Me too.
But you know,
the Lost Forest...
Something incredible awaits them there.
Now we can go... to the Lost Forest!
Under our feet, over our heads
The world is spinning
A dream flower
Is blooming, blooming
Tell me the rest, come on
Lead me by the hand
And take me with you
Don't leave me here alone
Red shoes
I can't take off
I'm the only one dancing
Find Yun! Run, Run, Yun!
Alright, the popular new segment!
Yun is hiding somewhere in the image
you're about to see, so please find him!
This'll be a little more
difficult than last time!
Yun's Hiding Level is 3!
Can you find Yun in the allotted
time limit of ten seconds?!
Let's have a heaping helping of start!
Have you found him yet?
It's hard?
I'll just give a one-gram hint for those
of you who don't know where he is.
Something looks kind of suspicious
in the center part of the screen...
Well, did you get it?
Yun is right here!
How was it?
Next time, Yun will hide in
another interesting place,
so everyone look for him, okay?
And now on to our next segment!
Th-there it is!
There it is! The legendary 10-star restaurant, Vanishing Japanese Cuisine!
Wait, no way! Is that really...?!
Put Your Hands Together and Bow! Gourmet National Treasure, Chin Chin-Chin, Appears!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!