Go! Shock!! Gourmet!! Gourmet!!
Go! Shock!!
Friends who can eat the same dream
Friends who share the same future
With you guys
It’s first-rate gourmet my way!
If we join forces
We’ll be invincible
Come on, let’s show ‘em
Delicious food gives life
So be thankful for everything and
Let’s eat!!
We can’t lose!! We can’t be stopped!!
We ain’t gonna let ‘em have that
We’re gonna win it!! Shock!
Shock! Gourmet king!!
Spiked Punch!! Infinity!!
I’ll punch through with this fist
First-rate gourmet my way!
Let’s gather ‘round the table
For the sake of tomorrow
Let’s go! Go! Gourmet!!
Someone once said...
In a sea of soup stock where the
best oden ingredients float,
there are penguins with bodies made
of first-rate, fluffy hanpen...
Hanpenguins!
There are swans with
exquisite banana feathers
and heads of the best quality eggplant...
Bananaswan Eggplant!
The world is in the Gourmet Age...
An age in which people quest for
yet unknown culinary delights!
The IGO President, Ichiryu,
sent Toriko and Komatsu
to get another training
ingredient, Bubble Fruit.
They made their way through the Lost Forest,
but the end of the Fortune Roll was scooped
away along with a chunk of the forest.
Toriko and Komatsu chased after
Chirin, a possible suspect.
That led them to the legendary
Vanishing Japanese Cuisine.
Vanishing Japanese Cuisine
Chiru, the master chef of the restaurant,
told Toriko and Komatsu that Bubble
Fruit is in the Chowlin Temple.
But a customer of the restaurant is Chin
Chin-Chin, master of Chowlin Temple!
People Without Gratitude Aren't
Welcome! Terrifying Chowlin Temple!
T-This person is...
...the master of Chowlin Temple?!
And one of the four Gourmet
National Treasures in the world?!
Honor the Food
Chin Chin-Chin!
Chin Chin-Chin, Master of Chowlin Temple
I am indeed Chin Chin-Chin.
That's got a certain ring to it.
Toshio and Kosugi...
Um, those aren't our names...
It's Toriko and Komatsu!
I've heard about you two from
the IGO President, Ryuichi.
Really?!
Except the old man's name is Ichiryu.
C-Chiru-san, you know the
master of Chowlin Temple?!
Yes. When I was a child, I learned
Gourmet Etiquette from the master.
Chirin, you should also go
to the temple for training.
Nah. Thanks, but I'll pass.
I hear it's really strict there.
So you learned your delicate cooking
techniques at Chowlin Temple, Chirin-san?
I want to learn them, too!
Then this is perfect!
Apparently, the old man already
told him what we're after.
Sounds like getting this ingredient
will be smooth sailing!
Smooth sailing?
Follow me, Tommy and Kotani.
You're still getting our names wrong...
Toriko-sama, Komatsu-sama...
By all means, please stop
here again on your way home.
I'm sure you'll be able to eat this
restaurant's entire full course by then.
Thank you.
We'll definitely stop by.
We'll be back soon.
That is, if you can make it back soon...
Good timing. You can accompany them there.
I don't wanna go! I don't
wanna! I don't wanna!
By the way, Chiro...
It's Chiru.
Granny Chiyo still hasn't come back?
No.
Unfortunately, the former
master chef is still gone.
What on earth could have become
of someone like Granny Chiyo?
Inform me immediately upon her return.
I want to eat Granny Chiyo's food again.
U-Um...
What is it, Konishi?
I-It's Komatsu...
C-Could it be that the Chiyo-san
you referred to before is...
Yes.
The first master chef of
Vanishing Japanese Cuisine,
Delicate Cooking Chiyo.
I-I knew it...
The chef who was paid 100 million
yen for every cut of her knife...
She was a genius, on a par with Gourmet
National Treasure Setsuno-san!
She was always in the top five
of the chef rankings, too.
I heard that with her overpowering charisma,
she had passionate disciples
all over the world.
But I believe her name and ranking
dropped off the chart a few years ago.
And speaking of chef ranking,
I wonder how Take-chan is doing these days.
Granny Chiyo suddenly vanished
one day, without a trace.
No one knows the cause.
But since then,
the number of chefs disappearing
worldwide has risen precipitously.
Could it be...?
Don't tell me she was kidnapped?
That's a hard pill to swallow.
Granny Chiyo's skills were so formidable
that she was originally an assistant
instructor at Chowlin Temple.
Incidentally, she was my partner.
So she's not so weak that
they'd be able to kidnap her.
Chiyo-san was your partner, Master?
Yes, well...
But more importantly, Tominaga and Kojima...
Those names aren't even close.
You'd best watch your step.
Watch our step?
Hey!
What the hell is this?!
The ground has disappeared!
The Disappearing Forest...
It's a forest with grass,
trees, and dirt formed
out of the same materials as
Vanishing Japanese Cuisine.
Well, you did make a mess in the forest
eating that giant Fortune Roll.
So perhaps this forest is invisible
to rude fellows like you.
Wait, are you the one who
took away our Fortune Roll?!
Indeed. The Fortune Roll
itself was quite tasty.
You know, I couldn't get
enough of that Madam Fish.
The Durian Bomb reeked to high
heaven but it was wonderful, too.
Wait a second! Then you scooped
out part of the forest, too?!
Toriko-san, maybe the forest was there,
but we just couldn't see it!
Try to see it now.
Look at the scenery before your eyes with
a gaze full of gratitude and respect.
C-Come on, gratitude and respect?!
Put your hands together. And then bow.
Put your hands together,
Toriko-san! And be thankful...
You may be able to see it.
The place you were looking for...
Grat...itude!
Chowlin Temple
T-This is...
I don't believe it!
So you can finally see it...
Welcome to Chowlin Temple,
the temple of Food Etiquette.
T-This is Chowlin Temple?!
We were already here?!
Just like with Vanishing Japanese Cuisine...
A temple made of invisible materials!
It's more than just being invisible...
Come closer and you'll understand.
But I remind you to always keep
etiquette in mind going forth.
Etiquette?
Display gratitude and respect.
That's what I mean by etiquette,
Tonkichi and Kohinata.
The names are getting farther off the mark...
I'd say that's a lack of
etiquette right there.
Well, anyway, we arrived here safely.
Yep. You're right about that.
Now let's just grab the Bubble Fruit and go!
What the...?!
Komatsu!
What was that?!
Well, well. So soon?
Toriko-san!
Fork Shield!
Spiked Punch!
W-What is this?!
I told you not to forget etiquette!
My building here,
its materials aren't so shy around strangers
that they conceal their appearance.
Sometimes they also attack
people who are rude.
The materials are quite unforgiving.
Attack?!
Hot! Hot!
I can't take it!
I'm quitting this hellish temple!
Hey, wait!
Master, it's terrible! The temple!
It lost its temper at a rude
person and burst into flames!
Hot!
It's on fire!
This is too dangerous!
At this rate, the Bubble
Fruit will burn up, too!
Alright! I'll handle this somehow!
Spiked Punch!
You did it, Toriko-san!
Oh, boy. You leave me no choice.
Spoon!
There!
You see? The fire is out!
Y-You scooped up the flames?!
Well, I don't expect you to do this much.
But unless you master the art
Chowlin Temple
of Honoring the Food, you won't even
be able to touch the Bubble Fruit.
I forgot...
One of the old man's training
ingredients is here.
Looks like it's not gonna
be an easy job after all.
The temple's attacking!
Knife!
Oh, my. You two have no
etiquette at all, do you...
You'll never be able to enter
the main hall at this rate.
How the hell are we supposed
to show etiquette?!
I already put my hands together
and bowed plenty of times,
but it keeps attackin'!
Well, I'll tell you, Tomato...
It's Toriko, not Tomato!
Your actions are correct,
but there's no heart in it.
What are you talkin' about?!
There's heart in this!
The premise of Honor the Food is
based on the existence of the heart.
When you visit a shrine,
you pray sincerely then,
but the moment it's over, the
feeling weakens, doesn't it?
Gratitude and respect for all things...
Never forgetting that feeling,
even for a moment...
That is the fundamental
mindset to Honor the Food.
Always feel gratitude...
I-It worked!
Even without putting our
hands together and bowing!
It stopped attacking!
Jeez! That was actually simple, Komatsu!
Toriko-san!
Are you okay, Toriko-san?!
I think this is going to take some time...
Listen, you two...
Appreciating food is the same
thing as appreciating life.
By that, I mean your own life
but also all life, everywhere.
Being grateful towards all things is
the foundation of Honoring the Food.
Always displaying respect for
everything seriously and sincerely...
Are you listening to me?
Y-Yes, I'm listening!
I'm concentrating!
I'm totally appreciative!
Very good. This is the
place where you learn that.
Hands together!
Bow!
Thank you for the food!
A-Are all of these people
students of Chowlin Temple?!
That's correct.
We have many students who want
to study Honoring the Food.
100,000 people every year,
from children to adults...
O-One hundred-thousand people?!
Most of them join
Chowlin Temple branches all over the
world and study Honoring the Food there.
But the headquarters here is the
harshest training ground in the world.
T-This is the harshest?
Still, all of these people here
shows there must be a lot to learn.
I wouldn't think many people could
find their way through that forest.
Well, these folks are criminals who
were brought here against their will.
Criminals?!
Hey, are you serious?!
Take Honey Prison, for example...
It's the end of the line for gourmet
criminals, and they're forbidden to leave,
but this is a place where they can
relearn how to Honor the Food.
If they complete the training
successfully, they're released.
But most of them can't withstand the
severe training and flee the temple.
Incidentally, those that do fly the coop
never do make it through the sea of trees.
I can see why that Chirin
kid didn't wanna come here.
Welcome home, Master Chin.
Mr. Ichiryu spoke of new challengers
Honor the Food
for the temple treasure
and this must be them.
Correct, Shoji.
My name is Shu, not Shoji.
I'll introduce you.
This is Tome and Julie.
No, it isn't!
You're getting even further off-base!
It's Toriko and Komatsu!
He's this temple's assistant instructor.
You're not even listening...
Shokichi...
It's Shu, Master Chin.
I'm going to have
Assistant Instructor Schwarz here continue
with your Honor the Food training.
Schwa-chan, show them to the main hall.
I, Shu, will take you there,
Toriko-san of the Four
Kings and Chef Komatsu-san.
I may not be up to the task,
but I'm looking forward to working with you.
If we really have to do this, I'd rather
be taught directly by the Master...
You think I'm not up to it?
Well, didn't you just say that yourself?!
We already have the basics
of Honoring the Food down
and don't have all the time in the
world to get the Bubble Fruit.
On top of that,
there's Spoon, the technique the Master
used to grab hold of those flames.
It's the first time I saw a
delicate technique like that.
If that's a secret technique
of Honoring the Food,
then I definitely wanna be taught
by the one who can use it.
However, the Master's training
is particularly tough.
I don't know if your bodies would hold
up if you're suddenly thrown into it...
Tough?
Yes. Actually,
you two have already received the
training baptism from the Master.
Baptism?
Yes.
The 50-meter-class mountain that plummeted
down Death Falls and right at you...
The Master scooped that out.
The Master threw that mountain at us?!
Is that true?!
I forgot about that...
Hey, it's nothin' to laugh about!
Sorry about surprising you
with that. At the time, um...
Why would you do something like that?!
Actually,
the President requested that I helped
train you from some time back.
The old man?!
To get our feet wet, so to speak, I
gave you a test at that waterfall.
T-Test?! What kind of test is that?!
We nearly died!
But you got through it somehow.
You fellows were amazing.
We barely made it!
What would you have done if we'd died?!
If you'd died, there wouldn't
be anything else to do.
It would've meant that you
weren't worthy of my training.
This guy is scary...
A-And he doesn't even remember our names...
I think that maybe even our
lives are nothing to him...
I was right...
That missing chunk of forest
with the Fortune Roll...
I bet the Master did scoop it out.
Did I do that?
He ain't delicate in the least...
This guy's got a way over
the top personality...
So who would you like to
train with, me or the Master?
Shu-san, please!
Do your very best.
As soon as you master Honoring the Food,
I'll teach you Gourmet Secret Techniques.
Under our feet, over our heads
The world is spinning
A dream flower
Is blooming, blooming
Tell me the rest, come on
Lead me by the hand
And take me with you
Don't leave me here alone
Red shoes
I can't take off
I'm the only one dancing
Find Yun! Run, Run, Yun!
Yun is hiding somewhere in the image
you're about to see, so please find him!
Hiding Level
Yun's Hiding Level is 2!
The allotted time limit is ten seconds!
Are you ready, everyone?
Let's have a heaping helping of start!
Today, the difficulty level is
2, so it's on the easy side.
Well, can you find Yun?
Yun is... right here!
Well? Was it easy today?
For the difficulty level here,
there will be peaks and valleys.
With Toriko's training too, there
are mountain peaks and valleys.
Now on to the next segment!
It's unbelievable, everyone. I'm not sure I believe my own ears.
Toriko has admitted defeat for the first time ever!
Toriko Totally Defeated?! The Delicate and Dynamic Power of Honoring the Food!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!