Go! Shock!! Gourmet!! Gourmet!!
Go! Shock!!
Friends who can eat the same dream
Friends who share the same future
With you guys
It’s first-rate gourmet my way!
If we join forces
We’ll be invincible
Come on, let’s show ‘em
Delicious food gives life
So be thankful for everything and
Let’s eat!!
We can’t lose!! We can’t be stopped!!
We ain’t gonna let ‘em have that
We’re gonna win it!! Shock!
Shock! Gourmet king!!
Spiked Punch!! Infinity!!
I’ll punch through with this fist
First-rate gourmet my way!
Let’s gather ‘round the table
For the sake of tomorrow
Let’s go! Go! Gourmet!!
Someone once said...
There are ants like top-shelf caviar...
Caviants!
There are pansies with delicious
nectar that tastes like champagne...
Champansies!
The world is in the Gourmet Age...
An age in which people quest for
yet unknown culinary delights!
Chiyo, who had joined the evil Gourmet
Corp, arrived at Chowlin Temple.
I've just come to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
Goodbye to all of you, who are
about to move to the "other side".
Chiyo and her cohorts
attacked Chowlin Temple.
Meanwhile, while on Bubble Way with
Master Chin, Toriko attained Food's End.
He successfully captured Bubble Fruit.
Not only before you eat
or while you're eating...
You also respect and appreciate the
ingredients after they're inside your body.
And continuing to feel grateful, even
after they become your flesh and blood,
that's appreciating food to the umpteenth
degree, which is called Food's End.
I didn't almost die.
I did die.
I'm so different from what
I was until just before
that I can't help thinking this way.
It feels like I've been reborn.
Komatsu was happy to be reunited
with his old friend Otake, but...
Now I can say goodbye.
Unrivaled Strength! The One who
Mastered Honoring the Food!
Oh, my. You intend to keep going?
You're no match for me.
Where's Chin-chan?
I said, where is Chin-chan?!
I won't let you...
...even bother the master!
I will...
...protect Chowlin Temple!
You're only an assistant instructor!
Assistant Instructor Kapow!
It's fast!
Hang in there, everyone!
Please! Let me be in time!
Honor the Food!
Instant Blood Drain!
T-Too tough!
My blade broke!
Take-chan... Why?!
Is something wrong?
No wound...
There's no wound!
Even though I felt the pain...!
It's a Revival Knife.
Revival Knife?
The more it cuts, the more it revives.
It's forbidden to use it like
that in the Human World...
...but that was its original function.
Although it's not like no one
does because it's prohibited.
It's just that there are hardly any chefs
who can use this technique.
A forbidden technique... Why...?
Because there are many ingredients
that can't be prepared otherwise...
...in the Gourmet World.
Gourmet World?
That's where I am now.
I believe I challenged
you to surpass me before,
but it seems the gap between
us is only widening.
I could tell after seeing you here
studying that stupid Honoring the Food.
Stupid?!
You're wrong!
You're wrong, Take-chan!
To chefs like us, Honoring the Food
is the most important thing of all!
Your important Honoring the Food...
...is on the verge of obliteration right now.
Listen, Komatsu.
Those who are strong win.
And winning is everything!
You're as naive as ever.
You don't understand anything.
You're the one who doesn't understand!
Toriko-san and I...
We've learned the importance
of Honoring the Food!
We've learned the importance of appreciation!
Toriko, eh?
Come to think of it,
your partner is that Gourmet
Hunter, Toriko, right?
I'm light years ahead of you there, too.
I'll tell you.
My partner...
...is Gourmet Corp's...
Master Chin!
Well, well...
This is a serious situation.
M-Master...
Master! Master!
Well, well...
If it isn't Chin-chan...
Long time no see. I've been waiting for you.
Granny Chiyo...
Why?! Why...
...did you join Gourmet Corp?!
Gourmet Corp?!
It's been ages, but let's
go on a date, Chiyo-chan.
It'll be our last date, Chin-chan.
You know...
...it makes me sad to hear that.
M-Master is going to change locations?
He's going to fight seriously!
That's how strong his opponent...
...Chiyo-san is right now!
I'll be right back.
Take care of the temple until then.
Then let's go, Granny Chiyo!
Master!!
And now it's all over, for the worthless
history of Honoring the Food, too!
Don't be in such a rush, Granny Chiyo.
Honoring the Food will never die.
As long as there are people and food,
it will continue to be passed down!
Is that right?!
Well?
Honoring the Food is good with appreciation,
but can you do it even now?!
Stop it...
Stop it!
Stop it!!
Toriko-san!
Sorry I'm late, Komatsu.
This is a brutal attack.
Toriko-san!
But it's strange...
Even under these circumstances,
I still appreciate.
Toriko-san!
It seems he made it in time.
In fact, I sense quite a
presence emanating from him.
I bet he ate every last bit of
the Bubble Way temple treasure.
What?! He ate the Bubble Fruit?!
More importantly, he sees this situation
and isn't shaken, enraged, or possessing
any other distracting thoughts.
I'd say it's proof that he's perfectly
mastered Honoring the Food.
The way Toriko is right now,
I think we'll be okay.
Spoon Dome!
M-My arm!
Lock!
Master...
Is that your final disciple?
You seem to be very confident in him.
Toriko...
That's right. Toriko...
I was finally able to remember his name.
And the other one, Komatsu, is it?
Names of people who are only pretty
good don't stick in my head.
Chiyo-chan...
I think yours was the last
name I remembered before them.
Are you saying their abilities
are on par with mine?
You're wasting your time.
I'm the only one who can
open a locked Spoon Dome.
Now then...
Let's enjoy
our final date,
Chiyo-chan!
T-Toriko-san?
He's the Gourmet Hunter, Toriko...
Komatsu's partner...
T-Toriko-san!
Please be careful!
It's... That Scum Beast...
It isn't normal!
It looks savage, but it
makes no wasted movements!
It's made up of dozens
of frighteningly powerful Beasts!
And my guess is that among them
is something that uses a similar
technique to Honoring the Food!
Alright...
What kind of man are you...
...Toriko?
Get back, Komatsu.
R-Right!
He's different than the usual Toriko-san.
He's calm...
My hair grew this long because of
the nutrients in the Bubble Fruit.
Gourmet Corp...
If I were the same man I was up to now,
I might've snapped in this situation.
Or, no...
It's not like I'm not angry...
but according to Honoring the Food,
heightening your emotions out of anger
produces wasteful power in the body.
So I'm doing this,
feeling appreciation even for this anger!
To beat you, you know.
It regenerated!
Spiked Punch.
I don't know what "fold" that was,
but it feels like I can keep going.
Toriko-san!
Unbelievable!
He destroyed that Golem with one punch!
I see, Toriko...
But if it were any other way...
...it wouldn't be worth defeating you.
Master! Thank goodness you're okay!
Master!
It can't be!
Come on, appreciation, appreciation!
You'd better appreciate
these circumstances, too!
You...
Under our feet, over our heads
The world is spinning
A dream flower
Is blooming, blooming
Tell me the rest, come on
Lead me by the hand
And take me with you
Don't leave me here alone
Red shoes
I can't take off
I'm the only one dancing
Find Yun! Run, Run, Yun!
Yun is hiding somewhere in the image
you're about to see, so please find him!
Hiding Level
Today, Yun's Hiding Level is 15!
The allotted time limit is 15 seconds!
Is everybody ready?
Let's have a heaping helping of start!
This is Toriko's home, Sweet House.
Where could he be?
The Hiding Level is 15, so
it's a little difficult.
Well, have you found him?
Yun is... right here!
That's Level 15 for you, a really tough one!
Next time, Toriko's in the
final stage of battle at last!
What will happen in the end?!
This is the finest type of battle between true masters!
Toriko's new powers are going to erupt!
"National Treasure Class" One Stroke 100 Million Yen Technique!
Toriko vs Granny Chiyo!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!