Go! Shock!! Gourmet!! Gourmet!!
Go! Shock!!
Friends who can eat the same dream
Friends who share the same future
With you guys
It’s first-rate gourmet my way!
If we join forces
We’ll be invincible
Come on, let’s show ‘em
Delicious food gives life
So be thankful for everything and
Let’s eat!!
We can’t lose!! We can’t be stopped!!
We ain’t gonna let ‘em have that
We’re gonna win it!! Shock!
Shock! Gourmet king!!
Spiked Punch!! Infinity!!
I’ll punch through with this fist
First-rate gourmet my way!
Let’s gather ‘round the table
For the sake of tomorrow
Let’s go! Go! Gourmet!!
Someone once said...
If prepared just right,
this anglerfish will respond to delighted
cries of "Encore!" and come back.
Anglercore created by
Nana Mizuki-san of Tokyo!
Anglercore!
However, if a "double
encore's" worth is eaten,
a white-garbed angel will appear
to gently soothe your malady,
Eggplanurse created by created
by Ryotaro Okiayu-san of Tokyo!
an eggplant that behaves like a nurse...
Eggplanurse!
I'm cured!
The world is in the Gourmet Age...
An age in which people quest for
yet unknown culinary delights!
The Four-Beasts have come from
the Gourmet World to eat humans,
but Toriko and the rest of the
Four Kings have intercepted them!
Meanwhile, Rin and Komatsu have learned
a shocking truth from Ichiryu's message.
Actually, the Four-Beasts aren't four Beasts.
They're one!
There's someone in the shadows
controlling the actual Four-Beasts.
The mastermind who truly
needs to be taken down
is him!
Not knowing the truth, the Four
Kings face the Four-Beasts!
Okay. Here's where we really get to it.
How about I show you my new skills,
gained through Honoring
the Food and Gut Instinct?
Toriko's New Crisis! The Creeping
Main Body of the Four-Beasts!
Toriko!
Go!
They're not known as the
Four Kings for nothing.
What's this?
Something's here!
T-The Four Beasts aren't four Beasts?!
That's too important for the president
to casually almost forget about!
We have to let everyone know, and fast!
Get back, Terry.
From here on out, it's a serious
showdown between me and this thing.
It's do or die.
What do you say we go with a natural,
savage battle, with no hard feelings,
Fang King?
I'm gonna show you... my serious Leg Knife!
Even to you,
it'll deliver a mortal wound if it hits!
Leg Knife!
Not surprised.
You were able to dodge it, huh?
But before I learned Honoring the Food,
I wasn't able to form quite this many.
Flying Fork.
One at a time, with their size and force,
they'd be hard-pressed
to serve you any damage,
but what about en masse?
I'll call it...
Cannon Fork!
At that speed,
you'll be able to avoid it.
I'm sure that's what you're figuring.
That's the Leg Knife you
thought you'd dodged.
Thanks to Honoring the Food and Gut Instinct,
it's become possible for me to have
finer control than ever before.
A tracking-type Knife...
I'll call it Leg Boomerang!
And like I said,
you'll suffer a mortal wound if it hits.
With the damage you've sustained,
you won't be able to avoid this Cannon Fork!
The living eats the living.
That's the law of nature.
And that's why
I have no grudge against you
for intending to eat humans.
I don't think it's an act of evil.
The only thing is...
There are some humans that
just don't make for easy prey.
Thank you for the meal.
He beat a Four-Beast!
He did it!
Toriko!
Hey, look at the screen over there!
Invite Death...
How's Coco doing?!
Inside my body,
I created antibodies that negate
the effects of your poison.
So your poison won't work on me.
So now you'll try a physical attack,
go for hand-to-hand combat, eh?
However,
take this first!
My Poison Arrow!
That arrow I just shot you with?
The tip is made out of a new kind of poison.
I call it Poison Virus!
Poison Virus changes its form,
turning into a poison that the
targeted creature is vulnerable to.
It's a virus that's particularly
effective against creatures that have
many antibodies against poison.
Right now, the virus is searching to
see what kind of poison works on you.
Naturally, you'll try to
kill me before that happens.
Unfortunately for you,
this poison spear will pierce
that thought in an instant.
According to one theory,
when mold spores fly,
they're the fastest things
in the living world.
Now, this poison spear
is made out of poison that's
similar to mold spores.
I'm sure you won't even
realize that it's hit you.
Mold Spear!
Dodging a poison spear that travels
at the speed of light is impossible.
Although it did take me all this
time to produce just one...
Still, in the battle of poisons,
it looks like I'm the winner.
Even a disgusting body like yours
loses some of the sting when it can't move.
There's no point in struggling. Those
tentacles of yours can't even twitch.
It's not my Hair Lock that's
keeping you in check.
Putting Hair Lock on a
strong bastard like you
might result in my hair being torn out.
My hair, which has become much more
sensitive from Honoring the Food,
has already invaded your nervous system
and taken over the movements
of your tentacles.
Hair Marionette!
Even now, you're my puppet.
Although having my hair inside your
body is completely repulsive...
On top of that, I'm deflecting a Hair Punch
with Super Spatula, making it
go back and forth over and over.
It takes some time, but the force
of the punch keeps increasing.
Even with just the scant hair
that I have left to use,
repeatedly employing Super Spatula
lets me build up plenty of power.
Super Hair Shot!
You're ugly even when
you're being blown away.
Voice Meteor Shower alone ain't
enough to bring you down, huh?
I was hopin' it wouldn't be!
But take the destructive force of my punch
an' add sound vibrations...
Let's see what happens.
I'm thinkin' it'll destroy
your body from the inside out!
Beat Punch!
Have you learned anything?
Like you don't wanna be cocky...
...around me!
You'll have plenty of time
to review in the afterlife.
That's your punishment for bein' cocky.
Somethin' weird about this.
I seen countless creatures die,
but that scream ain't
no kind of death rattle.
This guy's life ain't over yet.
What?
Toriko! Coco! Zebra!
Bro, can you hear me?!
Rin!
Huh. So this is a communication device too.
We're in real trouble here! I
found out something important!
The Four-Beasts isn't actually
four Beasts, but one!
What?!
It's not four Beasts?!
Rin, what do you mean?!
We watched the rest of
President Ichiryu's message
and that's what he said.
Terry!
The Four-Beasts is one Beast...
Certainly...
...I can't see
the shadow of death on it yet.
It went underground?!
Heading in that direction... Don't tell me...
Kiss!
What?!
No wonder it didn't let out a death rattle.
What's it doin'?!
Echo Location!
Where do you think you're goin'?!
Cocky bastard!
Let's go, Daruma Horse!
Komatsu! Rin!
Grab hold!
R-Right!
Hey, now what's this about being one Beast?!
What's the deal with this Four-Beasts?!
The president explained it
with images in his message.
Actually, the Four-Beasts aren't
four Beasts. They're one!
The Four-Beasts' main body
is like a control tower.
It grows bulbous seeds of life
on its limbs underground.
Those seeds take several hundred years
to become mature Beasts,
the four Beasts of the Four-Beasts.
The main body releases those four
Beasts into the Human World,
letting them eat to their heart's content.
And when the Beasts return, it takes them in
and absorbs the humans.
This is the Four-Beasts' established pattern.
However,
the last time they were sent
here, I drove them away.
So they didn't eat any humans then.
In fact, they were mortally wounded
when they returned to the main body.
So even the one-pattern Four-Beasts
may change its strategy this time.
It's possible that the main body
itself will head for the Human World.
The main body in the Human World?!
I see. Terry!
The direction you were looking in before
is the center of the Human World!
That's the way!
The Four-Beasts ran away!
The Four-Beasts were driven back!
The Four Kings won!
The human race won!
Terry looks...
...strange.
What is that?
It's... Oh, no!
What is it?!
What's wrong?!
What the hell...?!
Do you think the others
are able to pursue it too?
No problem there!
Just like Terry and I are tracking
Fang King with our olfactory senses...
...Coco's using electromagnetic waves...
...Sunny is using the sense of touch...
...and I'm sure Zebra is following
it with ultrasonic waves.
At least we're not gonna lose track of it!
But I don't believe the old man,
forgetting to tell us this upfront!
Well, some of it's due to Zebra-san
cutting the message off...
Hey, Rin!
Was there anything else
he forgot to mention?!
A-Actually, there is one more thing...
Gotta admit we weren't expecting this.
Is it time for me to step up?
I have been alone
Ever since that day
All I got was a definite history
But tomorrow is still, still,
still just an uncertain dream
It’s like a tautology, logy
This is a tautology, logy
A dream is still a dream
Not gonna wake up, logy, logy
Right now, we’re lookin’ at
What it is we're lookin' at
The thing we’re lookin’
at ain’t no illusion
Find Yun! Run, Run, Yun!
Yun is hiding somewhere in the image
you're about to see, so please find him!
Hiding Level 127
Today, Yun's Hiding Level is... 127?!
That's like Fang King's level!
Since this is a really tough one, the
allotted time limit is 20 seconds.
Let's have a heaping helping of start!
R-Reviver Teppei's illustrated diary?!
His letters are unique... and so is
the picture! What is that drawing?
Just like it says!
"When I went to the beach, Yun, Toriko
and the others were swimming."
The answer's right there, clear as day!
Actually, I can't make even one
gram of heads or tails of it.
W-What's what? Who's who?!
Yun is... right here!
beach ball
Rin
Ryu
watermelon
Komatsu
He's obviously right here!
We'll have a better one for you next time,
so don't abandon this segment!
At last, the Four-Beasts' true form appears!
What's the fate of the Four
Kings... and the human race?!
Toriko and the rest of the Four Kings are all...!
They're powerless against the massive beast they're up against!
And then, the poison rain begins to fall...!
The Four-Beasts' Shocking Combined Form and Green Rain!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!