The world is in the Gourmet Age.
Gourmet Hunters are explorers
who travel the world, searching
for your ingredients.
And the ingredient at the top of this world
is GOD, which is being sought
by one Gourmet Hunter.
Go! Shock!! Gourmet!! Gourmet!!
Go! Shock!!
Friends who can eat the same dream
Friends who share the same future
With you guys
It’s first-rate gourmet my way!
If we join forces
We’ll be invincible
Come on, let’s show ‘em
Delicious food gives life
So be thankful for everything and
Let’s eat!!
We can’t lose!! We can’t be stopped!!
We ain’t gonna let ‘em have that
We’re gonna win it!! Shock!
Shock! Gourmet king!!
Spiked Punch!! Infinity!!
I’ll punch through with this fist
First-rate gourmet my way!
Let’s gather ‘round the table
For the sake of tomorrow
Let’s go! Go! Gourmet!!
Komatsu is in a Pinch?! Triathlon Cooking!
Now, everybody!
This is the sure to be memorable
50th Cooking Festival!
The full gathering of all 100 chefs here
at Cooking Stadium is now complete!
Hey! Aren't you ready yet, Rin?!
The fest has already started!
Gimme a second, hairless!
Taming these guys is hard!
Taming Beasts is what you do, isn't it?
Those are clones we prepared for today.
Get 'em under control!
By the way, did you call me handsome...?
Of course not!
Shige-san,
we'll be leaving shortly, so...
Yes. Hurry it up.
This may well be the last fest.
The stadium is very hot!
Mostly with excitement...
In fact, it's like an oven in here!
And now, one of the G7 taste masters, as
elected by IGO leading member nations...
Judge Punch, please give
us a few delicious words!
In this stadium, we have 100
representatives of the Gourmet Age.
These chefs who should be considered
world treasures have gathered here today.
And among them are chefs who are
participating for the first time.
Though it's their first time, we at IGO...
Komatsu!
Good luck!
I'm looking forward to seeing how they
do in battle with the top-ranking chefs.
And I'll be feasting my eyes on
the battles of those same top-ranking chefs.
What an incredible lineup...
When it comes down to it, I'm so
nervous that my teeth are chattering.
Yikes! You're becoming a
weird character, Matsu!
It's okay, Komatsu!
You can do this! Have confidence!
Show your strength to the whole world!
Toriko-san...
My partner is Toriko-san!
So I've got to have confidence
and take on the challenge!
From the bottom of my stomach, I wish to see
a number of superlative, delicious battles,
the kind that become deeply etched
on my tongue and in my mind forever,
befitting the milestone of this festival.
I wish you all the best of luck.
Thank you, Judge Patch!
And now, just a moment before
the preliminary round begins.
Please wait a moment.
Are you Chef Komatsu?
I've been looking forward to meeting you.
Chef Wabutora, the Oil Artisan!
The Mors Oil you discovered
is wonderful stuff.
I use it at my restaurant
with deep-fried food.
I'm grateful to you.
Thank you!
Although I didn't find
the oil all on my own...
A-Anyway, this is an honor!
I read all of your books, Chef Wabutora.
I've already reserved a
copy of your latest work,
You and Me are Like Oil and Water.
Well, thank you.
Granny Kama, Miso Soup Hag
54th place in the World Chef Ranking
I use Mors OIl all the time too.
Granny Kama, the Miso Soup Hag!
All I have to do is add
one drop to my miso soup
and it gives it a nice subtle flavor.
S-Scary...
I was more impressed with the
Medicinal Mochi than Mors Oil.
I'm happy to get the chance
to meet you, Chef Komatsu.
If I'd been there during
the Four-Beasts fiasco,
you might've been able to make twice as much.
You know, Medicinal Mochi!
Only twice as much, Ton?
If I'd been there, we would've cranked
out three or four times as much.
Nerimaru, Tough Stuff Udon
56th place in the World Chef Ranking
You say you cook faster than
me, even with that bulky body?
Nerimaru, you're talking in your sleep!
In fact, you're always sleeping when we meet.
Your eyes are closed anyway.
They're not closed!
They're just narrow!
Now they're open.
They were open before too!
Just because someone can cook
fast doesn't mean it's good.
Master Kamizaru, the Soba Sage!
Kamizaru, the Soba Sage
34th place in the World Chef Ranking
If you seek speed,
it's difficult
to bring out the deep flavor.
Certainly, you have a deep face!
Right. That face is really persuasive.
U-Um, can I have your autograph, everyone?
That's a lot of autograph boards!
Oh, to be young again...
Right,
Zau-chan?
The next generation...
Do you think it's about time for us
to pass them the baton, Setsu-san?
You mean retire?
Chefs don't have that
word in their vocabulary.
Just as customers never retire from eating.
Supposedly, Froese-sama, the partner
of the Gourmet God, Acacia-sama,
was found gripping a knife
and facing a cutting board in the end.
A chef retires
when they die.
In that case, we can't let these
young'uns have it just yet...
The title of "Super Cook".
I don't intend to let you have it either.
After all, the years you won,
I was too busy to participate.
Then shall we settle it between
us this year, Setsu-san?
I was hoping you'd say that!
Sparks are already flying between the chefs!
Have they started preparing for battle?!
Because of what's been happening,
there are a lot of new
faces among the top 100.
But the crowd's favorites are the same.
Gourmet Living Legend Setsuno
and the Cooking King, Zaus.
Oh? Is Chef Brunch absent again this year?
You love long shots, Mr. Patch.
Who do you see winning?
A long shot, eh? Of course, I have one...
One of the newcomers.
Now, without further ado, let's go!
We'll start with the preliminary round!
Already?!
It's a gourmet endurance race made
up of swimming, biking, and running!
We call it Triathlon Cooking!
Triathlon?! Why?!
In this very, very hard Gourmet Age,
physical strength is
essential, even for chefs!
Now the chefs can display
the strength they've honed
on a daily basis!
I haven't done any honing like that...
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Alright! Just what I wanted to hear!
50 chefs out of 100 will
be cut during this round.
That is, they'll be out of the competition!
50% will be cut?!
Now let's move to the location
for the first battle,
the preliminary round that
is Triathlon Cooking!
It's called a triathlon, but the
battle really comes down to cooking.
Then are chefs who aren't
physically strong gonna be okay?
It starts with swimming.
They swim from Rice Beach to the halfway
point Takoyaki Island, get ingredients,
then ride on a bike with the ingredients.
They'll make their way
through Frozen Tofu Wilderness
that's like freeze-dried tofu.
Then they run,
going through Rock Candy Mountain
Pass, which has countless thin thorns.
They get their cooking utensils
from the steep Bonito Hill,
and if they make it to the
cooking station at the goal,
they begin cooking.
There, the 50 chefs who make
the most delicious food
clear the preliminary round.
So the competition isn't
just about speed, huh?
Of course.
Though, the faster ones have the advantage
of picking more delicious ingredients.
Then slower contestants like Matsu
will have to make up for it
with their cooking technique.
Well, chefs in the Gourmet Age
need to have a certain amount
of physical strength, right?
Hey! Why the hell are you chowin' down?!
Now! Our live report, please!
Hello!
I'm reporting to you live from
Cooking Island's famous Rice Beach.
Look at this white sand!
It's actually grains of rice!
A heaping helping!
50th CF Triathlon Cooking
Triathlon Cooking will start
here, from Rice Beach!
I can't do this...
I'm sure I'll be cut this round.
Toriko-san, please lend me your strength!
Toriko...
Watchin' Zebra eat made me hungry!
This is delish!
Hey! Keep the dishes comin'!
Those two...
The one who'll give the signal to start
is this man!
At an impressive 2,715th place
in the World Chef Ranking?
Dope! That's 2,714th place!
From Sushi Fortunetelling, the
sushi artisan, Chef Monchy!
Who is he?
Why Monchy?
Don't you look down on me, dolt!
Chef Monchy, please come on stage.
I got it, dumbass!
And they're off!
The curtain has risen on
the 50th Cooking Festival!
Crap!
The fest has already started!
It's started!
Go, Granny Setsu!
Zaus!
Fight, Chef Komatsu!
It started!
Matsu!
You better not lose!
Good luck, Koma-chan and Miss Sumire!
The spectators are very excited too!
I bet this passion and excitement
is being felt around the world!
What a delicious moment the start
of the preliminary round is!
The TV ratings for the 49th festival
were an amazing 95%!
The whole world is watching this hot battle
between the chefs!
The chefs are all starting to swim at once!
They have to swim about 1.5 kilometers!
That's 750 meters and back
from Takoyaki Island!
Alright, pulling ahead of the pack is
the pioneer of undersea restaurants,
Mami!
His seafood-specializing Gourmet
Hunter partner is Marky,
but he's also a top chef
who catches fish himself!
Marble Tuna, Dragon King Shell,
Flower Salmon, Deep Sea Mammoth, Snow Shrimp,
Sugar Jellyfish, Red Tide Wine!
For people who only love seafood,
it's a Full Course of which
they can't get enough!
Oh my! Now Wabutora, the Oil
Artisan, has pulled ahead!
Plum Oil Natto, Oily Sardines,
Low-fat Clams, Oily Beef,
Oil Chicken, Olive Tomato,
Rice Flour Dumpling Oil, Golden Grease!
It's the perfect thick, oily Full Course!
He really must have oil flowing in his veins!
No, blood.
The rest of the pack is
desperately trying to catch up!
That's because they choose ingredients
in the order they arrive on the island!
Uh-oh! Chef Komatsu is
lagging way, way behind!
Is he just slow or is he drowning?!
Yeesh...
Matsu swims like a brick!
Uh-oh...
Come to think of it, when we
were after the Puffer Whale,
that guy couldn't swim at all.
Voice Life Jacket.
Get swimmin', kid!
Zebra-san!
Thank you!
Alright! If I have this...
What's this?
You seem to be okay, Komatsu-kun.
Setsuno-san!
I came back because I
thought you were drowning.
Well...
Setsuno-san?!
Are you floating on top of the water?
Nope, nothing like that.
Yes, you are! You're 100% floating!
No, no. Look closely.
Before one foot sinks down, I lift it
up and put the other foot down, is all.
And then keep repeating.
I see...
I mean, that's impossible!
W-What is that superhuman feat?!
Anyway,
as long as you're alright,
I'm going on ahead.
After all, we're rivals here at the fest!
It's a fair and square fight, Komatsu-kun!
Fast...
Alright! I'm not going to lose either!
It's a fair and square fight, Komatsu-kun!
That's right...
This is the Cooking Festival.
This is a precious opportunity,
where even I can seriously compete
against Setsuno-san and the others!
Zebra-san!
Please take off this life jacket!
I'm going to fight fair and square,
with only my own strength!
Komatsu...
Suit yourself.
In the first place,
I don't give a damn whether you win or lose.
That is,
unless you become my partner...
Alright!
Here I go!
Wait for me, Setsuno-san!
Go, dammit!
Gettin' cocky...
Komatsu...
I know you'll be alright!
Tomorrow’s wind is gonna blow tomorrow
So your adventurous life will be sensational
Only a smile has no flavor,
so wipe your tears
After a downpour of rain from the
sky, the sun always rises high
Every time I know you’re working up a sweat
My heart races and I become captivated
Don’t give up! I’m closest to
you in the middle of a challenge
Always believe in yourself!
Find Yun! Run, Run, Yun!
Yun is hiding somewhere in the image
you're about to see, so please find him!
Hiding Level: 22
Today, Yun's Hiding Level is 22.
The allotted time limit is 10 seconds.
Let's have a heaping helping of start!
Okay, where could Yun be?
Yun is... right here!
Have Gourmet Corp.'s agents
even gotten to this segment?!
Don't look away even one gram
from the Cooking Fest's next developments!
A troublemaker of unprecedented porportions!
He's the biggest, worst thug ever, but, he's a super first-rate chef!
Enter Legendary Chef Brunch the Tengu!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!