The world is in the Gourmet Age.
Gourmet Hunters are explorers
who travel the world, searching
for your ingredients.
And the ingredient at the
top of this world is GOD,
which is being sought by one Gourmet Hunter.
Go! Shock!! Gourmet!! Gourmet!!
Go! Shock!!
Friends who can eat the same dream
Friends who share the same future
With you guys
It’s first-rate gourmet my way!
If we join forces
We’ll be invincible
Come on, let’s show ‘em
Delicious food gives life
So be thankful for everything and
Let’s eat!!
We can’t lose!! We can’t be stopped!!
We ain’t gonna let ‘em have that
We’re gonna win it!! Shock!
Shock! Gourmet king!!
Spiked Punch!! Infinity!!
I’ll punch through with this fist
First-rate gourmet my way!
Let’s gather ‘round the table
For the sake of tomorrow
Let’s go! Go! Gourmet!!
The curtain rose on the Cooking Fest at last!
The preliminary round is
the Cooking Triathlon!
Competing against chefs who
possess overwhelming ability,
Komatsu lagged way behind.
But then, a new chef awoke!
Crap!
The fest has already started!
Meet Legendary Chef Brunch the Tengu!
Alright, here I go!
Chef Komatsu is slow! Slow!
Way too slow!
He's slower than slow!
He's drowning after all, isn't he?
Hang in there, Komatsu!
Now most of the chefs are reaching
the halfway point of Takoyaki Island!
And with a big lead is...
...the oil-smeared Wabutora!
I'm not smeared with it.
Catching up to him is... Setsuno!
The National Gourmet Treasure, Setsuno!
Just like that, she sprints
her way to the top!
And now we've got the Cooking King, Zaus!
Also catching up is the Mach Cook, Ton!
Okay...
I'll do my best!
I'm gonna swim...
...under my own power!
Whoa.
Setsuno makes a cool arrival,
not even out of breath!
It took her just a minute
and a half to make it!
Munage-san! Munage-san!
Oh, yes, Tina-chin?
The leader of the pack,
Setsunon, I mean, Setsuno-san,
is about to choose her ingredients!
Let's see here...
This and this...
I'll take that too.
The next stage is by bicycle.
After finishing their swim, the contestants
take the ingredients they've chosen
Second Stage
over to one of those food
delivery-type bikes.
They'll put their ingredients in the carrier.
The second stage goes to
Rock Candy Mountain Pass.
After that, they have to run!
The key to winning is how
you choose the ingredients.
If you choose a heaping helping,
the race will become a real drag.
There! Zaus. Wabutora, and Ton have arrived!
What a thrilling race!
The arena is also heating up
from medium to well-done!
Munage-san! Bad news!
What?!
Mr. Hanage?
The troublemaker who's
always in the top ranking,
but has only participated in the fest once?!
B-But...
...he's also a genius chef
who won a decisive victory that one time!
If Zebra is the poster boy for
"bad boy Gourmet Hunters",
then the poster boy for "bad
boy chefs" is definitely
that man!
What the...?!
Look at that!
Somebody's standing there!
It can't be!
Everybody, let's look at
the roof of Hotel Cooking!
Not all the chefs
participating in this fest had shown up yet!
That's the last one!
He's a living legend!
This fest
is going to be a wild one.
He's a mysterious man who comes from a
place that's full of strange ingredients,
the Hex Food World!
The chef of Tengu Castle,
which serves bizarre food...
The chef who's ranked at number three!
Brunch the Tengu
is here!
It's Brunch!
Brunch the Tengu, Bizarre Cooking
3rd place in the World Chef Ranking
Brunch has come!
Is it the real thing?!
He really is a tengu!
Scary!
Still, I'm bummed out.
I came all this way, stayed
in a hotel, got ready...
But then I drank too much
Kappa Fin Sake last night.
Ah, well. All I gotta do is overtake
everybody else in a single spurt.
So that's Brunch?
This is the first time I've seen him.
Hey, look at that guy.
He must be hurtin' for money.
He ain't wearin' any socks.
That's our Zonge-sama! Always catching
details with your sharp eyes!
Tengu always go barefoot with geta.
What a delicious development!
The tension in the arena
could boil an egg in a flash!
It's super boiling in here!
Shut the hell up!
W-What a voice!
W-What the...?!
You got a lot of nerve!
C'mere, you tengu bastard!
Z-Zebra?!
You're...
...Zebra of the Four Kings!
You're Zebra.
You're just as the old
Daruma man described you.
The Gourmet Hunter who won't
partner up even if it kills him.
What are you talkin' about?
If that's an offer, forget about it, dumbass!
I already got
a partner in mind. Name's Komatsu
and you can't hold a candle to him!
Komatsu?
Who the hell is that?
You say he's better than me?
Although he's not a candidate
to be your partner, Zebra.
Komatsu is my partner!
He don't suit you!
What's that?!
Hey, Zebra! I ain't just gonna let that go.
Come on, you guys, not here!
Do you hear me?!
You're an annoying buzz in my ear!
These guys are a pain in the ass.
Okay, okay, both of you...
Now I'm mad!
Okay, okay, Toriko!
Don't you morons ignore me!
That's enough, you knuckleheads!
Mess with me and I'll kill ya!
What was that?!
Is that Komatsu guy in the fest?
Yeah, that's right...
Interesting...
The partner of Toriko of the Four Kings...
Then I think I'll make mincemeat out of him.
Not a chance, Brunch!
Say again?
There ain't nobody
who can beat me.
Better not underestimate Komatsu.
You guys have mastered Honoring the Food?
Perfect.
Then I'm gonna go check out
your precious Komatsu!
Even though he's late,
Brunch the Tengu
has entered the competition!
Go, Brunch!
This is getting even more interesting!
That bastard is totally cocky.
But one glance and he could tell
we've mastered Honoring the Food.
Yeah.
He's strong.
I sensed that he's bursting
with electromagnetic waves.
It's extremely rare to see
a life force like that.
The Hex Food World is in
the Gourmet World, right?
That alone guarantees his strength.
Although I think I could take him in a fight.
But we're not the ones who are
gonna fight him this time around.
Komatsu is!
Chef Komatsu has finally... at last...
...barely made it out of the sea! Good luck!
Matsu! Get a move on!
W-W-What is that?!
Brunch has arrived!
He finished his "swim" in
the twinkling of an eye!
H-Huh?
Um...
A-A-Are you...
Are you... Are you...?
Brunch-san? You are Brunch-san, aren't you?!
Who are you?
N-Nice to meet you.
Um, I'm Komatsu.
What'd you just say?
My name is Komatsu.
Komatsu?!
You're Komatsu?!
Y-Yes...
What?!
You're Komatsu?! Really?!
Yes.
I imagined someone really nasty!
You're just a kid!
Yes!
And you're in last place!
You're really Toriko's partner?!
Yes, that's right.
Um, though you probably can't tell...
Liar! Yank my chain and you get decked!
There's no way you're better
than me! It's unimaginable!
I'm better than you?
As if!
Yeah, right?!
Right!
What the hell's wrong with you?!
You gotta agree with everything I say?!
Um... Brunch-san...
A-Actually...
Could I have your autograph
about five times?
What the hell?! Why should
I give you my autograph?!
What's with five times?!
That's going overboard!
Really?
This is ridiculous!
The Four Kings bragged about you so much
that I was lookin' forward to this,
but you can't put up any kind of fight!
I'm really...
I'm goin' on ahead.
U-U-Um...
Matsu!
Don't let him make fun of you!
Komatsu-kun, you don't need his autograph!
Jeez, are these all the
ingredients that are left?
These ingredients bum me out too.
Not me!
A Ramen Spider that spews
ramen noodles from its mouth.
A fruit that has a slight chestnut
flavor, Chestnutangerine!
Eye-poppingly spiciness
that melts in with the savoriness of
the thick meat, Chili Pepper Pork.
Granted, there aren't any
high-class ingredients left,
but these are still all great ingredients
that can be used to cook tasty dishes!
I wish I could take them all with me!
What the...?! Suddenly, the
ingredients are glowing!
I see!
You want to go too, huh?
I see! You too, huh?
But all of you together are
too heavy for me to carry.
You too?
This kid can hear
the voices of the ingredients!
They're happy!
The ingredients were bummed out because
the other contestants didn't pick 'em,
but now they're all excited!
Komatsu...
So this is Komatsu...
Interesting.
What a waste.
With all this left,
and I have to leave it here...
I know what you mean. It is a waste.
So why don't we take everything
and cook it all up?
Without leaving one thing behind.
B-Brunch-san!
I-It seems Brunch and Chef Komatsu
are going to use the remainder
of the ingredients!
Alright, alright!
The ingredients say they wanna go,
so we'll take 'em all with us!
Brunch-san, thank you!
You ready? We're gonna overtake everybody
else in a single spurt. Komatsu!
Ready,
Brunch-san!
Tomorrow’s wind is gonna blow tomorrow
So your adventurous life will be sensational
Only a smile has no flavor,
so wipe your tears
After a downpour of rain from the
sky, the sun always rises high
Every time I know you’re working up a sweat
My heart races and I become captivated
Don’t give up! I’m closest to
you in the middle of a challenge
Always believe in yourself!
Guess the Legend! The Legend Gourmet Quiz!
I'm your host, Tina, and
welcome to a new segment!
This is a heaping helping
of an epoch-making segment,
in which you guess the legendary
ingredients of the Gourmet Age!
Really?! Level 1!
Alright, let's go to our first question.
Someone once said...
That voice! Don't tell me...
Yes.
I've come from the beginning of
the show to give you the quiz.
Looking forward to working with you!
Seriously?!
I've got a heaping helping of deep emotions!
Well, thank you.
Now, let's begin!
Ahem.
Really?! Level 1!
Someone once said...
There are pigs with bodies
made of delicious gummi drops.
Blah-blah-blah!
The allotted time limit is 10 seconds.
Like... Pork Drops?
But stick with the animal...
Okay, pig!
Pig! Pig something, right?!
But I don't know the answer!
There are pigs with bodies made
of delicious gummi drops...
Pigummi!
Pigummi?
You can enjoy various
fruit flavors then, huh?
Sure, if it really existed...
Okay, let's get back on
track with our next segment!
That's just unfair!
He'll use any dirty trick to win!
That tengu is scary!
Playing Dirty! Roaring Ahead!
Brunch Overtakes Everybody in a Single Spurt!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!