The world is in the Gourmet Age.
Gourmet Hunters are explorers
who travel the world,
searching for your ingredients.
And the ingredient at
the top of this world
is GOD, which is being sought
by one Gourmet Hunter.
Go! Shock!! Gourmet!! Gourmet!!
Go! Shock!!
Friends who can eat the same dream
Friends who share the same future
With you guys
It’s first-rate gourmet my way!
If we join forces
We’ll be invincible
Come on, let’s show ‘em
Delicious food gives life
So be thankful for everything and
Let’s eat!!
We can’t lose!! We can’t be stopped!!
We ain’t gonna let ‘em have that
We’re gonna win it!! Shock!
Shock! Gourmet king!!
Spiked Punch!! Infinity!!
I’ll punch through with this fist
First-rate gourmet my way!
Let’s gather ‘round the table
For the sake of tomorrow
Let’s go! Go! Gourmet!!
Gourmet Corp. invaded the Fest
in order to capture the chefs.
Toriko hammered Starjun
with all of his attacks,
to no avail!
Meanwhile, the chefs fought an
uphill battle against the Nitro.
Komatsu escaped on his own.
And the fierce battle between
Coco and Grinpatch unfolded.
Mortal Combat! Coco vs. Grinpatch!
Hey, come on! You're joking, right?
You're not really groggy yet, are you?
Of course not.
Eat this...
Poison Cannon!
What?!
I ate it, just as I was told!
Thanks for the food!
He even swallowed my Poison Cannon?!
Now this is how...
...you fire a cannon!
Breath Bazooka!
S-So powerful...
But that's to be expected of
a Gourmet Corp. Vice-chef.
Even so...
...I can't afford to lose here!
That's the spirit!
Machine Gun Poison, double barrel barrage!
What, you're out of new attacks already?
Just hitting with me twice as much
won't work!
Thanks!
Poison Sword!
You won't be able to suck up
my poison without that straw!
It's still in one piece!
This straw
is coated with the sap of
the Gourmet World's Rock Oak,
which is hundreds of times
harder than diamond.
It can't be cut through so easily.
In that case, I'll chop up your body!
Forget about it!
Crap. My arm...
Looks like you bit off
more than you could chew.
I don't believe you have the
strength to attack anymore.
You did show me a good time
with your full course of attacks.
However...
...you didn't quite satisfy my hunger.
There isn't anywhere to escape to!
Nowhere!
Like that one time...
Yun!
Y-You can fly now?!
There's nothing I can do...
Just get saved...
There's really nothing I can do?
I see. You're changing your strategy, eh?
If poison doesn't work,
then physical attacks...
You'll use that sword
to cut me up directly...
...is the idea.
But that's no easy task either!
I'm pretty confident in my
close combat ability too!
Besides, I'm happy you're
moving in closer to me.
Now I'll be able to suck you up!
Down the hatch!
Y-You can still stand up?
I told you before...
Travel... training...
...and eating delicious
food have made me stronger.
Starjun...
The last time we met was at Chowlin Temple.
I've gotten even stronger since then.
The battle with the Four-Beasts
made me stronger.
Still, you weren't as delicious
as I'd anticipated,
Coco of the Four Kings.
Well, of course not.
That's because you just sucked
up a dummy I made with poison.
W-What?!
When did you...?
In the battle with the Four-Beasts,
my power increased several times over.
The Four-Beasts wasn't an opponent
that could be beaten by one person.
But the four of us...
Me, Coco, Sunny, and Zebra...
By combining our power and fighting,
we were able to surpass our limits.
We did it by working hard together.
But that ain't all.
My strength right now...
...is also thanks to Komatsu's cooking!
Komatsu cooked Bubble Fruit, Medicinal Mochi,
and even the Four-Beasts.
Komatsu's delicious cooking
activated my Gourmet Cells!
When I got soaked from the
Four-Beasts' Green Rain,
it poisoned me, of all people.
But I was saved thanks to the
Medicinal Mochi Komatsu-kun made.
Just before, you said...
...that poison doesn't work on you,
so my new strategy was to
deal out physical damage.
That's half-correct.
Half?
I wanted to hit you with
some real firepower...
...so that's also why I got close!
Why, you...
Poison Cannon!
Yun...
Are you okay?!
What was that?
My Poison Cannon didn't work?!
No... He swallowed it!
Coco-san!
Komatsu-kun!
Stay back!
Right now
I'm radiating extremely dangerous poison.
Even with Zebra's barrier,
you mustn't get close to me!
What is he?
Not even my deadliest poison works on him...
Komatsu-kun, run!
Breath Missile!
Thank you, Yun!
The Wall Penguin... You've got
some mighty fine mobility.
I can't see the bottom of that hole.
I've never encountered
such destructive force,
nor lung capacity...
As a creature, he's a very curious specimen.
That was too close...
I almost blew away one of
the chefs accidentally.
I'll get a scolding from the Head
Chef if I don't bring 'em back alive!
I won't let you lay one
finger on Komatsu-kun!
C-Coco-san!
You can stop me?
Oh, no...
Now then, I think I'll take you...
...to the boss.
Why? Why is Gourmet Corp.
going this far to capture chefs?
Why?!
That's a stupid question, Komatsu-kun.
Coco-san!
You're still standing?!
Why is Gourmet Corp. so eager
to capture chefs?
It's because you're all that valuable,
as chefs.
In the Gourmet Age, the people
with the most influence
aren't politicians...
...or religious leaders or artists.
They're chefs.
One chef being born in the country
is equivalent to the discovery of oil.
Compared to chefs,
even we Gourmet Hunters
are blown away.
Even during the old Gourmet War,
it seems there was a struggle over chefs.
There are ingredients worth more than
military power and natural resources.
And there are those who have
value that never changes...
The chefs.
You understand, don't you, Komatsu-kun?
You chefs are the treasure of the world.
That's why Gourmet Corp. is
desperate to possess you.
And why we'll
will put our lives on
the line to protect you!
I don't know...
We chefs are valuable enough for you
to risk your lives over?
Yes.
The food that you and the others
put so much effort into creating
satisfies the hunger of
people all over the world,
wipes the tears of crying children
wherever they may be and comforts them...
...lights up the future...
...and gives people sun-like warmth
as well as hope.
That's why we fight!
To protect hope!
Chefs are...
...hope...
And I will not let
Gourmet Corp. take that hope away!
Coco-san!
You know, I hate that kind of soapboxing.
Enough already! I'm gonna
send you and that hope
to kingdom come!
Poison man!
Go, Komatsu-kun!
I saw it in my fortune!
Toriko needs you!
Go to him as quick as you can!
Go to Toriko!
Now!
Right!
Breath Missile!
Coco-san...
Yun!
Hey, penguin!
You look delicious...
Do you mind if I suck you up?
You...
Go, Komatsu-kun!
Right!
Now then, let's hang out a while longer.
But with a change of venue.
Change of venue?! Where are we going?!
A place where I can do my worst.
Or to be more specific, close to
where the River of Three Hells flows.
River of Three Hells? What's that?!
I have to figure out
his body's immune system.
And it'll be dangerous for me too,
but if worse comes to worst,
I'll have to use that poison!
What do you think, Starjun?
Is that all of your power?
That's it?
Unfortunate.
What?!
You're not the only one
whose power has increased.
I'm also not the same
person that I was before.
Now it's my turn to give you a feast.
Eat this!
Hey...
What the hell is with this guy?
Do I have to look at him?
I suppose I do?
Gross!
Disgusting!
Grody to the max!
Are you going to die? Tell
me, are you going to die?
Like this could kill me, idiot?!
You know who's gonna die?
All of you!
Even in a world that nobody's ever seen
There's something that can be
glimpsed if you keep chasing dreams
Flowers don't bloom on top of asphalt
Come on, let's go make
only your dreams come true
Mega Raba! The map that you
draw spreads out into infinity
Mega Raba! Nobody can stop you
Mega Raba! Let's go forth,
feeling excitement in our hearts
Let's go find what you've been longing for
Mega Raba
Guess the Legend
The Legend Gourmet Quiz
Guess the Legend!
The Legend Gourmet Quiz!
I'm your host, Tina.
This is a heaping helping
of an epoch-making segment,
in which you guess the legendary
ingredients of the Gourmet Age!
Really?! Level 3
Today's "Really?!" level is 3.
Someone once said...
Heavenly voice! Please help me today too!
Sure, sure. Okay, here I go.
Really?! Level 3
Someone once said...
There are soft, spongy grapes
that can even become boiled
tofu when put in a stew...
Something something!
The allotted time limit is 10 seconds.
Start!
Grapes that are like tofu?
Yes. Of course, you can have them raw too,
but this is the best way to eat them.
Especially during the cold season...
Someone once said...
Tofu Grapes
There are soft, spongy grapes
that can even become boiled
tofu when put in a stew...
Tofu Grapes!
They really do look like they'd warm you up!
I bet Tofu Grapes would
go great with hot sake.
Yep. Sake goes great with lots of things...
And now, let's get back on
track with our next segment!