Gobble!! Guts!! Gobble!! Guts!! Gobble!!
Calling everything delicious!
The more I eat, the more powerful I get!
Let’s capture ingredients around the world!
I dream of being an invincible
Gourmet Fighter!!
Now on to the bottom of the
sea, or the tops of glaciers!
Jump! Jump Jump Jump!
Knock! Knock Knock Knock!
Give thanks!
Let’s eat!
Wow wo!! Spiked Punch! Wow wo!! Multi-fold!
Guts! Gutsy Guts! I can eat any dream!
Wow wo!! My very own...
Wow wo!! ...Full Course!
Guts! Gutsy Guts! Gather them all up!
And put the world on my plate!
Wow wow wow! Eat the mountains!!
Wow wow wow! Toriko!!
Wow wow wow! Eat the oceans!!
Wow wow wow! Tori, Tori, Tori, Toriko!!
Someone once said...
There are chrysanthemums with
petals of crunchy crackers...
Chrysanthecrackers!
There are ginkgo nuts crammed
full of sweet red bean paste...
Ginredbean Pastenuts!
The world is in the Gourmet Age...
An age in which people quest for
yet unknown culinary delights!
Toriko-san, wait up!
I can't walk anymore!
Yeesh. Even after seeing that?
Seeing what?
What are you talking about?
The mountain that's overflowing
with fall taste sensations...
Autumn Mountain!
Assemble on Autumn Mountain!
Terry, Yun, Kiss, Queen!
But that mountain is gigantic...
It's as big as the Mors Mountains!
Actually, bigger than
the Mors Mountain Range.
It's about 20,000 kilometers long.
20,000 kilometers?!
The incredible length of this mountain range
has also had an effect on
the prevailing westerlies,
making the fall season extremely long.
The long, slow ripening process is extended,
making the autumn ingredients
grow even more deliciously.
Other than that, this has
apparently been a fruitful year,
with a bigger bumper crop than ever.
It sounds like what we heard at the
Gourmet Shrine was right on the money.
According to my supplier,
the legendary pears on
Autumn Mountain are ripe!
Legendary pears... Supears!
And I guess they really exist, Toriko-san!
Yep. Like they say, "It often
takes time to bear fruit."
And Supears supposedly take 38 years
to get to a fully ripened state.
If you bite into one, the fresh juice
splashes dozens of meters in the air!
It's like it bursts open!
Dang, I wanna try eatin' one!
But I have a feeling it'll be tough
looking for them on that huge mountain.
Yeah, well...
Rumor has it the pears originally
came from the Gourmet World,
so you can imagine having
a hard time getting 'em,
but it'll be okay.
Terry?!
Don't scare me!
Whoa!
Terry is a Battle Wolf
with an exceptional sense of
smell and most importantly,
a love for Gourmet World food.
There's no doubt he'll be able
to catch the Supear scent.
At any rate, Terry,
you get bigger every time I see you!
We've arrived at Autumn Mountain!
You're really excited, huh?
Despite moaning about not being able
to walk just a couple minutes ago...
Well, seeing these red leaves
would lift anybody's spirits!
Of course, there's capturing the Supears,
but also mushroom-gathering,
grape-picking, leaf-viewing...
I'm going to get my fill of autumn today!
There's a grape tree already!
There's a ton of them, Toriko-san!
Hey, wait a second!
What's wrong?!
Dancing Grapes (Plant Beast) Capture Level 30
W-W-What is this?!
Beast Plants that move like
they're dancing to capture prey.
Dancing Grapes.
Moving plants?!
Nothin' unusual about that.
There were some in the Wu Jungle
when we got the BB Corn.
Yeah, but...
Looks like this is gonna
be a thrilling flavor hunt.
"Hunt", you say...
I was thinking more along
the lines of "gathering"...
Now that's obviously a dangerous beastie...
A Beast that's in the middle of stockpiling
ingredients for hibernation...
In other words, we have to be careful
of more than just moving grapes, huh?
This isn't the image I had
of mushroom-gathering!
Mushrooms aren't supposed to run!
Mushrooms that trot away...
Trotrooms.
After all, mushrooms are
a kind of slime mold.
So it's no surprise that they run around.
I'll get it this time!
Alright!
Ow...
What?! What?! What?! What?!
Whoa, whoa, wait!
Yeesh...
Spiked Punch!
You okay, Komatsu?!
Yes! But what was that about?!
That's a Stinging Maple.
It hits you in the back
'til you turn bright red.
What kind of attack is that,
like a childish prank?!
It stings like heck!
Uh-oh! Peabees!
Now what?!
Peabea (Insect Beast) Capture Level 25
Peabees have a poison needle!
It's a thousand times more poisonous
than the poisonous mushroom, Poisroom!
An average human will die instantly
if they get pricked with it!
Run!
Their type of poison differs,
depending on the individual!
It's possible that even I don't
have the antibody against them!
Pains in the neck!
Comin' your way, Komatsu!
Gimme a break!
Poison Dressing!
I weakened the poison, so you'll
be able to move again soon.
Coco-san!
Hi, Komatsu. Toriko.
Long time no see.
Kiss has gotten huge!
So how's your training going?
Smoothly. Looks like it's the same for you.
My Gourmet Cells are
activating more than before.
What can I say? You're
going after Supears, too?
Yeah.
Although according to my fortune,
we're not the only ones who
have come to pick Supears.
Queen-chan! Then Sonny-san is here, too!
Coco! You made another beautiful entrance?!
It ticks me off to no end when
you steal my beautiful thunder!
Same old Sunny...
It's okay, Terry.
The Battle Wolf.
Gotten bigger, I see.
Whoop!
I've come to capture a few Supears so
beautiful Queen could get some exercise.
You're all after the same... Well,
I don't think I need to ask that.
Supears really are special!
For Coco-san and Sunny-san
to go after them, too...!
Well, why don't we split up and search?
Wait, since we're here
to hunt for a fall taste,
why not make it more fun?
Let's make it a contest to see which
party finds the Supears first.
Well?
What do you mean, "party"?
Each person and their partner.
Toriko and the Battle Wolf...
Coco and Kiss...
Queen and I, and finally...
Matsu and the Wall Penguin.
Us too?!
What do you think?!
Beautiful idea, isn't it?!
It does sound fun.
And I haven't played much with Kiss lately...
I could go along with it...
Right, Terry?
I think we'll sit this one out...
Then it's settled!
Um, did you hear what I said?!
Alright, then let's get started!
That's no fair!
Kiss!
We better get a move on too, Terry!
Don't leave us here!
Terry! Terry! Terry! Terry! Please,
let me ride on your back, too!
Please!
It's impossible to get a full view
of the mountain from the ground.
Like they say, "You can't see
the forest for the trees."
So it's advantageous to have
a literal bird's-eye view.
There are slightly more autumnal
leaves over to the north.
Kiss, let's head over there.
I bet Toriko thinks it'll be easy
for the Battle Wolf to find
a Gourmet World ingredient,
but Queen is from the Gourmet World, too.
Queen's tongue can sense
the smell of anything.
She can catch a scent as
well as some Battle Wolf.
Let's go, Queen!
Queen! Queen! Queen!
But this mountain
is full of creatures with
really high Capture Levels...
An exceptionally sweet scent.
That's what you're looking for, Terry.
Let's stick like glue to
Toriko-san and Terry-san.
If we lose them, it's all over.
Chestnut Rice Balls!
Chestnuts that taste like
newly harvested rice balls!
Chestnut Rice Balls are the best!
This is the kind of autumn
taste I'm looking for!
This is a big one, Yun!
Walking along like this
makes me think back...
...on that trip.
You've gotten big too, y'know?
What, are you marking territory?!
That marking has a little too much impact...
Toriko-san!
Thank goodness! I almost lost you!
I only found you because
I heard you yelling...
Thanks to that...?
Anyway, it saved me.
The path disappears when
the plants move, see...
The path?
Then Terry's marking comes in handy.
If we follow the smell of his marking,
we can get back to where we
started without getting lost.
As always, nice piss!
"Nice piss"...
What is it, Terry?!
Don't tell me...
Mutton Boars (Mammalian
Beast) Capture Level 33
These guys are Mutton Boars!
Whoa! I didn't know Mutton
Boars were this fast!
Can't be helped then...
Flying Knife!
Wha...?! I hit it!
Toriko-san!
Help!
Komatsu!
I can't catch up!
Terry!
You want me to get on?
Alright!
I'm countin' on you, Terry!
This is Terry's Battle Wolf power?!
What speed!
Komatsu!
Terry, charge!
Where'd they go?!
Toriko!
What is it? Did something happen?
Komatsu was kidnapped by a Mutton Boar!
What?!
They're up there?!
But the seasonal autumn wind is
supposed to be a mighty gale.
Going to the peak would
be dangerous, wouldn't it?
That guy is so reckless!
Bring him back, Toriko and Terry!
800 meters! This is as high as we can get!
Thanks!
There it is!
Nice, Terry!
Alright, give me back Komatsu.
W-Wait!
Hey, what the...?!
It looks like the Mutton Boar family.
I was covered up by the fur, so
I didn't realize it at first,
but they're thin as rails...
Now that you mention it...
...their electromagnetic waves are also weak.
They're starving.
Even though there are plenty of
ingredients on the mountain this year...
I see...
So the Beasts that grew quickly as a result
were only the ones with high Capture Levels.
Then the other Beasts had
to scramble for food,
but weren't able to get
enough to feed their young.
I'll give them my Chestnut Rice Balls,
but it won't be enough...
Terry!
Have you...?
Yes. You can see it from up here.
The leaves are reddest in this area.
And Queen senses a sweet aroma here.
Then maybe that means
the Supears are
in these clouds?!
Those are...
...Supears!
I wonder why the Mutton Boars
didn't notice the pears...
No wonder, really.
For one thing, the view
is obstructed by clouds
and they're translucent.
But more than that, their scent is faint.
It even took Terry and Queen
all this time to pick it up.
It takes time for Supears to ripen.
Hence they grow secretly,
so as not to be found.
Now that's a hefty fruit!
It's as heavy as a watermelon.
Bubbles are dancing inside
the fruit. Beautiful!
Here you go.
Alright, let's all eat our fill!
We give thanks for all this
world's great bounty...
Let's eat!
The juice is gushing out!
And like soda water,
sweet fruit juice is jumping
around in my mouth!
Pear, persimmon, chestnut...
The sweet fruity flavors of fall
are bursting through one after another!
I see! These clouds!
They're made from a
gathering of all the vapor
coming off of the mountain's autumn flavors!
That accounts for the Supear's taste!
The juice is overflowing...
and it doesn't stop!
What a refined and refreshing sweetness!
It's so fresh and juicy!
Delicious!
This time, Terry discovered it first,
so Terry and Toriko win.
Nah, the real winners are that family.
With a harvest like this, starvation
shouldn't be a problem.
That's thanks to Terry, too.
Hey...
The old man's ingredients...
How about havin' another go at it?
You mean...
That Full Course?
Yeah.
This week's Gourmet Fortune!
It's time for Gourmet Fortune, with
a heaping helping of accuracy!
We're going to use a camera this
week too, so get yours ready!
Okay, please choose one
of these three platters.
This week's lucky ingredient
is in one of them!
The higher the capture level,
the more Gourmet Luck it has!
Alright, here we go!
A heaping helping...
Open!
This week's best Gourmet Luck is...
C - Tundra Dragon Capture Level 55
...yours if you chose C!
If you go out wearing your favorite clothes,
you might just make a new acquaintance!
A - Rock Drum Capture Level 27
If you chose A, you get this
week's second-best luck.
If you keep your room tidy and in order,
something good may happen!
B - White Apple Capture Level <1
And I'm sorry. If you chose B, you're third.
Be careful about losing things!
Do a heaping helping of checking
to make sure you've got everything.
And finally, it's Gourmet
Good Luck Charm photo time!
Are you ready?
Good Luck Charm Photo Time
If you take a photo of the scene,
and carry it with you for a week as a
good luck charm, you'll be even luckier!
Alright, here we go!
3... 2... 1...
Scoop Chance!
Complaints, dissatisfaction,
a venomous tongue...
Go easy on it.
The wise words of a fortune teller!
They heaping helping hit home!
I promise not to grumble to the chief.
This week, anyway...
Toriko and Coco set out to prepare President Ichiryu's full course.
And Komatsu encounters an old friend from when he was training.
Reunion! Take-chan of Fairytale Castle!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!