Gobble!! Guts!! Gobble!! Guts!! Gobble!!
Calling everything delicious!
The more I eat, the more powerful I get!
Let’s capture ingredients around the world!
I dream of being an invincible
Gourmet Fighter!!
Now on to the bottom of the
sea, or the tops of glaciers!
Jump! Jump Jump Jump!
Knock! Knock Knock Knock!
Give thanks!
Let’s eat!
Wow wo!! Spiked Punch! Wow wo!! Multi-fold!
Guts! Gutsy Guts! I can eat any dream!
Wow wo!! My very own...
Wow wo!! ...Full Course!
Guts! Gutsy Guts! Gather them all up!
And put the world on my plate!
Wow wow wow! Eat the mountains!!
Wow wow wow! Toriko!!
Wow wow wow! Eat the oceans!!
Wow wow wow! Tori, Tori, Tori, Toriko!!
Someone once said...
There are birds with combs made
of silky green broccoli...
Broccobirds!
There are pigs that have sweet bodies
made of rice dumplings and bean jam...
Rice Dumpigs!
The world is in the Gourmet Age...
An age in which people quest for
yet unknown culinary delights!
In order to get Meteor Garlic,
a training ingredient,
Toriko and company went
to the Gourmet Casino.
They played against Livebearer in
a game of gourmet concentration,
called Gourmet Tasting.
I'll eat it all right...
The Poison Potato!!!
I told you once.
You had a bad eating combination.
Through Coco's strategy,
Livebearer was defeated.
You lose.
Fine! Enough!
I don't care about the game!
So you finally show your true colors...
After Toriko and company beat the
attacking Livebearer and his minions...
Toriko!
I found it!
The ingredient you guys are looking for!
Meteor Garlic, the real thing...
They found the Meteor Garlic at last!
A Taste that's Out of this World!
Eating the Meteor Garlic!
That's...
...Meteor Garlic!
It's gigantic!
What the hell?! You had
the real thing right here!
Apparently, he stored it here as
a good luck charm for the game.
That's good to hear!
Even Livebearer-san has
love for real ingredients!
That's not why...
I'll tell you right now,
Meteor Garlic is a Special
Preparation Ingredient.
Will you be able to cook it?
Yes! I'll manage it somehow!
Alright! I'm countin' on you, Komatsu!
Right, Toriko-san!
And with that decided, let's
get ready for a feast!
A restaurant with a scenic view!
It's a special private room. I
had one of my men prepare it.
We've got a bird's-eye view of the casino.
And a bunch of booze!
Hey, this looks like it's
gonna be a fantastic dinner!
Let's get started with an aperitif!
You downed a whole bottle of Summer
Whiskey and wanna drink more?
Hey...
Is Komatsu okay alone?
Yeah.
I used Knocking on Livebearer,
so he can't move freely.
Besides...
I can't peel the skin...
What should I do here?
You could spend the rest of your life
pulling on it and it'd be no use.
I told you. Meteor Garlic is a
Special Preparation Ingredient.
Preparing it is no simple thing...
I did it!
I peeled a little of it!
The key is cutting the skin along the
creases while toasting it with heat.
H-He figured out how to
peel it without any hints?!
And even if he knows how to peel
it, applying just the right amount
of pressure with the knife
takes considerable technique!
This boy...
He really is something special...
H-Huh?
Has the direction of the grain changed?
What should I do?
Livebearer-san, is there
any Cheese Cabbage left?
Alright!
What in the world are you doing?
I thought maybe the
microbes in Cheese Cabbage
would be able to break down the tough skin.
He heated up Cheese Cabbage
to just the right temperature
to make its microbes active?!
I'll try raising the heat a little more...
Three degrees...
No, maybe two degrees...
The skin's softer than before.
But now what should I do?
The Knocking wore off...
How should I cut it?
Like this?
Here!
Um...
How long has it been...
...since I last saw a chef do his
very best to find a cooking method?
L-Livebearer-san...
It only gets harder from here on in.
Okay!
Next, you have to cut
crosswise with the knife.
Right!
Thank you for your patience!
The Meteor Garlic is ready!
Way to go, Komatsu!
But what is Livebearer doing here?
Your forte, fortune-telling? You
saw that this was going to happen?
I didn't need to divine the future for this.
Komatsu's passion for food
made Livebearer's heart bounce back.
Coco...
Komatsu took the scum off of the
soup and out of Livebearer...
Coco...
Livebearer-san, please do the honors.
T-Teppanyaki?!
Livebearer-san taught me how to cook it!
What?! In the end, you
wanted to eat it too, huh?
A real ingredient!
Be careful.
It's going to burst open.
The heat of the teppanyaki sent it flying!
Awesome!
The clove inside is hard like a meteorite
and bursts forth like popcorn.
And now it looks like a shooting
star... like a meteor...
The part of the Meteor
Garlic that you can eat
is only one section of
the center of the clove.
Now it's ready... Meteor Garlic...
Th-That's...
Th-That...
...Meteor Garlic?!
You have my gratitude, Livebearer!
Thank you!
Well, let's chow down!
Come on!
Hurry up an' sit down!
Livebearer-san!
Are you sure?
Of course!
It's thanks to you that we're
able to eat it like this.
Besides, food tastes better when
you eat it together, right?
Toriko-chan...
Okay...
I give thanks for all this
world's great bounty...
Let's eat!
This is all we can eat from
that giant garlic bulb...
Just how much nutrition is packed in here?
What's this?!
Wha...?! Komatsu, what
happened to your body?!
Right after I ate the Meteor Garlic,
I got all muscular like this.
Like I figured...
After all, word is that after eating it,
you can go a month without sleeping!
You too?!
The outside has the texture
of a fried potato.
The inside like moist cream cheese...
It's been so long that I'd forgotten
the joy of savoring delicious food!
You got even bigger!
Watching Komatsu-chan made me
realize that I've lost my edge.
It looks like you've remembered how
much fun food can be, Livebearer.
Coco! Coco? Are you Coco?
I guess Meteor Garlic is an ingredient
that's compatible with me.
My cells have evolved.
That's too much evolution!
Livebearer...
Why don't you go back to being a chef?
A decent chef...
I agree!
You've got super-duper
skills, Livebearer-san!
Komatsu-chan...
You got that right!
Delicious...
This is delicious...
Meteor Garlic...
You're the best, Livebearer!
You're totally macho too, Toriko-san!
All I did was teach
Komatsu-chan how to cook it.
Also, Gourmet Mafia-san...
I'm going to turn the casino over to you.
And you can scrap or do what you
want with the illegal ingredients.
You...
Thank you for the food!
Meteor Garlic was so good...
I think it would've been even more delicious
accompanied by Poison Potato,
but I didn't know how to get the poison out.
I'll have to work on that problem...
I know how to do it.
You know?!
Or to be precise, I know a
man who knows how to do it.
The method to completely remove all
of the poison from a Poison Potato...
Really?!
Yes. In fact, Coco...
I'm sure he has information on
that ingredient you wanted
to know about, Atom.
Who is he?
The personal chef to the king of Jiddal...
Joie.
No one knows who he really is.
But he's called the Dark Chef.
He should be in the royal
palace, far west of here.
A Rose Oyster, Your Highness.
Throw this sow into the dungeon.
D-Did I say anything rude, Your Highness?!
You didn't put a drop of Rose
Lemon on the Rose Oyster!
I-I'm terribly sorry!
Please forgive me!
All of you can leave, too.
King of Jiddal, Darnil Kahn
Damn you, Livebearer...
You blew it.
The casino has gathered an
abundance of ingredients.
I would say he's done well up until now.
Still and all, he's sold out to some guests.
Joie, Personal Chef to the King of Jiddal
Right, Joie?
I believe the king knows everything
that goes on at the casino.
So you'd better steel yourselves.
The palace of the notoriously evil despot...
We don't know what he's capable of.
But I have a feeling that no matter
what happens tonight, we'll be alright!
You're not the Komatsu I know!
We never did share any important
information with Livebearer.
And there aren't any crucial memories
in storage at the casino either.
I see...
Then we have no more use
for this country either...
Correct.
I've already informed everyone in
the palace and they're moving on it.
I expected heavy security,
but there's nobody here.
Yeah. Something's fishy...
Anyway, this place is huge...
It's not far behind the Gourmet Pyramid.
That's because the king keeps most
of the earnings from the casino.
It was simple for him to have
a palace like this constructed.
Not just the casino...
I'm sure he made about 50 times more from
underground commerce than the casino.
And we've amassed a decent amount of
funds. So I believe the time is right.
Our plan is in its final stage as well.
Also...
...in order to get to that place,
the notebook is necessary.
The secret notebook that the Gourmet God
Acacia is said to have left behind...
And we know where it is...
That's the king's room.
Then let's get a little face time.
We already know where the notebook is.
For our information network far exceeds
that of IGO and Gourmet Corp...
Now that you mention IGO and Gourmet Corp...
...we have reports that their top
leaders have made contact recently.
That's very curious...
Would you tell me more
over a drink and snacks?
In good time.
It seems that Toriko and his party
will arrive here in moments.
They're looking for me, apparently.
It's a pain, so I'm going to take a powder.
And you, my liege, the Robo Engine...
I see...
In that case, I suppose
I shall return, too...
We're comin' in!
Uh... Nobody's here!
It looks like they've left long ago...
I don't sense any electromagnetic waves.
I don't think anyone's
still in the royal palace.
Then the king abandoned his country...
But why would a dictator with access
to the highest quality ingredients
ditch his country?
My guess is he found a place where he
can eat food that's even more delicious.
Joie, huh?
I wanted to meet him...
It's morning.
Quiet...
Well?
Have you made the preparations?
Yes, Sensei.
You've done a wonderful job freezing it.
That's my Nono!
The Special Preparation Ingredient,
Ice Ginger,
needs to be kept at -20 degrees
and cut up quickly or it's no good.
IGO, huh?
I thought you would show
up one of these days.
I know the reason you've come for me.
It seems your president
and the boss of Gourmet Corp.
have met!
In those younger days,
No matter how you chased them,
The sky-spanning rainbows got away
After that, time passed
Were you able to grasp
The rainbow by the name of dreams then?
When it comes to a new challenge,
You turn into a coward,
But your chance ain't gonna wait on you,
So now's the time!
Bet those tears and that kindness
Will light up tomorrow
That's right, rainbows are
all the more beautiful
Because we can't catch 'em
This week's Gourmet Fortune!
It's time for Gourmet Fortune, with
a heaping helping of accuracy!
We're going to use a camera this
week too, so get yours ready!
Please choose one of these three platters.
This week's lucky ingredient is in one of them!
The higher the capture level,
the more Gourmet Luck it has!
Here we go!
A heaping helping...
Open!
This week's best Gourmet Luck is...
A - Regal Mammoth Capture Level 48
...yours if you chose A!
There are lots of fun things
in store for you this week!
You may be smiling all week long!
C - Crystal Cola Capture Level 19
If you chose C, you get this
week's second-best luck.
You might find a hint to success
in the pages of a book!
Your lucky place is a library!
B - Crab Pig Capture Level 8
And I'm sorry. If you chose B, you're third.
Are you kind of worn out?
Early to bed, early to rise, and
you'll be fit as a fiddle in no time!
It might even improve your luck!
And finally, it's Gourmet
Good Luck Charm photo time!
Are you ready?
One of Toriko's friends will
appear with some words of wisdom.
Good Luck Charm Photo Time
If you take a photo of the scene,
and carry it with you for a week as a
good luck charm, you'll be even luckier!
Alright, here we go!
3... 2... 1...
Scoop chance!
This week too,
be sure to make
delicious memories!
Alright, make delicious memories right now!
Here's next week's preview!
Maximum intensity!
The head of IGO and the boss of Gourmet Corp.
It's a battle over the legendary ingredient, GOD.
Showdown at the Summit! Ichiryu Versus Midora of the Gourmet Corp.!
Look forward to another heaping helping of fun!