It's so hot...
Eating outside is becoming unbearable.
That's true...
We're going to have to use stronger sunscreen.
You are using it right, Onee-sama?
Why?
What do you mean "why"?
UV rays are your skin's enemy!
It would be terrible if that beautiful skin of yours went wrinkly!
Come, let me rub it in all over.
It's fine, I said!
Please don't hold back!
Stop that Kuroko, hey!
Onee-sama...
Shirai-san?
Hey!
Wannai-san...
And Awatsuki-san too.
What's up?
We have a request, actually...
hanatte kokoro ni kizanda yume mo mirai sae okizari ni shite
放った心に刻んだ夢を　未来さえ置き去りにして
This power which leaves even my hopes and future in the dust,
M
azui
presents
M
genkai nado shiranai imi nai
限界など知らない　意味ない
It knows no boundaries, has no meaning.
kono chikara ga hikari chirasu sono saki ni haruka na omoi wo
この力が　光散らすその先に　遥かな想いを
I lay my dreams where this power blazes with light.
aruitekita kono michi wo furikaeru koto shika
歩いてきたこの道を 振り返ることしか
If all I can do is look back at my past lit by my power,
dekinai nara ima koko de subete wo kowaseru
出来ないなら今ここですべてを壊せる
I could destroy everything now.
kurayami ni ochiru machinami
暗闇に堕ちる街並み
The streets plunge into darkness.
hito ha dokomade tachimukaeru no
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの?
How far will people resist?
kasoku suru sono itami kara dareka wo kitto mamoreru yo
加速する　その痛みから誰かをきっと守れるよ
I'm sure it would protect someone from that worsening pain.
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way
Only my railgun can shoot it! 今すぐ
karadajuu wo hikari no hayasa de kakemegutta tashika na yokan
身体中を光の速さで 駆け巡ぐった　確かな予感
A premonition of fate runs around my body at the speed of light.
tsukame nozomu mono nara nokosazu
掴め 望むものなら 残さず
Grab it — if it's your wish, leave none behind
kagayakeru jibunrashisade
輝ける　自分らしさで
Shining as yourself,
shinjiteru yo ano hi no chikai wo
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを
I trust in the oath you made that day.
kono hitomi ni hikaru namida soresaemo tsuyosa ni naru kara
この瞳に光る涙 それさえも強さになるから
Because even the shining tears in your eyes make me strong.
Swimsuit model?
Yes...
The brand sponsoring the swimming club insisted.
It's apparently for a web catalog.
The seniors are busy with competitions,
so we're the only ones available.
Onee-sama!
Let's help them out with this!
It sounds pretty hard to be a swimsuit model...
I'm a bit...
I thought so...
Sorry—
I've misjudged you, Onee-sama!
To ignore your precious juniors who have come to you in their time of distress...
I didn't think Onee-sama was so cruel and merciless...
I'm... I'm...
You guys too!
I get it...
I'll help out if you're okay with me.
That's the spirit, Onee-sama!
You've saved us!
Thank you so much, Misaka-sama!
With this, I'll get to see Onee-sama wearing this and that...
No, more importantly, I'll be able to do this and that with a more revealing swimsuit!
I can hear everything you're thinking!
I give up! I give up!
Wow...
This place looks so corporate!
It's so exciting!
Uiharu! Uiharu! Check out this weird thing!
Thank you for going to all the effort, even inviting your friends.
Don't worry about it.
It's more fun to do these things as a group anyway.
But are you sure we can be swimsuit models?
Don't worry.
No matter how childish your figure, science holds the power of photo manipulation.
That's mean, Shirai-san...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Who is she?
She's the person in charge for the brand.
Pleased to meet you.
Where are the other two?
Two?
Oh, Shirai-san?
This voice...
Oh my, coming in such a large group.
Are you visiting on social study work?
Kongo Mitsuko...
Konori-senpai too...
And what are you doing here in that getup?
Have you perhaps forgotten the school policy that you must wear your uniform even on days off?
I'm not a Tokiwadai student today.
I came as a model.
A model?
You too?
You mean...
You're here to model for swimsuits too, Konori-senpai?
Yes.
My seniors from Judgment at the gym I go to asked me to.
What about you guys?
We were asked by the swimming club.
From the looks of it it's your first time, so I'll teach you all about it.
I've been modeling since childhood.
The audience's applause and acclamation echoing throughout the halls of my house...
I can hear it even now...
Audience? Those would be your household...
Now then, let's hurry along.
Could you show us to the changing rooms?
Ah yes, it's this way.
Do you have a swimsuit to suit me?
Is she someone you know?
Though I wish I didn't...
Now then, please choose any swimsuit you like.
Okay!
How is this?
That's wonderful!
This is cute!
This is good too!
This isn't so good.
This either.
You still can't decide?
You're so helpless, I'll choose one for you.
I'm fine.
The halter neck swimsuit is for those with a bust.
The triangle swimsuit is fine for both those with and without a bust.
I said I'm fine.
With your bust... how pitiful!
I'll have to have a good talking to you some day.
That's cute, isn't it!
It is!
The frills look great!
Ah, that's not it...
It's not like I want to wear this...
I want to see Misaka-san in this swimsuit!
Me too, please try it on!
But it's really a bit...
Don't say that, just try it on!
It'll definitely be cute!
R-Really?
Well if you insist...
Misaka-san, you're a fan of some pretty childish designs, huh?
Th-That's not true!
I'm going with this one!
Time to change!
What?
Did I do something?
Why can't I be honest with myself?
It's a bit embarrassing...
We're all girls here, there's nothing to be shy about.
It suits you.
Really?
With bikinis, the focal points are split between top and bottom,
but with a one piece your curves show, so they only suit slim people.
The swimming group know their stuff!
Do you have any other advice for choosing swimsuits?
Let's see...
For example, sarongs are stylish, and they're also useful for hiding your lower body.
I'm not trying to hide anything!
Sorry for the wait!
I was a bit disappointed they only had reserved designs,
but I guess this is all you can expect from ready-made clothes.
How do I put it...
As expected of Shirai-san...
Individuality is important!
Yeah...
This probably doesn't fulfill your desires, but please bear with it Onee-sama.
No, I don't want more anyway.
Oh my, is that everyone's got?
Observe!
Sexy and exotic!
This is the extreme swimsuit model the audience is seeking!
A snake!!
She's cute!
She's called Ekaterina-chan?
Ekaterina-san!
That sure is a nice python there...
Wannai-san, don't praise her on that!
Shut it away somewhere quickly!
Why?
Even though she's so cute?
What do you think, Shirai-san?
You have a bad taste in accessories.
It's a bit tight, but there aren't any larger sizes so it can't be helped I guess.
Must be nice.
There's nothing here...
Are we taking the pictures here?
This studio can recreate all sorts of scenarios.
Wow, I can touch it!
It's the latest technology in Academy City.
Um...
Is the cameraman going to be a man?
I hadn't thought about that.
I kind of knew, but it's still a bit...
How amateur!
Models only shine when they're on display.
It's done entirely automatically.
You probably won't even see the camera, so please act naturally.
With bikinis, the focal
points are split between
top and bottom, but with
a one piece your curves
show, so they only
suit slim people.
With bikinis, the focal
points are split between
top and bottom, but with
a one piece your curves
show, so they only
suit slim people.
She said "naturally", but that's not quite natural...
Onee-sama, let's do it too.
Do what?
Of course, natural sunscreen application!
Not that again!
I said I don't need it!
Wait up!
Don't want it!
Rub rub!
I see...
So that's what being natural is.
That's our Misaka-sama!
Such a splendid model.
Let's follow her example!
Yes!
Wh-Where the heck is this?
It got cold all of a sudden...
When the scenery changes, it seems that the temperature changes to match.
Do they have to go that far?
Is this also considered natural?
I'm a model!
Even given an order like this...
You're overdoing it.
Hot!!
This is too hot...
I'm cooking...
Why so extreme...
Water! Water!
This is way too much water!
Why so extreme!
What's with this overdecorated boat?
Alright!
What do you think of this splendid tuna?
I'm afraid that's an island skipjack.
That's not what you're supposed to be pointing out...
It's also known as Yaito Bonito in western Japan!
It stopped.
The stars are so pretty!
Look!
The Earth over there...
Surface of the moon?!
It is pretty though...
I guess...
Look there!
That's...
Sorry, I'm just making adjustments.
I'm changing the scenery.
What is it this time?
A campground?
I'm so sorry!
We ran into an error in the camera system just now.
It'll be fixed soon, so take a break for a while.
Break?
Ah, that's right — those ingredients are real, so go ahead.
She says go ahead, but what should we do?
With just these ingredients in this situation...
It's gotta be curry!
Let's split up the rice and curry preparation.
I'll do curry!
Me too.
I'll do the rice then.
I'll do what Onee-sama does.
Honestly, such a commoner food like curry?
But it's delicious!
Don't you like curry?
She just doesn't know how to make it, right?
What are you talking about!
Of course I can!
The Kongo family's ultimate secret curry!
Wow, what kind of curry is that?
That sounds good!
I'd love to try it!
Please make it!
Well you were so excited about the commoner curry, so we can just go with that today...
We can just do both, right?
We have enough ingredients.
That sounds good!
Agreed!
Right?
W-Well, if you insist...
Awesome!
Now that's decided, let's start!
We'll handle the rice.
Okay!
Look forward to it!
Um, Kongo-san...
Y-Yes?
Might we help out as well?
B-But of course!
Well then...
Firstly, let's peel the onions.
Okay!
Huh?
Broken?
That's a problem...
Got it!
High tech, huh?
Don't talk to me.
If I'm not careful, it'll overflow...
Do this one too please!
There's more?
They've gotten quite small...
What do we do with these?
Um...
These are used like that!
To use only this much of a whole onion, this must be quite an exquisite recipe!
I-Is this instructive?
Yes!
Um, Kongo-san...
Thank you for going out of your way to teach us!
To tell the truth, neither of us have made curry before.
It's an honor to receive instruction from you!
Quarter-slicing carrots really is the best.
Don't you cut at angles for curry?
I think quarter-sliced is cuter...
It cooks faster too.
You don't get it do you?
Vegetables in curry have to be cut so they aren't too big or too small.
In the curry we do at my home, we chop the vegetables fine, making them blend with the sauce.
No, no, no.
There's no way they can be small.
You have to properly peel the potatoes, and make them look nice.
Taste is more important than looks!
It's still tasty!
Hey, vegetables in curry have to be big, right?
Small, right?
They're grating...
Sweetcorn?
Peeling tomatoes is pretty hard...
And slicing kelp is pretty difficult...
Slicing mandarins into rings, peel and all...
I got juice in my eye!
Oh Awatsuki-san...
I wonder what kind of curry this'll turn out like?
My first time making curry is so exciting!
The ingredients are very unique!
I never knew you use great burdock!
And strawberries too!
I'm starting to feel hungry!
I can't wait!
Huh?
Kongo-san?
Um...
The truth is...
I...
Actually, I've never made curry.
Never mind curry, I'm terrible at cooking...
Sorry.
I couldn't say it under the circumstances...
In that case, let's ask everyone how to do it!
Right?
Of course!
Um...
Work hard, work hard, Onee-sama~
It's done!
Chicken curry!
We made seafood curry!
Yep!
Let's eat then!
Let's eat!
It's good!
Small vegetables are pretty good!
Big ones too!
This is pretty good too!
It really is delicious!
Isn't that great?
It was worth the effort!
Yes...
Right?
It tastes good when everyone's worked together to make it.
You're a good person...
What's your name?
Misaka Mikoto...
Misaka...
Where have I heard...
Well, it's all good.
I'd be happy to call you a friend from now on, Misaka-san.
That so? Thanks.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
The system is repaired, so we'll continue with the shooting.
Already?
Ah, you can finish eating.
For now we'll just take one!
That was good.
If being a model is like this, I'd do it any day!
That was fun!
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Commoner food isn't bad once in a while.
Says the one who took seconds.
Huh? Where's Misaka-san?
Onee-sama?
Um...
That wasn't it...
This one?
Yahoo!
This is the cutest!
Take that!
Biribiri?
What the heck is she doing?
I did it!
Dear My Friend
Every day & night
Always be with you
Dear My Friend
Every day & night
Always be with you
kanashikutemo madamada tarinai mama
悲しくてもまだまだ足りないまま
Even though it's sad, it's not enough
yuuyake ga machi wo someteyuku
夕焼けが街を染めてゆく
the sunset dyes the city
omou you ni nakanaka ikanaitte
思うのように中々行かない...って
moving like the clouds, not really going anywhere
kizuitara issho ni naiteita
気付いたら　一緒に泣いていた
when I realized, we were crying together
koi mo yume mo hana mo niji mo kaze mo zenbu tsukamou yo
恋も夢も花も虹も風も全部掴もうよ
Love, dreams, flowers, rainbows and the wind, let's take it all!
daijoubu genki dashite
ダイジョウブ！　元気出して
It's ok, cheer up
watashi ga soba ni iru kara
私がそばにいるから
I'm right beside you.
kyou nomi sa kuyamu yori ima norikoete
今日のミス　悔やむより今乗り越えて
It's only today, let's get past this now and not worry.
daijoubu mayowanaide
ダイジョウブ！　迷わないで
it's ok, don't hesitate
mada minu mirai he to mukatte
まだ見ぬ未来へと向かって
let's keep walking on forever,
zutto aruiteyukou
ずっと　歩いてゆこう
right into the future.
Every day & night
Always be with you
Next Episode
Preview
Who are you?
Are you aware that you are addressing Tokiwadai's Kongo Mitsuko?
Special Course
Um, Kongo-san...
We don't appear next episode...