You're not getting away now.
Wait a second! I'm just—
Give it up!
Misaka-san!
Uiharu-san, Saten-san.
What happened?
There was a really loud noise just now...
Ah, that's...
haruka kokoro ni kizanda yume mo mirai sae okizari ni shite
遥か心に刻んだ 夢も未来さえ置き去りにして
This power which leaves even my hopes and future in the dust,
M
azui
presents
M
genkai nado shiranai imi nai
限界など知らない　意味ない
It knows no boundaries, has no meaning.
kono chikara ga hikari chirasu sono saki ni haruka na omoi wo
この力が　光散らすその先に　遥かな想いを
I lay my dreams where this power blazes with light.
aruitekita kono michi wo furikaeru koto shika
歩いてきたこの道を 振り返ることしか
If all I can do is look back at my past lit by my power,
dekinai nara ima koko de subete wo kowaseru
出来ないなら今ここですべてを壊せる
I could destroy everything now.
kurayami ni ochiru machinami
暗闇に落ちる街並み
The streets plunge into darkness.
hito ha dokomade tachimukaeru no
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの?
How far will people resist?
kasoku suru sono itami kara dareka wo kitto mamoreru yo
加速する　その痛みから誰かをきっと守れるよ
I'm sure it would protect someone from that worsening pain.
Looking the prism this planet to far such away
only my railgun can do let me want to that
karadajuu wo hikari no hayasa de kakemegutta tashika na yokan
体中を光の速さで 駆けめぐった　確かな予感
A premonition of fate runs around my body at the speed of light.
tsukame nozomu mono nara nokosazu
掴め 望むものなら 残さず
Grab it — if it's your wish, leave none behind
kagayakeru jibunrashisa
輝ける　自分らしさで
Shining as yourself,
shinjiteru yo ano hi no chikai wo
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを
I trust in the oath you made that day.
kono hitomi ni hikaru namida soresaemo tsuyosa ni naru kara
この瞳に光る涙 それさえも強さになるから
Because even the shining tears in your eyes make me strong.
Today is...
Kuroko and Onee-sama's anniversary.
It was one month ago today...
when we were tied with the red string of fate.
It's unfortunate the goods I ordered didn't arrive...
but today, Kuroko will...
give one to her without fail.
A present from my heart and soul.
That's right, me, and all that I am!
I'm ba...!
Onee-sama!
Excuse...
...us!
Wow!
It's a lady's room that I always wanted!
So stylish and chic!
And the bed's so cushy too!
You're right!
This is really amazing!
Geez, what were you thinking?
Onee-sama too, why are Uiharu and Saten-san here?
I happened to meet them in the city.
They came shopping with me and said they wanted to see my dorm.
Shopping?
Ah, nothing important.
The Tokiwadai girl's dorms really are amazing.
I'm jealous!
And the dining room was this big.
It's not really like that...
Why did Onee-sama have to do this today of all days?
What a way to spoil our anniversary!
Could it be...
Today is the one month anniversary of Kuroko and I being joined by the red string of fate.
Kuroko and myself are two but joined as one.
Uiharu-san, Saten-san, let's get along from now on too.
Here's to your beautiful eyes.
Um... Shirai-san, are you alright?
It's nothing.
We can't offer much, but make yourself at home.
Huh?
What are you doing over there, Saten-san?
Well, when you visit a friend's place, you've gotta start with a room search.
Woah!
Erotic!
Saten-san, you shouldn't look through people's belongings!
As expected of Misaka-san, so adult!
No, that's...
Mine.
These are Shirai-san's...
These bold panties?
Oh I wouldn't call them bold.
Having black underwear is a lady's choice.
So... this deep red butterfly too?
I choose that color when I want to spice up the mood.
And these pretty-much-just-string T-backs?
I treasure those because they don't leave a mark on my skin.
These full-body mesh stockings too?
There are times a lady has to catch attention.
What are you doing all of a sudden, Saten-san?!
Well you know, I just wanted to get back my everyday life.
Seeing Uiharu's striped panties helped me calm down.
Such a big fuss over underwear.
Look, I have all sorts besides those.
Heart-throbbing open-bra frilled babydoll.
Laced teddy with garter belt.
And...
Thank goodness...
Even Shirai-san wears this sort of thing.
My Shirai-san came back.
Sorry, these are mine.
The hell, Kuroko!
Why do you have my underwear under your bed?
You're making a mistake, Onee-sama!
Come now, Misaka-san...
I know! I want to see your photo albums.
Gotta do that!
I'd like to see what Misaka-san and Kuroko-san looked like in middle school and such.
Woah!
So cute!
Is this your elementary school entrance ceremony?
Is that pretty person beside you your mother?
Yeah...
Wow!
This is embarrassing.
Kimono!
But that's a bit unexpected.
What is?
Well you're Tokiwadai's Level 5 ace, right?
I thought you'd be a well bought up young lady, always in the company of the elite.
Of course not.
I started off as a Level 1.
A totally normal kid.
Really?
So, Shirai-san next!
With pleasure...
...is what I'd like to say, but unfortunately I don't keep one.
Kuroko lives in the present.
Rather than looking back to the past...
or dreaming of the future,
I want to gaze at this moment now!
That's how I've decided to live.
It's this, right?
Don't look at that!
Kuroko!
You definitely need to reflect on the now more than the past or the future!
I just... so earnestly and sincerely...
Onee-sama!
Don't you remember what today is?
You brought Uiharu and Saten-san back,
today of all days...
Today?
Uiharu-san and Saten-san...
Oh, right!
You've remembered?
It's been one week today since I met Uiharu-san and Saten-san!
It seems so fast, but that was a whole week ago wasn't it?
More like, it's only been a week?
It feels like we've been together for a long time.
Hope we can continue to get along!
What's with this difference in treatment?
Maybe... I'm not wanted?
These red beans...
They'll be discarded without anyone giving a second thought.
I'm the same as these lonely beans!
It's surprisingly good!
Pork cutlet sandwich?
And then afterwards, Uiharu...
Hey, Saten-san!
That's so wrong!
You're so noisy!
I'm drowning my sorrows in red bean juice.
Huh?
Who could be in my shoes and not despair?
Um...
Meeting a week ago?
Don't make me laugh.
One month!
This is the one month anniversary of the red string of fate tying Onee-sama and me together!
One month ago on this day...
Chance brought together Onee-san and I here as roommates.
Since then, we've shared times of joy and sadness together.
Here!
In this room!
And yet...
And yet, Onee-sama... you...
Shirai-san...
Maybe we shouldn't have come today?
Kuroko.
You...
Onee-sama...
...forced your way in here, if I remember right.
Not by coincidence or by the red string of fate.
And what were you saying?
Joy? Sadness? Drowning your sorrows in red bean juice?
Um... I... just... remembered... I... have to...
You've got nerve saying all that!
Id'sa badda porsvertib!
You're right, bad perverts should be thrown out!
It's a matter of perspective!
Also, I...
I just wanted to hold some modest celebrations with you today...
Yes?
Express delivery.
Is room 208, Shirai Kuroko-san's residence?
Yes...
What's the package?
It says "Computer parts".
That's right,
those kinds of retailers take that into consideration.
Who's the sender?
Love & Herbs: Quality Aphrodisiacs, Ltd.
What's the point when the name's plainly written down?!
Kuroko...
What kind of aphrodisiacs might you need for 'modest celebrations'?
It seems I need to take drastic measures to correct that perverted streak of yours.
I'm going to char you as black as your name!
Onee-sama...
It's no good if you forget about my power, now.
Now it's down to this, it's eat or be eaten.
If you won't accept my love,
then fight with me!
Onee-sama?
Dorm rule #9:
Esper power usage within the dorm is strictly forbidden.
Surely you haven't forgotten this, Shirai?
W-W-What a lovely day it is, dorm mistress!
I certainly haven't forgotten, but we weren't using our powers for mischief, you see.
There are extenuating circumstances that—
I see.
Extenuating circumstances?
T-That's right!
The truth is...
However!
Kuroko!
If I were to listen to every circumstance every time, I would not be able to uphold the rules of the dorm.
Punishment must be exacted on those who break the rules.
Don't you think,
Misaka?
Y...
You Need to be Hydrated
When You Work Under the Sun
Yes!
Geez.
Why do I have to do this?
I did go a bit overboard,
but a punishment like cleaning up this ridiculously large pool...
That's impossible no matter how you look at it!
Even though we've been going since morning, it's already past noon,
and we haven't even finished a third of it!
Will we even finish by the end of today?
How lucky!
I get to spend some private time with the sweaty, dripping wet Onee-sama...
This is a once in a lifetime chance to get revenge for yesterday!
Onee-sama!
You need to be hydrated when you work under the sun.
How about some of my specially-made drink?
No need.
Why not?
Don't tell me you put some of those "computer parts" you got yesterday into it?
I thought so.
Shirai-san?
It really is Shirai-san!
What might you be doing here?
As you can see, cleaning the pool.
But why?
Even in summer, the winds of society can be cold.
What about you two?
We're part of the swimming club so...
Kuroko's classmates?
That means...
They're younger than me...
Onee-sama.
These are my classmates,
Wannai Kinoho-san and Awatsuki Maaya-san.
Afternoon.
And this is—
Hm, excuse me but... are you Misaka-sama?
Yes...
I thought so!
Don't you remember?
The other day when I was surrounded by a group of thugs, you saved me.
Ah, I remember something like that.
You really helped me out back then.
You're just like I've heard.
It's an honor to meet you.
As expected from Onee-sama.
She's punishing bad guys even when I'm not watching her.
Those men were really scary.
Honestly,
all the weirdos come out when it gets hot.
But it was really impressive.
You were really amazing back there!
No, no, no.
It's kind of like doing odd jobs, for me.
This is...
Deja-vu!
It's just my imagination.
I'm just nervous because of what happened yesterday.
Leaving only me out... that can't be.
It must be tiresome working in this heat.
I have a sports drink so if you'd like...
Thanks!
I'll have some.
Wha—
What's with this difference in treatment?
Come to think of it...
All my approaches till now have been ignored.
And when I fondled her to try deepen our friendship,
I was violently rejected.
Is it possible Onee-sama is really shunning me?
Get a grip, Kuroko!
If you don't have confidence, just get it back!
If you have uncertanties, just blow them away!
That's right, I have a unique advantage.
With my teleport ability, there are countless ways I can be of use to Onee-sama!
Amazing!
You can see it getting clean!
My power is water-current manipulation.
I have to go submit my examination results to the teacher,
but once that's over, would you let me help out?
Really? But...
It's the least I can do as thanks for saving me.
Thanks, that'd be a great help.
I'm glad to be of service!
It really is amazing.
With this we'll be done in no time!
Well then, see you later.
I'll leave my sports drink here, so feel free to have the rest.
They seem like nice friends, Kuroko.
That's true.
I'm glad she came.
With her we'll be done in 10 minutes.
That's true.
I want to hurry up and finish so I can get some ice cream.
Which Chinese Queen was born in the 10th century?
That's true.
What's the matter?
You look down.
No, don't mind me...
I can't even help out with cleaning, after all...
Um...
Is something bothering you—
I'm fine!
I'm not suitable to be with Onee-sama.
I always cause you trouble, and I can't help you...
I'm not fit to stay by your side!
Wha...
What do I do?
This is so sudden I can't keep up.
I wonder if Misaka-san already gave it to her.
I wanted to see her give it.
We went out of the way to help her find it, after all.
I want to see Shirai-san's reaction.
After all, with that taste in underwear of hers...
That's true.
I wouldn't have thought she had that kind of taste.
But you know, with this sort of thing, feelings are the most important thing.
That's true.
Hey, Kuroko.
Do you remember what happened a month ago today?
A month ago today?
Yep.
The evening after you barged into my room.
You got caught by the dorm mistress and we got scolded.
Then, the next day,
they made the two of us clean the cafeteria.
Then in the end, we ended up being together till today.
Which means that if there's an anniversary for us,
it would be today, right?
Can I open it?
Of course.
We'll always be together from now on too, so let's get along.
O-Onee-sama...
"Always together"...
Of course.
We go the same school, we live in the same room.
Even if we wanted to, we couldn't be apart.
After all, we're partners.
Here.
A toast to our partnership.
As a couple tied by the red string of fate!
As roommates.
Alright then!
We've still got work to do.
Onee-sama...
Wouldn't it be better to work in swimsuits so the water doesn't bother us?
It'd be a hassle to go get them.
The truth is, just in case...
Ta da!
I've already brought your school swimsuit!
That was in my locked locker!
Keys mean nothing in the face of my power.
Come now, please undress.
Dear me, Onee-sama.
Wearing such childish things again...
Hey! Give that back!
You're changing into your swimsuit.
Huh?
What's this?
It matches! It matches!
Matches, matches!
It matches Onee-sama's!
Kuroko!
It seems lively here.
Misaka-sama, the examination is over, so we can hel—
Wonderful!
Onee-sama's love whip is wonderfu—
Enough of that, give it back!
Give it back!
I don't want to.
I said give it back!
This pain...
You're still saying that?!
Let's pretend we didn't see anything.
Good idea.
I'll never be disheartened.
I'll stay by Onee-sama's side forever.
Dear my friend
every day now
Always be with you
Dear my friend
every day now
Always be with you
kanashikutemo madamada tarinai mama
悲しくてもまだまだ足りないまま
Even though it's sad, it's not enough
yuuyake ga machi wo someteyuku
夕焼けが街を染めてゆく
the sunset dyes the city
kumo no you ni nakanaka ikanakute
雲のようになかなかいかないて
moving like the clouds, not really going anywhere
kizuitara issho ni naiteita
気付いたら　一緒に泣いていた
when I realised, we were crying together
koi mo yume mo hana mo niji mo kaze mo zenbu tsukamou yo
恋も夢も花も虹も風も全部掴もうよ
Love, dreams, flowers, rainbows and the wind, let's take it all!
daijoubu genki dashite
大丈夫元気出して
It's ok, cheer up
watashi ga soba ni iru kara
私が傍に居るから
I'm right beside you.
kyou nomi sa kuyamu yori ima norikoete
今日のみさ　悔やむより今乗り越えて
It's only today, let's get past this now and not worry.
daijoubu mayowanaide
大丈夫迷わないで
it's ok, don't hesitate
mada minu mirai he to mukatte
まだ見ぬ未来へとむかって
let's keep walking on forever,
zutto aruiteyukou
ずっと歩いてゆこう
right into the future.
every day now
Always be with you
Next Episode
Preview
She loves me.
She loves me not.
Tokiwadai in danger
She loves me.
She loves me not.
Shirai-san!
She loves me.
Please stop reading your love fortune with the flowers on my head!
She loves me not.
She loves me.