What was that?
What?
A firework?
That gave me a shock.
Yeah...
hanatte kokoro ni kizanda yume mo mirai sae okizari ni shite
放った心に刻んだ夢を　未来さえ置き去りにして
This power which leaves even my hopes and future in the dust,
M
azui
presents
M
genkai nado shiranai imi nai
限界など知らない　意味ない
It knows no boundaries, has no meaning.
kono chikara ga hikari chirasu sono saki ni haruka na omoi wo
この力が　光散らすその先に　遥かな想いを
I lay my dreams where this power blazes with light.
aruitekita kono michi wo furikaeru koto shika
歩いてきたこの道を 振り返ることしか
If all I can do is look back at my past lit by my power,
dekinai nara ima koko de subete wo kowaseru
出来ないなら今ここですべてを壊せる
I could destroy everything now.
kurayami ni ochiru machinami
暗闇に堕ちる街並み
The streets plunge into darkness.
hito ha dokomade tachimukaeru no
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの?
How far will people resist?
kasoku suru sono itami kara dareka wo kitto mamoreru yo
加速する　その痛みから誰かをきっと守れるよ
I'm sure it would protect someone from that worsening pain.
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way 今すぐ
Only my railgun can shoot it! 今すぐ
karadajuu wo hikari no hayasa de kakemegutta tashika na yokan
身体中を光の速さで 駆け巡ぐった　確かな予感
A premonition of fate runs around my body at the speed of light.
tsukame nozomu mono nara nokosazu
掴め 望むものなら 残さず
Grab it — if it's your wish, leave none behind
kagayakeru jibunrashisade
輝ける　自分らしさで
Shining as yourself,
shinjiteru yo ano hi no chikai wo
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを
I trust in the oath you made that day.
kono hitomi ni hikaru namida soresaemo tsuyosa ni naru kara
この瞳に光る涙 それさえも強さになるから
Because even the shining tears in your eyes make me strong.
That case again?
This is the fifth incident.
The explosions are small scale and no one's been injured,
however...
It's not very funny, even if it's meant to be a practical joke.
So, any clues as to the culprit's objectives?
We finally got a lead yesterday.
Have you ever heard of gravitons, Onee-sama?
Gravitons...
Those gravity particles?
In all the cases so far, just before an explosion, satellites observe a rapid acceleration of gravitons.
Using aluminum as an origin point, they force gravitons to accelerate explosively, scattering the aluminum into the surroundings.
Basically, they turn aluminum into an explosive.
Why aluminum?
Who knows.
'Who knows'?
So basically, this means an esper's behind it.
Couldn't you find them instantly if you searched Academy City's databanks?
All students' abilities are registered there, right?
We've already tried that, of course.
The ability matching the crime is 'Synchrotron'.
When we filter it down to those who'd be able to use it to detonate aluminum, there's only one Level 4 student that fits.
So doesn't that make her the culpr—
However, she has an alibi.
She's been hospitalized while the crimes were taking place, so it's impossible for her to have committed them.
I see.
So that's why you're at a dead end.
And I doubt there's any problem with the databanks either.
Could it be...
the work of an esper who isn't registered yet?
Hey, how about I help find the culprit?
No thank you.
Onee-sama.
You weren't thinking...
"Oh my! This sounds interesting, I might get to try out my skills on them if they're good"... were you?
That's not...
There's no use playing dumb.
I know what you're thinking!
Honestly, I always have to tell you.
You're only a member of the public. Maintaining order is—
"the responsibility of Judgment", right?
I got it.
If you think you can do Judgment work purely out of curiosity, you're very mistaken.
Like I said, that's not—
I'll have you promise me this.
First!
Don't run recklessly into trouble.
What's with that one-sided demand?
Second!
Even if you get caught up in trouble by chance, you are forbidden to fight alone. Wait for Judgment to arrive.
But it's over by the time you guys arrive!
Third!
Don't wear shorts under your skirt!
That's got nothing to do with this!
I'd like you to reconsider your clothing and attitude while we're at it.
And I'm always distressed at how you are more than slightly lacking in awareness of your status as Tokiwadai's ace.
That's...
No, let me finish.
If you had even the slightest awareness,
then you would not hug your teddy bear while you slept, or find Gekota floating in the bath entertaining,
and you'd put an end to your childish interests.
There's more.
Those immeasurably infantile, pastel underwear and pajamas — as the third strongest Level 5 of Academy City...
A-Are you...
Are you my mother?!
U-Um...
What do you think, Uiharu-san?
Why don't you have a seat first, Misaka-san...
This is just what I think, but she probably doesn't want you involved in dangerous things.
Dangerous?
And about this graviton case...
So that's what you're calling it.
At first they were just empty cans in garbage bins,
but recently they've been putting aluminum in normally harmless things like stuffed animals and children's bags.
That's pretty awful.
So while it might not excuse her entirely, that's why Shirai-san's been more worried about you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's your jumbo fruit parfait.
Alright!
Thanks for the food!
U—i—ha—ru!
Sh-Shirai-san!
You've got a lot of nerve slacking in a place like this.
Come! We're going on patrol.
Yes.
But my parfait...
My parfait!
I'm the one who asked her out.
Parfait...
If you have any complaints, say them to me.
Not at all.
This is a Judgment issue.
So the opinion of a commoner doesn't mean anything?
Have you perhaps forgotten, Onee-sama?
Judgment's work isn't as simple as you think, Onee-sama.
Wait!
Parfait!
Why's she acting all high and mighty?
All she ever says is Judgment this, Judgment that.
How about you try getting there before I can beat up the criminals just once?
Ah, whatever.
I'll return it to her later.
What are you doing lounging around here?
Um...
Me?
Yes, you, assistant.
Assistant?
No, you see,
earlier I was—
Come on, hurry up and put your armband on.
We're going.
Wait, going where?
To do work, of course!
You didn't hear?
Work?
Meaning...
What's up with you?
Speaking of which, I've never seen you before...
Are you a new recruit?
Yes!
I'm Misaka, I was just assigned.
Misaka...
Where have I heard that name...
What's your name?
I'm Konori Mii from the 177th branch.
Pleased to meet you, Konori-senpai!
Same here...
I'll show her I'm perfectly capable of Judgment work too.
Arrows or guns, bring it on!
Here.
What's this?
What do you mean?
It's a broom, of course.
I see...
We got a request to clean up this place.
Um...
I'm part of Judgment...
Right.
We in Judgment get to clean up the garbage that students drop.
Didn't you learn that in training?
Oh, that's right!
Is this what Judgment's job is?
Hey, stop right there!
Oh, take care of this too.
I said wait...
Didn't I?!
You reap what you sow.
Realize—
Honestly.
There's a limit to carelessness. Leaving your armband...
Was it there?
Well... I couldn't find it, and they said they didn't have one.
I'm sorry.
There's no helping that.
We'll write the letter of apology later.
For now, let's head back to the branch and...
What's wrong?
Are you lost?
You can't just use your powers thoughtlessly like that!
But...
No buts!
Protecting public order and using force are totally separate things.
U-Um...
Oh, that's right!
In training—
Try using common sense, not training.
Judgment's work isn't so simple.
Honestly.
I'll work hard!
I will do this job properly!
Right.
Good luck.
I'm totally useless...
Thank you.
I take it work in the field is completely different from training?
Yeah...
More like, I didn't know I couldn't read maps or hold back or read the mood that badly...
I was bad at it too.
Reading maps.
It takes a bit of work, even if you know the city.
Yes. Konori here.
I see.
Understood.
We'll look for it too.
We got a request to search for something.
Search for something?
Right. A bag.
A bag.
...but recently they've been putting aluminum in normally harmless things, like stuffed animals and children's bags.
Could it be a children's bag?
Oh, you catch on fast.
It's pink with flowers on it.
They left it on a bench and a dog made off with it.
A dog?
Isn't that bad?
We have to catch that dog quick!
Right.
It'll be a hassle if it gets dropped somewhere.
Dropped somewhere?
Someone might pick it up and take it.
Take it...
Quickly!
We have to recover it quickly!
Um... yeah.
Everyone's Proactive
When it Comes to This
Right.
Sorry about this!
I can't fit in there.
Well, I kind of "fit"...
Misaka-san?
Are you okay?
Something just now...
with lots of legs...
Don't come near me!
Where on earth could it be?
What's wrong?
Something just now...
with no legs...
Don't come near me!
Not here either...
Why am I on the bottom?
Speaking of which, it isn't a cat.
No matter how you look at it, we're not searching the right places.
Misaka-san, a little bit to the right.
Y-Yes...
Scary bugs scary bugs scary bugs!!
Don't fling—
I see...
Not in area D either...
Understood.
We appreciate the help.
Heya!
Is Uiharu in?
She's inside.
This is Judgment branch 177.
Uiharu!
Check this out, I finally found that track I was look—
Shhh!
She was so worn out she fell asleep.
So cute!
So you have a kid?
I know!
Wait, what?
So, when do her flowers grow out?
These aren't growing from me!
That, huh.
I don't have any kids!
But look, her eyes match yours.
No they don't!
Now now, keep it down or she'll wake up.
It's your fault!
Sorry!
So what's with this kid?
Lost child?
No.
She asked us to help her look for her bag.
Apparently it was a birthday present from her parents,
so while we're requesting help from other branches, I'm keeping watch over her.
Wow.
But getting help from other branches?
Isn't that a bit overboard?
A fundamental aspect of Academy City is being separated from your family.
Everyone's proactive when it comes to this kind of thing.
Judgment do all sorts of things, don't they.
Good girl.
Must be hard.
Where did she go?
Don't act like nothing happened!
Bumping into someone without even an apology?
You guys bumped int—
You think you can just talk back at me like that?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Judgment?
Nothing.
"Nothing" my ass!
You two were ganging up on—
You're so noisy.
Stupid kid.
Kid?!
Bear with it, bear with it.
Are you okay?
Get here faster!
What's with him?
Misaka-san!
Did you find it?
Ah, no...
Not here either, huh.
Where else haven't we looked...
Here.
It can't be...
It were here...
Yeah, I expect some of the kids aren't good with dogs.
No, that's not the issue here.
You're right.
If they got bitten...
Like I said, that's unrelated!
Let's search, I guess.
You take that area.
Ignoring me?!
Good luck!
Geez...
Are you a Judgment person?
Wow, a Tokiwadai Middle uniform!
Rich girl!
Um...
She's got shorts under her skirt.
Why's she wearing something like that?
Maybe cause she's a rich girl?
Don't you have normal panties?
I've got them on underneath!
No panties!
No panties Judgment!
I said that's not it!
A dog!
There it is!
Konori-senpai!
Stop right ther—
Leave it to me!
It's fast!
Got no choice.
Alright, got you now!
Huh?
No way!
Don't take me lightly!
Misaka-san!
Objective safely acquired!
Wow!
Awesome!
Good work.
You did well.
Wait—
Should you be handling it like that?
We need to call the bomb disposal unit!
Bomb?
Here.
Be sure not to lose it again.
Yup!
Good work!
That's our Konori-san!
It wasn't me who found it.
Onee-sama?!
Misaka-san?
Oh? Do you two know her?
You could say that...
That's Misaka Mikoto-san,
from Tokiwadai Middle School.
Misaka...
Mikoto...
Wait, the Railgun?
But why did she...
And why's she dripping wet?
Ah, well you see...
She jumped into the fountain to protect the bag.
Apparently she thought it was going to blow up.
That's...
Goodness Onee-sama, even after that talk we had.
But that's kind of like her.
K-Kuroko!
Um, this is...
There's no need to kick up a fuss,
Tokiwadai's Railgun-san.
I see...
Crap!
You found out?
Um, this...
Over here.
Onee-chan!
Thank you!
Um... well...
You're welcome.
Isn't that great?
Yeah!
Seriously, Onee-sama...
I guess that's fine.
That was one heck of a day.
That's what you get.
To think you suddenly became a Judgment because you were irritated...
Just how childish are you?
I hope you've learned your lesson.
Judgment really is tough work.
Onee-sama...
I see you in a better light now.
How long I have waited for this day...
See me in a better light, please!
Look over every inch of me!
Idiot!
That's not the kind of seeing I was talking about!
Onee-sama! Onee-sama!
Come now!
You're noisy!
Dear My Friend
Every day & night
Always be with you
Dear My Friend
Every day & night
Always be with you
kanashikutemo madamada tarinai mama
悲しくてもまだまだ足りないまま
Even though it's sad, it's not enough
yuuyake ga machi wo someteyuku
夕焼けが街を染めてゆく
the sunset dyes the city
omou you ni nakanaka ikanaitte
思うのように中々行かない...って
moving like the clouds, not really going anywhere
kizuitara issho ni naiteita
気付いたら　一緒に泣いていた
when I realized, we were crying together
koi mo yume mo hana mo niji mo kaze mo zenbu tsukamou yo
恋も夢も花も虹も風も全部掴もうよ
Love, dreams, flowers, rainbows and the wind, let's take it all!
daijoubu genki dashite
ダイジョウブ！　元気出して
It's ok, cheer up
watashi ga soba ni iru kara
私がそばにいるから
I'm right beside you.
kyou nomi sa kuyamu yori ima norikoete
今日のミス　悔やむより今乗り越えて
It's only today, let's get past this now and not worry.
daijoubu mayowanaide
ダイジョウブ！　迷わないで
it's ok, don't hesitate
mada minu mirai he to mukatte
まだ見ぬ未来へと向かって
let's keep walking on forever,
zutto aruiteyukou
ずっと　歩いてゆこう
right into the future.
every day now
Always be with you
We're with Judgment!
Everyone, please evacuate the premises immediately!
Is there something wrong with my store?
A graviton particle acceleration has been detected.
Graviton?
There is the possibility of a bomb in this store.
A bomb?
Dammit, where is it...
What's wrong?
Sorry, I hurt my leg...
We have to hurry up and evacuate.
Right.
No way...
Are you okay?
Any injuries?
This person... protected me...
To Be
Continued
Next Episode
Preview
I'm doing it.
I'm doing it!
Ability and Power
If I said I'm doing it, I'm doing it!
I'll show you I'm doing it!
Doing what?
Wait, who are you?