Imagine, us meeting again in this fashion.
All of you are my guinea pigs!
Academy City is a breeding farm,
and every last one of you are livestock!
But right now, the one who holds the key to saving Febri...
Long time no see,
my little guinea pig.
Therestina Kihara Lifeline.
A blazing hope is blasting through the city
It gives me the strength to hold hands with my trusted friends
and keep looking for a tomorrow that will satisfy us
A Certain Scientific Railgun
On a crowded street I saw your shape drawing away
Because we understand the love we share now
smiles light up around me
and brighten our days
I want to protect that simple happiness
Once my dreams start coming true, with the sky as my witness,
I will begin to have power over my reality
I had the strength to talk about my fears
I won't forget when it was that I did
I will hold dear the bonds that bind us
and blast open a path to a future I can be proud of
Mugino, come on!
Yeah, later.
Wah! Are you all right?
Hmm?
Ah, this is great.
Huh? What are you talking about?
In short, it's about saving face.
We can't just sit back and do nothing while being taken advantage of.
If you get taken for granted in this world, it's all over.
Being manipulated by bad information is your problem.
Are you not gonna swim?
Why should we have to clean up your mess?!
This is fun.
I can't believe you!
I told you that you'd get paid for it, so stop complaining!
You said yourself that you were pissed about being tricked, right?
Tch...
We're free to get rowdy, right?
As much as you like.
What's going on, Mugino? Work?
Yeah. I'm not very enthusiastic about it, though.
We're going to go work up a little sweat.
What?
That look on your face has gotten better, no?
You must have seen your fill of the darkness this town has to offer.
Did you lose hope?
Did you get spooked when you jumped into the deep end?
What did you do? Curse Academy City here?
And then finally, you realized that I was right?
Academy City is a test site. All its students are guinea pigs!
So?
What did you want to ask?
Or perhaps you wanted me to pat your head and comfort you?
I want to save a friend.
Huh?
Her name is Febri.
She's an artificially-made little girl,
and unless I do something, she'll only have seventy-two hours to live.
So I want to help her.
I know that it was an underground organization that made her.
I thought that maybe you'd know something about it—
What are you, stupid?
Friend, huh?
After you've had a whole heap of your clones killed,
you can still go on spouting such nonsense?
This kid, whatever her name is,
is just one more guinea pig produced by the darkness of the city!
If you're going to make it here,
you either get swallowed up by it and live as cattle,
or you blow everything away, including the darkness.
There are no other choices to be made.
That's not true.
Huh?
Sure, I've had a good look at the darkness you speak of.
I've gotten a shock from it, and I've even become desperate.
However,
it was the people I met in this city that saved me.
I have many precious friends, and if it weren't for this city,
I'd have never met them.
There are many things that disgust me,
but I still don't hate Academy City.
That's enough.
Go away.
I'm not leaving.
Not until you tell me.
Who was it that created Febri?
Who knows?
What is their objective? What is this thing?!
Tell me!
Please!
What if I lie?
Do I have any reason to tell you the truth?
Would you believe anything I say?
Yes, I'll believe it.
Why?
Because I've decided to believe you.
Hold out your hand.
Now, eat it.
It's just chocolate, nothing added to it.
What's the matter? You believe me, right?
I said I'd believe you, didn't I?
Go away.
No. Tell me about Febri.
I don't have anything to tell you!
I'm not leaving until you tell me!
You're so annoying! Get lost!
Please, tell me about Febri!
Please!
Ah, you're such a pain.
Chemicaloid.
If I remember, that's what they called it.
They?
A chemicaloid is what Febri is?
It was all just theoretical at the time,
but those boys must've perfected it.
Then they're the guys that made Febri? What's their objective?
No clue.
They probably want to draw attention to themselves.
Attention?
There's some kind of event coming up, isn't there?
Event?
The Reach Assembly!
What do you mean, draw attention?
What would that have to do with Febri?!
What would it?
Ha, such is the mindset of the chosen Level 5, huh?
Huh?
Remember this, young lady...
Here in Academy City, just by having a Level 5 nametag on you,
even a lab rat like you has lots of precious friends that flock to them.
When you find out how deep the darkness goes for those who can't even become lab rats,
don't get so scared that you wet yourself,
you filthy brat!
Huh? So you met with Therestina?
Yeah, sorry. It all happened so quickly,
I didn't have the chance to tell you guys.
So the official name for what Febri is called is a "chemicaloid," then?
And these people are planning to do something at the Reach Assembly?
She didn't come out and say that exactly.
The guy that Kongou and the others saw,
who was talking about Febri, was also at the Assembly site.
When she said there's an event being held soon,
that's got to be it.
I have to ask though, it was that doctor at the hospital
that arranged for you to see Therestina, huh?
That doctor's face looks like a plushie mascot.
Who is he, exactly?
He did tell me one other thing.
That being?
Given the amount of lollipops Febri has,
she only has about seventy-two hours left.
Huh? No way!
Oh, no...
Seventy-two hours...
Uiharu?
I'm going to try screening everyone involved in the Assembly.
The administrators and participating students, as well.
Uiharu...
You awake now, Febri?
Yeah...
How are you all doing, ladies?
We brought something fabulous for you today.
Did you find any leads, by chance?
Huh? Oh, no, not exactly.
I'm really sorry.
We searched everywhere looking for that guy...
We haven't been able to find anything worth mentioning.
B-But in time, we'll find him for sure!
Anyway, we're here for other business today.
We came to deliver a present to Febri.
A present?
It just so happens that we found a very cute outfit.
We thought it would look adorable on Febri.
Oh, really? Isn't that nice?
A present for you, Febri!
All right! Let's open it and see, okay?
Wow!
Oh, how cute!
This is mine?
Yes.
Mitsuko, Wanna, Atsuki, thank you!
N-No need to thank us! It's just a token of our friendship!
This is mine!
Yeah, it looks good, it does!
Febri!
Your face is all red. Do you feel really warm?
I dunno. My head is foggy.
Oh, have a lollipop! Okay?
Let's see...
We have to hurry.
Yeah.
Oh?
Oh, goodness gracious!
It's him! The guy we saw at the Reach Assembly site!
Right, Wannai, Awatsuki?
Yes, definitely.
That's him, no doubt about it.
Aritomi Haruki
What about the photo?
It's from the participants list from last year.
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki...
Oh, he won the Reach Assembly's first prize two years ago.
In fact, he's a regular winner of the top prizes, every year.
Wow! If he's a high-ranked regular at the Reach Assembly...
It means he's one of the most brilliant people in Academy City.
This guy?
I don't know anything about him.
Right. I mean, compared to a high-level esper,
an ordinary genius doesn't stand out much.
When you find out how deep the darkness goes for those who can't even become lab rats...
Huh? This man...
It doesn't look like he's attending this year.
Now that you mention it, I think Yomikawa said something about that.
About how a lot of the regulars weren't showing up this year.
Let's see.
Oh, you're right.
There are many people who aren't participating this year.
There's a chance that some of them are his associates.
No relevant data.
That just leaves Lab One.
Hey, you!
I can't see!
Say, Febri, do you still feel warm?
Are you really all right?
Yeah!
She had a good appetite too. So it looks like we can rest easy for now.
Have you been looking all this time, Uiharu?
Yeah, I just couldn't sit still.
This Aritomi person appears to have dropped out of school not too long ago.
Hmm... What a shame, huh?
Huh?
I mean, if he was so smart and talented that he won prizes,
he could use that for something more respectable.
Trying to abduct Febri, being in underworld organizations...
I just don't get it.
Hmm, yeah, you're right about that.
I only just learned about the Reach Assembly for the first time,
but knowing that there are other non-espers who are working so hard,
kinda made me happy.
Saten...
Yes, if you'd be so kind, Yomikawa.
Okay.
She said that there's not enough evidence to take action.
But that's what we expected.
We knew that given the pressure Antiskill is under, we can't expect much from them.
Milady, is there something else bothering you?
Yeah, a bit. Something Therestina said to me.
A lot of people have to know about Tokiwadai's Railgun, right?
I've gotten to meet so many people as a result of that.
If I hadn't been Level 5, I was thinking...
Would you and the others have become the kind of friends we are now?
Oh, come on...
The reason I am so attached to you
isn't because you're the Level 5 Railgun of Tokiwadai,
but because you're slightly unconventional and immature,
kind to your juniors and thoughtful...
Milady Misaka Mikoto.
Kuroko...
Thank you. However...
Don't you dare try taking advantage of me!
And don't call me immature!
M-Milady...
I also do love how you show no mercy when punishing someone.
Study Corporation?
Yes. Aritomi Haruki's name came up as one of the company's directors.
What kind of company is it?
Febri, which hand has the Gekota?
They seem to do a lot of things,
centering around pharmaceutical manufacturing and chemistry.
This one!
Sure is!
So, do they have any suspicious facilities?
The Study Corp. does own a factory in School District 17.
It's an old factory with nothing unusual about it,
but the fact that they paid a tremendous price for it bothers me.
That sure does smell fishy.
If it's a factory, do you think that's where they made Febri?
It's possible that that's where the candy is from.
Which hand?
This one.
Or if we could at least figure out the data for its components...
Looks like the quickest way to find out is to go there and look ourselves.
But we don't have any time.
Keeping Febri's eventual health improvements in mind,
getting that candy is the highest priority,
or at the very least, the method of making it.
I can't fail.
Febri's life is hanging in the balance.
That bridge...
Having everyone come back smiling,
without having to lose anything, is my dream.
So work with me, so that it can come true.
Thinking back on it now,
that's quite a pushy, self-indulgent idea, isn't it?
Just because it's your dream,
don't you think about what'll happen if it doesn't come true?
I guess you just have to believe it'll come true, right?
Yeah.
What is it?
There's an intruder in Lab One.
Intruder? Who is it?
I don't know.
The guard system just went to a Shift A alert.
Lab One's data security is set to be low.
It is a decoy, after all.
It's unsurprising that someone would come sniffing around.
If they're just now arriving at Lab One,
it won't interfere with our plans, right?
There's nothing in there that'll hurt us if it gets seen, is there?
All of Janie's data has been relocated.
All that's left is the neutralizing agent data.
To make sure, I'm going to have a look.
To Lab One?
You'd be exterminated along with the intruder.
I don't intend to actually set foot inside.
Now that our plan is nearly at hand,
I just want to make sure everything is safe,
so there are no unforeseen situations.
All right.
Again, there's nobody here, is there? Damn it!
Just like last time, looks like ultra-bad intel.
You're sure we're gonna get paid for this, right?
H-How come?
Why are those guys here?
Don't tell me they knew I was coming and were waiting for me.
Well, doesn't look that way.
Are they working against the people who made Febri?
A feud between underground organizations?
Huh? What's the matter, Takitsubo?
Mugino!
Ha! It's no use, no use!
As long as Takitsubo has her AIM Stalker,
which lets her track any ability she remembers,
sneak attacks are just impossible!
Ability?
Does that mean that someone is moving those powered suits using psychokinesis?
But there's no sign of anyone around.
Remote handling? But even if they were remotely located...
It was inside the powered suit.
It appears to be made of the same components
as those that comprise Febri's body.
Assuming that hair acted as a receiver of sorts for some ability...
And if it did,
assuming that one person's ability could move that many of them,
that would certainly take a Level 5's power.
Which means that hair must belong to—
Takitsubo!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I guess I swam a bit too much earlier.
That was swimming?
Ugh, this is so aggravating! We're out.
Roger that.
Let's go, Takitsubo.
Sure.
Yikes!
Takitsubo? Is someone still here?
Nah, it's all right.
The work portion of the day is over.
Oh?
Ah, I'm all sweaty. Let's head back to the pool!
Sure.
Takitsubo, you probably shouldn't go back in.
They sure did make a royal mess of things, didn't they?
From the way it looks, there might not be anything even left.
Inside there...
There's an area that has functioning electricity.
Don't move.
Try anything funny and...
You!
Why are you here?
And sure enough, you're involved in all this.
What's going on? Are you in league with those guys?
You're the one who told Febri my name, aren't you?!
Hey, would you say something—
Take that with you.
It has the neutralizing agent data on it.
Neutralizing agent?
The data on the candy.
If you act now, there should still be enough time.
Why are you giving this to me?
Sorry. I feel the need to apologize to you.
Yes, I'm the one who gave Febri your name.
I couldn't think of anyone I could turn to besides you.
It looks like my estimates fell short, huh?
But today, there was a disturbance here in Lab One.
Fortunately, I was able to meet you here.
Now you'll be able to help Febri.
After that, she can...
I'm afraid not.
That recipe data is a dummy.
You can't save Febri with that.
I was wise to have some insurance.
So you were the one who let Febri escape after all.
Not only did you turn out to be a traitor,
but you met with a celebrity.
Just as you said, this is a fortunate day.
This is the first time we're meeting in person, huh, Railgun?
The data I procured from you has proven quite useful to me.
Then you must be Aritomi Haruki.
I have to say,
I'm surprised that the reason for you coming all this way
is to save the life of Febri, one of our products.
Product?
Then you really are the ones who made her!
Whoa...
Better that you don't use electricity.
You don't want to destroy the real recipe data, do you?
Nunotaba...
Inject that into Railgun.
It'll only incapacitate her. It won't kill her.
Besides, if you do as I say, I'm willing to give this to you.
We have no use for it anymore, after all.
I couldn't.
Do it.
It's to help Febri.
Ha! Even a Level 5 is rendered powerless like this.
I did as you ordered.
Now hand it over.
Ah, you're right.
Wha—
That's enough.
Febri is nothing more than a spare, after all.
Spare?
Yes.
For our great invention,
Janie.
A Certain
Scientific Railgun S
S
Next Episode
Preview
I knew you were involved in this! Why, exactly?!
To tell the truth, it's a long story.
Once upon a time...
Oh come on now!