So you want an afterhours pass?
Afterhours Pass Request Form
Y-Yes!
After giving me such a flimsy excuse for being out so much without permission,
you're actually asking?
You have some nerve, Misaka.
Now, all the necessary paperwork seems to be here.
Incidentally,
I got a request with the exact same content from Shirai.
Not only did it have tomorrow's date, it had the same reason for absence on it,
"a study group with friends."
Well, yes, I'm going with Kuroko—
What are you scheming?
N-Nothing! Studying! It's a study group!
If you're studying, you can do it in the dorm.
There has to be a reason to go elsewhere.
It's for a change of pace, basically.
We're studying with friends from another school.
All of us are loaded with summer vacation homework. Uh...
Very well. Request granted.
Huh?
Approved
Be good to your friends. However...
If you're even one minute late coming back,
you know what will happen.
Don't you?
Y-Yes!
A blazing hope is blasting through the city
It gives me the strength to hold hands with my trusted friends
and keep looking for a tomorrow that will satisfy us
A Certain Scientific Railgun
On a crowded street I saw your shape drawing away
Because we understand the love we share now
smiles light up around me
and brighten our days
I want to protect that simple happiness
Once my dreams start coming true, with the sky as my witness,
I will begin to have power over my reality
I had the strength to talk about my fears
I won't forget when it was that I did
I will hold dear the bonds that bind us
and blast open a path to a future I can be proud of
Hello, hello! Uiharu? What's up?
Sounds like Misaka and Shirai both got their passes.
Really? Great!
They said that getting the paperwork would be a huge hassle,
but I guess it's all good.
That means we can go ahead with the study group as planned today,
so we'll finally get together for the first time in a while, huh?
Yeah.
Heh, and when we see Misaka this time,
we'll totally have to find out who she gave the cookies too.
C'mon, Saten,
we're not even entirely sure she gave them to a boy—
There's no doubt about it!
I've never seen our innocent and pure Misaka look like that before.
All right, all done.
Okay, put them in the oven.
Now we just have to let them finish baking.
Sorry for the sudden request to let me use your kitchen, Saten.
Oh, no, I don't mind at all,
but if you're baking cookies, I'm sure your dorm has better equipment than I do.
Oh, well...
No, my dorm's kitchen has too many peering eyes, so I can't.
That is to say Kuroko, Kuroko, and Kuroko.
Oh-ho...
So this is a gift for someone you don't want people asking about, isn't it?
N-No!
I'm just in their debt,
and you know how I am about being in someone's debt.
Personally, store-bought cookies are good enough,
but that idiot decided that cookies should be homemade.
Oh, but I'm not doing this because I was asked to!
It's actually to just make them stop whining since I've already gone this far.
Still, I'm glad for you.
Huh?
Uiharu and I have been really worried about you, Misaka,
and I don't even have to mention Shirai.
I know I'm not someone you can turn to for help,
but I'd be delighted if you needed someone to talk to.
Sorry, it's just...
I'm the one who created this problem,
so I can't bear to drag anyone else into it.
Thinking on it now, I guess I was really at my wit's end.
From now on, I'll be more careful. I promise!
All right.
So then, the reason you feel better now
is due to this boyfriend I've been hearing about?
Boyf—
N-No! I just told you, it's not...
The flour! And the eggs!
She's so cute.
Oh, what the hell?!
She trashed the room though.
You really shouldn't try to force it out of her, Saten.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Once Shirai and I are done with Judgment work,
we'll go shopping and head over, and Haruue...
She has something to take care of, so she'll be a bit late.
Sure thing.
I'll get things ready while I wait, then.
All right, see you later.
Shirai, good morning!
Good morning.
So you're back to having tons of free time, Misaka?
Listen here! Why do you act like I'm never busy?
I can finally take it easy because nothing's going on until this afternoon.
You've been skipping meals at the dorm lately, huh?
What've you been up to?
Hmm, I've been busy here and there.
Shirai usually ate here all alone.
Yeah,
I know.
It sure is peaceful, huh?
The Money Card drama died down,
and the back alleyways of Academy City appear to be calm once more.
Hey, where'd you get that?
Wanna come with me?
Really? I'd love to!
Found one!
Huh? Again?
See? Isn't this place awesome?
Nice. All I've found is regular clovers.
Ah, Judgment lady!
Hello there.
Long time no see, eh?
Here, look!
When I told them I found them all here,
everyone else said they wanted one, so I brought them here!
Is that so?
Well, make sure not to stay out too late, okay?
Sure!
Found another one!
I found one too! With five leaves!
Let me see! Let me see!
Look!
Oh, cool! You're right!
Things really are peaceful, huh?
Homework?
Yeah. I have a book report, but I don't know where to start.
Summer vacation is almost over, isn't it?
Sure is, and there's so much of everything left to do...
Ah, not again.
What's up?
Someone's trying to hack into Sakugawa's newspaper club's server,
which I was asked to supervise.
We have a cracker.
For crying out loud, this has been happening a lot lately.
Who would go after a middle school newspaper club?
Well, when you have an ironclad goalkeeper,
people are going to want to take their best shot.
Huh? Did you say something?
Hmm?
Ah, they broke through the firewall again. That's amazing.
You're almost in. Fight for it!
Fight for it? Are you sure you should let them in?
It's okay. The server itself is actually a trap.
Reporting the IP address of the one who got in to Antiskill now...
Ugh. Maybe I should read a different book.
But then I wouldn't even know what to read.
Imagine, the legendary goalkeeper's one weakness is a book report.
Huh? Goalkeeper?
Oh, nothing. Can I do anything to help?
Thank you so much.
Oh, this isn't homework, but Konori,
do you know of a supermarket around here with a good selection?
A supermarket? For what?
I'm going to a study group after this.
We're each buying something we like to eat
and getting together at Saten's place.
There.
Oh, my, my...
Who have we here? If it isn't Shirai.
Kongou Mitsuko...
Are you out here shopping?
Well, yes.
What are you buying?
A few items of food.
What a coincidence, so am I.
If you would like me to, I wouldn't mind accompanying you.
You don't have to look down on me to ask,
and since we're buying the same thing, we're just spontaneously going to the same store.
But I must say, you must be lonely,
going shopping without a single friend.
It appears that you are also shopping by yourself.
Th-That is not the case at all!
Wannai and Awatsuki are waiting for me.
Not that we have anything planned, however.
I'm just passing the time by doing some shopping
until they finish their swim practice.
Otherwise known as "being by yourself."
Come, this way! This shop over here is a favorite of mine!
Huh? Wait!
A pet shop?
Oh, the selection here is as wonderful as ever!
Uh, Kongou...
They have such a large volume!
Uh...
Can you hold these a second?
So when you said food, you meant for your pet then?!
Ecaterina, like me, has very delicate tastes.
And Ecaterina is
your python?!
Turtle?
Ah...
Here for the girls?
#17 "Study Group"
A Certain
Scientific Railgun
S
Yes.
They're all doing well.
The one who was injured is also making good progress.
Well, on the surface anyway.
On the surface?
Following my examination, I learned a few things.
They are clones, created from your somatic cells,
but by being administered various drugs within the culture fluid,
their bodies have grown rapidly.
Such that from a fertilized egg,
it took merely fourteen days for them to get to their current form.
As a result,
these somatic cell clones, whose life-spans were already shorter anyway,
had their lives shortened even further.
How long do you mean?
I don't want to generalize,
but I'd say another year or two at most.
Oh, no...
Which is why they need to be adjusted.
Adjusted?
By balancing the hormones that promote this growth,
and regulating the cell nuclei's rate of division,
we should be able to recover a certain degree of their life-spans.
There are so many of them, after all.
We're currently in the process of dividing this up
among research organizations outside Academy City.
From here on out, as we collect more data,
that'll most likely continue at each of these facilities.
Outside facilities?
I see...
The fight for those girls will still go on.
Though this time, it won't be a fight to die,
but to live.
Hmm... I just don't know.
I wonder what everyone else is going to buy.
I've managed to find the ultimate ingredient!
All right.
Yikes, I'm running late.
I'm sure Kuroko is waiting.
Welcome!
Ah, I'm meeting someone here.
I'll bring you a menu and some water right away.
Oh, no! I'm not with them.
Tch. This is why I hate family restaurants.
They're filled with spoiled, sheltered little girls.
You're not actually convinced that you won back there, are you?
Huh?
Truth be told, it's just for my information.
If I had known you were the Railgun,
I'd have been way more careful setting up my dolls...
Frenda!
Huh?
Did you forget that it was because of your neglect that she got away in the first place?
Oh, uh, that's right, isn't it?
Teehee!
Learn your lesson, blockhead!
Ow!
What's going on here?
Fighting inside a restaurant will disturb the other customers.
As a member of Judgment, I won't overlook...
Wait, Milady, it's you?
Are you really starting a fight in a public place like this?
I-I am not! I was just—
You have to be more circumspect in your behavior!
You shouldn't get into fights with the weaker general public.
Who are you calling weak, you grade-schooler?!
If you're referring to me, then as you can see,
I'm clearly in middle school.
Besides, I was only speaking out of concern for your well-being.
If you get Milady seriously angry, you could pay with your lives.
As I was saying,
you keep your nose out of this, small fry!
If we got into it, she'd be the one shredded to bits!
I happen to take issue with that.
Are you aware that Milady here is the Railgun of Tokiwadai when you spout such nonsense?
She has a much different combat record than that little girl.
Truth be told, Mugino will be victorious!
No, Milady will!
Mugino will!
Milady!
Mugino!
Being older doesn't mean anything!
Hold on, Kuroko.
You've got some nerve, little girl!
Hey, Frenda...
Sure, her underwear might have cartoon characters on them,
and she her childish tastes aren't good at all,
but as Tokiwadai's Ace, she possesses respectable power!
Same for Mugino! Even though she has some sore spots,
like showing off her underwear to anyone,
her fighting ability is unmatched!
Truth be told, she doesn't have much presence with that flat chest!
Ah, how vulgar, thinking that only size matters!
When it comes to future potential, Milady has it all!
Watch your damn hands!
Man, now I'll never be able to go to that place again!
Wait, Mugino!
Hello!
Ah, come in!
Huh? What happened to you, Shirai?
Absolutely nothing.
Ta-da!
Oh, a pot for stew!
I borrowed it from a friend of mine.
I have the stock all ready to go.
Wow, we must be the only ones who'd have a stew party in the middle of summer, huh?
Milady, this isn't a party. It's a study group.
Ah, of course, of course.
Still, eating hot food when it's hot out is good for you.
What ingredients did you guys bring?
Well, I wasn't really sure what to get...
The guy at the meat counter suggested this,
so I went ahead and bought it.
Boxes?
Whoa! There's beef inside!
Such incredible marbling!
Huh? Did I get the wrong thing?
No, I've just never seen this before!
What did you bring, Uiharu?
Oh, I got a whole bunch of vegetables.
I focused on summer veggies,
like corn, okra, more okra, and some tofu and mushrooms too.
Sounds like it'll be really healthy.
Oh, yeah!
Young ladies must seek beauty at mealtimes as well!
As it stands, the ingredient I prepared will steal the show!
What did you get, Shirai?
I was unsure at first.
When I was in the pet shop, plump mice in hand, I wasn't sure what I would do.
M-Mice?
The pet shop?
However!
I had an epiphany immediately afterward!
I said to myself, this is the perfect ingredient for Milady.
What on earth did you buy?!
Nobody likes surprises, Shirai.
And that ingredient is...
Soft Shell Turtle
Turtle?
The soft collagen is certain to enhance her youthful skin to be even more beautiful!
And then!
Wh-What is that?
Fresh soft-shell turtle blood.
Mixed with apple juice to make it easier to drink.
Now then, bottoms up.
After this, you'll be bursting with vigor—No,
rather, you'll be completely filled with vitality.
You might get so fired up, there's a possibility you'll be unable to sleep,
but I'd be more than happy to lay beside you if that happens.
Now then, let's put it all in!
Mm, this is delicious! Tastes great!
This is the first time I've eaten turtle, but it's pretty good.
The turtle's all right, but this beef is the best!
The veggies are pretty good too.
Which means that this was a great success.
Sure was.
I hope Haruue gets here soon.
I'm sure she'll get here any minute.
Should we have started without her?
We still have plenty left.
Yeah, yeah, let's keep eating!
Y'know, it's a real mystery, huh?
What do you mean?
Why is it that food tastes better when you eat with others?
Yeah, the fact that we're cooking it while we eat helps too, no?
I guess when it comes to main dishes and cookies,
nothing beats homemade, does it, Misaka?
Milady, what's the matter?!
Are you all right?
I-I'm fine.
But your face is bright red and you're sweating like crazy.
Huh?! I said I'm fine!
Oh, what delicious looking mushrooms! Oh! Hot! Hot!
She's so cute.
Oh, Saten...
I'm sorry I'm so late.
Come in, come in! We've been waiting for you!
Oh, it's Haruue!
Wow, this looks delicious!
Did you finish your errands, then?
Yeah, I needed to speak to my teacher.
The stew is really good. Let me get you a bowl.
Did you get any ingredients for us, Haruue?
I bought some udon noodles.
Oh, that's the perfect thing to round this out.
Okay, let's eat, let's eat!
Yeah, sure, Milady.
Oh, why not?
Ah, I'm so full.
Guess we'll need to diet for a little while, huh?
Still, that sure was fun, wasn't it?
I wanna do another study group sometime.
Yeah. Getting the paperwork is so hard though.
We're not running late, are we?!
We should be all right, but I think we should hurry a little.
If we're even one minute late, our punishment will be merciless.
Yikes, let's hurry!
Kuroko? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Right, Milady!
I walked through our town,
but it was too big for me
I tried to hide my discomfort,
made myself a little taller and pretended to be strong
I got an answer that puzzled me,
and everything became complicated
My daily life has given me trouble,
but I'll take a deep breath
Above that hill
I see a rainbow
Let's go find it
I will make sure I will never forget this day
I'm so happy
I could meet you
It will always be special
Let's be proud and walk forward
Our happiness will be our link to tomorrow
When you share
your happiness and your pain,
it's twice the fun and half the pain
Next Episode
Preview
On a certain day after the end of
summer break, Mikoto runs into a
certain girl. This is the story of
Mikoto and a girl said to have a
miraculous singing voice.
On a certain day after the end of
summer break, Mikoto runs into a
certain girl. This is the story of
Mikoto and a girl said to have a
miraculous singing voice.
The Movie
A Certain Magical Index
The Miracle of Endymion
Special
Version