Young man, you must remember this well.
This is the emblem of the empire
where you will live in the future.
That is…
Yes.
The emblem used by Father was too simple.
So, when I ascended the throne,
I personally redesigned one.
Cool, right?
It was the emblem of a destroyed empire
I once lived in.
Why does it appear here?
THINGS ARE URGENT RIGHT NOW.
WHY WAS IT EXPOSED? WHY?
OUR COMPATRIOTS IN JAPAN HAVE BEEN ATTACKED BY THE FIRE-BREATHING BUG AGAIN.
YOU'RE STILL SO WELL-INFORMED.
THE MOST CRUCIAL THING NOW IS TO KEEP THIS MATTER FROM BEING MADE PUBLIC.
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE TO SUPPRESS THIS MATTER ANYMORE.
HIDE IT, HIDE IT, HIDE IT.
DIDN'T WE ALREADY DISGUISE IT AS THE WORK OF A VIOLENT GANG?
DON'T MAKE ANY RECKLESS MOVES, YOU FILTHY BUGS.
KILL SOLITAIRE, KILL HIM, KILL HIM, KILL HIM.
KILL HIM IN ONE STRIKE, DON'T EVEN GIVE HIM TIME TO SUFFER.
MASSACRING COULD BRING US SOME VENGEANCE, BUT IT MIGHT ACCIDENTALLY EXPOSE US.
JUST LIKE THE INCIDENT FIVE YEARS AGO.
(Episode 10: The Emblem)
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
What's going on?
Is that the sign mentioned earlier?
It seems there's no need
for me to hide it anymore.
It's just slightly different in shape.
DO NOT TRUST ANYONE. THE KEY IS BEHIND THE MIRROR AT NUMBER 383
Is this the pattern that Polka Shinoyama drew?
Yes.
Since Solitaire directed this,
it means that he has
a connection with Mr. Hosorogi.
No, maybe he has a connection with the
group that Mr. Hosorogi was investigating.
Anyway, we have seen the same sign
keep appearing.
At this point, five years after
Prosecutor Hosorogi's disappearance,
it's better to think of it as
a sign of something
rather than a coincidence.
Yes.
Solitaire
might be targeting me.
He might be hiding somewhere,
and he saw me getting
a divination from Polka Shinoyama.
It's not the time to focus on
making inferences right now.
Anyway, the information…
Ah, I finally found you!
Tsubaki-chan, Tsubaki-chan.
Ms. Yamada.
The situation seems to be getting worse.
Someone is looking for you, Tsubaki-chan.
Looking for me?
Who is looking for me?
It's the headquarters
of the Metropolitan Police Department.
Both the Tokyo Metropolitan Government
and the Metropolitan Police Department
said that the airships in this area now
do not have a flight permit.
-At this time, compared to the news,
-The possibility of this incident being related
-there is more information on the Internet.
-to the government or terrorist attacks is very low.
-But this time,
-There is a certain possibility that
-I really went all out,
-it's an event planned by an art company.
I even bought the whole airships.
So,
can you tell me how much the information
I'm looking for costs me right now?
Three trillion yen.
Pardon?
It is worth three trillion yen.
There was a decimal before,
but I'll leave it out this time.
Hold on, hold on.
Isn't this strange?
You helped me with radio interference for
three minutes for 30 million yen, right?
As I said before,
I set prices according to
the money the customer has.
The money mentioned here
refers to the value of
the customer's life.
I don't understand.
So why does it cost three trillion yen?
According to my estimate,
if you do your best
and use various means to make money,
you can earn six trillion yen
in your lifetime,
although this is just a rough estimate.
It is worth to spend half of your life
to obtain the value of this sign.
Please don't misunderstand.
This price is only for you.
If someone else came to
buy this information,
I would sell it for dozens of yen.
Because for others,
the true meaning of this sign
is just a leisure-time topic.
It is no different from
a piece of gum chewed to pass the time.
But you are different.
I guarantee you
that this information can be
a panacea that determines
your fate.
This is beyond doubt.
However, improper use will destroy you.
I don't think three trillion yen
is too much to pay for this prescription.
I see.
I'll accept it as it is the opinion
of someone who the
previous generation valued.
But let's forget about the transaction.
It's a wise decision.
Since we've come this far,
it's boring to just listen to
the answer you give me.
I'll try to find the answer on my own.
But I still need to spend money
to ask you to do something for me.
I want to get a few airships.
How much will they cost?
Using people as ropes to control balloons
is something worth learning from.
Huh? Did I hit it?
It missed. You can tell by looking.
Is this considered a mission failure?
I don't know, but it seems like
we can't get the reward.
We can't get any decent jobs
in Shibuya or Ikebukuro.
Shall we go find jobs at Shinjuku?
The intermediary agency
there has a good reputation.
SHOCKING!! AN ENIGMATIC ORGANIZATION HIDING WITHIN SOCIETY!
My puppet was sniped 58 minutes
after the airship took off.
How did they know
that I was on that airship?
Before this, only the police helicopter
could climb up to that position.
In other words, within less than an hour,
an organization capable of sniping at me
has already infiltrated the police.
Therefore, I am here
to challenge the audience.
The moment I revealed this sign,
someone wanted to assassinate me.
It's not an exaggeration
to call those guys a secret organization.
Doesn't this sound good?
There are such dangerous
things in the world.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I am also very interested
in the emblem on the airships.
I need information related to the emblem,
such as people or places involved.
I will choose a few people who provide
the most valuable information,
and give them 300 million yen.
As for whether I will really
fulfill my promise,
people who know what I have done so far
should understand, right?
I'll tell you how to contact me later.
Goodbye.
I forgot to say my farewell greetings.
THE LIVE BROADCAST HAS ENDED
It seems to have turned
into a very bad situation.
Hmm, what should we do?
Let's think about it one by one.
What's the first thing to consider?
That naturally is… right?
Yes.
Exactly, I want to hear an explanation.
About empires and reincarnations.
Polka, you will explain it
to me clearly, right?
Yes.
CORPSE GOD
Here is a brief summary of the background.
Corpse God, that is, Polka Shinoyama,
is a reincarnated human being.
BYANDY EMPIRE
In his previous life, he was transformed into a court wizard.
Byandy Empire
is an armed country with
no ambition to dominate the world.
HERO SHAGRUA
A hundred years after the empire's collapse,
the so-called Calamity Crusher,
the hero Shagrua,
defeated Corpse God.
However, Corpse God cast a spell,
and was reincarnated into the body of
Polka Shinoyama in Shinjuku.
I HAVE TO WORK
He has struggled for a stable life
THE FOLLOWING IS OMITTED
and faced the uncertainty of the future.
That's how it is.
The soul of the real Polka is safe.
I will return his body to him later.
How could she believe such a statement?
It's easier not to believe it.
It seems you don't intend
to tell me the truth.
Enough, I'm angry.
I see.
I believe what you said.
You believe it?
I can vaguely feel that you are not Polka.
When you were doing the divination,
even when the police officer grabbed
your collar, you remained very calm.
Polka can't be so calm.
However, I'm still confused
about the situation.
Polka was actually killed by someone,
although I don't want to believe it.
I need to take a bath to calm down
before hearing your detailed explanation.
Xiaoyu went out shopping. I won't tell
him about this, so please rest assured.
Her personality is extremely
difficult to understand.
Letting her see dancing bones
should be alright?
I think she probably
won't spread it around.
It's best to prepare for the worst.
Can you erase memories?
There is a necromancy that drives the soul
to possess the target's soul
and removes a part of the memory.
It's using the soul as a scalpel
SOUL MEMORY
to remove a piece of the target's soul.
This approach may cause a chain reaction
in the physical brain.
This kind of necromancy and
the brainwashing or interrogation magic
used by Geldwood are not
part of the same system.
Is it a difficult magic?
Honestly, it's not too difficult.
But this is for people in my world.
If it is applied to people in this world,
a fatal mistake will turn
them into wrecks.
It's not easy to try then.
If the target is clearly an enemy,
messing with them casually
to break their spirit might not be bad.
Did you
manipulate the memories of those thugs?
I was careful when I took action,
in order to avoid turning them into
complete wrecks.
You can be quite frightening at times.
What's wrong?
You said I'm only frightening "at times,"
which makes me feel a little happy.
Although I do feel a bit scared,
compared to Misaki you killed,
it's not much at all.
Uh, where is she?
Misaki?
THE SHARK CANNOT SEE
What do you want from me?
I want to talk to you.
Talk?
Aren't you curious about
what was just said?
Who
killed Polka?
Or you have already known,
so you don't care?
Let's talk about sharks instead of this.
Don't change the subject.
If I say it was me who killed Polka,
what would you think?
Is that so?
I see.
You want someone to blame you, don't you?
Polka must have forgiven you.
After all, he is a kind child.
When he saw the man-eating shark
being killed at the end of the movie,
he would say he felt sorry
for both the person and the shark.
I'll ask you more about
what exactly happened later on.
But,
although Polka has forgiven you,
you still cannot accept
his forgiveness in your heart.
So, you want to alleviate
your guilt a little
through my scolding.
What a cunning child.
But it's okay. I forgive you.
I won't scold you.
You saw right through me.
You're like a detective.
Aren't you scared?
I'm the killer who cut Polka's throat
and killed him.
I'm not scared.
Why?
People who like shark movies are kind.
Huh?
Although I haven't spent
a lot of time with you,
talking about sharks and shark movies
with you is really enjoyable.
Someone who can talk to me about
sharks and shark movies
couldn't be a bad person.
Even if you cut off the heads of
my family members,
sharks would forgive you.
I NEVER EXPECTED MY OWN FAMILY TO BE SO NONSENSICAL
IN THE FACE OF SUCH A REALITY, POLKA SHINOYAMA'S SOUL
CHOOSES TO ACT AS IF NOTHING HAS HAPPENED
THE SHARK DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING!
By the way,
you saved Kazuki and Shizuki.
Although it's not a big deal,
this is my second reason
for forgiving you.
Really? Is it just incidental?
Ah, it's so annoying.
I don't know what to say.
Then don't think about it.
Talk to me about sharks, will you?
So,
SOFT, SMOOTH
I was originally going to test
whether Sayo was the one
who commissioned me to kill Polka.
But I failed.
However, I think
Sayo has nothing to do
with the assassination of Polka.
Got it. What are you doing?
Are you an idiot?
From the conversation just now,
I can only figure out
that you are definitely crazy.
You're really rude.
I just keep thinking about sharks,
and I'm not interested in anything else.
So I wouldn't commission
someone to kill Polka.
Is there a connection between the two?
I mean,
if I wanted to kill Polka, I would
definitely throw him to feed the sharks.
It's surprisingly persuasive.
How annoying.
Did you soak the doll in hot water?
I didn't do that.
Sorry, I took the shark doll
without your permission.
Living with someone like this
must not be easy for you.
I'm seeing it for the first time.
I hope all sharks and I can be a family.
By the way,
did you bring it in knowing whose it was?
What are you talking about?
Although you didn't know,
because it witnessed you
getting changed, I feel sorry for you.
It doesn't matter at all.
It doesn't matter?
I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING
I never thought my family would turn into a shark.
I thought there were two souls
fused together
inside your body.
Mr. Rozan said the same thing.
I understand now.
I'll lend my body to Polka.
Then you can turn me into a shark.
Why?
I CAN'T KEEP UP WITH THE CONVERSATION ANYMORE
THE SHARK DARES NOT SPEAK
POLKA’S SOUL STOPS LOOKING INTO IT
Speaking of which,
how should we handle
this important issue, Polka?
This is a very important sign
for you, right?
There's no problem with
making this sign public.
But if there's a group of
people who plan to
do something using this sign,
I must go to meet them.
That sign is our precious memory.
But if it's tainted and
I still sit idly by,
I can no longer live peacefully.
I got it.
Now the only thing
we can do is to investigate
whether there really is an organization
behind the scenes using that sign.
Moreover, this might also be
a trap set by Solitaire.
In other words,
that person named Solitaire
is a wizard from the same world as Polka?
No.
He wants to get information
about that sign.
So,
I don't think he's from my world.
Can't you use something like
analysis magic to determine it?
Analysis magic?
TITLE: GOOD YOUTH OF SHINJUKU TITLE: CORPSE GOD
Something that allows you to know the other person's
level, profession, or skills
just by looking at them.
Isn't that the same as the move
Takumi used during divination?
Focusing on the customer's name
and casting a spell
to obtain identity information!
SECURITY SYSTEM, IT DOESN'T WORK FOR OBJECTS WITH HIGHER LEVELS
Could I be considered an analysis magician?
I know the secret art of reincarnation
because I spent years learning it.
I don't know if there are other people
who have come to this world.
But these bones were summoned
from your world, right?
I was surprised to be able to summon them.
I simply used nearby objects
as temporary targets possessed.
What I summoned was only the soul.
Are there more articulate souls?
There are.
However,
I freed almost all souls before
the last church subjugation unit arrived.
Even so, there were still people who
continued to fulfill their contracts.
But what kind of expression should
I have while summoning
as someone who was once
called a world calamity?
So, only memories…
Let's stop talking about gloomy things.
When you want to summon,
just summon with a smile.
If you upset the other person
or get beaten up,
just apologize to them sincerely.
Will I be forgiven just like this?
Please believe in those
who contracted with you out of trust.
Sis Sayo.
I'm sorry. I once suspected you were
the bad guy who wanted to kill Polka.
Also,
if there is such necromancy, there should
also be the magic related to sharks.
It's the most important thing right now.
What?
Are you trying to forcefully interrupt us
with the topic of sharks this time?
THE DEEP SEA WIZARD, THE GRIMLOP SISTERS
Indeed, there are people in the ocean who can manipulate schools of fish.
You don't need to go along
with this topic.
In summary,
what we need to consider now
is how to deal with that sign.
Everyone has their own talent.
For the matter like this,
leave it to an analysis magician like me.
You really like that title, huh?
In that case,
according to that jerk Solitaire,
I'll start by investigating the police.
ALTHOUGH I CANNOT DISCLOSE THE DETAILS YET, I AM AWARE OF SOME INFORMATION
Really?
I WON'T STOP YOU AT THIS POINT, BUT IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT, BE CAREFUL
ALTHOUGH IT IS JUST A PART OF IT, THE POLICE ORGANIZATION
IS MUCH MORE FORMIDABLE THAN YOU CAN IMAGINE.
POLICE HEADQUARTERS
Sorry for suddenly calling you here.
No problem. It's great to
have Inspector Habaki here.
I ended up returning here after
leaving my original jurisdiction.
I really hope
that you can be a civil servant
in a proper manner.
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
The director is a versatile person.
Be careful not to be overwhelmed
by him. Go in.
Alright.
You're Tsubaki Iwanome,
the one in charge of
the Solitaire's case, right?
Yes.
You look more like
a male host than a police officer.
After all, your department
is quite special.
As for the earrings and dyed hair,
I'll consider them as your disguise.
There's only one important thing.
Can you become a cog that
maintains the organization's operation?
DIRECTOR JIROTAROU TAKANOSU
I hope your cog can
mesh smoothly with mine.
JIROTAROU TAKANOSU
Is this the current director of the police?
Although judging people by their
appearance is bad, he looks frightening.
He's so cool.
What's so cool about?
Iwanome has been frequently investigating
about Mr. Hosorogi.
DID THAT GUY ACTUALLY USE AN INTERNAL POLICE COMPUTER FOR THE INVESTIGATION?
That happened a few years ago, right?
THAT GUY DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO USE A COMPUTER
It seems he was punished for that.
In the police database,
there are still such records.
The coordination of the cogs?
I think it is not a problem,
Director Jirotarou Takanosu.
After all, I'm very good at
cooperating with others,
unless a stone falls into
the gap between the cogs.
Are you referring to
Prosecutor Miyabi Hosorogi as a stone?
It seems I am right.
I can't agree.
Although he is still missing,
you refer to your superior as a stone.
To you, Hosorogi is as worthless
as a small stone on the road.
Right?
You're joking.
What I mentioned is not that person.
It's the dirty rat
hiding in this building
that cornered him.
I thought you would impulsively attack me.
But you turned out to
be unexpectedly calm.
However,
your words and deeds can hardly be
called calm, which is quite interesting.
I see.
When your cog is spinning in the system,
it seems to make a different sound.
But you need to pay more attention.
Once I feel that
it is making a different sound,
I will not hesitate to destroy you.
I will keep that in mind.
By the way, before getting to the main
topic, I need to remind you of one thing.
My name is not jiroutarou, but jirotarou.
Pronounced jiro, not jirou.
Don't drag it too long
when pronouncing it.
WRONG: JIROUTAROU, CORRECT: JIROTAROU
I'll keep this in mind as well.
The reason I called you here today
is because of Phantom Solitaire case.
The police decided to reorganize
the investigation team.
And you have an inexplicable
connection with him.
Thus, I hope you can
lead the investigation.
SHINJUKU GYOEN
And then?
Is there any news from the police?
Yes, several people hacked into
the police's internal system.
Among them, only one person
has a clear goal.
This is really interesting.
Have you figured out
the signal source, granny?
GRANNY CAFÉ, AMAGURI
Of course, I have. Young master.
It is in Shinjuku.
A diviner's base with a recently submitted
application for a new business?
It seems I have to ask him
to predict my own future for me.
(Episode 11: The Beginning)