Unifying this peninsula was once
the empire's long-cherished wish.
Although it is said to
be for future peace,
it's also true
that I have blood on my hands.
So, my dear friend,
don't wear such an expression.
It's not your will
that drives you to kill me.
Corpse God.
No, Rizdilusia Redrazalf.
I've finally got out of
that Wandering Balcony
and bound your name
by a curse hidden behind the corpse.
Let me write a new chapter
for your destiny.
Well, let's hide the key evidence first.
The testimony given by the souls
controlled by the necromancers
is not enough to serve
as material for defense.
I can't believe I would cover
for a criminal who killed me.
That's why life is fun.
Now I am your accomplice.
You killed me, your dear friend.
I want you to live forever
and ever to atone.
I'm not saying so to bind you.
You're still so foolish, my dear friend.
Are you going to kill yourself
over someone again like this?
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
(Episode 24: The Shinjuku War)
The Enemy of the World.
Alright.
Although I don't know why
you're so attached to this world.
And what did you say about
returning the body?
I see.
So, as a necromancer
you're merely possessing a body?
Yes.
Next, I will possess your body.
I…
sympathized with that guy's desire
to live in peace.
How did this happen?
Darn it.
Why did I become like this?
This is so not me. Darn it.
Hey, Polka!
You, don't underestimate us anymore.
Kurupon?
What's that about just now?
How can you just start saying goodbye?
You said you don't fit in with this world?
I do fear your power.
I thought I could never
have anything to do with you.
But
you, me, Misaki,
and the real Polka,
we've been sincere partners.
However,
you just said goodbye to us?
Didn't you tell me before?
I have no secrets more important
than my friend's life.
Don't underestimate your friends.
And Misaki and I are
to help you fit into this world.
Power outage?
I've hacked into your power
and surveillance systems.
Anyway, you shouldn't be
caught on public surveillance.
You don't have to pretend
to be good or bad,
just do what you want to do.
Corpse God.
Takumi.
I see.
Those people in that building
are the chains that bind you.
Then I'll just deal with them first…
What are you going to do with them first?
Your vibe has changed again.
Yes.
I don't have to pretend to be bad anymore.
I know what you're going to do.
So let me say it again.
I will stop you.
Gems?
Are they used to replace magic?
But that's a lot.
For everyone…
No.
This is my wish.
For the peace of the city…
Where did he get all these magic gems?
Even if you say so, but
aren't you also using others?
You used that body and
the wealth of Polka Shinoyama.
This is the money I have earned and
the assistance from my important friends.
Yes.
Someone willing to help me
when I'm immature.
No matter in this world,
or in that world, it's the same.
Don't underestimate your friends.
Right.
Is your wish the peace of the city?
It's over.
Only a small fraction of those
were killed by my attack just now.
No matter how you destroy the cameras,
there's too many dead to hide.
Neither you nor I can hide it.
You got one thing wrong.
Today, not a single person
would die in this city.
Because I was prepared in advance.
Could it be…
There are hardly
any people alive in the city now.
This place is already in my temple.
This place is full of dead people.
Did you set up a barrier
to disperse the people?
So I don't have to control power anymore.
How's it going?
I'm very sorry.
We can't get close yet.
The enemy is sniping.
It seems to hinder us.
This is the best we can do.
I leave this district of Shinjuku to you.
You make the call from now on.
That bat is just like you.
Why don't you want to change the world?
Isn't that a waste, even a blasphemy,
of your own power?
That's not true.
After all, there is someone
far stronger than me
who also desires peace.
I, a stupid corpse,
was raised to be an assassin
under the control of an enemy necromancer.
Even a useless corpse like me,
that powerful man still
considers me his dear friend.
Who are you talking about?
I've told you.
I have support from important friends.
Thanks to their support,
I also received that person's help.
You finally called me here.
Sorry, it took me a long time.
There's something I want
to protect no matter what,
please help me, Your Majesty.
No.
Can you help me?
My dear friend.
Your Majesty?
Is he…
the former emperor of the Byandy Empire,
Vlamrodiya Bayatilaz?
Why?
The records state that the Corpse God is
the traitor who murdered the emperor,
but why would he be here?
Why did they sign the contract?
I should've mentioned it before.
No matter what you become,
I and Empire will be your partners.
Necromancer.
Did you preserve the entire fallen empire?
Don't underestimate Corpse God,
he is my court wizard after all.
But there are very few magic elements.
Refining magic seems to take a while.
Then let me try to buy some time.
I'll use magic wire
to protect the towers of the city.
I guess I'll have to
deal with something else.
Thank you.
It's been like a dream today.
Dada Dada…
I have to admit it.
It is a power
that does not exist in this world.
But the strange feeling that began
just now could not be ignored.
Fire-breathing Bug, what do you think?
BE CAREFUL OF THE FIRE
Dangerous, it should be burnt.
Before it causes an accident,
BE CAREFUL OF THE FIRE
before it became a tragedy,
it should be burnt down with the city.
Could you wait a moment, please?
Miss, you are…
Whether he's a danger to the world,
why don't you observe first?
On what basis
and for what reason,
you want to stop us.
This concerns me.
I've been burnt by someone's fire,
which are the false bugs
that are obsessed with you.
And he has done me a favor.
Did that strange feeling
have anything to do with her presence?
So what do we do, Fire-breathing Bug?
Maybe you do have a right to revenge.
Leader?
But it's our job to protect this city.
Are you saying that the people
of Sabaramond are part of the city?
I'm talking about the ordinary citizens
you're currently possessing.
If you complete your revenge,
the fact that they killed people
will remain.
And at that moment,
aren't you distorting their lives
by letting them stand here?
I will let you finish your revenge
in some other way.
At least those Sabaramond in Japan
will be destroyed by me.
So you have to let those
innocent people go.
Do you want us to trust you and walk away?
That's not what I mean.
Since you want to
witness revenge so badly,
then transfer your consciousness to me.
Why would you do that?
Why?
It's neither atonement nor repayment.
I know but I can't express it.
If I give up like this, it seems that
my meeting with Polka will be in vain.
So I will try my best.
I'll do whatever it takes
to get that shark doll back.
Wow.
Are you a vampire?
You saw it? Wow!
What?
It never ends. What's the matter with you?
Are you one of the Lemmings?
Then I'll just have to use
a little more power to deal with you.
I can't believe this kid doesn't
fear me being this form.
Unfortunately, I've already
met guys just like you.
Movements, breathing,
and soul.
I used that power to my best advantage.
Earthquake?
This is…
Is the elf about to make a move?
But I can only leave it to them now.
What's more important…
The formation of the magic circle.
With each touch, I can feel that he's
getting closer to the deeper mystery.
He's just a layman, how arrogant he is.
Is he really a genius?
Even so,
how can he stand up after being attacked
by a magic of the level of court wizard?
I don't think he's even
a wizard in this world.
Even though I felt that way
when I met him.
But it would be like facing Mr. Arius.
Although I don't want to fight
for anyone other than my Master,
if that's what the Master wants,
I work for the Shinoyama.
So you don't need to worry about
what's going on around you, just as usual.
Just as usual,
don't notice my ugly jealousy
and live a life of laughter
with the Master.
Rather than saying
it's about taking back Polka,
it's more like an attack on me.
So it's better if Polka
stays away from me.
Miss Sakimiya.
Xiaoyu.
I leave the real Polka to you.
Miss Sakimiya.
So impressive.
In the past, I could only control
my own body.
I can't believe I can even do this now.
Am I rescued?
Is someone meddling?
Am I falling down?
It's the Lord Elf who's
being overly vigilant.
I never thought that monster
would come into the world.
W-Who are you?
Oh my.
It's only been 100 years since I was killed,
and even the language of Elf is extinct.
How shameful.
Fine.
Even so, I didn't put my soul
to Corpse God in vain.
After all, I can see the faces
of my children and grandchildren.
The boy had the hand of a dragon.
If I had known this, I wouldn't
have cut off its prosthetic limb
He seems to be out of danger.
After that battle,
I appreciate you telling me
about the crisis my brother is facing.
So I will keep my covenant
to cease fire with you
until Xiaoyu chooses his own path.
I can't believe it could
suppress the power of the elf.
I'm just getting used to it.
It's amazing how far
you've gotten on your own.
But I don't want to lose to you like this.
I'll give it my all until the end.
That is…
This is not just like it.
Isn't that the magic circle
that Mr. Arius uses?
Oh no. The whole city will be blown away.
You haven't lost yet.
In terms of strength alone,
you're much stronger.
I have just borrowed power.
No, I have driven power,
driving everyone like props.
That's good.
I and the others are dead people,
relics of the past.
Just use us as props
and keep moving forward.
Because you're still alive.
I'm already dead over there.
What's here right now is just a corpse.
Being alive is not about a corpse,
but about being able
to face life positively.
Corpse God.
No, Riz.
This time you must protect
what needs to be protected in this world
by your own will.
You're not like me.
You always move forward.
Why are you always so positive?
I didn't know it then,
but now I understand more or less.
This time I'm going to drag you into this.
Let me pave the way for you.
What a beautiful magic circle.
It was that time,
the way I felt
when I first saw magic books.
Looks like that's it.
But I am very happy.
Since you want to
witness revenge so badly,
then transfer your consciousness to me.
Mr. Iwa.
Don't tell me
you're going to do this for me.
This is my judgment.
- Sorry.
- What?
Wow.
I stopped you when you were acting out
as we agreed.
At least show some mercy.
I did show mercy.
Mr. Iwa.
You're acting out about
Mr. Hosorogi again, right?
Please do not forget.
For us,
you are also a part of the city
that we need to protect.
I'm sorry.
We understand your enlightenment.
Whether that boy has bugs or not,
we still need to observe.
That boy?
It's up to you to decide
if he's going to disappear.
What? Where is this? What?
BE CAREFUL OF THE FIRE
Why am I here?
It's Solitaire. Seriously?
Please give me an autograph.
Of course. Don't be fooled by my looking,
I'm actually a celebrity.
And you, that ghost-like lady…
What?
Is it a dream?
I remember what those guys
at the institute said,
the heart-like thing transplanted into me
is the core of a two-headed tiger monster.
So itchy.
Am I still alive?
Although you have been seriously injured,
you are not dead.
I turned part of you into a corpse,
which will slowly
transform into a living body.
Why did you save me?
You are a necromancer, aren't you?
Wouldn't it be better
to kill me and then use me?
I'm just giving you
back the magic you gave me.
This is what I gave you…
- Moreover…
- Lord Civil.
I didn't hear anything
over the loud noise,
neither did I see anything.
But at that moment,
I just don't want to see the kid sad.
I don't like taking something
away from a kid.
You might regret it.
Perhaps.
But by then,
I'll do everything I can to
protect everyone from the start.
I get it.
I've given up on returning
to the original world for now.
Because I realize that
this world is also worth living in.
Polka.
Lord Civil.
I agree with that.
TRACKING REPORT
SNIPING OCCURRED, TARGET WAS POLKA SHINOYAMA, NO EXTERNAL INJURIES
Those who want to kill Polka Shinoyama
seem to be connected to the intermediary agency
in Ikebukuro or Roppongi.
Don't forget, Corpse God.
So does Polka.
Before you get the peace you want,
there are many challenges waiting for you.