Like cards,
all people have a front and a back.
Sometimes they intentionally
conceal the facts.
Sometimes they don't.
And the same card will change
its patterns each time you turn it over.
And,
once in a while,
there are those whose front
and back sides are both wicked.
Those cards curiously enough,
tend to gather in the same hand.
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
(Episode 16: The Fake)
Don't move around.
O-okay, thanks.
Are you really Heilei--
There's plenty that I want to ask too,
but we will talk later.
Those extensions are your fingers?
Don't overdo it, boy.
Your legs are shaking.
Hey.
And what's with those hands
and feet anyway?
The ones that my oldest sister cut off
should still be in the collection room.
Oh well. I don't know if you're hoping
to get revenge on her or what,
but I already know
all about the Heilei's tricks.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not a Heilei anymore.
And you think this shaking is from fear?
Are you shaking with excitement?
No.
It's a beast's warning growl.
I see!
What a blast!
This isn't Heilei's moves at all.
But
your luck and your way of trying
to confuse your opponent are still Heilei.
Game over.
What a pity.
You were so close just now.
The way you're going after Mr. Higuro
here is so the Heilei way.
Looks like you didn't manage to escape
from the Heilei's karma.
Hehehe.
Mr. Momoya!
Misaki!
Miss Sakimiya?
Hehehe.
I had a hunch.
You're on our side
after all, aren't you, Xiaoyu?
Put me down!
What is going on?
Wasn't she killed by Momoya?
Is this something
that bends the laws of nature?
In addition to mission instructions,
our superiors told us to report anything
that appeared to violate nature's laws.
I did not expect to see it
with my own eyes, though.
But before that…
Can I get out
of this alive?
Okay, okay.
It doesn't make any sense,
but I think I've got the picture.
The girl I supposedly killed is alive.
And she's even stronger than before.
Talk about creepy, huh?
It causes people's skin to crawl.
It's the end of the world.
But it's quite interesting.
Now then, should we get started?
Very interesting.
Let's all play our trump cards.
Hehehe! What beautiful long legs!
They're like a model's!
Are you trying to seduce me?
Oh, my sisters always tell me,
"You are weak, so seduce
your opponent to confuse them."
He's fast.
But wait.
He barely moved.
Miss Sakimiya's able to keep up with him.
That was close!
I barely dodged that!
So what should we do, Xiaoyu?
Huh?
Should we take him on together?
Or are you the type who finds it
cooler to fight one-on-one?
I'm fine with either!
Strange. I'm confused.
I could've sworn I timed
my attack perfectly to cut you.
What could have happened?
I've been wondering for a while.
Why is it
I'm not hearing Miss Sakimiya's heartbeat?
So to speak,
is Misaki currently a vampire?
Yes.
You could say she is close to a vampire.
By interfering with the connection
between body and soul via necromancy,
her body functions similarly
to that of a vampire.
So,
the current Misaki has
augmented regenerative power
and can…
Whoa.
And can transform her body into a bat.
This guy!
His footwork and the positioning
of his long legs confuse his opponent.
What a seduction.
Even the color of his jacket.
It's all been calculated to
give the illusion
that he is tall and large.
Are you up?
What're you going to show me next?
Then, let me mimic
your long arm from earlier.
Are you going to throw that crowbar?
No tricks.
What the heck is this?
Hey, hey.
She's not trying to hide it at all.
Too bad,
I couldn't cut you in half.
There was no centrifugal force
involved in that throw.
That thing cut into me of its own will.
Are you an apprentice of Solitaire?
Shouldn't we explain
the situation to Xiaoyu?
Yes.
I'll fill him in as soon as he gets back.
What's wrong, Mr. Hosorogi?
I NEED YOUR HELP WITH SOMETHING
We're playing at a table
that's already full of bad cards.
You cannot win
by counting on the joker alone.
Whoever holds the stronger trump card
in this situation will win.
It's time for the players holding the cards to
scrutinize each other's poker faces, don't you think?
INCOMING CALL, UNKNOWN NUMBER
Who is this?
Hello.
I can't believe I got through.
Who is this?
You're too easy to manipulate.
Didn't I say you should regularly
change your phone and number?
You are…
Mr.
Hosorogi?
I wonder if the Shinoyama family
has any connection to that building.
Let's see.
The building is owned by Lisa Kuraki.
The granddaughter of
the industrialist Luis Kuraki.
After coming into her inheritance following
the disappearance of her parents,
she was the victim of
a kidnapping as a high schooler.
Huh?
But that kidnapping incident
was resolved by the police officer
INSPECTOR, MIYABI HOSOROGI
who disappeared in the building.
Mr. Hosorogi?
Is that really you, Mr. Hosorogi?
Calm down.
Don't go shouting my name.
Wouldn't want someone overhearing you.
Is it really you?
I can't properly speak on my own anymore.
Or, I suppose, it's more accurate to say
that I've been deprived of speech.
Where are you now?
Can't I see you in person?
You're smart.
You must already know that's impossible.
BORROWED VOCAL CORDS OF A DIED PIGEON
But I doubt you'd be
WITH THE PERMISSION OF HOSOROGI'S SOUL
able to fully grasp my current situation.
This appearance is overly dramatic.
Sure, I don't get it at all!
The old you would have never involved
a high schooler to pull a stunt like that!
You mean Polka Shinoyama?
The old me is dead.
I'm not the Miyabi Hosorogi you once knew.
The craziest part is,
he's telling the truth.
We are facing many enemies.
Do you still carry that note?
Yes.
DON'T HOLD ONTO THE PAST. SELECT WHAT YOU ENJOY
I left a number of clues
NO ONE CAN BE TRUSTED
on that note.
ON THE WEST SIDE OF THAT PLACE, THERE'S ONE MORE GARAGE
But I don't have time
THERE'S A SIGNPOST, THE KEY IS BEHIND 1-383 MIRROR
to tell you everything.
I'll just tell you the basics.
Clarissa's going to be involved again.
If the enemy is on the move again,
we will make preparations
to intercept them too.
Clarissa?
You do realize she's a criminal, right?
That's that. This is this.
I don't expect you to believe everything.
We'll save that conversation
for next time.
Okay.
Let's have a good, long talk later.
Well, what is it I should know?
Actually, I want to tell you that
the suspect was rooted
in the police department.
This isn't funny.
So?
These "players" you speak of…
In other words, you're saying
I'm the mastermind?
I believe your position as a superintendent
general qualifies you as a player.
The superintendent general is just one of
the authorities responsible for the scene.
It's the National Police Agency
manages the organization.
I should say it's the prime minister along
with the National Public Safety Commission
above that who are at the top.
Going further, in light of popular sovereignty,
it's the citizens who supersede the prime minister.
That's not what I'm talking about…
Then the "players" you speak of
could refer to each and every citizen.
Hmm…
Everybody's a player, a pawn and a cog.
Just like when you made PM Kubikigawara a
pawn for your own attention-seeking needs.
Heh. That brings back memories.
The sarcastic thing I said
did not mean to make you angry.
Do you want to scare me with words?
In any case, you're implying
I'm the mastermind behind "something"?
Then why did you show yourself to me?
Just what is it you want?
Heh-heh. You don't get it, do you?
That's right.
You can't figure out my plans,
Mr. Superintendent General.
Can you even imagine?
I have no plan for what comes next!
The mystery person
who ordered to assassinate me
I'M A STAND-IN
must be someone in a high position.
I only came to see what I can get from him.
CURRENT RESULT: HE'S PISSED OFF
What should I do next?
Do you have any plans next?
That trick of extending an arm?
I don't think that's going to work again.
You're probably right.
That guy's a tough one.
Huh?
But will this work?
Trust me.
Don't blame me if you die.
Wow! Are you worried about me?
This is very kind of you.
You done with your team meeting?
Yes! Thanks for waiting.
No need to thank me.
I wanted some time too.
A moment to think
about that little trick of yours
and to prepare myself.
I knew it, the fabric's been cut.
So my blade did land.
Got you!
Am I dreaming?
I…
Oh well.
It's fine.
Did they do it?
They seriously beat one of the Agakura?
Is this real?
We did it.
But…
What happened just now?
When he's got ahold of me,
you can stab me right through.
It was too dark to see clearly.
The shadows and flapping
coming from Miss Misak
looked and sounded exactly like bats.
We did it!
Watch out! Higuro still has a gun!
Ah, that person has already escaped.
What?
Phew, I'm safe.
I knew I could count on Mr. Momoya.
I really appreciate him going berserk
to keep everyone's eyes on him.
If he beats those two,
I hope we get to work together again.
If he loses,
I can only mourn for him.
I won't let your sacrifice go to waste.
So,
I'll report what I just saw,
things that bend the law of nature,
METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
to the superiors.
INCOMING CALL, UNKNOWN NUMBER
Not going to answer that?
It's just a personal call.
And I'm still on the job.
I see.
Are you saying your "suspects"
include people I've been
close to for years?
I only wish this were just a joke.
But Tsubaki,
once you've joined the police,
the entire organization is close to you.
From the faceless resident officers
to the partner you've been
assigned to for years.
The moment you suspect the police,
there's no difference between them.
You've convinced me.
You really are the same.
You want me to think of you as dead?
Not possible.
You will always live in our hearts.
I won't let you wiped out
easily from my heart.
Whatever you want.
I'm hanging up now. I'll be in touch.
Senior, I have one last question.
Do you think I'm the spy
for the mastermind you mentioned?
Have you forgotten what I'm like?
If it ever came to that, I'd put
a bullet right between your eyes.
Fair enough.
UNKNOWN NUMBER, CALL ENDED
I can't call him back with his unknown number.
Shall I issue a warrant
and get his number released?
If you do that,
it'll out the whole thing to the traitors.
I'm relieved then.
You're still the manager I know.
Yeah.
If anything,
I feel like I've got my old spirit back.
UNKNOWN NUMBER, INCOMING CALL
Is it Mr. Hosorogi again?
Maybe he forgot to say something?
Question.
I've finished the job. Who am I?
Huh?
First clue.
My real name is Tena Sorimura.
Solitaire?
That's correct!
You must be very smart to
have figured that out after just one clue!
As your reward, I'll throw you a "bone"!
Quit joking around.
It's about the mastermind you were
just speaking with Prosecutor Hosorogi.
Don't you want some hard evidence?
When you make bold moves, you end up
with some unexpected gains, you know?
Yes, just like me.
I'm sorry for causing trouble for you all.
I didn't want to involve you two.
But once they came here,
I was left with no choice.
This Iwanome person
was probably over the moon
thinking you're still alive.
But you're so cruel.
I'm well aware.
I'd always believed
there was no decent way to die.
But that's exactly how it's turned out.
But right now,
everything is going as planned for me.
I hope Iwanome does an excellent job.
Mr. Hosorogi aside,
do you believe what Solitaire said?
Not one damn word of it.
But I told you before.
"Whatever a person says…"
"It has a meaning,
whether or not it's true."
That's just something
I picked up from Hosorogi.
This is urgent. Seriously, please pick up.
Shouldn't you pick up?
Sorry, I'll only be a minute.
No calling me during work.
Didn't I tell you that already?
I have some information
that's a top priority.
It's the high school girl
who was in that building.
Even though I killed her,
she came right back to life.
She "bends the laws of nature."
Also, I had a tussle
with the Shinoyama in the process.
I need to hide for a while.
Can I ask you to protect me from
the Shinoyama family's threat?
Don't worry.
You'll be fine.
As long as you're still
under the protection of Sabaramond.
Good work, Higuro.
You…
You!
I can't be speaking on the phone
to a journalist in the headquarters!
I just wanted to tell you something, Bro!
REAL NAME: KOCHOU YATSU
YATSU = EIGHT PORT
After the death of Mr. Hosorogi,
only one officer received
a suspicious promotion.
To be honest, I'm quite shocked.
I never imagined that the person who
helped me when I was about to be fired,
someone I considered family,
would betray me.
I made the same mistake just now.
You were so careless to say the name
of your contact over the phone like that.
Inspector Habaki.
That man there isn't moving.
What do we do with him?
We probably shouldn't mess with him.
But
does this mean that it's over?
Are you kidding me?
There is no way Mr. Habaki…
-Listen.
-Small carp fish…
Don't tell Mr. Iwa about this.
The fisherman
fished in the river.
Those dreams
even now
return to me.
How I miss
my hometown.
The number you have dialed is powered off
or out of service.
Please try again later.
He deserves to be punished.
Momo, how dare you
ignore such an important
phone call from your dear sister?
(Episode 17: The Matriarch)