Don't you dare start a fight without me!
Aura is moving?!
Vox System has been activated!
Its CSR Border Line has already exceeded 100%.
It's not responding to the A.I. Remote System, sir!
Full throttle from the get go, huh?
Mr. Tadokoro!
I'll stop those two!
Hold on a minute!
You haven't piloted that thing in nearly a year!
Distance between Lympha and Ignis, zero!
Lympha's cockpit has been damaged!
Lan!
Pilot has lost consciousness!
The craft is losing altitude!
Hurry, Midori!
ano koro watashitachi wa (tobenai puropera de)
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't carry us
sora no mou hanbun miage (hadashi de hashitteta yo ne)
We ran with bare feet with our eyes fixed on the other side of the sky
watashitachi wa itsudemo
We always live
kanchigai da to ka
in a world full of conviction
jishin de ikiteru
and misunderstandings
daiji na takaramono ne
I wish I could store these
shimaeru you ni kokoro
precious feelings in my heart
kitto mienaku natteru yo
I'll get over it
guru guru mawase
Spin the wheel of fate
kono mahou no tsue de
With this magic staff,
namida to sunny day mazerun da
I'll blend tears and sunny days
samishigariyasan
Oh, lonely girl
yume wa kanau yo
I'm sure your dream will come true
itsu datte issho da yo watashitachi
and we will be together forever
Mayhem on Kamogawa Beach
Lympha, respond!
Laffinty!
Lan...
Lympha...
Please respond! Lympha...
Lympha!
Lan...
Lan!
That voice just now...
Madoka!
Aura is approaching the battle zone!
Madoka?!
You two...
... stop fighting...
... right—
She went right past them.
Huh?
What?
Lympha and Ignis have resumed battle!
Wait...
Hey, what're you doing?!
I have no idea!
Hey, Midori! Snap out of it!
The three of us are finally together again, so why...?
I was hoping we could get together like we did before.
What?
What was that?
Why do I have to fight you, Muginami?!
I really... love you, Lan!
Are these their thoughts?
Why won't you understand?!
Stay away from Madoka!
I should be the one saying that!
Your people tried to destroy De Metrio!
Do you plan on being a puppet for your brother forever?!
Look who's talking!
I don't know who started all this, but...
Madoka?
I said...
Stop fighting!
What is wrong with you two?!
You're crazy! Why must you two fight?!
Say something!
What?
It's the Le Garite Occupation Forces.
Switch to an open channel.
But then Ignis will be able to overhear the transmission.
That's fine...
Kyouno!
A Le Garite platoon is closing in on your position.
They plan to shoot down the enemy unit, Ignis.
Reinforcements are sure to follow.
Back away so that you do not get mixed up in this.
Huh? What do you mean shoot down Muginami?!
Did you get that?
Thank you...
Muginami?!
Lan, let's go!
I'm sorry, Madoka.
Lan?!
I'm sorry.
"Sorry"?
Hey wait, Lan!
Why are you two...?
I don't get it.
Huh?
Hey... Hey, hey!
Midori?!
I keep telling you that I can't authorize that.
Please let me go search for them!
That's what you get for trying to swim after them.
We are on the lookout for Lympha and Ignis.
Even if you were to go look for those two with Aura,
you don't have any leads to begin with.
Besides, their fight is part of a galactic dispute between two planets.
Earth needn't interfere.
Both of them were acting strange.
Lan and Muginami seemed like they were acting against their will.
I mean, why are they even fighting in the first place?
Girl, do you understand the words that are coming out of my mouth?
They finally came back to Kamogawa. So why?
I guess not...
Wh-What is it this time?!
That's it.
It's Kamogawa.
That's gotta be it!
Thank you!
Hey, Kyouno? Kyouno?!
She already left.
What?
Lan!
Muginami!
Huh?
They're not back.
Oh, welcome home.
They're back!
Man, I'm starving.
Another busy day, wasn't it?
Hey, what the hell?
Are they back?!
Oh, hey... Welcome back.
Where are Lan and Muginami?!
Huh?
Are those two coming back here?
That's odd... It wasn't Kamogawa then?
I was positive they'd be here.
Maybe they went home.
I guess so, since they're not here.
Hey, do you guys know where they live?
Do you know?
I don't know!
I understand Laffinty and Muginami went at it.
I'm sure this is the motive.
You mean the Thousand Year Polyhedron problem?
The astral phenomenon that will cause the orbits of Le Garite and De Metrio to collide
and result in the destruction of both planets.
But I was under the impression
that a plan of action would be discussed at the upcoming intergalactic conference?
Do you plan on being a puppet for your brother forever?!
Look who's talking!
Judging from this recording, Laffinty was trying to get Madoka to pilot Aura under her brother's orders.
By all accounts, he is willing to destroy De Metrio in order to correct the orbit.
They believe that Aura has the power to destroy a planet?
According to what Izo and others have said, it's possible.
Apparently, the princess of De Metrio
destroyed a natural satellite named Militia Zodia during a Vox Core experiment.
What is a Vox Core?
It's the prototype of the Vox cockpit.
In any case, Dizelmine is planning something outside the intergalactic conference
and intends to make use of Madoka and Aura.
Depending on her actions...
a full-blown stellar war may very well break out.
It's no use. I can't detect Ignis' signal.
She's always been good at hiding, that Muginami.
Is this it?
Are we connected to them?
Yeah, as long as they haven't changed their identification signal.
State your ship's affiliation and I.D. number.
This ship belongs to the De Metrio Army.
Hold it, Grania...
Oh, hello?
Uh... This is Kyouno Madoka, from Kamogawa.
Repairs will be expedited and should take about one week.
We should be done by the time the intergalactic conference starts.
Thank you.
Are you relieved to see that Aura is operational again?
Just more hijinks waiting to happen.
Say, Cap...
What is it?
Look...
Hey, Giuvi...
Is Muginami over there?
I saw her this afternoon,
but then she left and now I can't find her anymore.
"Giuvi"?!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
Kyouno! What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, Mr. Tadokoro...
I'm on the phone.
That's not what I meant!
Uehara!
Intercept her call from the bridge and terminate it!
W-Wait!
The nerve these fools have!
You moron!
Didn't I just order you not to act recklessly?!
At this point, De Metrio is a hostile force!
Did you really think you could contact them without clearing it first with the Le Garite Occupation Forces?!
Why do we have to be here too?
And you guys...!
You work for the Chairman, so you have no excuse for not knowing the situation.
But we do.
We've been out of the loop for six months.
Longer than that.
Aren't you worried about those two, Mr. Tadokoro?
Listen, whether or not I worry about them is not the issue here.
What is it then?
Stop!
In any case, those two did not return to their brothers.
If they had left this planet, our surveillance satellites would have caught it.
Then where are they?
They haven't left Earth.
They're still on Earth?
Hey, Kyouno!
I'm going back to Kamogawa.
If they haven't gone back to their brothers,
then the only place they can return to has got to be Kamogawa!
Are you going to just let her go?
There are no more operating shuttles to take her back to shore.
There's no way she can leave Pharos.
Lan... Muginami...
She hasn't changed at all, that Madoka.
Lord Villagiulio, over half a day has passed since we lost Muginami's signal.
Even if she is on the run from the Le Garite force, isn't that a bit too long?
You allowed her to act on her own under the assumption that if Aura fell into Le Garite's hands,
Muginami would personally deal with Kyouno Madoka, right?
But if she is having second thoughts,
then maybe you should order her to—
I will not give the order.
Haven't I already said so before?
I won't do what Dizel would do.
But...
He plans to sacrifice our planet for his to survive.
Thus I must oppose him.
Who am I to tell Muginami to bury her feelings?
If I did, I'd be betraying the very ideal for which I took the throne.
She'll show up in time,
along with whatever result her feelings have wrought.
Cycle Narabe
Kamogawa Girls' High School
Jersey
Club
Jersey Club!
Always looking
for new members!!!
Jersey
Club
Lan?
Why?
This place hasn't changed at all.
My locker... It's still here.
Madoka would never throw it out.
You're right.
Say, Lan...
What is it?
Are you going to involve Madoka, no matter what?
What about you? You're trying to kill Madoka.
I'll never allow it!
I will protect Madoka!
You got a lot of nerve saying that.
You're trying to take advantage of Madoka!
You don't know anything!
If I don't do anything, Le Garite will use Madoka by force!
That's why I put myself between them!
See? You're just doing what your brother wants!
You know, Lan...
I came here to make sure of something.
It's why I came to this place where we three went together...
Back when the three of us were in the Jersey Club.
I came here to make sure of my feelings.
Me, kill Madoka?
I could never do that.
I mean, I like Madoka.
I love her!
That's why I will not allow Madoka to become entangled in this!
Please leave.
And never come near Madoka again!
I refuse.
Lan!
I told you.
I am Madoka's guardian.
Madoka?
I knew it.
You two were here, after all!
M-Madoka?
Madoka?
You two...
You don't really want to fight, do you?
I heard your voices.
It wasn't too clear.
But I could feel the pain you two were going through.
Because I felt it too.
It was so sad.
How did this happen?
Please tell me.
I'll do anything I can. Anything.
I'm sorry, Madoka.
Lan?
It's too late.
Our planets...
Our brothers are beyond reaching an understanding.
Muginami?
There's nothing we can do anymore.
Wha—
If that's the case, then don't worry!
We can make your brothers become friends again.
I'll make them.
Like I did just now!
Then you two won't have to fight.
Let's try it!
To give up without even trying and fighting when you're against it
isn't the Jersey Club way!
The three of us together can do it!
Madoka...
Listen, Madoka. It isn't that simple.
Wh-What are you doing?!
I've made up my mind!
Muginami will rejoin the Jersey Club!
Muginami!
I haven't got a clue as to what we'll do.
But the three of us...
The three of us together... I feel like we can pull it off.
Didn't you just say you didn't want Madoka to get involved?
But now, I think something is possible.
Lan, you should join in too.
Okay...
No, I can't! We don't have a plan!
No way! It's impossible!
You're starting to think it's going to work out, aren't you?
You're thinking it just might work.
Back off.
You're thinking it might just work!
Enough!
Ow!
I-I'm sorry!
Hey Lan!
Haven't I always told to keep a sharp eye on Madoka?
How do you explain this, then?
We've been pretty busy.
We were careless.
Asteria, please don't scold them too much.
I'm sure they've learned their lesson.
Whose fault do you think this is?
Well...
When I heard that Laffinty and Muginami had begun fighting in Kamogawa,
I did get a bad feeling about this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
We're being swamped with government inquiries from both nations.
Let me get straight to the point, then.
Both of you, seek asylum on Earth.
That's the only way to avoid war.
Yes, ma'am.
Please help us.
All right, you two! No time for idle thoughts!
You're back.
It sounded awfully noisy out here.
Your dear cousin has done it again.
I'm glad nothing has changed.
So?
Our measurements exposed the presence of Vox particles.
Same goes for the flower.
As we envisioned, the Vox may possess the potential to be more than a weapon.
If we can prove that, it could be the trump card to end this deadlock.
That's if I can make sure things run smoothly.
It's unlike you to sound so uncertain.
That's because I cannot risk the tragedy from 20,000 years ago repeating itself...
jaajibu damashii jaajibu damashii
The Jersey Club spirit! The Jersey Club spirit!
hottokenai hello and let's genki damashii
I won't leave you alone, hello and let's be cheery!
tanoshii ka dou ka tagai ni
Who knows if it's fun?
imadani kakuninchuu
We're still trying to work that out
kyoudoutai mittsu no seishun
This is the youth of us three!
unmei no deai wa masa ni isshun
Our destined meeting happened in a split second
mae muite aruku no mo issho
We're together when we walk ahead
hitoiki tsuku no mo mata issho
We're together with each of the breaths we take
hora
Look
kokoro no soko kara warau no mo issho
We're together when we laugh from the bottom of our hearts
are kore tte yuujou?
Is this friendship?
daijoubu
We'll be fine!
horisagenai kara ii yo
I won't press the issue!
tashikamenai kara ii yo
I won't delve into it too deep!
hitsuyou nai kara watashitachi ni wa
We don't really have to know that
nande soko made shinjiaeru tte
Why can we trust each other so much, you ask?
kimatteru jan sonna no
That's obvious!
sannin wa doushi dakara
We're comrades!
jaajibu damashii jaajibu damashii
The Jersey Club spirit! The Jersey Club spirit!
suketto shitai hello and let's honki damashii
I want to help you, hello and let's be honest!
Are you telling me to have my first summer experience?!
That's "experience".
We're asking you to do an "experiment".
I'll do it if I have to, but it's my first time you know.
You're talking about "experience" again!
Okay, I've made up my mind. Bring it on!
How brave of you.
Well, I'll make sure you enjoy this.
The Kamogawa Experiment
Scary...