You know, the universe is so large, we can't even begin to fathom it.
And time has been flowing for an eternity...
And yet, we were able to meet.
Do you think it's a miracle?
I don't think it is.
I mean...
Our encounter had to be destined.
Destined?
Yes, like one single bee out of a swarm...
Like a single flower out of a myriad...
They come together to bear a mellow fruit.
Single droplets of night mist that fall from the leaves
fill the springs that become the foundation of a great river.
I'm sure that our encounter held meaning.
Meaning? How so?
Well, for example...
To make me fall in love?
I've been feeling this way since we first met.
I love you!
You can't...
Huh?
I wanted to say it first.
We'll always be together.
Yes. Forever and ever.
Cut!
That's a wrap for "The Lily and the Spaceship"!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you!
You did it!
That was perfect!
It's over.
Uh-huh.
That was a little embarrassing, wasn't it?
Yes.
That was the last job for the Jersey Club.
Good job, Lan.
Good job, Madoka.
Try
akirame nai kokoro
The courage to never give up
kono mune no naka ni wasurenai kara itsumo
will always be right here in my heart
Don't cry
kitto yakusoku yo
Promise me
hitori de naitari shinai de
that you won't cry all by yourself
itsu datte issho dakara
Because I'm always with you
kanashimi hitotsu sotto wakeattara
If we can share even one sorrow
motto tsuyoku nareru yo
Then we'll get stronger
ima sugu waratte my friend!
Smile now, my friend!
dareka no tame ja nakute
Not for someone else
jibun de kimeta kimochi dakara
Because it's the path you chose
massugu na koe de Hello!
Stand tall and say "Hello!"
utatte yo itsumo no uta
Let me hear that song of yours
hitotsubu no yuuki wo kokoro ni e
Pass me a fragment of your courage
Until We Meet Again, In Kamogawa
It has been two weeks since the delegation
from Le Garite came to Earth.
Today, their representative and the U.N. delegate
Hey, look up there!
met in a conference for the 12th time
at the Kamogawa Municipal Auditorium in Kamogawa City, Chiba Prefecture.
Also participating in the meetings were the Prime Minister, the Foreign Minister,
the governor of Chiba Prefecture and mayor of Kamogawa City.
The talks were conducted cordially interspersed with occasional planetary and regional jokes.
Reserved for the day
Sorry
A princess from a distant planet!
How romantic!
But I still can't believe it. Are you seriously an alien?
Can I touch you?
Huh? S-Sure...
Hey, come on. Stop slapping her like a sumo wrestler.
Here you go!
I'll keep bringing out food, so eat up.
Besides, Uncle's cooking, not me!
Here you go!
I'll help too.
What are you saying?!
Lan!
Have
a
back
to
your
safe
journey
home
planet!
And the wrap party for "The Lily and The Spaceship"!
You're the guest of honor, so sit back and enjoy yourself!
It will be lonely around the shop again.
How many times do I need to repeat myself? No gloomy talk!
She's right, Mr. Hiroshi!
You're coming right back to Earth, aren't you?
I'm not sure about that.
Huh?
What?
Intergalactic travel isn't that easy.
Are you saying this is really good-bye?
Lan...
Lan!
Lan should just play along
Take good care of yourself.
and say she's coming right back.
We'll never forget you, Lan!
She's just too honest.
So please don't forget about us too!
All right, that's enough!
How can Lan go back to her planet feeling happy with a send-off like that?!
Princess Lan, will you spare a few parting words to us plebeians?
What?
Ahem!
We are gathered here today under such wonderful weather...
Not like that...
No one is surprised anymore
by the fact that you're an alien.
Uh-huh.
It's been two weeks since that incident.
You're right.
Wow!
How beautiful!
Isn't it?
I should've brought you here to the Hill of Vows earlier,
but it totally slipped my mind.
The Hill of Vows?
I vow that we will meet again in Kamogawa some day.
You too, Lan!
All right. I vow too.
Good.
Until we meet again, in Kamogawa! Madoka & Lan & Muginami
As long as this lock remains here
we must honor our vow, no matter what.
I wish Muginami were here too...
Do you think we'll all meet again?
Yes, absolutely.
After all, the view before us is still here.
That's right.
Yes.
It's because you protected it.
Flowers?
Why did it have to be Sis... Why us?
If you wanted to hurt someone
Madoka!
you should have just done it to me.
I've been ready to risk my life for a long time.
I was prepared...
Madoka...
Why does it always have to be the ones I love?
If I try to go in for close-range combat, my craft will mutate.
Damage report!
Long-range attacks are ineffective as well.
Ovids Garua, Baizand, and Nekusan are out of commission
So what are my options now?
due to the effects of the anomaly!
Detecting an ultra-sized energy field!
What is that?
What's about to happen here?
What is the situation with the energy field?
It's growing even larger!
Phochville Ships 1 and 2 are going to be swallowed up!
All ships within the field range are to go into overdrive without hesitation!
Get out of there!
Aura, Lympha and Ignis...
The telemetry from each one is off the grid!
Just what is happening, Moid?
Shut the hell up! Don't talk to me now!
Can't you see I'm trying to enjoy the best part?
Uehara!
Yes sir!
Can we communicate with the pilots?
We can't. We're disconnected from all three—
No, wait! It's Aura...
What is this... static?
There are lots of people I want to protect.
There's Sis, Uncle, everyone at school...
The people of Kamogawa... and... and...
Hey... Was I really the right choice?
Do I really have what it takes?
If I say you don't, are you going to give up?
If it's impossible, it's impossible.
You don't know that until you try.
It's a fact that you were chosen.
But whether or not you can do it, no one knows.
In other words...
It's all up to you.
"All up to me"?
Before I came here, there was someone else.
She went back to her own world, almost like she was switching places with me.
She said she was going to try once again.
But I didn't ask what she was going to do.
Have you ever thought of leaving this place?
I'm staying here because...
that's the path I've chosen.
I see...
So...
who are you?
"That's the path I've chosen", huh.
That's so cool!
Let's try this...
my way!
Lan!
Muginami!
Let's go...
together!
What?
The only thing I can do...
is to fly with everything I've got, just like this!
A-Aura!
It's beautiful...
Well?
Does my kid sister have potential?
Yes...
She's an outrageous girl
that Kyouno Madoka.
Sis? She's alive!
Midori, Sis is okay!
What happened?
What the heck?!
What's wrong, Madoka?
Midori stopped moving!
Why?
I don't know! Maybe she fell asleep?
Hey, wake up! Come on, Midori!
Bravo! That was a brilliant illusion.
There is no doubt that the Voxes hide a frightening power.
In fact, we just saw the proof.
Villagiulio!
It appears that in order for the people of De Metrio to sleep safely at night...
you must be put to sleep!
You! The leader of the giant demons!
Brother...
Brother!
It can't be...
Dizelmine...
Eliminate all resistant forces within Earth's domain.
There is no need to pursue anyone who flees.
Yes, my lord.
Muginami!
Let her go!
If she stays, my brother will definitely kill them...
Both Villagiulio, and Muginami for trying to save him.
If I knew earlier that my brother's ship was coming to get me,
I wouldn't have let Muginami go to battle.
I'm sorry, Madoka.
It's not your fault, Lan.
I hope she's doing okay.
I wonder what planet she's on?
I'll find her.
Huh?
I'll find her and we'll return together.
To this town, where the three of us first met.
I promise.
And when that time comes,
will you let us be your comrades again?
Yes!
Well... I'll be going, okay?
Uh-huh.
See you!
Bye-bye!
See you again!
Succe—
And so, Muginami left and Lan returned to her home planet
and time passed.
And autumn in Kamogawa slowly came to an end.
We're counting on you, Madoka!
You got it!
Stop! Stop!
Safe!
You did it!
Madoka, help!
Okay!
At dawn's break...
As though lit by the morning moon...
Got it!
Huh?
Madoka!
Bring it on!
Hey, Kyouno!
Oh, just a minute!
The next opening I have in the Jersey Club schedule is...
Not that. You received a letter.
Huh?
It's addressed to the Jersey Club.
Midori hasn't moved since that day.
Even the people on Pharos don't seem to know why.
So many things happened that I think she just wants to rest.
Yeah, I'm sure that's it.
Mr. Moid returned to Le Garite with Lan and her brother.
Because of that, it's like the wind has been taken out of Mr. Tadokoro's sails.
H-Hot!
My sister Youko recovered completely from her injuries.
Just what I'd expect from her.
The scar doesn't bother her one bit.
She seems to have gotten close to Asteria lately.
Madoka said that during the last battle, she realized she was on a beach.
A beach?
And she got some advice from a girl she didn't know.
I see. So she saw her too.
Isn't it about time you shared your story with me too?
If I did, what would you do?
Nothing. I'm just curious.
They say girls who are too curious miss their chance at marriage.
I am the witch who pulled this universe into an eternal loop
comprised of peace and calamity.
But don't worry, I promise I'll disappear.
Once Madoka severs this...
endless cycle of Rin-ne.
Come on—!
I was looking forward to the roasted roe inside!
Isn't this the...?
The Chairman of Novumundus is your personal reference, huh...?
I saw Lan recently.
We talked about so many things.
About each other, about our future, and about you... Madoka.
We ended up arguing again,
but we made up just like when we were a trio.
We argued a lot and made up a lot.
And now, I love you two even more.
Even if I squint really hard,
I still can't see the Earth from here.
But... I promise I'll return to Kamogawa some day.
When I do, let's argue lots and lots!
To my dearest Madoka...
Success!
Didn't I tell you to hold on to it since the wind is blowing?
You never listen to your mother!
Just a minute!
I'll get it for you in a jiffy!
I'll be right there!