Okay!
I'm off!
Have some Kamogawa Soup.
It's good.
Thank you.
Thanks for waiting!
Shall we get going?
Yes.
We're leaving.
Where?
Isn't it obvious? To get revenge!
Why?
What do you mean, "why"?
Hey, Uncle! Look after her for us!
What?
Giuvigiuvio...
I swear...
I'm going to kick your butt!
jersey no onna no ko nani ka motteru
There's something about the jersey girl
chakku wo hazushitara nani ni demo nareru kara
Pull down my zipper and the world will open up to me
taisetsu na koto sagashite umi no soko nimo ikeru
I can even reach the seabed in search of things that matter
takamari ga do wo sugi ribon mo tokeru
Overwhelming excitement sets me free
sugu ai ni iku yo
I'll come to see you
kimi no hijou sign ga yonde kuretara
Whenever your siren calls for me
mawaridase unmei wo kakikaete
Revolve! Rewrite your own destiny
tobidase fly away on a brighter day
Go on! Fly away on a brighter day
shita wo dashi fumidasu kiken nara
If I can step into danger with a smile
moete kuru fly away try unite tonight
Burn away! Fly away try unite tonight
The Wind, Fire and Water Above Kamogawa
Sorry to keep you waiting, sir. I'm ready now!
Midori, taking off!
Kyouno...
Yes, sir!
Who said we're attacking anybody?
What do you mean? I just said it.
Listen... We can't just let you take it out for a flight whenever you feel like it.
Besides, how do you expect to win when you don't even have a strategy?
The one who makes the first move wins!
That's the first rule of the Jersey Club!
Get out of the cockpit and go on standby!
That's all.
Hey, wait!
Now explain again from the beginning.
So if we don't get rid of all three Vox units,
he'll destroy them along with Pharos?
His objective is pretty clear.
What sort of person are we dealing with?
He sure is polite enough to declare war on us.
He's debris.
Debris?
Space trash.
More accurately, he's ex-royalty from a planet
that shared a longstanding alliance with us.
However, currently he's the leader of a criminal group that calls itself "Kiss".
You could say he's the enemy mastermind.
How the mighty has fallen.
You said we have until daybreak.
According to my calculation,
we only have about five hours left.
Let's say we comply with his demand and destroy all the Vox.
Do you think the enemy will leave Earth peacefully?
Of course not.
We'll just be losing our only means of defense.
I got lost! This place is too big!
Mr. Tadokoro! You need to hear me out!
Muginami is my—!
All right. That's enough.
"That's enough"?
Ms. Watabe, please find us a marine location suitable for battle.
We'll head there once all civilian personnel have been evacuated from this ship.
I'm on it.
James, report the situation to every branch of the Foundation.
Coordinate with them to make absolutely sure
no ship or aircraft enters the airspace where the fighting will take place.
Roger!
Uehara...
Hurry and complete final checks on both Vox units
so that Kyouno and Laffinty can fly at any time.
Roger!
Don't just stand there.
Huh?
It's an all-out war.
Success!
Let's go, Lan!
I'm sure you understand,
but this doesn't mean you may attack immediately.
Woof.
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Yes, sir!
Get revenge?
That's what Dad's email said.
What's wrong?
No, never mind. It's nothing.
I don't get this Villagiulio guy.
What do you mean?
Why did he bother to come all the way here?
Oh, now that you mention it...
Ta-dah!
What is that?
Let's open it and...
Find out!
Hey, what's the big idea?!
It's delicious!
Try it. It hits the spot!
I think I'll pass...
Then I'll try some.
Knowing your enemy begins from stuff like this.
Kirius!
It tastes pleasant and refreshing at first.
But the moment it hits your stomach,
this overpowering sweetness hits.
I was right.
This planet cannot be underestimated, Izo!
Man, you're so dramatic.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
Hey, what did you go down there for, anyway?
Two more hours 'til dawn.
You'll find out then.
What time is it?
Rest while you can or your body won't hold up.
I'll be just fine!
My Energy is fully replenished!
Do you think she's all right?
You mean Muginami?
Well, knowing her,
I'm sure she won't let something like that get to her...
Of course it would!
Who wouldn't?!
I guess you're right.
Anyone would react that way after being told such a horrible thing.
He didn't use to be like that.
He was so noble, and caring.
The past doesn't matter!
After all, I don't know anything about that Giuvigiuvi guy's past!
Yes... You're right, Madoka.
Right now, I have every reason to fight him!
Let's kick his butt!
Then... here!
Charge up and let's go!
Thank you...
My wife... Well, she's my ex-wife now.
She also had quite a sharp tongue.
She always let me have an earful.
To be honest, it hurts even now,
especially when I'm feeling lonely.
But during times like that...
And who might you be?
I'm from Novumundus Japan.
Novumundus Foundation Japan International Management Group Chief Advisor
Balance T. Moid
If you're here for Madoka, she already left.
Actually, I have some business with this one.
Enemy unit presence confirmed. All hands to battle stations.
I repeat...
What is the enemy mother ship's position?
It's matching our velocity...
and hovering above satellite tracking range.
Then why aren't they attacking?
I thought I ordered all non-combatant personnel off this ship.
Oh, don't mind us.
I'm related to that girl.
Patch me through to the two pilots.
It's almost daybreak.
The enemy is right above us.
They're practically sitting on top of us and we can't run nor hide.
By the way, what's wrong with Laffinty?
It seems she drank too much Energy.
Aren't you supposed to dilute that stuff before drinking it?
I'm all right.
I'm good to go.
Just remember your previous battle.
The two of you can do this!
Attack!
Opening barrier walls numbers one and two.
Pilot's heart rate, blood pressure, respiratory rate... all normal.
Opening the top hatch.
A.I. Remote Systems are normal.
All systems go.
Vox Aura, Vox Lympha, take off!
Let's go, Midori!
Orca! Taking off!
It's not dawn yet, you two.
Madoka!
Are you kidding me?
Multiple enemy Ovid launches confirmed.
Number count...
What is it?
The two Vox crafts are about to make contact with the enemy units!
Get the weapon prototypes ready for launch, now!
Yes, sir!
Where are Madoka and Lan?
They took off to get revenge for you.
Normally, one shouldn't sympathize with the enemy.
But after hearing your story,
even I felt like punching that man.
Truly a terrible man, that Villagiulio.
A subordinate risks her life to sneak behind enemy lines
and manages to steal their treasure.
Yet he shows no remorse in discarding her, simply because she acted against his wishes.
Even though he was aware of your sincere feelings for him.
How ungrateful of him.
Doesn't he realize that not everyone can achieve Memoria?
Hey, you have some neat stuff!
Be careful.
Thanks!
Man! There's no end to this!
Help is on its way.
Moid?
Cap!
There's someone in Ignis's cockpit!
Put it up on the monitor!
Her?!
Get her out now!
I can't!
She's already entered the T.O. sequence!
She's taking off!
Brother...
I'm serious!
If you don't stop me now...
This will really, really...
Be good-bye!
Muginami?
She doesn't know when to give up.
Ignis's Vox System has been activated.
We can no longer control it with the A.I. Remote!
I find her to be quite gifted, don't you agree?
What have you done?
You can scold me later.
What is it that you find so amusing?
Brother, if this means good-bye...
I might as well... I'll just...
Is she planning to go in alone?!
Muginami!
Let's go!
Right...
Hold it.
You boys stand by here.
What are you talking about?
Are you planning to take on those three by yourself?
Harem night!
Oh wait. It's almost morning, huh?
It's another manned enemy craft!
Henceforth, it will be identified as enemy unit four!
That must be the one that appeared in Kamogawa last night.
Brother!
That bastard!
This is good-bye.
Brother...
Giuvigiubaro!
Madoka!
Stop, Madoka!
It's my fault for acting on my own
without ever taking Brother's feelings into account!
Brother isn't to blame!
This is all my fault!
You...
stupid girl!
Are you still defending him after what he said to you?!
You should dump someone like him.
You have no right to say that!
You don't know anything about me!
You haven't considered my feelings in the least!
No one asked you to get revenge for me!
You talk big about wanting to help other people,
but the Jersey Club and everything you do...
You're only doing it for your own selfish reasons!
So that's how you thought of me?
Until today...
This whole time?
Hey, what is that?
It can't be...
Yes, that's it.
Hey, what is...?
Madoka!
Is this what Villagiulio was really after?
Impossible! But for what purpose?
Or...is this just a coincidence?
The Rin-Ne has blossomed!
Try
akirame nai kokoro
The courage to never give up
kono mune no naka ni wasurenai kara itsumo
will always be right here in my heart
Don't cry
kitto yakusoku yo
Promise me
hitori de naitari shinai de
that you won't cry all by yourself
itsu datte issho dakara
Because I'm always with you
kanashimi hitotsu sotto wakeattara
If we can share even one sorrow
motto tsuyoku nareru yo
Then we'll get stronger
ima sugu waratte my friend!
Smile now, my friend!
dareka no tame ja nakute
Not for someone else
jibun de kimeta kimochi dakara
Because it's the path you chose
massugu na koe de Hello!
Stand tall and say "Hello!"
utatte yo itsumo no uta
Let me hear that song of yours
hitotsubu no yuuki wo kokoro ni e
Pass me a fragment of your courage
My jersey is gone!
Look in your bag.
It's not there!
What about the washing machine?
It's not there. Maybe someone stole it?
Muginami?
Did you...?
I didn't steal it.
Return it.
Come on, now, Lan.
I didn't take it. I just tried it on, that's all.
But it was really tight around my chest...
Cloudy Skies, Followed by Kamogawa