Come out, one of the twelve disciples...
Sister Angelene!
Man...
Don't show me something as pathetic as that!
Here, use this.
What is it?
An escape pod.
It's a better alternative than staying here.
Sister Lucia, your hand's shaking...
Of course it is.
Come on, I'm not going to die here.
We'll all go back together, right?
You... as well as everyone else fighting here...
Everyone will be together...
That's why I won't die.
So, please... fight your hardest to protect everyone...
Say something, Lucia.
I'll help if possible.
Even if it means destroying as many
of these stupid illusions as I have to.
So say something that will make her think it was worth being here.
Something that will make her believe it was worth gritting her teeth!
Yes.
I'll protect everyone, no matter what.
So, please, you have your own fight right now.
#16 Appointed Time
of the Rosary
Are they still at it?!
Sheesh.
I didn't think we'd have to go through
so much trouble just to sink one city.
That face...
Absolutely wonderful.
That expression that says you still believe in them.
And what would I believe in?
I'm going to break your hopes now.
You've no need for such emotions.
Go!
Get that girl at all costs!
Let's go, Index, Orsola!
Nobody seems to be here.
This ship is most likely monitoring the entire fleet using magic.
That'd explain why the Sisters haven't followed us.
Just a moment.
I'll unlock it.
I'm starting to get a little tired of thinking things through!
What was that?
A block structure.
Unlike the escort ships, this ship has
magic embedded throughout its structure.
Those knights...
Crap!
Go inside.
W-Wait!
You guys go on ahead!
Touma!
Sister Angelene, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
If they weren't my comrades...
Sheesh.
How boring.
Stop picking on the injured girl.
Crap, another one!
This is...
Another one?!
Is that all?
It connected!
Orsola?
Touma, is it true that, to activate The Queen of The Adriatic Sea,
they need to cast another spell called
"Appointed Time of the Rosary"?
Something like that.
My 103,000 grimoires say nothing about that!
Then what kind of a spell is it?
I think it's a codename only known by
members of the Roman Catholic Church.
That right hand...
Do you like it?
Not one bit.
Not only does it cancel out the blessing of the Lord,
but you swing it around like it's some sort of weapon.
If you had ever heard God's teachings,
then you would do anything to receive his
blessings, even if you had to rip your arm off!
I suppose the language of humans would
make no sense to a pagan monkey.
In that case, I, Biagio Buzoni, will put an end to this enemy of the Lord.
So you're Biagio?
That means you know where Agnese is.
Knowing and telling are two very different things.
The cross is the way of repentance!
The cross can eliminate enemies, as well
as provide a safe zone anywhere near it.
Just like this.
Additionally, the cross also holds the
power to correct a man of his pride.
Again... just like this.
Where am I?
Now, now...
Must you break everything around you?
You might affect the purity of the spell.
What do you mean?
The Appointed Time of the Rosary.
Don't pretend you know nothing of it.
It doesn't matter. This will be over if I
crush you and get Agnese out of here.
Are you really going against the will of the Lord?
Such evil words.
My crosses will reject that evil.
Damn it!
You think you have the right to do whatever you want with Venice?!
That is not my intention.
What did you say?
At the very least, it's a hundred times more
interesting than what you're thinking.
Do you know what the oldest execution tool in Christianity is?
Execution tool, I said.
Simon bears the cross of the Son of God!
What the...
The cross is the way of repentance!
This is...
There's a defensive spell on it.
C.A.H.
Shift focus onto me
Go get Agnese!
I'll keep these guys busy!
Index-san?!
Orsola Aquinas?
Thank goodness you're safe.
Why are you here?
Did you not want to escape The Queen's Fleet?
Don't you know what you're getting yourself into?!
Once we understood the situation at
hand, not one person wished to flee.
They did not wish to leave you as a sacrifice and run away.
That's not right.
You remember what I did for The Book of the Law, don't you?
How can you just save me after everything we've been through?!
I, myself, do not know why.
But Lucia and Angelene-san swore to save you.
Even in the midst of a desperate situation,
and even when they had an infinite number of blades pointing at them.
They wanted to save you.
Is that not enough of a reason?
It's no use, Sister Agnese.
Even if you die here, the operation will go on as planned.
But finding another compatible person is such a tedious task.
And I really hate things that are tedious.
That blood...
I said I hate tedious things.
So I crushed him in the quickest manner possible.
I'd rather not have to do it again here.
I can't have you hurt for our plan.
The anti-Venice large-scale spell...
Why are you activating it now?
We're not trying to use the anti-government attack.
It's something beyond that.
The Queen of the Adriatic Sea is a spell
made only to be used against Venice.
No matter how compelling it seems, if we can't
undo the lock-on limitation, then it has no point.
Then why...
It seems you've realized.
We're undoing the lock-on limitation
of The Queen of the Adriatic Sea.
That's what The Appointed Time of the Rosary is for.
Are you saying that you plan to destroy all cities that are in your way?
The Queen of the Adriatic Sea destroys
everything connected to the city!
What do you think would happen if we aimed
it at the city where the enemy kingdom lies?
Academy City?!
All kinds of science are connected to Academy City's technology.
If we destroy it, we can destroy everything that has to
do with the other half of the world in a single night!
Do you think that will make everyone happy?
Not at all.
I know that there are evildoers on the magic side.
But they can continue whatever they were doing.
Eventually, all those impurities will be eliminated.
Do you—
That's what the Roman Catholic Church wishes for.
The cross is the way of repentance!
Just stop, Sister Orsola.
The burden of the cross chastises the proud!
Now then, we're ahead of schedule, but
how about we start this, Sister Agnese?
Rejoice!
You will go down in history as the one who eradicated
the largest number of enemies to Christianity in history!
Those "enemies" you speak of...
They include Agnese, don't they?
You fear because you now belong to the Church of England.
You really can't act on anything but suspicion, can you?
You don't understand what it means to act on hope.
Or, though you do understand, you cannot bring yourself to believe it.
Please move.
There's no way you can stop Biagio.
If you don't stand up to him you can make it out of here alive.
I can't do that!
This is the end, Sister Orsola.
Too bad, Sister Agnese.
Both your dreams are about to be crushed.
What is the meaning of this?
All things correspond with each other.
Of the five elements, one of the fifth.
The symbol of peace and order.
Expand the Bishop's Staff!
Sister Agnese!
I asked you what the meaning of this was!
What do you think?
I'm probably wrong.
I'm wrong to want to continue taking care of
Sister Lucia, Sister Angelene, and the rest.
When I think of all the Sisters who are out
there, fighting because of your stupid order...
It makes my blood boil.
Don't speak as if you're so high and mighty, you sinner!
Simon bears the cross of the Son of God!
If my memory serves correctly, the Son of God did not
have the strength to carry the cross himself.
Simon carried it up the hill for the execution instead!
Am I wrong?
You realized it?
The true form of this attack is in
making the enemy bear a heavy weight!
You focus the weight of all the personnel and
equipment here onto one point and turn it into weight.
Something like that, right?
That weak hand of yours can't do anything.
You're going to need a stronger hand.
Really?
Then how about this right hand?
Why, you...
You pagan monkey!
Next time, at least make sure I'm dead.
My right hand isn't as easy to beat as you think!
Too slow!
Like that'd work on me twice!
Agnese.
Yes?
Thank you.
If you hadn't protected Orsola, things would have gotten a lot worse.
Oh...
So, how do we go about destroying
The Queen of the Adriatic Sea entirely?
Well, this room can't be changed.
If we completely destroy its functions, they can never reconstruct—
Agnese!
Agnese! What's wrong?!
The Appointed Time of the Rosary...
Is that...
He's activated it and has done something to Agnese!
I can't use it without proper adjustments.
But I have all the power I need right here.
The Roman Catholic Church feared that the
weapon might be stolen and turned against us,
so all those restrictions and limits were put into place.
So if it ever did fall into the hands of the enemy,
what do you think their last resort would be?
A self-destruct?
This is a large-scale magical tool supported
alchemically by this entire fleet of sinners.
Don't go thinking that simply destroying the walls or floors can stop it.
With the sheer amount of magic in here, the
explosion will be at least 10 kilometers wide...
There will be casualties on land, too!
Agnese!
Orsola, take Agnese and get out of here!
Get the Amakusa people to leave, too!
But what about you?
I have to stop him.
I promise I'll meet up with you later.
Just go, Orsola!
But...
It's a promise!
That bastard...
"Carve your name into Roman Catholic history," my ass!
I told him it was too early for a plan like this!
I'm done for.
So you're going to take down everything with you?
In the end all you want to do is console yourself!
Nobody wouldn't feel that this situation is dangerous!
This is the ultimate will of the Roman Catholic Church.
Anyone would agree with my decision.
This is the last flower that will bloom in my life.
I will gladly destroy the coast of the Adriatic Sea for that goal.
Biagio!
That look!
That look of persistence is exactly what threatens us!
And that is why I will be sure to destroy you here.
That will be my final legacy to the Roman Catholic Church!
Biagio!
The cross is the way of repentance!
The burden of the cross chastises the proud!
Is Sister Agnese such a great prize for all this?
There is no longer any safe harbor for that woman.
Why don't you understand that, you pagan monkey?!
Who needs to understand that?!
Who'd accept that?!
The cross is the way of repentance!
Biagio!
His left hand?!
He used my own attack?!
Of course I'll fight.
If you dare lay a finger on Agnese again,
I'll beat you down to a pulp.
Hey, Touma!
Have you come to?
The Adriatic Sea isn't all that cold, huh?
Why do you look so happy?
Is it because I didn't abandon you this time?
I-It's not like I'm happy or anything...
You have a phone call, Touma.
Come back to Academy City right now.
It would be troublesome for other
facilities to be poking around your body.
There should be a supersonic jet sitting
around in the Academy City airport.
But I haven't even been in Italy for a whole day—
Oh, right!
Some girl came looking for you earlier and left a message.
"When you get back, be prepared for
the penalty game from the Daihaseisai."
Misaka Mikoto?!
Wai— Let go of me!
I don't want to go back!
I see.
Thanks for your help.
And you should really ask the Amakusa people
rather than me if you want a debriefing.
hitori de ii to tsubuyaita toaru sekai no chuushin de
In the center of a certain world, I whispered "I'm okay by myself"
I'm no longer associated with the Amakusa Church...
tokei no hari wo orimagete hitomi tojiteta
I closed my eyes as the hands of the clock turned
True as that is, you sure dragged Kami-yan
into a lot of trouble again, Nee-chin.
At this point, even serving him as his personal maid
for a whole day wouldn't be enough to cover it!
sugisatta toki wa modosenai kedo
We can't bring back the past
Oh, hey, why don't I lend you the fallen
angel maid battle costume I have?
You can use that as your battle outfit!
ano hi oshietekureta yo ne
But you told me that day
What kind of ridiculous crap are you talking about?
sore de iin da to
"It's okay this way"
And why do you have something like that anyway?!
You're one of only 20 Saints in the
world. I'm sure you're prepared for—
meguri meguru kisetsu ni kimi ga ita kiseki
In the passing seasons, with the miracle of you being there for me
kowareteta tokei sae ugokidasu kara
Even the broken clock begins to move again
ima wa sou muryoku na garakuta dakedo
And though I may not be powerful now
fushigi da ne kaerareru sonna ki ga suru
It's strange how I feel that I can go back
L-Like this, Touma...
kimi no koe ga ima mo mada koko ni aru kara
Even now, I can still hear your voice right next to me
I-I'm back.
I accidentally picked up more luggage on the way back.
But that was a bit rushed.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Do you understand who it is you're running your mouth off at?
The Pope.
What of it?
If you treat me badly, you're going to die!
The Right Seat of God...
The title of Pope means nothing to you, does it?
Read this and sign it.
You're giving me an order?
W-Wait, this document is...
You were planning on issuing the order yourself at some point, no?
Kmaijou Touma. Investigate this individual immediately.
If he is confirmed as an enemy of God, eliminate him.
Next Episode
Autumn quietly arrives in Academy City.
One promise destroys those peaceful days.
What's transpiring?
Next time: "Penalty Game."
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!