Kihara Amata of Hound Dog defeats Accelerator.
His goal was to retrieve Last Order.
Accelerator allows Last Order to escape,
but has no means of fighting back.
That's when...
What do you think you're doing?
#20 Hound Dog
Hunting Dog Unit
What should we do?
What else?
Make her disappear.
Drive.
You're going to die if you don't get to a hospital soon.
What the hell are you doing?
Shoot him!
Don't make a fuss.
And you, just keep going straight.
We both don't have much time.
Wh-Where should we go?
I know a good doctor.
Ahh, man.
Bring that thing over!
Give it here!
Come on.
Being in a car is like having a big sign saying you can't control wind in there.
See you later, shithead.
Oh come on.
What a nice city.
I was thinking the corruption would move much faster.
Who the hell are you?
Your business rival in hitman services.
Kill her.
You don't consider me a threat, do you?
If you want me to, then get a little better at what you're doing.
Well, it looks like he totally blew me off.
But can you guys really do as he says?
"He was assaulted by them," says MISAKA says MISAKA stating the truth.
But didn't your friend do all this?
"That's very unlikely."
"He's short-tempered and really likes to fight."
"So I don't think he would leave such a small mess behind,"
says MISAKA says MISAKA attempting some simple extrapolation.
We have to call the police—
"They're here!" reports MISAKA reports MISAKA hiding herself behind the car.
Who are they?
Oh, what's this?
It's a scent sensor.
That's how we track our targets.
So it's a police dog machine.
But man, it's too quiet.
Don't tell me this is another detail Kihara decided to include.
And why the hell were you there?
I came back to return something.
Here, the newest in hygienic toiletries!
Are you stupid?
That's disposable.
"And the duckling that everyone kept calling ugly was actually a sexy swan."
"The end."
Hey, what does "sexy" mean?
That's not how The Ugly Duckling goes.
Then how does it go?
What was it, anyway?
According to that brat, it was something like the little swan was really happy
when he found out the truth that he can't join the ducklings' social circle even if he wanted to.
Is "that brat" the person you were looking for?
The one I'm still looking for.
You two got separated again?
Yeah.
That's why I have to say bye to you now.
I'll look for her with you!
I can tell it's a problem for you.
Touma would say the same thing.
Stop here.
There's a huge hospital around here.
Go there, and look for the frog-faced doctor.
Tell him to prepare a battery for the MISAKA Network connection terminal.
He'll know what I mean.
Okay!
A battery for the MISAKA Network connection terminal.
Please wait here.
I wouldn't like it if you went off without me.
Fine, just go.
Keep moving.
You still won't let me go?
Do you want to live or die?
Still alive, Last Order?!
Crap, it's closed.
"This might do something about it."
Let's go somewhere with a lot of people.
They wouldn't want to cause a ruckus.
"I wonder if this can really save him," says MISAKA says MISAKA lamenting her lack of power.
I dunno, but...
If we don't survive first, we'll never save him.
If you want to save him, make sure you don't die first.
"Okay," says MISAKA says MISAKA nodding in agreement.
All right, then. Let's go.
What's going on?
Let's head outside—
What sort of business do you have calling me this late?
We have trouble. Big trouble.
I have the general idea of things from the little sister MISAKA.
Apparently there's information transfer going on in their network right now.
Then I don't need to explain.
Where's that brat?
It seems like she's being chased by another Hound Dog squad.
Apparently she's with an ordinary person she happened to run into.
Where?
She doesn't seem to know herself.
Did a brat wearing a white sister outfit come your way?
Why does she know about your alternative calculation?
That's none of your business.
Just keep her there.
Good grief.
How far are you planning to go with this?
I'll kill Kihara.
I'll crush Hound Dog.
And I'll save that brat without a scratch on her.
Impossible.
You have too many objectives in your current situation.
You won't be able to achieve them all.
You're a doctor, what the hell do you—
I've seen hell, places far worse than you know.
That's why I can say these things, Accelerator.
Don't shoot for the targets you can't hit.
Just make Last Order's safety your top priority.
If you bring her to me alive I will cure her, no questions asked.
Making sure that happens is what a doctor is about.
Fair enough.
Must be God's Right Seat.
I didn't think they'd go this far.
Yomikawa to HQ.
Requesting details on Call 334.
This woman...
What... the...
Resource Recycling Center Number 3.
The target's scent leads inside.
This has to be it.
If you want to go home safely, you'd better stay calm.
A cleaning product...?
Found it.
I guess I'll wipe my scent then get out of here.
Shit.
They're faster than I thought.
They only have small ones?
Onee-sama!
What do you want, Kuroko?
I'm going to be home late because of some Judgment work.
Could you let that annoying dorm mistress know for me?
It's way past curf—
Um, I'm actually out at the convenience store.
I didn't think Onee-sama would be out as well...
We're going to get minus points for sure now.
I wonder why Misaka-san is out past curfew tonight.
D-Don't tell me...
Onee-sama is out on an evening date with that monkey bastard?!
Damn it!
He's got good taste, I'll give him that; asking her out to see the rain this evening.
There's no other choice.
It is my duty to protect Onee-sama's chastity!
You can't.
There's still a mountain of paperwork we haven't finished yet.
What the hell is going on?
Why aren't they coming?
Hi!
Did I surprise you?
There's no need to be scared, just come on out.
I have other work I need to do, you know.
So, if you don't listen to me,
I'm gonna beat you to a pulp!
Who the hell are you?
One from God's Right Seat, Vento of the Front.
Target acquired.
Now then, Kamijou Touma, I'm gonna kill you!
Rod, what's the scent sensor saying?
Hang on, it's still analyzing.
Come on, there's no reason to be scared.
I won't give you the chance to feel any pain.
Find somewhere to hide, Last Order!
So that's the infamous right hand of yours.
Good job keeping up with me!
From above?
This is so much fun!
I see, I see!
Just like the reports state, that right hand of yours is extraordinary!
My favorite "attack from all directions" is totally ineffective!
Favorite?
Alas, I don't understand a thing about it.
Well, let's try this then.
You bitch!
Hmm. I see, I see.
My bad!
I guess I can't finish you off painlessly.
So, if you truly wish to be happy, try becoming a masochist.
Why have those attacks not come from the same direction as her hammer swing?
Could it be...
that cross?!
Oh, man! You found out?
Shit!
Okay, this is starting to get bothersome.
Run!
Go! Please!
Find someone who can help!
Forget it!
That's pretty cold.
How could you make a little girl run around the streets at night?
Wouldn't it be better if you two died together?
She'll be fine once I go after her.
That's why I'm not going to die here.
That sounds fun.
But do you really think you'll say the same thing after I turn your guts into human juice?
Well, whatever. You're my only target.
And I can't thank you enough for deciding not to run away!
Y-You've gotta be kidding me...
"Kidding you"? I guess so.
It's a new routine.
What a shame.
Don't you know who you were messing with?
Well aren't you the kind one.
But do you really have time to be watching out for others?
You bitch!
What are you going to do now that you're mad?
Surely you know what kind of situation Academy City is in.
You need to realize your own worth.
My objective is you, Kamijou Touma.
Anything else is just extra.
Even that Index is insignificant compared to you.
Right now, you are unquestionably an enemy of the Roman Catholic Church.
And we use any means necessary to defeat our enemies.
Even if it means the eradication of all of Japan.
As you can see, the Pope himself signed it.
What are you talking about?
You think I'm joking?
I'll start by killing everyone in this store, then!
Stop!
Let's do this!
Vera here. Requesting an update.
Over.
Damn it!
Nancy?!
Shit...
What?
Is this a side effect of her magic?
Hey, Shirai-san!
Which bento do you want?
There's chop suey and there's fish bento.
Right now, that monkey and Onee-sama are strolling through the evening streets...
Oh, the variety show I always watch is about to start!
TV, TV...
I don't care!
We're getting reports of intruder riots in Academy City.
Various locations within the city have suffered widespread damage.
Oh, we're getting the video now.
Please standby
Did they just say there's an intruder?
The intruder must be really powerful, taking out Anti-skill members alone...
If the situation worsens, an assistance request would be sent by Anti-skill.
Until then, we can only handle the paperwork as best we can.
Uiharu?
That should take care of any scent traces I left.
There you are.
H-Help me! That's the guy that did it!
Sucks to be you, I'm saved now!
Your days of protecting that little brat are over now!
What the...
Wait! Stop, please, Accelerator!
Help m—
S-Step away from that man!
This is one bizarre scene.
I see.
So this is how they plan to attack Academy City.
They're going to skewer everyone while they're paralyzed.
This is pretty bad.
Aiho!
We've compared evidence from the crime scene at District 5 with the one from the databanks,
and are releasing a search order for this person on charges of attempted murder.
Next Episode
People are collapsing one after another.
Accelerator notices the strange events occurring in Academy City.
And a huge pair of wings soars through the heavens.
No way, is that...
Next time: "Testament."
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!