What are you trying to make me do?
You're gonna help me with a job.
A job?
I refuse.
You’re fine with something happening
to Keith Flick?
Leave me alone.
Fine, but if he dies...
I’ll go after Yuna next.
Don't mock me!
If you don’t accept,
then I’ll kill Canopus.
He'll die in four days anyway
if you leave him be.
Next is Yuna.
Then Lily Hoshina. Her family.
Everyone you know will die.
Koku.
I’m going to have you kill God.
God?
A symbol that anyone can imagine.
The details of the operation are in there.
We're going to assign you some people,
and you'll have to eliminate them
within 48 hours.
Get it done and we'll release Keith Flick.
You don't, we reset the timer.
We'll kill someone else.
For example...
Scary.
Even if you kill us, you can't save Yuna.
It's your role to save her. Always.
What’s wrong? Aren’t you going to kill me?
Oh Canon of Jaula Blanca,
may you swing down your blade.
I've been prepared since that day
I sent out those orders for the raid.
But I shall not become ash.
What should I do?
He hasn't changed.
I told you, didn't I?
Reality won't hit him
until he kills someone first.
He's mocking us.
You're soft and weak...
In the end...
you'll throw us away.
Your Majesty!
Please explain!
You have to explain to us!
Take responsibility!
Stop human experiments!
Don't run away!
Where’s Zachary?
The thing is, there's still nothing.
Not even a declaration of crime
or a demand for a ransom.
There wouldn't be.
If that thing
is a Jaula Blanca child, that is.
Vengeance, is it?
Your Highness.
Go.
The people, no,
the world is becoming aware.
Perhaps it's time
we put in a more advanced system.
This country was in ruins,
and recovered thanks to Zachary
and Dr. Albert Ross' achievements.
You should know that.
But...
Sudden changes will provoke chaos.
I'm saying that I need time.
However...
That coup d'etat commotion the other day.
You're the one who sparked it, right?
Gilbert Ross running wild and the Reggie
becoming history are both facts.
Knowing everything that I know,
I don't plan to deny any of your actions.
But it’s also true that the fear
the Reggies create
maintains the authority
of the Royal Palace.
That's a convenient interpretation.
By being persistent, it's also possible
that it would put the nation
in a tough spot.
It's fine already.
Make it a reality in your generation.
It's a future that's not too far away.
But for now, it's my country.
That's true.
What?
Your Highness.
Zachary has been found.
We're broadcasting live
where Senator Zachary's body was found.
Killer B, who has been laying low
for a while, left a mark at the scene.
There are also people voicing their fears
regarding the dangers
of the serial murders starting again.
Look at this.
There's been an unconfirmed witness report
that the victim was attacked
by a monster with wings.
Mother of God.
They even uploaded images of the body.
It got leaked.
Mario, Boris, come with me.
I'll talk to the boss.
-Roger.
-Got it.
Kaela, Bran. Look into
where they got the information from.
Illegal sources okay?
I'll leave it to you!
Lily! Please find Keith!
Only you would know. Please!
Ah, y-yes!
And this one.
Bran! I'm headed to my cubicle,
so take over.
Got it!
Hold on.
What’s the security code?
My measurements!
Still the same?
Gained two cm. on my waist!
Too much booze and carbs.
Currently constipated!
Is there a problem?
Everything is under control.
Please do not worry.
Otherwise, how were things
on your end?
He turned me down.
He won't accept the harsh truth
of moving on from the past.
I see.
We’re proceeding as planned.
We can't wait any longer.
We need to begin the second generation
research as soon as possible.
I got intel that the Eastern powers will
invest heavily for the Canon Project.
That land is the Tiger of the East.
If we hesitate, they'll soon catch up...
and all of our interests
will be monopolized.
We can't waste any time.
It seems so.
That was close.
Getting dehydrated...
At best I've got 12 more hours.
Huh?
Rain?
I see, so it comes up to even here, huh.
Are you sure about this?
Going to the public
when a killer is still out there.
I'm prepared to face death
every time I appear in public.
I'll always live as a proud King
and die as such.
That's a monarch's fate.
I learned that from my father,
who ruled before me.
Your Majesty.
What’s going on?
A trespasser inside the palace.
We believe it’s the same thing
that attacked Sir Zachary.
Impossible! From where?
We must take you to a safe place.
Let’s go.
No.
We're going to proceed as is.
I understand how you feel,
but the attendees are in danger.
We must suspend the ceremony
and evacuate everyone.
Your Highness, you should go
to a safe place as well.
Your Majesty!
Is it a bomb?
Come with me.
What?
Until a certain issue is resolved,
I'm going to have you hide.
If you obey me calmly,
I will ensure your safety.
Y-You’re telling me to believe you?
The one who killed Zachary?
It wasn't me!
It's too bad,
but Kirisame was right, huh?
It seems you're not determined
to join our side.
What are you talking about?
The plan is already in motion.
We don't have time,
so we'll force things forward.
Why are you protecting him?
Kirisame ordered you
to kill him, right?
As expected, it was just like you said.
Yes, I understand.
No problem, I'll do it myself.
Koku.
You're...
No need to go after him.
Subtitle translation by: Katie Kuyama