You were alive after all.
So you know who I am.
Kirisame.
Is the increase in Reggie deaths
in the last few days your doing?
We’ve been given an order to dispose
all Reggies for restructuring.
From where?
I got it. Fine.
Troublesome as ever.
And?
What is it this time?
Can I assume that I’m still worth using?
You really are interesting.
Mhm, I get that a lot.
I appreciate your hard work.
Thanks a lot.
It's true that I was the one
who left signs only you could understand
everywhere you went.
There's no way that Gilbert
in his last stages
could've made such an intricate design.
It was an incredibly
good piece of work, Kirisame.
Keith Kazama.
I’ve been meaning to ask you.
Why do you always show up
even when you know it's a trap?
Call it curiosity.
Those who kill God are to become devils.
Those who kill devils are to become Kings.
Hey, what do you think?
Am I the one being fooled by the stone?
Or is it you guys?
HANDGUN SUICIDE OF A MAN
WHO LOST HIS SANITY
THE WAY THE BLOOD SPLATTERED
TWO BULLET HOLES
THERE WAS ONE MORE PERSON HERE
THAT PERSON SHOT AND KILLED THE MAN
FAINTLY SEEN DISORDERLY FOOTSTEPS
ESTIMATING THE POLICE WOULD RETREAT,
AND KEITH ARRIVED.
THEY TOOK HIM
This was a trap.
Koku?
A little more to the right. To the right.
Yeah, yeah. Okay. All right.
No, no.
If you limit us, we can't investigate.
-It's our job.
-Can you take prints here and here?
How troublesome.
It can't be helped.
We need a special permit to perform
an autopsy on the Royal Family.
Then let's get one.
They won't give it to us.
We can't investigate
without knowing the victim’s situation.
What’s the cause of death?
The weapon?
How and what
are we supposed to be investigating?
Boris.
Don't you think it's strange?
Enough already. We can't work like this!
Our job is to remain right here.
Indeed. And after this,
there's an official announcement
from the Royal Bureau.
Any word from Lily?
None.
No scheduled contact either?
That's the usual, isn't it?
RCC is the standard.
Report, Communicate, Consult.
-Shut up, shut up, shut up...
-You youngins.
-Shut up, shut up...
-What do I do with you?
Huh?
So you're saying
there’s a possibility that Keith
was kidnapped by this Kirisame.
Is that right?
Yes.
I'm wondering.
Yes?
I think Keith wanted to get kidnapped.
He knew that this would happen
and still went there.
What for?
I don't know yet.
But he was looking into something
and found the "answer" as he calls it.
And he headed out to the scene
for his "confirmation" like always.
Knowing it was possible he could
be kidnapped during his "confirmation."
He should've said something.
He says useless stuff
like he needs to poop or has diarrhea
or constipation, but never tells me
the important things.
Lily?
That guy never believes anything
unless he sees it himself.
He’s smart, but he has
the mentality of a child.
His personality is like
a nasty and stupid fifth grader.
No, third grader!
Seriously, I hope he gets
his guts eaten clean and dies!
Your vocabulary for slander is impressive.
Anyway, we have no choice
but to follow the traces.
It's not moldy.
Just as I thought, it's here.
For now, let’s look around
and take things with us.
Got it.
Hey, take a look at this.
Is this you, Koku?
Ah, yes.
So cute.
That's Yuna, right?
That's Kirisame.
I wonder what this Kirisame wants to do?
There's no meaning to any of this.
He's only making a big fuss.
If he wants to kill the King,
he should just do it.
I don’t get why he's bringing
you and Keith into this.
He’s just adding in extra elements.
He’s endangering his own plan.
I don't get it at all.
I don't think the King’s life
is his objective.
I think his aim
is to make me kill the King.
It'd be nice if we could find some clues.
Hey Koku.
What is it?
What's that?
Lily, go!
Go faster!
Flooring it as we speak!
Thy form,
it flutters like a startled swan.
Thy beauty,
is as graceful as a playful dragon.
The autumn chrysanthemums of glory...
the bounding spring pines
as reminiscence,
thou art the hidden moon
of the light clouds.
As a flutter, thou art the swirling snow
of the flowing wind.
What should we do now?
Stick to the plan.
Hi.
Who's this?
It's been a while.
How’s the leg?
Seriously, who is that?
I've gotten quite used to it.
I'm glad.
The size is quite different,
so it's hard to find matching shoes.
Well whatever. We don't have time.
Let's go before they catch onto us.
Yeah.
Seriously. Who's this?
Well then, right this way.
Yuna!
Lily.
Thank God. You were safe.
Yes. I'm relieved
that you're safe too, Lily.
Ah, you’re so cute! You're so cute!
You're too good for Koku!
-Good girl, good girl, good girl!
-U-Um, please let me go.
Hey, what is this place?
It's the office we Market Makers
were using.
We won't have to worry
about Kirisame finding us here.
I see.
I think it's about time
we confirm the luggage that we collected.
No freaking way!
Wait a second. How are you alive?
I mean, alive and well, Your Majesty.
Wait, what do you even say
in a situation like this?
-Please calm down.
-I-I'll calm down.
Why did you save me?
The person who ordered the raid
on Jaula Blanca...
was me.
That's right. This is a good opportunity.
I wanted to ask you.
Why?
Dr. Kazama didn't tell you anything?
There's no point in hiding it.
This is something
I heard directly from him.
From Dr. Kazama?
Everything started
when you children were born.
Your body cells can reset and regenerate.
And instantly as well.
That can become a panacea.
But you can only transplant them
to your kind.
If we tried with anyone else, their cells
would turn cancerous within minutes.
It's a safety mechanism
to protect you and your kind.
But there's a key to cancel this effect.
A neutral-bodied Canon
who has met a special condition.
By choosing you, that Canon
will transform into a female.
She will then turn into a key
to cancel you out.
It'll be possible to transplant
the multiplied cells
of the next generation to us humans.
Moreover, the blood will drive us forever.
There'll be no need
to consider compatibility,
and regenerative medicine within minutes
will become possible.
Everything will change.
It's like a dream.
Nearly all diseases could be treated.
Enormous interest will occur from this.
A generation where only the rich
can buy their lifespan is coming.
If it was just lives, it'd be fine.
But your cells can even conquer time.
A semi-eternal life
wouldn't be impossible either.
God's rights can be bought with money.
A dispute over that interest
is unimaginable.
This country just recovered
from being a burnt field.
And it has no military power.
You couldn't develop decent weapons
under the Defeated Country Clause.
Therefore, you used human weapons
called Reggies.
Reggies are a necessary evil.
Canons are overkill.
So that's your conclusion?
If you disposed of us,
then there'd be no conflict.
All in the name of national ethics.
That’s why you ordered the raid?
You tried to protect what you needed to.
But...
You didn't acknowledge that
we are also alive just like you.
A one-sided justice. That may be true.
But what you did was simply murder.
May sentience reincarnate
and be born from the six paths,
and may the wheels be endless.
At this point, it's already too late
to atone for my sins,
but please allow me to help you.
After that, I'll leave my life
in your hands once again.
Where's Keith?
What about inside the Royal Palace?
I think he would have a trump card
up his sleeve in times of emergencies.
I had the same idea,
but didn't find any signs of that.
Somewhere they won't need to keep nearby,
yet can't be easily snatched away.
They have their own domain.
Most likely.
How about the Amo District?
This area's managed by the military.
Since it’s used for military exercises,
it’s off limits for anybody else.
There’s no one there.
It’s like a natural prison.
Sounds like the place to be.
All of you don't understand
Kirisame at all.
What do you mean?
The man is a romantic for logic.
Double standard.
You can't think so straight.
What kind of fierce insinuation is that?
Sheesh.
Why am I surrounded by all these weirdos?
-Yuna, you're my only ray of hope--
-Lily.
Kirisame wanted to make
Koku commit the assassinations.
Oh.
Now I get it.
He's not simply confining Keith.
There's meaning to having Koku join in.
He's our King.
Kirisame believed in Jet Black
more than anyone else.
How many ancient ruins exist?
There's a lot.
There's no time to go to each one.
We have to narrow them down.
Then, shouldn't it be a place where it has
the deepest connection
to the Black-winged King?
Kazan.
He said he was having him rest
in a special place.
A good place.
Near the ocean,
and a paradise if he had wings.
A paradise?
That's what he said.
The Four Towers built to protect
Jet Black's North, South, East, and West.
I heard it was a holy place connected
to the Black-winged King.
What about there?
Subtitle translation by: Katie Kuyama