You... cowards!
Just shut up!
And bet everything you have on me!
What you need is a dog's training, not a man's education.
Then my decision is made.
The Reconnaissance Legion has gained custody of Eren.
They now begin preparations for the expedition beyond the walls.
O, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
O, my friend!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel...
We will kill-
The enemy is huge...
We will jump-
In our hands we hold blades of glory
We sing of victory
On our backs we have wings of freedom
We put our iron determination into our hearts
We slash apart the circle of idiocy
We fly through the endless blue
on wings of freedom
the eotena onslaught
Special Ops Squad
The Night Before the Counterattack ( 2 )
Trost
Former Reconnaissance Legion Headquarters
This is our old HQ.
It was originally an ancient castle; we just repurposed it.
It's nothing if not imposing.
But being so far from any rivers or the Walls,
it was never very useful to us.
The Legion established itself here just after its formation,
when ideals were its only asset.
But to think we'd wind up using this huge piece of frippery
as a hiding place for you.
Don't get cocky, new kid.
Sir?
I don't care if you are an Eoten.
I can't believe Captain Levi would actually give a brat like you—
If you don't want to bite your tongue, don't give lectures from horseback!
But first impressions are important.
That new kid practically pissed his pants.
Probably from sheer shock at your stupidity.
Irregardless, I accomplished my goal.
Y'know, you haven't always talked like this, have you?
Do...
Do you seriously think it makes you sound like Captain Levi?
Please, just stop.
Trust me, you're not him.
Trying to trammel my wild spirit, Petra?
Funny, I don't remember you being my wife.
Now I really wish you'd just bled to death.
Making yourself sound like some kind of Eotena-slaying hero...
Don't worry.
I bragged about the rest of you, too.
Those people are members of the Reconnaissance Legion's Special Operations Squad.
Also known as Squad Levi.
You're such a loser!
Petra Rall.
Eotenes kills, ten.
Assists, forty-eight.
Orlo Bossard.
Kills, thirty-nine.
Assists, nine.
They're the best by any standard.
Elad Gin.
Kills, fourteen.
Assists, thirty-two.
Gunther Schultz.
Kills, seven.
Assists, forty.
They're the cream of the Legion,
hand-picked by Captain Levi.
And...
If I lose control, they'll be the ones who kill me.
Just look at all these weeds.
What a mess.
This place has been neglected for years.
It's probably full of dust, too.
That cannot be tolerated.
We must begin posthaste.
I've finished cleaning the upper floor.
Which are my quarters?
You sleep in the basement.
The basement again?
Naturally.
You've yet to master yourself.
Underground, you're more easily containable if you transform while half-asleep.
That control was one of the conditions of your coming here.
This is a rule you'll have to follow.
I'll inspect your work.
Eren, take over here.
Yes, sir.
Disillusionment setting in, Eren?
Excuse me?
Oh, I'll just call you Eren, like Captain Levi does.
Here, he sets all the rules.
Sure, I don't mind.
But did I really look so, uh, disappointed?
It's a totally normal reaction.
Not exactly the inspiring hero of legend, is he?
The real Captain Levi
is short, irritable, and prone to violence. Honestly, he's kind of a bully.
No, what surprised me was how rigidly
he seemed to adhere to the letter of his orders.
You assumed his power and fame
must mean he was more of a free spirit?
Yes.
I figured he wouldn't let anyone boss him around.
This is all secondhand,
but I've heard that he may have been exactly like that in the past.
Before he joined the Legion,
he was an infamous thug in the Capital's underworld.
Why would someone like that...
No clue.
I'm not sure how it happened,
but I've heard Captain Elwin adopted him into the Legion.
Captain Elwin?
Hey! Eren!
Y-Yes, sir!
Your cleaning sucks ass.
Redo it from scratch.
So in thirty days, we'll sortie beyond the walls to set up resupply stations?
With the new recruits from this year's graduates, too.
If there are any new recruits, that is.
No matter how many people we have, I believe this action is premature.
Eren's current position is very unstable.
We must demonstrate to Central
that he can assist Mankind as quickly as we can.
If we don't, we'll have the Gendarmerie all over us yet aga—
You think I'm going to buy that story, Elwin?
You're sharp as ever, Mike.
Well, not as sharp as you.
I'll let you in on the real plan when the time comes.
We'll be on standby for a few more days.
I hear we're already planning a major expedition beyond the walls for next month.
Not to mention we'll be bringing this year's graduates along, too.
Is that really true, Elad?
That's pretty brutal.
The new troops just went through that Eotena onslaught.
It probably terrified those tenderfoots.
So is it true, Captain?
I'm not the strategist.
But knowing Elwin,
he's got bigger plans than we could imagine.
It is true that the situation has changed.
For a moment, I thought that all our sacrifices in preparing a route to retake Maria
had been in vain.
But now we find an entirely different hope.
I still can't believe it.
What does it actually mean
to turn into an Eoten, Eren?
I don't really remember what happened myself.
I was so desperate, I didn't have time to think.
But the trigger is self-inflicted injury.
I bite my hand like this...
What? How do I know this?
You all know asking him is pointless.
Everything we know is covered in the reports.
Although I'm sure that won't stop her.
She'll toy with you like a cat with a mouse.
Be prepared to die, Eren.
Who?!
Salutations, Squad Levi!
How're you likin' the digs?
You're here early.
I just couldn't hold back any longer!
Commander Hanji?
Your patience was appreciated, Eren.
I'm in charge of probing those two Eotenas we captured in town,
and I'd sure appreciate your help with tomorrow's experiment.
I came to get yer consent.
Experiment?
What exactly would I be doing?
Why naturally—
Something orgasmically amazing!
U-Uh...
Legally, I'm not my own guardian.
I don't have the authority to give consent.
Levi, what's Eren up to tomorrow?
Cleaning the courtyard.
Super-duper!
We're go!
Eren! Tomorrow, you're all mine!
R-Right...
But what do you mean by "experiments" with the Eotenas?
Hmm?
U-Um, what do you mean by...
Hey, knock it off! Don't ask!
I knew it.
I knew you had a healthy, curious adolescent mind...
If you really want it that bad...
Well, that's perfectly natural.
I'll just have to give ya...
The story of the boys we captured.
Wallists ( 1 )
Members of a religious organization proselytizing
within the Walls. They worship the Walls as
incarnations of God and vehemently oppose any
alterations to them, even for defensive purposes.
Wallists ( 1 )
Members of a religious organization proselytizing
within the Walls. They worship the Walls as
incarnations of God and vehemently oppose any
alterations to them, even for defensive purposes.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Wallists ( 2 )
Since Wall Maria's fall, their following has
increased rapidly, as has their influence.
Wallists ( 2 )
Since Wall Maria's fall, their following has
increased rapidly, as has their influence.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
We began with a repeat of the experiments
from the last five successful captures.
Salutations!
First, we assessed the possibility of communication.
Ya feelin' OK?
Got a name?
Doesn't that hurt?
Ma'am! You're too close!
Salutations to you.
Isn't this weather just glorious?
Hungry?
Holycrap!
Holy crap!
Ma'am, it's too dangerous!
Unfortunately, we arrived at our usual conclusion:
communication with the Eotenas is impossible.
But my time with those boys
has been so satisfying, it's like my daily stress has melted away.
Once upon a time,
there lived a tribe that ate human beings.
'Course I'm not talking about you Eotenas.
This was a human tribe.
They hid in a cave deep in the mountains
and waylaid travelers on the road,
purloining their valuables and consuming their flesh.
Looks like it's the usual naming ceremony again.
Yeah, what was it last time?
Chikatilo and Albert.
They kept at this for twenty-five years.
They say that there were well over five hundred victims in all.
I'll bet even you haven't eaten that many humans.
And they were highly imaginative in their cookery.
They made buttocks into steaks.
Cut thighs into chunks for stew.
The tougher flesh they chopped, tenderized, and baked as mincemeat.
Internal organs were ground into blood sausage.
Indeed, they were amazing cooks.
That sets them apart from you.
But that tribe of cannibals made a single fatal mistake, got captured,
and were executed.
Just like you two.
You made the mistake of attacking Mankind,
and you were captured.
And so, I'd like to name you two after the patriarch of that tribe.
You're Sawney.
You're Bean.
But don't worry.
I won't let them execute you.
A pleasure to meet you, Sawney.
You too, Bean.
Let's all be friends.
And so, I dubbed the seven-meter fellow Bean,
and the four-meter one Sawney.
Next, we tried depriving them of sunlight.
We know that Eotenas gradually lose energy as the night progresses.
We wanted to experimentally verify
that sunlight was somehow powering them.
There were major individual discrepancies in their responses.
That'll do, Sawney.
Sleep well.
See ya in the morning.
Once cut off from sunlight, Sawney started to poop out after an hour...
You're quite the night owl, Bean.
Fret not. I'll keep ya company.
But Bean was fine for three hours.
I was blown away once again.
They don't require food or drink.
They have vocal organs, but no need to breathe.
For energy, the sun alone suffices.
I wonder what would happen if we kept them in the dark for an extended period?
A tempting idea, but it just wouldn't do if they died on us.
Tragically, we killed the last couple we caught by mistake.
When we tried out some decapitation,
we took off the backs of their necks, too.
Chikatilo and Albert were their names.
They had such adorable smiles.
I feel really badly about killing them like that.
I never want to feel that way again!
Commander Hanji...
So then! We started ramming 'em raw,
to test their senses of pain!
Calm down, Ma'am! You don't need to scream, too!
Have I not a heart?!
Look at how deeply Bean is suffering.
Bean, don't give up!
It'll only hurt for a moment!
We had to see if the Eotenas had any vulnerabilities
apart from the backs of their necks.
It hurt me more than it hurt them.
Sawney.
Look, I've screwed it straight into your heart.
Doesn't it hurt?
How are you feeling?
Compared to Bean, Sawney was a dead fish.
He rarely responded to anything.
What?
Are you feeling it?
Ma'am, get back!
You were so close, Sawney...
You are seriously gonna die!
Sawney really isn't very good at expressing his feelings.
He just keeps on trying to bite my head off.
Um, Commander Hanji?
How can be so nonchalant about the Eotenas?
I mean to say,
they've all but wiped us out. They're our natural predators.
And you yourself have seen what they can do.
I have indeed.
I've watched the Eotenas devour many, many of my friends.
When I first joined the Legion, I was driven by hatred.
But one day, I had an epiphany.
I had just given this three-meter Eotenes' head a good punt.
The head was light. Super-light.
That Eotenes' body...
Something that size shouldn't even have been able to stand,
let alone walk, on two feet.
That applies to all Eotenas.
I once cut off an arm,
only to find that it didn't weigh anything like what it should've.
I'm told when you transform into an Eoten,
your giant body appears out of thin air.
It is my belief
that Eotenas as we perceive them may be very different
from Eotenas in their natural states.
For decades, we've tried to fight them with the power of hatred and gotten nowhere.
I want to see if I can step outside our normative attitudes and get a fresh perspective on them.
It may be a futile effort.
But I'm going to make it anyways.
Since I joined the Legion, I've had one shock after another.
It's not just Commander Hanji.
Everyone here is weird.
It's like a den of insanity.
That said...
All of the people in the Legion desire change!
Commander Hanji.
Could you tell some more about your experiments?
For serious?
Yes!
I think it's best if I know what to expect for tomorrow's experiment.
G-Got a point...
Right.
There's a lotta stuff I skipped over.
I'll give ya the juicy details.
But it'll take some time.
That's fine!
When we first captured an Eoten, I had the following hypotheses:
...and thus, we failed to glean any new information from these experiments.
I'm guessing you learned everything
I just told you when you were still a trainee.
You remember all that stuff, right?
Yes.
I could never forget.
So let's go over it once more, this time incorporating my own hypotheses.
What?
Um, I'm pretty sure—
First, the Eotenas...
Is Commander Hanji here?
It's the test subjects!
Both Eotenas have been killed!
NOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!
Sawney!
Bean!
Say it ain't so!
How could this happen?!
Those subjects were incredibly valuable.
Was it one of the soldiers?
Probably. We still don't know who killed them.
They were both dispatched before dawn.
By the time the guards noticed anything,
the culprit had escaped using Multiaxial Mobility Gear.
So this was a premeditated attack by two or more people.
Sawney!
Check it out. Hanji's gone bonkers.
What happened here?
Let's go.
This is in the Gendarmerie's jurisdiction now.
R-Right...
What do you see?
What do you think the enemy is?
Forgive me for asking such a strange question.
If we assume that I am not truly who I think I am,
then how can you claim that you are yourself?
A castle of sand guarded your heart, and it fell apart
Can you gather the pieces and repair yourself?
The voices of others calling you
are just a ringing in your ear now
It's like time has stopped
Now, wake up
I want to escape the darkness
I want to flee like a raging storm
We lived like corpses, as though already dead
Let us meet again
outside the walls
where maps reach terra incognita
Preview
The hunt for Sawney and Bean's killers begins.
Meanwhile, Mikasa, Armin, and the other alumni of the 104th Cadet Corps
wrestle with their own demons
as they choose which branch to join.
What Should Be Done
The Night Before the Counterattack ( 3 )