We have no choice.
This is a world of cruelty.
I'll exterminate you... exterminate you...
No.
I'll fucking kill you!
That day, Mankind remembered.
The terror of Their domination.
The horrible ignominy of life in Their birdcage.
Eren!
Eren.
O, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
O, my friend!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel...
We will kill-
The enemy is huge...
We will jump-
In our hands we hold blades of glory
We sing of victory
On our backs we have wings of freedom
We put our iron determination into our hearts
We slash apart the circle of idiocy
We fly through the endless blue
on wings of freedom
the eotena onslaught
The Wall
Raid on Stohess District ( 3 )
Let us pray. O incorruptible Maria! Rose! Sina! O Goddesses Three!
May we keep Ye that Ye may keep us.
Let us doubt not the Holy Walls!
By God's hand incarnate as three graceful Walls of light,
may we now shore Ye up with the buttresses of our faithful devotion.
May we know that an innocent heart, beating for God alone,
is our sole safeguard from the Eotena blight!
That Ye alone are our shield and our sal—
An Eoten?
How can it be here?
No.
Approach not the Walls.
Not the Walls!
Looks like he's retaining control this time.
Yes.
But Eren's never managed to beat the Eoten Fatale.
If he's transformed, he's gotta be rarin' to fight.
He won't let himself be—
Willpower alone isn't enough to win battles.
You know that, Jean!
Defeating Annie will require something far greater.
Level ground!
The Eoten's heading for an open area!
Our Gear is ineffective there!
Split up and circle round to the other side!
Roger!
Faster, faster, faster!
This makes no sense!
What's an Eoten doing here?
Annie...
You always seemed to think this world was so incredibly stupid.
Always detached, bored.
But there were those times when you came alive:
when you showed off your fighting skills.
You said none of it mattered, and yet,
to me, that seemed so far from the truth.
I just figured you were a terrible liar.
Tell me, Annie.
What are you fighting for?
What could justify
murdering so many people?!
What is this?
Ma'am, even if we can capture the Eoten Fatale,
those two'll destroy the whole city first!
We do it nevertheless.
Elwin's already made the decision.
Prepare for capture operations.
Yes, ma'am.
Eren.
No one told me this could happen.
Why's there some Eotena throwdown here?
What's going on?
Eotenas are fighting each other?
They are.
They're wreaking unimaginable destruction!
Troops and civilians alike are taking heavy casualties.
Elwin! Is all this because of your plan?!
It is.
My decisions alone created this situation.
I don't intend to make any excuses.
You must have known what would happen
if you executed this operation inside a city!
How? How could you lead this madness?
I lead...
to Mankind's victory.
Bullshit!
You fucking traitor!
If I shot you down here and now, none of the brass would even give a damn!
Then do it.
But then you'd need to assume command.
You must not let the Eoten Fatale escape.
Paehl's in charge of troop deployment.
Vyler handles supplies.
Work with them to push her towards the eastern Wall at all costs.
W-Wait. Wait!
You—
You really believe
that this will save Mankind?
I believe it is a step in that direction.
Weapons down, all of you.
Put him in irons!
Yes, sir.
Deploy every man.
Top priority is civilian rescue and evacuation!
Yes, sir!
Elwin, I'll leave your punishment to the courts martial.
Once this is over, I'll face them with pleasure.
Levi, you stay put.
You dislike death without meaning.
Yeah, I hate it.
Be it dealt to me or by me.
One unwilling to sacrifice what he holds most dear
can never change this world!
A human must throw aside his humanity
for the sake of fighting monsters!
Annie is surely capable of that sacrifice!
Annie.
Annie!
Annie...
Daddy's here. I alone am on your side.
I'll
exterminate
them!
Every single fucking one of them!
Eren!
That's—
Don't!
We don't know that Eren can recognize you right now.
W-Woah...
Hey!
The Wall!
She means to climb it?!
We've failed!
She's going to get away!
Not on my watch!
Annie.
Fall.
I was wrong.
It's too late to beg your forgiveness.
But...
I have just one...
One request.
You can make the whole world your enemy...
I'll tear down the entire world!
But even if the whole world hates you, remember:
Daddy's here. I alone am on your side!
Not good! He'll eat the girl inside, too!
Eren! Stop!
Eren!
I am... free!
So promise me.
Promise me you'll come home.
What happened?
What the—?
They're fusing?!
Eren!
Don't eat our most important evidence, dumbass.
The Walls ( 1 )
- The year was 784. One blisteringly hot night, a poor miner decided to dig under Wall Sina and start a new life within the inner ring. "Life inside Wall Sina would be pretty swell." This epiphany had come to him suddenly and unbidden a few days before, as his shovel prized at the black chthonic coal. It was almost a sort of divine inspiration. And so the miner spent the next few days wandering along the Wall, finally settling on a spot where the forest pressed it closely. No one would chance upon him, and the forest's thick canopy would conceal him and his task from the prying eyes of the guards above.
The next night, he began. Deftly plying his trusty shovel, the miner broke through the topsoil. The work went smoothly and before long, the pit was as deep as he was tall. Once the diggings became too deep to fling the dirt out from, he began stuffing it into sacks and climbing a ladder to discard it. The miner's dedication to his task was so profound that he took only a very few short breaks to drink water and stretch his weary muscles. He'd spent twenty years of his life digging without a single day of rest, and so the miner trusted his skill implicitly. During his time, he'd learned to dig more deeply, quickly, and efficiently than any other man alive. Earths that would baffle any other digger were no match for his shovel. But this day was different. He dug for hours, yet he never seemed to make any progress. As he excavated he carefully probed either side of the main pit with his shovel, but to no avail.
The Wall's foundations seemed to go down forever, eternally into the earth, blocking his progress at every turn. Still he persevered. No longer was his goal the "swell" life inside Wall Sina. He simply wanted to conquer the Wall. "I swear by all the years I have spent in the earth: I will beat this infernal Wall!" The miner wiped the sweat from his brow and dug on. The hole was a little over four or five times the miner's height when he struck a very hard rock. He wondered if he'd hit bedrock. But this new substance seemed to be of the same material as the Wall's foundation itself. With all his strength, the miner swung his shovel down into the rock. The shovel sparked and shattered... yet the strange rock was unscathed. The miner exhausted miner heaved a sigh, and that weary sigh was deeper than any hole he'd dug in his twenty long years.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
The Walls ( 2 )
"The Wall?" The miner's friend frowned deeply. "Isn't it weird?" the miner said, lifting his drink to his lips. "Who knew that the Wall continued so deep underground?" The miner and his friend sat at their usual table in the back of the seedy tavern. The miner met this friend (in truth, his only friend) like this most days in the evening.
That day, the day after his failed attempt to dig under the Wall, they'd gone there after work as usual. And there the miner told his friend the story, certain that the other man could keep a secret. "Perhaps the Walls encompass us not only above ground, but beneath the Earth itself as well," said the miner. "Tell me, friend... What, exactly, are the Walls?" His friend cut him off with a cough as he glanced around the tavern. The other men there were all busily drinking, harassing the maids, shouting, fighting. Each living his own life. None watching them. But even so, the miner decided to say nothing more about the Walls.
If anyone did hear him, the Gendarmes would be on him in an instant. "Does it really matter?" his friend asked. "Just keep at life as you always have. You may be poor, but you have a steady job and enough money to drink. What more do you need?" "You're right," the miner replied. "I guess this'll do. Back to digging for me. In the end, I guess that's my place in life." But the next day, the miner failed to come to work.
The next day was the same, and the next, and the next. The miner's friend went to his house many times, but saw nor sight nor slot of him. The miner had no relatives, nor any other close friends, and so no one inquired where he might have gone. Unsure what to do, his friend eventually went to the Garrison and told them the whole tale. The next day, the Gendarmerie and the Garrison organized a full-scale search effort. It actually seemed a little excessive for one poor miner, even if that miner was a criminal who'd tried to undermine the Walls. His friend just couldn't understand the soldiers' fanatic desire to find him. But the search party never uncovered any trace of the miner. They couldn't even find the pit he'd dug. And soon enough their only witness was lost as well, for the miner's friend mysteriously vanished... never to be seen again.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Eren.
Mikasa?
Where's Annie?
Fuckshit!
What is this?!
We've come this far, and you still won't say a word, Annie?!
Get out here!
Get out and finish what you started!
Goddamnit! This isn't fair! Annie! Annie!
Stop it.
It's meaningless.
Use your wires to weave a net!
We'll wrap her up and carry her underground.
Yes, ma'am.
If we can't get any information out of Annie, what was the point of all this?
We caused so much death.
And at the end of all that death, we still find more mysteries than answers.
What was it all for?
Operation successful... or not, huh?
It was.
We have ensured the continued survival of the Reconnaissance Legion,
if only by the skin of its teeth.
I hope you're right.
Elwin.
I have several questions about this plan of yours.
If you had a suspect,
why didn't you ask the Gendarmerie for help?
Allow me to explain, Governor.
Given the chance that the Eoten Fatale had allies,
I needed to limit the operation to those I was certain were loyal.
But what about the destruction you wrought in Stohess?
Our best efforts to control damages were not enough.
Please accept our sincere apologies.
You think you can get away with an apology?!
Had we left her alone,
the Walls would surely have been destroyed, and Mankind itself might have perished.
I see.
And after all the casualties this operation caused,
what proof do you have that it forestalled Mankind's extinction?
I can't imagine we'll be able to get anything out of Annie Leonhardt now.
Indeed, I doubt that is possible.
So in other words... this was all for nothing?
Eren.
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah.
I've healed so fast, it's almost creepy.
I hear that Annie's still frozen.
Yeah.
Fuckshit.
That whole massive operation, and nothing to show for it!
She was willing to sacrifice her very self to protect her information.
Yeah, she escaped after all.
Eren's the one who let her go.
Isn't that right, Eren?
In that single moment of hesitation.
Yeah.
You're right.
I couldn't do it.
When I saw Annie, I froze.
Armin Arlart.
Jean Kirschstein.
It's time for your questioning.
Yes, sir.
They're starting with us?
Okay, see you later.
Sure.
It felt so good, you know.
Even as my body was breaking, it felt so good.
I don't think I'd have minded dying.
Eren!
That isn't how I feel now.
You came back.
Thank God.
I just don't get it.
Throwing aside your humanity to fight monsters?
That's the only way to win?
It's one possible path to Mankind's victory over the Eotenas.
I think Eren can follow that path.
So tell me...
Even if he did sacrifice his humanity to destroy every last Eoten,
would that really be a victory for Mankind?
Eat.
The road will not be easy...
But I believe we have gained a tremendous opportunity
to ensure Mankind's survival.
Before this began, we had never even imagined that humans could transform into Eotenas.
Now we've captured one of the enemy—a huge step forward.
Yes, they are out there.
And we will hunt them all down.
Every last Eoten within the Walls.
Now it is our turn for an onslaught!
The royal summons for Eren Jaeger and the Reconnaissance Legion were suspended indefinitely.
If we assume that I am not truly who I think I am,
Annie Leonhardt was remanded to the Legion,
then how can you claim that you are yourself?
which kept her deep underground.
A castle of sand guarded your heart, and it fell apart
However,
much sacrifice and much time remained before Mankind learned
Can you gather the pieces and repair yourself?
The voices of others calling you
what it was that really held us captive...
are just a ringing in your ear now
It's like time has stopped
Now, wake up
I want to escape the darkness
I want to flee like a raging storm
We lived like corpses,
as though already dead
Let us meet again
outside the walls
where maps reach terra incognita
the eotena onslaught