15

天使墜落(Angel Fall)
主角父親偶然發動的大魔術
每次上條刀夜出國出差都會買禮物回來
而且多是為了給兒子祈福的宗教物
久而久之 在家里偶爾形成一個魔法陣(下集講到
影響范圍到達覆蓋整個地球

生命之樹(Sephirothic Tree)
神裂跟土御門的臺詞有講
欲知更詳細資料
可以到http://pign.net/index.php?hl=f5&q=uggc%3A%2F%2Fwn.jvxvcrqvn.bet%2Fjvxv%2F%25R3%2583%2580%25R3%2582%25N2%25R3%2583%2588
參考
或者
http://home.so-net.net.tw/wwlcom/02/list_a/cabala.htm

水喲 化作蛇形 如利劍般突刺(Mem·Teth·Lamed·Zain)
數值 四十·九·三十·七
這裡的數字 全部取自希伯來文的數字
每個數字都有自己的意思
同樣地 這個網站都有介紹
http://home.so-net.net.tw/wwlcom/02/list_a/cabala.htm

俄羅斯成教
魔術側的Top3宗派 以解析跟解決心靈現象為目的

殲滅白書(Annihilatus)
隸屬俄羅斯成教的特殊部隊

Yes We Can
美國新任總統奧巴馬去年在新罕布什爾州的演講neta
演講全文+視頻可以在這裡看到
http://my.barackobama.com/page/community/post_group/ObamaHQ/CGTN
摘錄一下精彩片段(翻譯就免了 大家應該都懂 toka
But in the unlikely story that is America, there has never been
anything false about hope. For when we have faced down impossible
odds; when we've been told that we're not ready, or that we shouldn't
try, or that we can't, generations of Americans have responded with a
simple creed that sums up the spirit of a people.

Yes we can.

It was a creed written into the founding documents that declared the
destiny of a nation.

Yes we can.

It was whispered by slaves and abolitionists as they blazed a trail
toward freedom through the darkest of nights.

Yes we can.

It was sung by immigrants as they struck out from distant shores and
pioneers who pushed westward against an unforgiving wilderness.

Yes we can.

It was the call of workers who organized; women who reached for the
ballot; a President who chose the moon as our new frontier; and a King 
who took us to the mountaintop and pointed the way to the Promised Land.

Yes we can to justice and equality. Yes we can to opportunity and
prosperity. Yes we can heal this nation. Yes we can repair this
world. Yes we can.

And so tomorrow, as we take this campaign South and West; as we learn
that the struggles of the textile worker in Spartanburg are not so
different than the plight of the dishwasher in Las Vegas; that the
hopes of the little girl who goes to a crumbling school in Dillon are
the same as the dreams of the boy who learns on the streets of LA; we
will remember that there is something happening in America; that we
are not as divided as our politics suggests; that we are one people;
we are one nation; and together, we will begin the next great chapter
in America's story with three words that will ring from coast to
coast; from sea to shining sea - Yes. We. Can.

另外 根據這個演講 有愛人士還制作了一個MTV 觀看人數已達6百多萬
在線觀看地址：
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2fZHou18Cdk

R-15
日本的電影觀看分級制度 也就是15X
R是Restricted的縮寫

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

15

天使坠落(Angel Fall)
主角父亲偶然发动的大魔术
每次上条刀夜出国出差都会买礼物回来
而且多是为了给儿子祈福的宗教物
久而久之 在家里偶尔形成一个魔法阵(下集讲到
影响范围到达覆盖整个地球

生命之树(Sephirothic Tree)
神裂跟土御门的台词有讲
欲知更详细资料
可以到http://pign.net/index.php?hl=f5&q=uggc%3A%2F%2Fwn.jvxvcrqvn.bet%2Fjvxv%2F%25R3%2583%2580%25R3%2582%25N2%25R3%2583%2588
参考
或者
http://home.so-net.net.tw/wwlcom/02/list_a/cabala.htm

水哟 化作蛇形 如利剑般突刺(Mem·Teth·Lamed·Zain)
数值 四十·九·三十·七
这里的数字 全部取自希伯来文的数字
每个数字都有自己的意思
同样地 这个网站都有介绍
http://home.so-net.net.tw/wwlcom/02/list_a/cabala.htm

俄罗斯成教
魔术侧的Top3宗派 以解析跟解决心灵现象为目的

歼灭白书(Annihilatus)
隶属俄罗斯成教的特殊部队

Yes We Can
美国新任总统奥巴马去年在新罕布什尔州的演讲neta
演讲全文+视频可以在这里看到
http://my.barackobama.com/page/community/post_group/ObamaHQ/CGTN
摘录一下精彩片段(翻译就免了 大家应该都懂 toka
But in the unlikely story that is America, there has never been
anything false about hope. For when we have faced down impossible
odds; when we've been told that we're not ready, or that we shouldn't
try, or that we can't, generations of Americans have responded with a
simple creed that sums up the spirit of a people.

Yes we can.

It was a creed written into the founding documents that declared the
destiny of a nation.

Yes we can.

It was whispered by slaves and abolitionists as they blazed a trail
toward freedom through the darkest of nights.

Yes we can.

It was sung by immigrants as they struck out from distant shores and
pioneers who pushed westward against an unforgiving wilderness.

Yes we can.

It was the call of workers who organized; women who reached for the
ballot; a President who chose the moon as our new frontier; and a King 
who took us to the mountaintop and pointed the way to the Promised Land.

Yes we can to justice and equality. Yes we can to opportunity and
prosperity. Yes we can heal this nation. Yes we can repair this
world. Yes we can.

And so tomorrow, as we take this campaign South and West; as we learn
that the struggles of the textile worker in Spartanburg are not so
different than the plight of the dishwasher in Las Vegas; that the
hopes of the little girl who goes to a crumbling school in Dillon are
the same as the dreams of the boy who learns on the streets of LA; we
will remember that there is something happening in America; that we
are not as divided as our politics suggests; that we are one people;
we are one nation; and together, we will begin the next great chapter
in America's story with three words that will ring from coast to
coast; from sea to shining sea - Yes. We. Can.

另外 根据这个演讲 有爱人士还制作了一个MTV 观看人数已达6百多万
在线观看地址：
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2fZHou18Cdk

R-15
日本的电影观看分级制度 也就是15X
R是Restricted的缩写