[Script Info]
Title:滑头鬼之孙
Original Script:四魂制作组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Chinese,SIMHEI,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,5,5,8,1
Style: Staff,Microsoft YaHei,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00804000,&H004D2600,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,5,5,8,1
Style: Title,PMingLiU,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,30,1
Style: OP-ED-JP,Microsoft YaHei,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00800040,&H00FF0080,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,5,5,10,1
Style: OP-ED-Ch,Microsoft YaHei,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00A00000,&H00FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,5,5,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.60,0:01:56.60,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}本字幕由四魂製作組(snm.5d6d.com)製作\N僅供交流試看 如喜歡本作品請支持正版
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.60,0:01:56.60,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2\fad(130,130)}翻譯：mushishi；時間：問答無用、橄榄楪；後期：铁碎牙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.64,0:00:28.52,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明日を照らすよSunshine 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.67,0:00:35.55,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}窓から射込む...扉開いて 
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.48,0:00:47.90,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Stop! `cause you got me thinking that I`m a little quicker 
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.91,0:00:50.48,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Go! Maybe the rhythm`s off, but I will never let you 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.49,0:00:53.06,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Know! I wish that you could see it for yourself 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.15,0:00:55.27,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}It`s not, it`s not, just stop, hey y`all! やだ！ 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.35,0:00:57.50,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}I never thought that I would take over it all 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.83,0:00:59.86,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And now I know that there`s no way I could fall 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.99,0:01:02.26,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s on and on and off and on 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.39,0:01:03.92,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And no one gets away 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.10,0:01:08.89,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕の夢は 何処に在るのか？ 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.96,0:01:13.58,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}影も形も見えなくて 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.74,0:01:18.50,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追いかけていた 守るべきもの 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.63,0:01:23.66,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}There`s a sunshine in my mind 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.70,0:01:31.17,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明日を照らすよSunshineどこまでも続く 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.25,0:01:35.85,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}目の前に広がるヒカリの先へ 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.01,0:01:38.16,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}未来のSunshine 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.26,0:01:40.68,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}輝くSunshine 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.80,0:01:42.71,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s hard, just take a chance 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.79,0:01:44.01,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}信じて 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.20,0:01:48.77,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明日も晴れるかな？ 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.64,0:00:28.52,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}照耀明日的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.67,0:00:35.55,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}從窗口透進來...打開門扉吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.48,0:00:47.90,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Stop! `cause you got me thinking that I`m a little quicker
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,PopSub,0000,0000,0000,,// PopSub注释: 下一行不需要检查时间轴 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.91,0:00:50.48,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Go! Maybe the rhythm`s off, but I will never let you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.49,0:00:53.06,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Know! I wish that you could see it for yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.15,0:00:55.27,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}It`s not, it`s not, just stop, hey y`all! やだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.35,0:00:57.50,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}I never thought that I would take over it all
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.83,0:00:59.86,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And now I know that there`s no way I could fall
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.99,0:01:02.26,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s on and on and off and on
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.39,0:01:03.92,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}And no one gets away 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.10,0:01:08.89,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我的夢想在何方？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.96,0:01:13.58,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}無跡可尋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.74,0:01:18.50,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}追尋著守護之物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.63,0:01:23.66,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}There`s a sunshine in my mind
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.70,0:01:31.17,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}照耀明日的陽光連綿不絕
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.25,0:01:35.85,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}奔向眼前放射的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.01,0:01:38.16,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}未來的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.26,0:01:40.68,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}閃耀的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.80,0:01:42.71,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}You know it`s hard, just take a chance
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.79,0:01:44.01,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}請堅信
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.20,0:01:48.77,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}明天也是晴天吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.64,0:22:24.39,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}宵闇に紛れ 摘み去られた花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.48,0:22:33.20,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ひとつの希望も 傷付けさせない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.55,0:22:42.06,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}怖がる心を試すように 竜巻が嘲笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.24,0:22:51.47,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}揺れる吊り橋 繋いだ手と手 歴史を駆け抜ける
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.03,0:23:03.28,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}まっすぐ光る眼差し 教えてくれた 立ち向かう勇気
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.69,0:23:13.73,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}生きとし生けるすべて キミの時代に 奏でるSymphony
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.85,0:23:19.60,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Be Yourself 信じて まだ見ぬ至上の地
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.71,0:23:26.82,OP-ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}キミはキミのままで そう Go Your Way!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.64,0:22:24.39,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}伴隨著黃昏的墜落之花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.48,0:22:33.20,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}守護好唯一的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.55,0:22:42.06,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}宛如試探恐懼的心靈 龍捲風在嘲笑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.24,0:22:51.47,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}搖晃的吊橋 緊握的手 超越了歷史
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.03,0:23:03.28,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}閃耀著直率的目光 給予了我前進的勇氣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.69,0:23:13.73,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}活著的萬物在你的時代演奏Symphony
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.85,0:23:19.60,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Be Yourself 自信 雖未達至頂點
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.71,0:23:26.82,OP-ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你仍然是你 是的 Go Your Way!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.75,0:00:06.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自古以來 人們就對妖怪心存畏懼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.67,0:00:12.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而走在那眾妖之前 統領著百鬼夜行的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.18,0:00:16.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人們稱其為妖怪的總大將
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.38,0:00:18.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抑或是如此稱呼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.97,0:00:21.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魑魅魍魎之主
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.53,0:00:23.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑頭鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.07,0:02:02.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你才配取得天下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.05,0:02:09.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下命令吧 讓我去取他首級
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.44,0:02:12.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了 玉章
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.44,0:02:16.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我成為你的爪牙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.01,0:02:23.10,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,300)}凶犬 咆哮於廢墟之中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.92,0:02:38.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已沒有統領百鬼的能力了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.96,0:02:41.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不覺中 數量就減少到七十一了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.27,0:02:44.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都老了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.62,0:02:45.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.60,0:02:48.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前幾天狒狒掛了 只有七十了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.77,0:02:52.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被一個叫鞭的年輕妖怪幹掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.14,0:02:55.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鞭…鞭？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.06,0:02:57.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是因此而來的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.39,0:03:00.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來你心裡有數呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.81,0:03:02.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那群傻兒子們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.22,0:03:06.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是你的兒子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.06,0:03:12.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉章是我的第八十八個老婆的第八個兒子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.62,0:03:15.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很好地繼承了我的神通之力
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.80,0:03:18.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第…第八十八個老婆？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.38,0:03:20.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你驚訝的地方錯了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.71,0:03:24.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉章就跟我年輕時一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.22,0:03:28.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想憑藉「畏」成為妖怪之主
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.23,0:03:33.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與被稱為「七人同行」的妖怪一起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.23,0:03:36.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「七人同行」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.73,0:03:41.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有個叫犬神的幹部非常危險
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.34,0:03:44.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪犬神
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.54,0:03:50.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是個能利用憎恨來增加自己力量的可怕妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.56,0:03:58.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你對奴良很執著嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.09,0:04:00.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看他不順眼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.08,0:04:05.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明沒什麼實力 卻還繼承了奴良組
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.09,0:04:10.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因如此我才沒要他命 讓他當個花瓶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.87,0:04:12.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太溫和了 玉章
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.96,0:04:18.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱者就得死 這就是四國妖怪的規定 沒錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.40,0:04:20.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨你的便吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.12,0:04:24.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的話一定能秒殺那群護衛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.55,0:04:31.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就去大幹一場了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.17,0:04:35.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.05,0:04:36.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.29,0:04:40.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了玉章 你是什麼都肯做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.51,0:04:41.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.80,0:04:43.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就那麼有魅力嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.94,0:04:45.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對你來說 玉章…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.88,0:04:48.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是玉章改變了我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.94,0:04:53.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓沉睡於我體內的力量覺醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.53,0:04:56.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憎恨的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.10,0:05:02.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬神的內在很醜惡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.99,0:05:05.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是不要去看為好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.00,0:05:09.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又…又是滑頭鬼那張牌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.05,0:05:11.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輸了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.38,0:05:13.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十一連敗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.59,0:05:16.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還連續抽中納豆小僧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.81,0:05:20.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然連續抽中同一張牌 某種意義上很厲害…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.00,0:05:23.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說你們還真是玩不膩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.26,0:05:23.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.97,0:05:29.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡的納豆小僧 你跟我有什麼仇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.47,0:05:30.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一盤？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.92,0:05:32.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求之不得
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.04,0:05:36.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 怎麼又是納豆小僧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.96,0:05:38.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十二連敗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.30,0:05:42.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 竟然跟人類打成一片
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.29,0:05:47.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為何身為妖怪的你會如此受歡迎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.43,0:05:53.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 發現可疑的人了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.67,0:05:56.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛才感覺到了妖氣…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.98,0:05:59.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.98,0:06:00.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.48,0:06:05.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還被小心保護著
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.77,0:06:09.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別人總不能保護你一輩子吧 奴良陸生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.93,0:06:13.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 又輸了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.11,0:06:15.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少主居然也玩不膩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.10,0:06:17.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.32,0:06:20.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這關鍵時刻 他到底在想什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.80,0:06:22.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們連這都不明白嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.54,0:06:28.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四國妖怪們企圖通過清除土地神來破壞我們的根基
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.97,0:06:33.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是擅長殺害土地神的袖捥已經不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.68,0:06:36.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他們就要用下一招了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.78,0:06:38.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一招是？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.77,0:06:40.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.73,0:06:43.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擒妖先擒王
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.93,0:06:46.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說少主就是他們的下一個目標
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.08,0:06:53.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話與少主關係很好的人類也可能會被盯上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.86,0:07:00.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 少主要盡力把他們留在本家
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.84,0:07:09.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼…為什麼又是納豆小僧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.77,0:07:11.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一百零七連敗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.18,0:07:13.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼贏不了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.00,0:07:15.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一盤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.45,0:07:19.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,郵件來了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.27,0:07:20.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,郵件？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.34,0:07:23.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情報論壇來了新帖子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.77,0:07:30.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如大家所知 我們清十字怪奇偵探團官方網站
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.43,0:07:34.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能收到來自全國的各種妖怪的目擊情報
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.21,0:07:36.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過大都是假情報
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.90,0:07:37.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.59,0:07:41.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一萬條情報裡有一條是真的就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.10,0:07:43.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這…這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.44,0:07:44.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.43,0:07:46.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們收到有力的情報了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.79,0:07:48.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真…真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.33,0:07:50.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是關於舊校舍的情報
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.56,0:07:51.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舊校舍？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.93,0:08:00.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家來看看這個
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.41,0:08:04.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清十字怪奇偵探團 情報論壇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.03,0:08:10.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盤踞在浮世繪中學舊校舍的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.96,0:08:13.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個帖子說
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.45,0:08:16.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮世繪中學舊校舍的講堂裡有一台放映機
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.91,0:08:20.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把妖怪反射在屏幕上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.01,0:08:22.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放映機用的是16毫米膠片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.66,0:08:26.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放映室裡有電源 接通的話就能工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.36,0:08:27.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說得還真詳細
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.10,0:08:31.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說我們還沒調查過講堂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.39,0:08:34.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舊校舍裡果然有妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.12,0:08:36.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得進行調查
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.00,0:08:38.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以不顧一切
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.39,0:08:41.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清十字怪奇偵探團出動
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.51,0:08:45.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.55,0:08:46.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.68,0:08:49.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良同學 你這麼緊張幹嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.99,0:08:52.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天太陽都落山了 還是別去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.82,0:08:54.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是正好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.41,0:08:57.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪就是在夜晚才出現的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.46,0:08:58.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.52,0:09:00.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是別去舊校舍了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.66,0:09:01.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.96,0:09:04.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還沒去過講堂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.42,0:09:08.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我們說不定還能遇見百鬼之主
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.56,0:09:16.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是但是 晚飯就快做好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.89,0:09:20.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良同學 你今天有點奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.53,0:09:22.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒…沒有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.68,0:09:24.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實沒什麼幹勁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.92,0:09:26.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.90,0:09:31.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢…今天我不想外出
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.93,0:09:36.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陸生大人 有您的電話
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.57,0:09:38.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的電話？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.18,0:09:50.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是陸生 您是哪位啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.66,0:09:52.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請說話
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.32,0:09:56.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.19,0:10:00.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前小小地打了次招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.57,0:10:02.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…那時的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.54,0:10:09.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有何貴幹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.53,0:10:15.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良陸生 雖然我現在就想殺了你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.92,0:10:18.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你躲在家裡不出來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.32,0:10:24.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就只好殺死你重視的朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.66,0:10:29.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 我已準備好了一個讓你朋友感興趣的故事了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.36,0:10:33.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 奴良陸生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.24,0:10:49.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良同學 清十字團已經出動了 到舊校舍來匯合吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.35,0:10:50.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.02,0:10:54.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.83,0:10:55.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.02,0:11:16.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲 柚羅同學
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.51,0:11:18.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然叫你出來真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.98,0:11:19.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.12,0:11:21.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去舊校舍？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.77,0:11:25.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我們有了有力的情報
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.43,0:11:28.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次一定要證明妖怪是存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.03,0:11:32.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太陽就要落山了 有危險
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.61,0:11:33.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.75,0:11:35.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬一發生什麼了的話 我還有這個
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.60,0:11:38.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來來 大家來看看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.27,0:11:43.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿著的這把劍可是非比尋常的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.06,0:11:48.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是退治妖怪的秘密武器 名為破魔七枝刀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.66,0:11:54.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山伏的祖師爺小角伏于原野深山 極盡修驗之道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.35,0:11:57.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他堂兄弟的孫子的岳父的子孫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.02,0:12:01.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花了三天三夜精心打造出的靈驗的網絡限定商品
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.29,0:12:04.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被騙了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.59,0:12:05.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是木制的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.65,0:12:07.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請說木刀 木刀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.64,0:12:09.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 明白了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.54,0:12:11.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會跟你去的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.04,0:12:16.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身為陰陽師的柚羅同學也一起來的話就是如虎添翼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.56,0:12:17.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.94,0:12:18.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良同學呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.02,0:12:20.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一會兒就來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.05,0:12:25.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,願神明保佑清十字團和我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.52,0:12:35.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.07,0:12:38.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又到這裡來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.20,0:12:41.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連自己成了誘餌都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.23,0:12:47.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果聽我的指示
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.10,0:12:53.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你們這群不入流的妖怪也能加入四國八十八鬼夜行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.29,0:12:59.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良陸生 你明明是個妖怪 為何要去救人類
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.15,0:13:01.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讓人火大
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.29,0:13:25.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然讓少主單獨行動
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.93,0:13:27.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我發覺時他已經不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.52,0:13:29.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是接完電話就出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.31,0:13:30.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之迅速前往舊校舍
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.00,0:13:32.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少主 請等等我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.60,0:13:37.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經是第二次來這裡了 都習慣了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.49,0:13:40.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 講堂卻是個盲點呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.38,0:13:42.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡有講堂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.27,0:13:43.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.89,0:13:47.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據情報講 舊校舍被廢棄之前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.51,0:13:50.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,講堂就已經被封鎖了 禁止使用
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.90,0:13:51.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被封鎖了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.08,0:13:53.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不會有問題吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.85,0:13:59.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事 到處都彌漫著妖氣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.62,0:14:02.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻看不到形體
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.22,0:14:13.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡就是講堂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.36,0:14:19.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都發黴了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.89,0:14:22.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒看見有放映機啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.30,0:14:23.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家別慌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.85,0:14:26.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放映機當然是放在放映室裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.20,0:14:28.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那個
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.19,0:14:30.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看哪個？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.25,0:14:33.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屏幕嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.42,0:14:34.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,島同學回答得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.39,0:14:36.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 就是屏幕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.33,0:14:40.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情報講 放映室就在屏幕背後
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.85,0:14:44.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說 該死的這是背投式的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.81,0:14:46.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.69,0:14:49.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 島同學 我們去設置一下放映機吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.43,0:14:52.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生們就在這裡等著哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.39,0:14:52.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 清繼同學
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.00,0:14:55.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題嗎 小心點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.26,0:14:58.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用擔心 我有這把劍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.93,0:15:00.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪什麼的 根本不在話下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.03,0:15:02.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們就好好期待吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.47,0:15:12.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得情形不對
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.12,0:15:18.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 島同學
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.87,0:15:20.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺得好像有什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.10,0:15:22.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.65,0:15:25.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪的話要等放映機工作之後才會出現哦 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.73,0:15:26.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但…但…但是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.01,0:15:28.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,島同學 你還真是膽小呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.46,0:15:32.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是說過要是發生什麼了 還有這個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.55,0:15:33.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說…說的是呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.31,0:15:37.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你怎麼這麼膽小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.67,0:15:56.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.46,0:15:57.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陸生同學
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.82,0:15:58.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你來得真遲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.46,0:16:00.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 花開院同學也來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.42,0:16:03.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清繼同學和島同學呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.36,0:16:05.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才去放映室了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.48,0:16:07.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了 臉色好差啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.75,0:16:09.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們沒事就好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.13,0:16:14.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可沒有人類朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:19.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當妖怪有多痛苦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.47,0:16:24.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良陸生 為何你不痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.95,0:16:32.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雜碎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.32,0:16:34.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗器黑演舞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.66,0:16:39.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垂發 遊女之舞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.37,0:16:43.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咒吹雪 雪化妝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.52,0:16:54.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎能從背後偷襲呢 真卑鄙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.85,0:16:59.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須儘快找到少主
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.44,0:17:00.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.53,0:17:04.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是沒完沒了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.08,0:17:06.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部打倒就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.53,0:17:13.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.41,0:17:17.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事 突然又彌漫起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.79,0:17:19.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.69,0:17:20.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 這邊也有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.71,0:17:22.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些數量…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.75,0:17:29.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經照情報所說換了燈泡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.93,0:17:32.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,預備電池也已接通 沒問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.78,0:17:35.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該能工作了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.54,0:17:37.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全沒反應呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.71,0:17:39.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家快點離開這裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.10,0:17:41.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 清繼同學他們還…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.30,0:17:43.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們兩個就交給我好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.41,0:17:46.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花開院同學 她們三個就拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.76,0:17:50.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法 只有用最後一招了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.68,0:17:51.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後一招？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.16,0:17:52.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.86,0:17:55.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,島同學 看好了 你以後可以參考
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.84,0:17:56.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.32,0:17:59.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難…難道…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.89,0:18:08.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖傳 清繼流家電再生拳
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.33,0:18:18.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,chest
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.38,0:18:21.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修…修好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.21,0:18:25.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奴良陸生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.90,0:18:27.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還真愛管閒事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.29,0:18:30.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.78,0:18:32.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要救人類？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.51,0:18:36.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有秉性嘛 奴良陸生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.72,0:18:37.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.86,0:18:39.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 都是徒勞的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.39,0:18:44.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人類會成為盤踞在這裡的妖怪的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.40,0:18:47.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.36,0:18:51.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要小看花開院陰陽術
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.31,0:18:55.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼 為什麼像你這樣的弱小妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.72,0:18:58.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然能在人類和妖怪間左右逢源
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.27,0:19:03.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我 為何要與人類做朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.27,0:19:07.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人類可是厭惡妖怪的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.93,0:19:11.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並不是所有人都厭惡人類
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.61,0:19:19.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,優等生就當到今天為止了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.01,0:19:26.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有不厭惡妖怪的人類
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.90,0:19:28.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.74,0:19:29.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡的人類
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.44,0:19:30.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡的人類
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.18,0:19:34.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個個都把我當成怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.27,0:19:37.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我當成怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.00,0:19:40.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是卻沒人這樣對你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.16,0:19:42.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這到底是為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.07,0:19:46.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我更弱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.03,0:19:51.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不如我 卻擁有我所沒有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.90,0:19:55.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不認同你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.54,0:19:56.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不認同
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.95,0:20:03.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這股強大的妖氣是什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.28,0:20:04.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柚羅同學
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.50,0:20:06.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.69,0:20:11.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不覺得很吵嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.71,0:20:14.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是妖怪出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.59,0:20:15.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.98,0:20:19.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,島同學 換電燈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.43,0:20:21.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 備用的剛才已經用了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.94,0:20:24.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那邊找找吧 應該還有一個
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.26,0:20:25.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是常識啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.16,0:20:26.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有這常識嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.34,0:20:27.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.78,0:20:30.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你能抵抗多久
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.93,0:20:41.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此為止了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.29,0:20:46.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不就是上次的小狗仔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.74,0:20:49.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.34,0:20:52.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼謝謝大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.23,0:20:54.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 真沒勁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.76,0:20:57.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 我要把你們全部殺死
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.50,0:20:58.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.10,0:21:00.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有很多事要問你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.15,0:21:04.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如說四國妖怪的戰鬥力 基地的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.96,0:21:09.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙總是被同伴保護著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.97,0:21:11.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.72,0:21:13.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你們能保護他多久
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.86,0:21:15.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨死你這樣的小鬼了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.84,0:21:17.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.84,0:21:20.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好恨你啊 奴良陸生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.90,0:21:22.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.27,0:21:48.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少主
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.15,0:23:29.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 柚羅同學身高是多少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.82,0:23:31.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一米四三
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.37,0:23:31.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體重呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.91,0:23:32.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.84,0:23:35.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜是三十四公斤
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.48,0:23:37.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什麼人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.52,0:23:38.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回 滑頭鬼之孫
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.33,0:23:41.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開幕於黑暗之中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
