[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-07-18 12:58:09
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000080,&H00FF0080,-1,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: c,黑体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000040,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: t,方正卡通简体,33,&H00800CF3,&HF0000000,&H00C0C0C0,&HF0FFA54A,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGPOP1-W5,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H008000FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCH,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H008000FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFGPOP1-W5,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H008000FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,10,128
Style: EDCH,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF00FF,&H008000FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.37,0:00:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不能原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.54,0:00:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.59,0:00:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 只是想起了早上的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.44,0:00:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.76,0:00:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.24,0:00:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面有效 一本
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.66,0:00:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.64,0:00:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 果然赢不了弥子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.93,0:00:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的天赋不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.89,0:00:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耕太只决断差了些而已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.86,0:00:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.43,0:00:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 那个…弥子… 这边是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.12,0:00:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 女子更衣室的钥匙找不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.11,0:00:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就在这边换衣服了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.90,0:00:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.21,0:00:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近早起练习的就我们而已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.60,0:01:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没啥的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.55,0:01:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.43,0:01:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 你剑道部那边怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.77,0:01:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你入部了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.46,0:01:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像进入了去年县大会的前四了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.96,0:01:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.01,0:01:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家在和你说话呢好歹吱个声吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.74,0:01:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要转过去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.87,0:01:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.15,0:01:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥子就不害羞么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.36,0:01:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和男生一起换衣服…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.55,0:01:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不 也没啥的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.37,0:01:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（还要挥多少下啊）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.06,0:01:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都现在了你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.50,0:01:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的男生我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.46,0:01:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是耕太嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.47,0:01:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种无聊的内衣就算看了也没啥好高兴的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.01,0:01:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话我可不能当成没听见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.90,0:01:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说实话而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.16,0:02:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明就没有胸 还穿个像胸罩似的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.56,0:02:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.20,0:02:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种内衣 弥子根本就不需要嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.47,0:02:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先跟你说 这可不是像胸罩一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.56,0:02:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是运动胸罩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.32,0:02:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.52,0:02:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是无可救药的家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.48,0:02:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 搞不好是这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.94,0:02:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.23,0:02:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,运动胸罩也是胸罩 完全就不明白嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.30,0:02:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你指这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.34,0:02:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死耕太 别小看运动胸罩哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.99,0:02:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.87,0:04:06.83,c,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由极影字幕社制作，仅供试看之用,如你喜欢本作品，请支持正版！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.87,0:04:06.83,c,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译:Saturn    歌词:弥生      后期:碧水海蓝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.86,0:04:11.82,t,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}{\pos(424,300)}初一的暑假
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.33,0:04:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话说回来那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.06,0:04:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会这么生气呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.34,0:04:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为尴尬么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.48,0:04:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尴尬？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.80,0:04:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 之前小町也说过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.29,0:04:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是男生所以会用色情的眼光看内衣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.32,0:04:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生会用H的眼光看待内衣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.61,0:04:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个哭鼻子的耕太？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.79,0:04:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.52,0:04:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.58,0:04:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 我也觉得奈由说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.46,0:04:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是青梅竹马
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.20,0:04:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也是中学的男生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.92,0:04:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是像家人一样的人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.13,0:04:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 去问问小町如何
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.76,0:04:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？去问死猫？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.94,0:04:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 小町的话我觉得会很好商量的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.04,0:05:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能顺利和男生说话 也是多亏了小町
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.14,0:05:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于内衣同好会他可是一直给我好的建议哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.02,0:05:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙好像脑子挺不错的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.63,0:05:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯 祭典的时候问问他怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.10,0:05:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.46,0:05:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得这附近有一瞬的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.70,0:05:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要进行游泳练习的在右半边进行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.01,0:05:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.88,0:05:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是神宫寺同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.46,0:05:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真行啊 真是运动万能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.23,0:05:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是叶山同学呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.33,0:05:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像说过这个夏天要以能游25米为目标
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.46,0:05:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也算是青春的一页呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.48,0:05:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白石同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.92,0:05:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.33,0:05:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 坐在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.21,0:05:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.55,0:06:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 难道说哪里不舒服么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.21,0:06:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是…不是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.75,0:06:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得有时候 这里会变得很紧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.54,0:06:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.62,0:06:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是因为胸部在成长么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.58,0:06:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 一学期就因为那群家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.70,0:06:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害得我都没怎么学习
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.09,0:06:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落下的那份必须得在暑假给补回来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.08,0:06:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.93,0:06:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶山 又是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.27,0:06:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候会变得这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.08,0:06:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.17,0:06:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 要怎么用划水板才会飞起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.81,0:06:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我好好练习下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.61,0:06:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 稍微有点高兴了就飞出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.88,0:06:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是小孩么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.59,0:06:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.93,0:06:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.63,0:07:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.52,0:07:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.55,0:07:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于今天的夏日祭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.47,0:07:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小町也会来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.01,0:07:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.96,0:07:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是内衣同好会的一环吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.75,0:07:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 然后呢 小町会穿浴衣来么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.34,0:07:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭吾有一件 虽然可能有点大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.54,0:07:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我觉得稍微调整下应该也能穿 如何
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.97,0:07:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 关于刚才那个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.52,0:07:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸口会痛是不是因为心在成长呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.98,0:07:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.26,0:07:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得在大家这个年龄
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.69,0:07:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随着身体变化的同时
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.77,0:07:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心也在变得成熟起来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.74,0:07:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白石同学的紧 是不是因为这个原因呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.66,0:08:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 我知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.06,0:08:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傍晚去你家就好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.28,0:08:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.05,0:08:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.23,0:08:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.38,0:08:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在还不是很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.30,0:08:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 我想可能对大人来说也是个复杂的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.31,0:08:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始慢慢的去寻找答案怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.63,0:08:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.46,0:08:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.65,0:08:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是初中生嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.26,0:08:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在意的男生也没什么稀奇的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.25,0:08:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.87,0:08:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候学长只是进入我的视线就让我心跳不已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.42,0:08:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长 无论在哪都像一个王子一般闪耀呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.43,0:08:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水野老师啊 有些时候很糟糕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.38,0:08:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.51,0:09:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天要保持化妆很难呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.91,0:09:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.31,0:09:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 要无视我？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.39,0:09:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.79,0:09:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.44,0:09:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下…不行的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.96,0:09:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我跳下去…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.22,0:09:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样也算男人么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.29,0:09:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家不是男人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.83,0:09:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶山同学
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.26,0:09:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈 原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.35,0:09:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥子 不用脱下来也可以的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.90,0:09:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 穿浴衣的时候不是不穿内裤的么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.05,0:09:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去似乎是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.47,0:09:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在短裤的上面再穿件衬裙就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.84,0:09:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 只要内衣的痕迹不会出来就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.42,0:09:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.40,0:09:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用穿那令人烦躁的东西也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.75,0:09:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丁字裤不是也可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.54,0:09:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来还有这一手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.09,0:09:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大胆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.25,0:10:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.79,0:10:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 对初中生来说还太早了点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.38,0:10:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就算小学生该穿的也会穿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.28,0:10:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样一年到头都穿运动服的家伙才…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.42,0:10:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 老师 这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.59,0:10:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和服用的胸罩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.66,0:10:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部比平常看起来更清爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.26,0:10:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 像老师胸部这么大的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.54,0:10:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着这个穿浴衣会更漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.21,0:10:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和服的基本是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.59,0:10:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽可能的接近水桶型
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.85,0:10:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时都是内衣同好会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.13,0:10:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是奈由呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.74,0:10:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此 你连浴衣都不会穿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.42,0:10:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由 我要拉下衣领咯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.21,0:10:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.81,0:10:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害呢 遥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.49,0:10:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都迷上你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.50,0:10:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过奖了 我只是在小的时候学过而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.63,0:11:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起我来 了解内衣的奈由才厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.16,0:11:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.53,0:11:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短信
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.50,0:11:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耕太
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.67,0:11:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是要和好的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.67,0:11:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要是这么说的话就没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.99,0:11:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 明明没什么胸就别穿什么胸罩了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.03,0:11:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙 说我笨蛋 笨蛋？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.42,0:11:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我记好了 明天去道场你打得破破烂烂的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.63,0:11:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说 胸罩可是必要的哦 明白么 耕太
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.73,0:11:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么了 发生什么了么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.39,0:11:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.19,0:11:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是神宫寺同学不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.02,0:11:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.42,0:11:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就在这边换衣服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.68,0:11:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.91,0:11:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我必须要去道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.73,0:11:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是理所当然的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.65,0:11:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了算了 你们两个都冷静下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.31,0:12:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师别说话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.69,0:12:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.70,0:12:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真热闹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.30,0:12:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.28,0:12:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那个叫耕太的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.40,0:12:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像刚才那样大叫也可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.69,0:12:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为这样你也…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.28,0:12:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不被当成异性来看待这件事究竟有多痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.10,0:12:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有经历过的人才知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.53,0:12:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不被当成异性来看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.58,0:12:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥子 耕太因为这样而受伤了么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.72,0:12:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小町怎么觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.04,0:12:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得怎样都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.51,0:12:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.83,0:13:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由 去那边捞金鱼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.98,0:13:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.93,0:13:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍微去买点东西 你们先走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.80,0:13:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天原同学 会走散的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.13,0:13:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是小孩子了才不会犯这种傻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.88,0:13:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这群孩子也有自己的思想了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.48,0:13:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话说回来 学长被公司紧急叫去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.33,0:13:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能赶得上烟花么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.63,0:13:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烟花 和学长…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.89,0:13:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.61,0:13:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 但你更加漂亮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.09,0:13:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 胸部会露出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.91,0:13:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.33,0:13:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我的手来代替你的胸罩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.49,0:13:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是变成这样要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.46,0:14:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 大家在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.40,0:14:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 快看 这些金鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.32,0:14:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.82,0:14:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾巴真长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.13,0:14:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 要来一回么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.49,0:14:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耕太
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.59,0:14:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好的和他说下比较好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.69,0:14:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.17,0:14:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子啊 可是很固执的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.03,0:14:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己是不会主动道歉的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.91,0:14:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死猫
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.39,0:14:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.74,0:14:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己去创造机会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.31,0:14:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错啊 这样子根本不像弥子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.25,0:14:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.24,0:14:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我也这么想
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.48,0:14:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.19,0:14:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是青梅竹马么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.24,0:14:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好珍惜比较好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.46,0:14:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 一直这么磨磨蹭蹭的也不合我性格
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.96,0:15:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我先走一步
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.93,0:15:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.11,0:15:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能和好就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.17,0:15:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.31,0:15:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.06,0:15:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 为什么戴着面具呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.43,0:15:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对叶山同学要保密
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.57,0:15:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.70,0:15:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.05,0:15:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家真是的 别走散了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.86,0:15:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师真拿手 真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.27,0:15:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了这个面具
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.58,0:15:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会被奈由看到你那张色脸了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.71,0:15:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会可是要给我钱的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.08,0:15:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.07,0:15:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万元
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.25,0:15:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是商店街的大叔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.04,0:15:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长 夏天可是女孩子变得开放的季节哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.48,0:15:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去邀请叶山同学约会怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.72,0:15:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 要再来光顾哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.40,0:15:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 真是值得捉弄啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.74,0:16:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系好像很好呢 那两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.95,0:16:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为都是一个班上的原因么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.09,0:16:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.52,0:16:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也有好多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.13,0:16:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥 你觉得哪个比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.30,0:16:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由不介意么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.92,0:16:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,介意什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.99,0:16:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…小町…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.07,0:16:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.00,0:16:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.33,0:16:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是糟透了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.39,0:16:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的话就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.87,0:16:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 遥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.90,0:16:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.50,0:16:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先先调整下胸罩的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.55,0:16:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微把手放进去下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.08,0:16:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 疼么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.34,0:16:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.51,0:16:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.76,0:16:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比试穿的时候更大声了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.49,0:16:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 别让奈由听到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.66,0:17:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 OK
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.73,0:17:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 今天的内衣有点姐姐的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.06,0:17:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.84,0:17:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然想穿下这种的了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.90,0:17:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥 难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.31,0:17:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有喜欢的人了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.79,0:17:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.99,0:17:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 想起了以前奶奶说过的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.16,0:17:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内衣和恋爱是斩也斩不断的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.45,0:17:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 就觉得换了内衣的遥是不是喜欢上了谁呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.84,0:17:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要是说错了的话就抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.18,0:17:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 被金鱼咬到哪里了么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.60,0:17:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.92,0:17:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说不定有让我在意的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.68,0:18:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 刚才说什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.03,0:18:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 那个 我啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.83,0:18:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在这附近么 叶山同学 白石同学
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.78,0:18:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.32,0:18:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.71,0:18:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 我去借毛巾了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.09,0:18:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭吾哥发来的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.16,0:18:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.17,0:18:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎马上就要来这边了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.52,0:18:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.04,0:18:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去接他一下比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.00,0:18:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.53,0:18:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.49,0:18:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经没事了 老师也在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.49,0:18:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这样的话就由我…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.91,0:18:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍微过去下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.36,0:18:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.69,0:18:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 带我来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.29,0:18:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今今今…今天早上真是对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.06,0:18:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你看那么无聊的内衣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.10,0:19:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.58,0:19:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这种内衣的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.66,0:19:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有印象了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.41,0:19:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.36,0:19:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.17,0:19:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要给男生的你看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.69,0:19:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是青梅竹马
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.05,0:19:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥子…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后我会注意的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.83,0:19:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才该说抱歉 说了过分的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.29,0:19:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有短信也是…虽然想要写和好的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.19,0:19:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不小心就…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.91,0:19:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的和死猫说的一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.79,0:19:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.26,0:19:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就扯平了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.01,0:19:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开始要严格的训练了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.70,0:19:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正合我意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.38,0:19:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.01,0:19:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有破绽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.94,0:19:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.52,0:19:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时都不得大意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.92,0:19:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是武士道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.42,0:19:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你的腿…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.09,0:20:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.66,0:20:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.00,0:20:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 耕太的事平安解决了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.29,0:20:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 发生什么事了么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.53,0:20:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到叶山同学了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.25,0:20:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 圭吾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.70,0:20:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走散了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.05,0:20:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是不接
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.87,0:20:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥 别哭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.54,0:20:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 现在先找叶山去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.09,0:20:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.11,0:20:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是爱惹麻烦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.17,0:20:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 都怪我没有跟着她
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.02,0:20:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是老师的错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.83,0:20:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了哦 在找到妈妈之前姐姐会陪着你的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.82,0:20:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 苹果糖
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.35,0:20:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.15,0:20:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈由
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.68,0:20:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.24,0:21:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.47,0:21:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 大家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.73,0:21:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烟花结束了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.69,0:21:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烟花每年都有的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.22,0:21:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年再一起来就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.92,0:21:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明年也好 后年也好 就算变成大人了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.74,0:21:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都想像这样和奈由还有大家一起来祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.71,0:21:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.21,0:21:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 要添麻烦也是适可而止点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.58,0:21:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 手机原来丢了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.78,0:21:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.02,0:21:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来现在才发现么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.02,0:21:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.17,0:21:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子你必须请客吃巧克力香蕉了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.67,0:21:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.21,0:21:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家可是专门把你的丢的东西送来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.56,0:21:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交到好朋友了呢 奈由
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.81,0:21:54.57,c,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（你的计划好像被京都总公司选为新计划了呢 干得不错 恭喜你）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.83,0:23:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罩杯的形状也有很多种呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.34,0:23:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.05,0:23:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吊钟型 碗型 火箭型
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.82,0:23:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后还有丝瓜型
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.11,0:23:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丝瓜是指下垂的么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.09,0:23:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就算大我也不要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.83,0:23:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回 青春CUP 敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.27,0:23:44.85,t,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}{\pos(424,300)}自豪的挺胸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.95,0:02:42.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,”好き”を全部ね　ハグしたい（抱きしめたい）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.52,0:02:45.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,膨らむハートで　ギュッとね（目一杯ね）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.27,0:02:47.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ドキドキ発生多発（事件勃発）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.74,0:02:50.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改札で　信号で　校門で（anywhere）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.38,0:02:52.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突き進んじゃって　いんじゃない（全然いんじゃない）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.92,0:02:55.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弾んだヒップのノリでね（楽しくね）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.55,0:02:57.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ワクワク加速ャバい（まじ止まんない）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.06,0:03:00.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.74,0:03:04.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,A·B·C·D·E·F·G じゃ測れない　制服の内側
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.77,0:03:08.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進化中だし　サイズ変わる夢　予測は不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.54,0:03:12.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,興味に理由はないよね？（単純明快）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.18,0:03:15.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気になることが　気になります
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.78,0:03:18.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解けない数式とデレない（難解困憊）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.45,0:03:20.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのコは常にね　同じ重要さ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.84,0:03:23.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.34,0:03:26.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.62,0:03:30.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenager
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.86,0:03:36.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フリルで隠した本音　なぜ教え合いたい...！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.22,0:03:41.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,”好き”に全部ね　タッチしたい（確かめたい）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.92,0:03:44.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ときめくハートで　そっとね（優しくね）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.57,0:03:46.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きらきら発信奮発（実験連発）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.09,0:03:49.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教室で　廊下で　部室で（anywhere）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.77,0:03:52.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突き進んじゃって　いんじゃない（全然いんじゃない）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.30,0:03:54.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尻込みヒップもポップに（元気にね）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.93,0:03:57.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フルフル勇気を出し（その気を出し）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.44,0:04:01.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向かえ敵なし　迷う暇なし　学んで遊んで
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:02.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,We Must Choose Bright Things！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.95,0:02:42.31,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想去拥抱所有的“喜欢”（想去拥抱）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.52,0:02:45.11,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用满满的内心 紧紧拥抱（紧紧的呢）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.27,0:02:47.56,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张心动多多发生（事件频发）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.74,0:02:50.22,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在检票口 在红绿灯 在校门口（anywhere）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.38,0:02:52.78,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一往直前 这样不好吗（一点也不好）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.92,0:02:55.41,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用飞扬的小屁屁的劲头（快快乐乐地呢）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.55,0:02:57.89,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扑通扑通加快速度出事了（真的停不下来了）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.06,0:03:00.55,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴天也好雨天也好 Our Morning's Brightening！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.74,0:03:04.62,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只用A·B·C·D·E·F·G 可没法衡量 制服的里面
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.77,0:03:08.40,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在进化中 尺寸增大的梦想 不可预测
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.54,0:03:12.99,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兴趣是没有理由的吧？（简单明快）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.18,0:03:15.55,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在意的事情 还是在意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.78,0:03:18.11,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解不开的算式配上毫不偷懒（难解困乏）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.45,0:03:20.62,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个东东在平常 也同样重要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.84,0:03:23.05,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上课的铃声就是重新开始的标志
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.34,0:03:26.29,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的失态全部消去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.62,0:03:30.78,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敏感而又充满朝气 Low Teenager
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.86,0:03:36.86,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用花边遮住的真心 为什么想要相互倾诉...？！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.22,0:03:41.70,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想去触碰所有的“喜欢”（想去确认）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.92,0:03:44.38,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用怦怦跳动的心 悄悄地呢（柔柔地呢）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.57,0:03:46.93,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪闪发光频频发信（实验连发）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.09,0:03:49.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在教室 在走廊 在活动室（anywhere）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.77,0:03:52.14,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一往直前 这样不好吗（一点也不好）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.30,0:03:54.75,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犹豫的小屁屁也和着摇滚（健健康康地）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.93,0:03:57.25,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿出足足勇气（拿出勇气）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.44,0:04:01.32,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无对敌 毫无犹豫 学习游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:02.71,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,We Must Choose Bright Things！！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.67,0:22:05.09,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Step By Step　一歩ずつ歩き出そう！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.75,0:22:09.70,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光り輝く　あしたへ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.91,0:22:15.36,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.95,0:22:30.75,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制服の下にも　みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.03,0:22:36.01,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恥ずかしがらないでいい　乙女心に自信を持って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.18,0:22:40.87,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああしたい　こうしたい　情熱は止まらない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.14,0:22:47.95,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怖がらないで　いま　できることを始めましょ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.93,0:22:54.46,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女の子は悩んでいる　鏡を覗いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.94,0:22:59.28,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,みんなどこか弱気になる　年頃だから
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.04,0:23:04.39,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy Smile　笑顔から始めよう！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.04,0:23:09.40,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どんな時だって　ひとりじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.17,0:23:14.31,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運命を切りひらく　この想い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.15,0:23:19.20,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光り輝く　あしたへ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.43,0:23:24.90,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.67,0:22:05.09,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Step By Step 一步步向前迈进
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.75,0:22:09.70,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈向闪闪发光的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.91,0:22:15.36,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去寻找心动吧  Shy Girls
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.95,0:22:30.75,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制服里面 有大家各自的主张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.03,0:22:36.01,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用害羞 要对自己的少女之心充满信心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.18,0:22:40.87,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想这样 想那样 热情不减
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.14,0:22:47.95,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要害怕 现在 开始做力所能及的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.93,0:22:54.46,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子在烦恼 窥着镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.94,0:22:59.28,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家或许都会胆小 正值年少嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.04,0:23:04.39,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy Smile 从笑脸开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.04,0:23:09.40,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时 都不是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.17,0:23:14.31,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开启命运之门 抱着这种想法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.15,0:23:19.20,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈向闪闪发光的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.43,0:23:24.90,EDCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去寻找心动吧  Shy Girls


