[Script Info]
; This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;
; Script created by cySub 1.4.0 Release Build 1203
;
Title: [LiouMing][Kanon][11][Xvid_704x396].cht.ssa
Original Script: LiouMing Anime Station
Original Editing: LiouMing Anime Station
Original Timing: LiouMing Anime Station
Script Updated By: LiouMing Anime Station
Script Type: V4.00+
ScriptType: V4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 396
Timer: 100.000
WrapStyle: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,華康中圓體,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFCC,&H00CD7765,&H00FF0000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,0,10,136
Style: Title,華康中黑體,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFCC,&H00400040,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,0,10,136
Style: PS,華康中黑體,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00CD7765,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,10,10,5,136

Style: OPjpn,DFPMaruGothic-Md,22,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&HB0FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: OPchn,FZZhunYuan-M02,25,&H00000000,&HFF000000,&HB0FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: EDjpn,DFPMaruGothic-Md,22,&HFFCB56A3,&H00CB56A3,&HB0FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,30,30,10,1
Style: EDjp2,DFPMaruGothic-Md,22,&HFF9B4B36,&H009B4B36,&HB0FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,30,30,10,1
Style: EDjp3,DFPMaruGothic-Md,22,&HFFA87A55,&H00A87A55,&HB0FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,30,30,10,1
Style: EDjp4,DFPMaruGothic-Md,22,&HFF3D65B7,&H003D65B7,&HB0FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,30,30,10,1
Style: EDchn,FZZhunYuan-M02,23,&H00CB56A3,&HFF000000,&HB0FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,7,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

;前提對話
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.06,0:00:02.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.80,0:00:05.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在夢境失去終點的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.26,0:00:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只能如往常一般　在往常的地點
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.26,0:00:14.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不停地　不停地等待
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.84,0:00:17.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是我唯一能做到的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.75,0:00:19.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.95,0:00:22.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在　我也依然持續等待著

;本話標題
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.18,0:01:57.71,Title,,0000,0000,0080,,第11話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.18,0:01:57.71,Title,,0000,0000,0050,,光與影的間奏曲

;正文字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.21,0:02:10.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,秋子阿姨　這個房間
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.26,0:02:12.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不可以讓它一直保持現在的樣子？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.75,0:02:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.02,0:02:16.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣真琴不管什麼時候回來都沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.72,0:02:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　我也打算這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.54,0:02:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一　你記起以前的事了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.23,0:02:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.20,0:02:32.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為　你不是記起真琴的事了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.36,0:02:34.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那　其他的事情也…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.50,0:02:37.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不　回想起來的只有那傢伙的事而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.21,0:02:40.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除此之外的還是一片模糊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.93,0:02:44.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天沒有晨練嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.56,0:02:45.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,休息一天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.07,0:02:48.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾也得讓身體休養一下才行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.37,0:02:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那回家時也一起走吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.59,0:02:50.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.19,0:02:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水瀨學姊　早安
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.47,0:02:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.95,0:02:57.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水瀨學姊耶…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.23,0:02:59.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唷　相澤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.59,0:03:02.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早啊北川　今天也穿同一件嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.36,0:03:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈　制服一樣不是理所當然的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.56,0:03:07.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的也每天都一樣不是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.32,0:03:10.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈　我的雖然乍看之下是同一件
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.43,0:03:12.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實每天都不同啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.23,0:03:14.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪哈哈　我的事實上也是這樣喔！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.30,0:03:16.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.25,0:03:17.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.40,0:03:18.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是一樣莫名地起勁啊　那兩個人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.58,0:03:20.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臭味相投嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.53,0:03:23.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感冒已經好了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.34,0:03:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.08,0:03:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話說在前頭　這感冒可不是被妳傳染的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.65,0:03:30.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我就安心了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.62,0:03:33.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳才是　不是應該乖乖待在家裡才對嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.21,0:03:36.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　但果然還是覺得無聊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.06,0:03:40.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且又遇不到祐一　挺沒意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.06,0:03:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.55,0:03:44.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈　肚子空了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.13,0:03:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然肚子餓了　就…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.91,0:03:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.33,0:03:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我什麼都還沒講耶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.26,0:03:51.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要叫我回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.00,0:03:53.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又要叫我乖一點趕快把病養好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.91,0:03:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那當然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.95,0:03:56.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳總是這樣才沒有好轉的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.31,0:03:59.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我討厭說這種話的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.80,0:04:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭也沒關係　快回去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.51,0:04:07.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真拿妳沒輒啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.63,0:04:10.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起…我很任性吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.37,0:04:13.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一你明明是這麼擔心我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.48,0:04:19.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有想吃什麼嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.73,0:04:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.76,0:04:23.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳餓了吧？　我去買些吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.56,0:04:26.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.98,0:04:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點說　要沒時間了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.23,0:04:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好　那就…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.94,0:04:33.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冰淇淋好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.86,0:04:35.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.48,0:04:41.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至少…進校舍裡怎樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.23,0:04:44.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被老師發現的話　會挨罵的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.61,0:04:51.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.23,0:04:57.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呃…沒什麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.59,0:05:01.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.25,0:05:06.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一　已經午休了喔？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.92,0:05:08.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用妳說我也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.74,0:05:10.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,午餐怎麼辦？　去餐廳吃？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.75,0:05:13.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉　我有約人了　掰啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.74,0:05:17.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙　都是跟誰一起吃啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.31,0:05:18.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.46,0:05:23.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,地點換了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.76,0:05:25.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這又是那個人做的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.64,0:05:26.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那個吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.81,0:05:29.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚上潛進來弄壞的對吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.46,0:05:31.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次可不能光停學就算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.98,0:05:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說到底這種事到底重複幾次了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.01,0:05:39.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛她也被叫去辦公室了　或許就是要談這事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.90,0:05:44.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　祐一
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.86,0:05:45.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舞她？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.10,0:05:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.79,0:05:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舞在之前　也曾經打破過學校的窗戶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.17,0:05:57.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然那是一年級的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.66,0:06:01.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算問她理由　也不跟我說
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.42,0:06:07.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從那次之後　每當發生事情舞就總會被懷疑…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.51,0:06:11.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佐祐理學姊妳認為不是舞幹的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.43,0:06:17.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想如果是舞做的　她一定會告訴我緣由
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.05,0:06:18.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.73,0:06:21.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舞　怎麼樣了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.83,0:06:25.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挨罵了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.05,0:06:28.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有這樣？　有沒有說要停學什麼的？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.67,0:06:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.09,0:06:32.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佐祐理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.87,0:06:33.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？　什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.03,0:06:35.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子餓了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.33,0:06:37.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈　我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.52,0:06:40.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在老地方等我　我帶便當過去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.72,0:06:47.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘻嘻　所以啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.70,0:06:48.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喔？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.66,0:06:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂　那傢伙是傳聞的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.04,0:06:51.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　那個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.32,0:06:54.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說妳…還真是個名人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.30,0:06:58.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想點辦法比較好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.73,0:07:03.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來　請用吧　舞
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.45,0:07:05.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃佐祐理的份也沒關係喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.51,0:07:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那佐祐理學姊　妳就吃我的份吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.89,0:07:16.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那這個也讓舞妳…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.59,0:07:19.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那這個就給佐祐理學姊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.74,0:07:23.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那　這個也…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.78,0:07:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.63,0:07:26.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂！　不要拿食物來玩啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.86,0:07:31.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一　放學了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.29,0:07:35.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對現在的我而言　這些都無所謂了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.65,0:07:37.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才不是無所謂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.44,0:07:39.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為今天要一起回去呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.81,0:07:40.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.78,0:07:41.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.97,0:07:42.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.89,0:07:43.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.13,0:07:44.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.25,0:07:46.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們約好了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.25,0:07:47.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.20,0:07:49.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.38,0:07:49.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.52,0:07:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.52,0:07:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.75,0:07:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們約好了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.75,0:07:55.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.72,0:07:57.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們是欠別人吐嘈是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.12,0:08:00.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不　我正在期待你出現
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.60,0:08:03.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,北川你還沒有要回去嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.43,0:08:05.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為香里有社團　我要等到她結束
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.26,0:08:08.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我要回去了　掰啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.14,0:08:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啥！？　喂　等一下啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.93,0:08:10.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂　香里！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.69,0:08:12.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,受歡迎的秘密？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.62,0:08:15.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳不是挺受學妹喜愛的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.00,0:08:18.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,教教我要怎麼做才能受人歡迎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.54,0:08:20.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種事我不知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.59,0:08:22.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也沒有說很受歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.11,0:08:23.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.08,0:08:26.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有讓女孩子看來像女孩子的方法嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.19,0:08:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你說的我有聽沒有懂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.13,0:08:33.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是讓大猩猩似的女孩子　也能看起來很可愛的方法啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.51,0:08:35.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那女生　像大猩猩一樣嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.70,0:08:37.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不　雖然不像大猩猩啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.71,0:08:39.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那她可愛嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.87,0:08:40.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.12,0:08:43.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　譬如說參加這個之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.97,0:08:45.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,預防蛀牙的海報嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.95,0:08:48.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這個看起來會像預防蛀牙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,校園舞會…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.75,0:08:51.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.11,0:08:55.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作業的講義　我忘在桌子裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.30,0:08:58.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你先走吧　我會跟上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.48,0:08:59.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.23,0:09:00.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在校舍門口等妳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.92,0:09:01.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.46,0:09:06.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舞　妳看！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.15,0:09:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太近了看不到…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.14,0:09:12.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　後天的舞會呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.17,0:09:13.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,學生會主辦的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.96,0:09:15.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太近了看不到…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.55,0:09:17.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我打算讓舞參加這個
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.54,0:09:18.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.35,0:09:19.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太近了看不到…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.33,0:09:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是改善舞的形象的策略喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.87,0:09:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盛裝參加的話　人氣會一口氣大爆發喔！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.99,0:09:29.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯～可能是個好主意喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.31,0:09:32.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舞　參加看看嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.85,0:09:34.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有禮服
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.54,0:09:36.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個跟別人借一下就好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.16,0:09:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佐祐理　妳沒有嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.69,0:09:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然沒有　但我可以問看看認識的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.59,0:09:45.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一你也可以找找看嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.74,0:09:47.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,秋子阿姨說不定有
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.13,0:09:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,名雪的話大概沒有吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.59,0:09:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.65,0:09:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙子…

;B
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.99,0:10:09.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,心情好點了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.54,0:10:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　我最喜歡這裡的草莓聖代了～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.10,0:10:15.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼甜的東西　妳竟然還能吃那麼多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.32,0:10:19.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再吃三份我想也是沒問題的唷～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.43,0:10:22.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,禮服？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.56,0:10:25.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是我之前跟妳說過的那個朋友要去參加舞會
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.22,0:10:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為是妳出的主意　禮服也幫忙搞定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.98,0:10:31.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你這麼說也…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.87,0:10:34.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽她好像也沒有的樣子唷…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.49,0:10:35.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我從沒看到過…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.15,0:10:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那其他可能會有禮服的人嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.89,0:10:40.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.96,0:10:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一君
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.34,0:10:45.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想是沒辦法了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.20,0:10:47.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們在說什麼啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.57,0:10:50.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姑且還是確認一下　妳有禮服嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.70,0:10:52.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,禮服？　什麼禮服？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.50,0:10:54.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳話都沒在聽的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.51,0:10:56.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是說了是要參加舞會用的禮服嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.06,0:10:58.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你在說什麼耶…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的希望就只剩妳了耶…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.60,0:11:04.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話妳的一生都會在「嗚咕」中度過喔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.22,0:11:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一…　你這種問法會讓人越來越覺得莫名奇妙喔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.83,0:11:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對呀　這麼久沒見面了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.20,0:11:13.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一碰面馬上就說些奇怪的話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.40,0:11:16.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且…這些話還相當失禮唷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.39,0:11:18.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯沒錯　祐一君你好沒禮貌喔！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.04,0:11:20.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.36,0:11:25.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,……妳是誰呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.00,0:11:29.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欸～　妳是秋子阿姨的女兒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.00,0:11:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,順便一提　也是我的表妹
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.43,0:11:34.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我從媽媽那邊聽說了唷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.35,0:11:39.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳是祐一以前的朋友　有時候還會來我家吃早餐對吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.44,0:11:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳早上都在睡覺　才會都沒見過面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.66,0:11:46.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　雖然我有聽說過　但這是第一次碰面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.89,0:11:48.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以叫妳亞由嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.12,0:11:50.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　亞由就可以囉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.93,0:11:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳也叫我小名雪就可以囉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.81,0:11:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小名雪？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.58,0:11:56.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個太複雜了不要這樣叫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.81,0:11:56.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.61,0:11:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.72,0:12:00.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳希望她這樣叫啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.84,0:12:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.96,0:12:03.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.33,0:12:07.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽　亞由她來玩了唷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.24,0:12:09.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,名雪　祐一　你們看！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.13,0:12:11.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皮羅牠回來了唷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.85,0:12:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇～皮羅！　皮羅！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.75,0:12:15.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇　我說了快住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.70,0:12:17.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳對貓過敏啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.68,0:12:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（皮羅！皮羅！）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.54,0:12:20.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？　牠是偷鯛魚燒的那隻貓
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.40,0:12:22.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！　這傢伙跟妳是共犯嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.67,0:12:23.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才不是共犯咧！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.72,0:12:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳要找的東西還沒找到嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.35,0:12:32.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　可是總有一天一定會找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.29,0:12:35.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好想摸皮羅喔～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.03,0:12:37.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亞由　要不要吃個飯啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.14,0:12:39.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？　可以嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.99,0:12:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果秋子阿姨答應的話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.20,0:12:44.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我想她只要一秒就會准了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.02,0:12:45.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,准了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.40,0:12:48.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇　還真的是一秒就…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.41,0:12:49.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是秋子阿姨對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.15,0:12:53.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是　還是跟家裡的人打個電話比較好唷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.87,0:12:56.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是太晚的話家人會擔心的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.65,0:13:02.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪喔　沒人接耶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.53,0:13:04.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會不會是出門了呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.01,0:13:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　我想起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.79,0:13:09.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我家裡的人去旅行了所以不在家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.75,0:13:10.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.74,0:13:13.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種事不要忘記啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.41,0:13:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的耶　為什麼我會忘記呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.33,0:13:19.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說　亞由
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.65,0:13:22.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在妳的家人回來之前　要不要住在這裡呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.73,0:13:23.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.51,0:13:25.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是個好主意　對妳來說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.95,0:13:27.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,後面那句話是多餘的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.78,0:13:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒關係的唷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.00,0:13:31.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正還有很多房間…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.18,0:13:32.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.97,0:13:34.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這麼辦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.96,0:13:37.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是說妳晚上一個人住也沒關係？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.53,0:13:39.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能沒關係！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.95,0:13:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這麼決定　今天開始一起住囉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.36,0:13:43.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.92,0:13:45.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常歡迎唷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.11,0:13:48.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就麻煩你們照顧了！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.37,0:14:15.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真琴她怎麼了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.15,0:14:18.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙…　已經回家了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.37,0:14:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回自己的家？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.90,0:14:21.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個嘛　算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.22,0:14:24.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯～這樣啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.75,0:14:28.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好想再一次…跟她說說話呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.40,0:14:35.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亞由她要住在這裡　妳好像很高興呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.38,0:14:40.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　我們少了一個家人對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.76,0:14:43.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然表面上裝得很開朗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.75,0:14:46.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但媽媽她…好像很寂寞的樣子…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.86,0:14:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有…我也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.45,0:14:52.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以　多虧了亞由讓家裡熱鬧起來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.83,0:14:54.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很高興
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.52,0:14:59.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且　我覺得我一定可以跟亞由成為很好的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.97,0:15:04.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　你做什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.12,0:15:08.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳想得還真不少啊　雖然看起來呆呆的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.30,0:15:10.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,後面那句話是多餘的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.04,0:15:12.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡水放好囉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.59,0:15:15.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼　我們一起洗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.85,0:15:17.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎　那我們去洗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.16,0:15:19.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祐一你不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.19,0:15:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先去洗囉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.33,0:15:26.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.01,0:15:32.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳還沒吃夠苦頭　又跑來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.84,0:15:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也好久沒來這裡了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.06,0:15:40.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為最近都待在真琴旁邊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.76,0:15:42.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.15,0:15:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這說來話長了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.37,0:15:46.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總而言之　先來吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.18,0:15:50.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳想從什麼開始吃起？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.25,0:15:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上等鮪魚肚…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.75,0:15:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,便利商店的壽司哪來那種東西啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.29,0:15:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐點吃蔥花鮪魚肚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.11,0:16:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃的時候也不能大意…嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.53,0:16:06.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳也差不多可以告訴我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.94,0:16:09.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼妳會一個人在這裡戰鬥？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.70,0:16:13.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得…就算說了也不會有人相信…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.21,0:16:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒這回事吧　至少佐祐理學姊應該會聽妳說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.76,0:16:24.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…我不想讓佐祐理擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.91,0:16:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這我是能理解啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.30,0:16:31.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼妖魔要襲擊妳呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.70,0:16:33.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,牠們的目的是什麼呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.15,0:16:35.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.84,0:16:39.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒妖魔的話就能知道了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.37,0:16:43.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…也許吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.34,0:16:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,關於那孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.83,0:16:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　妳是說真琴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.59,0:16:51.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或許聽起來難以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.19,0:16:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不　如果是妳的話應該會相信吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.83,0:17:02.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我差不多該走了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.63,0:17:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天見囉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.19,0:17:15.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都已經睡了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.39,0:17:34.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個…是妳做的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.81,0:17:37.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈　我是想當做回禮的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.62,0:17:38.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是失敗了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.14,0:17:40.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好強烈的味道喔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.68,0:17:44.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個…　難道是荷包蛋？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.13,0:17:45.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害！　真虧妳看得出來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.81,0:17:47.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在不是佩服的時候吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.45,0:17:49.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗚咕…　對不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.03,0:17:53.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,結果　只能不吃早餐了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.31,0:17:57.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亞由留下來沒問題嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.52,0:18:01.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係吧　她本人都說要幫忙收拾了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.75,0:18:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是她不會遲到嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.89,0:18:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亞由她…到底是唸哪間學校呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.60,0:18:08.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　這麼說來　到底是哪裡呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.75,0:18:14.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呼　總算是趕上了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.36,0:18:16.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,距離上課時間還有十分鐘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.77,0:18:17.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刷新記錄了唷
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.33,0:18:19.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還真是奇蹟呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.68,0:18:21.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽到你們兩個的對話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.80,0:18:23.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓人覺得奇蹟也未免太廉價了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.29,0:18:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,香里　早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.94,0:18:28.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天已經做好會遲到的覺悟了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.68,0:18:31.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到還早到十分鐘　這可是奇蹟啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.56,0:18:34.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相澤君　所謂的奇蹟…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.65,0:18:36.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是那麼簡單就會發生的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.94,0:18:37.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.13,0:18:39.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了　再見
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.68,0:18:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,香里那傢伙　今天心情不好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.68,0:18:45.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看來是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.65,0:18:51.26,PS,,0000,0000,0000,,（此為日本文學名作《山椒大夫》其中的名句）
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.65,0:18:48.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想念安壽呀　HO─YAREHO
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.62,0:18:51.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想念廚子王呀　HO─YAREHO
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.65,0:18:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鳥若有生命…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.13,0:18:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,禮服？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.24,0:18:58.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　如果妳有的話我想跟妳借
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.35,0:19:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…很抱歉　想不到什麼主意…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.35,0:19:04.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.07,0:19:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,名雪　午休了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.31,0:19:11.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,名雪！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.21,0:19:15.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法　她完全睡死了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.20,0:19:18.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請問相澤祐一同學在嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.31,0:19:20.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是誰啊　好漂亮…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.77,0:19:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是三年級的倉田學姊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.04,0:19:26.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相澤！　為什麼你會認識這麼漂亮的人　給我說清楚！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.31,0:19:28.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　我在趕時間　等等再說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.65,0:19:33.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咕～不可原諒　竟然跟那麼漂亮的人…跟那麼漂亮的人～～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.73,0:19:34.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡那種類型啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.10,0:19:35.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊　不是啦　我比較喜歡妳啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.00,0:19:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳拿到禮服了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.82,0:19:43.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯　我從熟人那邊借來的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.17,0:19:46.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想要快點讓你知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.33,0:19:47.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好耶！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.26,0:19:48.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了呢！　舞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.29,0:19:52.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再表現得高興一點嘛　來嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.64,0:19:54.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萬歲！　萬歲！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.82,0:20:00.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佐祐理的禮服跟祐一的燕尾服也都借來了唷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.25,0:20:02.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？　我也要參加嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.38,0:20:06.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然啊　明天就三個人一起去玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.66,0:20:07.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好嗎？　舞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.16,0:20:09.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.49,0:20:14.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天送來的可是很豪華的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.84,0:20:15.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.86,0:20:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又快又便宜又好吃的牛丼喔！　牛丼！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.01,0:20:21.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舞妳討厭吃牛丼嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.36,0:20:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…不討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.76,0:20:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳喜歡醬汁多的還是少的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.60,0:20:28.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…多的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.58,0:20:30.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好　那妳吃這一份
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.04,0:20:37.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.15,0:20:39.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…我沒辦法吃
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.19,0:20:41.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳把劍放下來不就行了？　把劍放下來！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.22,0:20:48.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是　竟然可以這麼簡單就借到禮服跟燕尾服…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.69,0:20:52.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佐祐理學姊難道是有錢人家的大小姐嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.02,0:20:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個人…真的什麼都沒察覺嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.50,0:21:01.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,…應該是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.99,0:21:09.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說妳啊…都不會笑嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.42,0:21:14.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多點笑容嘛　明天可是要展現妳的優點給大家看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.26,0:21:23.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好　ＹＥＳ是蜂蜜小熊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.68,0:21:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,問答題啦　問答題
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.55,0:21:30.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ＹＥＳ是蜂蜜小熊　ＮＯ則是碰碰狸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.97,0:21:32.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話稍微有點吸引力…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.83,0:21:33.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.96,0:21:35.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂！　舞！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.93,0:21:45.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舞…舞！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.67,0:21:49.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳解決牠了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.21,0:21:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘿哈豪要喏…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.57,0:21:53.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我吞下去再說話！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.70,0:21:57.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被牠逃掉了…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.95,0:21:59.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不必重講一遍我也知道啦

;次回預告
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.45,0:23:44.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相澤！水瀨！　你們看看這個！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.82,0:23:46.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.75,0:23:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是學生會長　我叫久瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.95,0:23:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜂蜜小熊…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.58,0:23:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.66,0:23:54.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可要警告妳　川澄同學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.11,0:23:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,碰碰狸…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.75,0:23:58.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好自為之吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.69,0:24:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜂蜜小熊…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.69,0:24:05.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…不習慣這種場合
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.90,0:24:09.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)}我希望祐一你能在我身邊

;次回標題
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.39,0:24:11.43,Title,,0000,0000,0070,,{\fad(500,0)}第12話
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.39,0:24:11.43,Title,,0000,0000,0040,,{\fad(500,0)}古怪的圓舞曲


Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.90,0:00:37.73,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H995D56&}ありがとう言わないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.17,0:00:39.45,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H995D56&}ずっとしまっておく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.45,0:00:49.44,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,200)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H995D56&\t(0,2790,\1c&H3F4C56&)}ずっとしまっておく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.44,0:00:49.58,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H3F4C56&}さよならは翳りない夢のあと静かに降り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.58,0:00:59.93,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H3F4C56&\t(0,2670,\1c&H4484DD&)}さよならは翳りない夢のあと静かに降り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.93,0:01:08.16,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H4484DD&\t(0,2710,\1c&H6D4C47&)}さよならは翳りない夢のあと静かに降り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.16,0:01:10.06,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H6D4C47&\t(0,0280,\1c&H4672BB&)}さよならは翳りない夢のあと静かに降り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.06,0:01:10.53,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,200)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H6D4C47&\t(0,0280,\1c&H995D56&)}さよならは翳りない夢のあと静かに降り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.44,0:01:11.02,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H995D56&}両手には降り注ぐかけらを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.02,0:01:13.32,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H995D56&\t(0,0250,\1c&H72959D&)}両手には降り注ぐかけらを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.32,0:01:15.90,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H72959D&\t(0,0450,\1c&H985C66&)}両手には降り注ぐかけらを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.90,0:01:21.04,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,200)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H985C66&\t(0,0500,\1c&H4F586A&)}両手には降り注ぐかけらを
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.80,0:01:21.11,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,000)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H4F586A&}いつまでもいつまでも抱いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.11,0:01:31.37,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,200)\pos(350,385)}{\1c&H4F586A&\t(0,1550,\1c&H4672BB&)}いつまでもいつまでも抱いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.97,0:01:50.81,OPjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\pos(360,385)}{\1c&H4672BB&}最後まで笑ってる強さをもう知っていた
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓OPCN↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.90,0:00:37.73,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H995D56&}不會訴說內心的「感謝」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.17,0:00:39.45,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H995D56&}而就此永遠珍藏於心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.45,0:00:49.44,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,200)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H995D56&\t(0,2790,\1c&H3F4C56&)}而就此永遠珍藏於心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.44,0:00:49.58,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H3F4C56&}「再見」悄無聲息地降臨到晶瑩的夢之彼岸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.58,0:00:59.93,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H3F4C56&\t(0,2670,\1c&H4484DD&)}「再見」悄無聲息地降臨到晶瑩的夢之彼岸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.93,0:01:08.16,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H4484DD&\t(0,2710,\1c&H6D4C47&)}「再見」悄無聲息地降臨到晶瑩的夢之彼岸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.16,0:01:10.06,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H6D4C47&\t(0,0280,\1c&H4672BB&)}「再見」悄無聲息地降臨到晶瑩的夢之彼岸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.06,0:01:10.53,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,200)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H6D4C47&\t(0,0280,\1c&H995D56&)}「再見」悄無聲息地降臨到晶瑩的夢之彼岸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.44,0:01:11.02,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H995D56&}雙手一直懷抱著飄落下的碎片  直到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.02,0:01:13.32,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H995D56&\t(0,0250,\1c&H72959D&)}雙手一直懷抱著飄落下的碎片  直到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.32,0:01:15.90,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H72959D&\t(0,0450,\1c&H985C66&)}雙手一直懷抱著飄落下的碎片  直到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.90,0:01:21.11,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H985C66&\t(0,0500,\1c&H4F586A&)}雙手一直懷抱著飄落下的碎片  直到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.11,0:01:31.37,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(000,200)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H4F586A&\t(0,1550,\1c&H4672BB&)}雙手一直懷抱著飄落下的碎片  直到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.97,0:01:50.81,OPchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\pos(350,10)}{\1c&H4672BB&}因為已經明白  始終如一的微笑才是真正的堅強






Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.66,0:22:21.86,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k40}足{\k40}下{\k40}に{\k90}風{\k40} {\k60}光{\k100}が{\k20}{\k40}舞っ{\k60}た
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.86,0:22:15.16,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}足{\r}下に風 光が舞った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.26,0:22:15.56,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}足{\1a&H00&}下{\r}に風 光が舞った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.66,0:22:15.86,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}足下{\1a&H00&}に{\r}風 光が舞った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.06,0:22:16.26,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}足下に{\1a&H00&}風{\r} 光が舞った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.36,0:22:17.56,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}足下に風 {\1a&H00&}光{\r}が舞った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.96,0:22:18.16,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}足下に風 光{\1a&H00&}が{\r}舞った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.16,0:22:19.36,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}足下に風 光が{\1a&H00&}舞っ{\r}た
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.56,0:22:19.76,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}足下に風 光が舞っ{\1a&H00&}た{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.79,0:22:25.92,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k40}日{\k60}常{\k20}に{\k20}だ{\k80}け{\k60}{\k20}積{\k50}もっ{\k20}た{\k25}ぶ{\k25}ん{\k20}の{\k110}奇{\k50}跡{\k60}が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.99,0:22:21.29,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}日{\r}常にだけ積もったぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.39,0:22:21.69,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日{\1a&H00&}常{\r}にだけ積もったぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.99,0:22:22.29,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常{\1a&H00&}に{\r}だけ積もったぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.19,0:22:22.49,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常に{\1a&H00&}だ{\r}け積もったぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.39,0:22:22.69,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだ{\1a&H00&}け{\r}積もったぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.79,0:22:24.09,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ{\1a&H00&}積{\r}もったぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.99,0:22:24.29,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積{\1a&H00&}もっ{\r}たぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.49,0:22:24.79,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積もっ{\1a&H00&}た{\r}ぶんの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.69,0:22:24.99,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積もった{\1a&H00&}ぶ{\r}んの奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.94,0:22:25.24,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積もったぶ{\1a&H00&}ん{\r}の奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.19,0:22:25.49,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積もったぶん{\1a&H00&}の{\r}奇跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.39,0:22:25.69,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積もったぶんの{\1a&H00&}奇{\r}跡が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.49,0:22:26.79,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積もったぶんの奇{\1a&H00&}跡{\r}が
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.99,0:22:27.29,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}日常にだけ積もったぶんの奇跡{\1a&H00&}が{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.22,0:22:33.31,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k30}見{\k30}上{\k30}げ{\k30}れ{\k30}ば{\k80}雲{\k40}　{\k40}遠{\k30}く{\k90}へ{\k45}の{\k30}帰{\k60}路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.42,0:22:29.72,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}見{\r}上げれば雲　遠くへの帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.72,0:22:30.02,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見{\1a&H00&}上{\r}げれば雲　遠くへの帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.02,0:22:30.32,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上{\1a&H00&}げ{\r}れば雲　遠くへの帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.32,0:22:30.62,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げ{\1a&H00&}れ{\r}ば雲　遠くへの帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.62,0:22:30.92,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれ{\1a&H00&}ば{\r}雲　遠くへの帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.92,0:22:31.22,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれば{\1a&H00&}雲{\r}　遠くへの帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.12,0:22:32.42,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれば雲　{\1a&H00&}遠{\r}くへの帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.52,0:22:32.82,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれば雲　遠{\1a&H00&}く{\r}への帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.82,0:22:33.12,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれば雲　遠く{\1a&H00&}へ{\r}の帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.72,0:22:34.02,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれば雲　遠くへ{\1a&H00&}の{\r}帰路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.17,0:22:34.47,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれば雲　遠くへの{\1a&H00&}帰{\r}路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.47,0:22:34.77,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}見上げれば雲　遠くへの帰{\1a&H00&}路{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.48,0:22:41.72,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k60}幼{\k40}い{\k30}日{\k40}の{\k110}{\k30}自{\k50}分{\k30}よ{\k30}り{\k60}も{\k95}{\k35}早{\k120}く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.68,0:22:35.98,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}幼{\r}い日の自分よりも早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.28,0:22:36.58,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼{\1a&H00&}い{\r}日の自分よりも早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.68,0:22:36.98,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い{\1a&H00&}日{\r}の自分よりも早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.98,0:22:37.28,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日{\1a&H00&}の{\r}自分よりも早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.48,0:22:38.78,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日の{\1a&H00&}自{\r}分よりも早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.78,0:22:39.08,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日の自{\1a&H00&}分{\r}よりも早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.28,0:22:39.58,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日の自分{\1a&H00&}よ{\r}りも早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.58,0:22:39.88,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日の自分よ{\1a&H00&}り{\r}も早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.88,0:22:40.18,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日の自分より{\1a&H00&}も{\r}早く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.43,0:22:41.73,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日の自分よりも{\1a&H00&}早{\r}く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.78,0:22:42.08,EDjpn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}幼い日の自分よりも早{\1a&H00&}く{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.93,0:22:51.14,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k40}雪{\k20}解{\k20}け{\k60}を{\k30}待っ{\k20}{\k20}て{\k20}い{\k100}た{\k40}{\k25}子{\k50}供{\k25}の{\k30}よ{\k30}う{\k60}に{\k60}　{\k40}走{\k25}る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.13,0:22:46.43,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}雪{\r}解けを待っていた子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.53,0:22:46.83,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪{\1a&H00&}解{\r}けを待っていた子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.73,0:22:47.03,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解{\1a&H00&}け{\r}を待っていた子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.93,0:22:47.23,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解け{\1a&H00&}を{\r}待っていた子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.53,0:22:47.83,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを{\1a&H00&}待っ{\r}ていた子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.03,0:22:48.33,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っ{\1a&H00&}て{\r}いた子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.23,0:22:48.53,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待って{\1a&H00&}い{\r}た子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.43,0:22:48.73,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待ってい{\1a&H00&}た{\r}子供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.83,0:22:50.13,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた{\1a&H00&}子{\r}供のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.08,0:22:50.38,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた子{\1a&H00&}供{\r}のように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.58,0:22:50.88,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた子供{\1a&H00&}の{\r}ように　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.83,0:22:51.13,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた子供の{\1a&H00&}よ{\r}うに　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.13,0:22:51.43,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた子供のよ{\1a&H00&}う{\r}に　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.43,0:22:51.73,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた子供のよう{\1a&H00&}に{\r}　走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.63,0:22:52.93,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた子供のように　{\1a&H00&}走{\r}る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.03,0:22:53.33,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}雪解けを待っていた子供のように　走{\1a&H00&}る{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.96,0:22:57.07,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k60}光{\k30}る{\k25}{\k75}滴{\k100}　{\k25}飛{\k25}び{\k50}跳{\k50}ね{\k50}て{\k50}る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.16,0:22:53.46,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}光{\r}る滴　飛び跳ねてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.76,0:22:54.06,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光{\1a&H00&}る{\r}滴　飛び跳ねてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.31,0:22:54.61,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光る{\1a&H00&}滴{\r}　飛び跳ねてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.06,0:22:56.36,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光る滴　{\1a&H00&}飛{\r}び跳ねてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.31,0:22:56.61,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光る滴　飛{\1a&H00&}び{\r}跳ねてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.56,0:22:56.86,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光る滴　飛び{\1a&H00&}跳{\r}ねてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.06,0:22:57.36,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光る滴　飛び跳{\1a&H00&}ね{\r}てる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.56,0:22:57.86,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光る滴　飛び跳ね{\1a&H00&}て{\r}る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.06,0:22:58.36,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}光る滴　飛び跳ねて{\1a&H00&}る{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.47,0:23:04.57,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k20}明{\k20}日{\k40}の{\k20}出{\k45}会{\k45}い{\k45}さ{\k55}え{\k85}{\k25}気{\k20}づ{\k20}か{\k25}ず{\k30}に{\k25}い{\k40}る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.67,0:23:00.97,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}明{\r}日の出会いさえ気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.87,0:23:01.17,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明{\1a&H00&}日{\r}の出会いさえ気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.07,0:23:01.37,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日{\1a&H00&}の{\r}出会いさえ気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.47,0:23:01.77,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の{\1a&H00&}出{\r}会いさえ気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.67,0:23:01.97,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出{\1a&H00&}会{\r}いさえ気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.12,0:23:02.42,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会{\1a&H00&}い{\r}さえ気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.57,0:23:02.87,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会い{\1a&H00&}さ{\r}え気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:03.32,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさ{\1a&H00&}え{\r}気づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.42,0:23:04.72,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさえ{\1a&H00&}気{\r}づかずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.67,0:23:04.97,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさえ気{\1a&H00&}づ{\r}かずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.87,0:23:05.17,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさえ気づ{\1a&H00&}か{\r}ずにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.07,0:23:05.37,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさえ気づか{\1a&H00&}ず{\r}にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.32,0:23:05.62,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさえ気づかず{\1a&H00&}に{\r}いる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.62,0:23:05.92,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさえ気づかずに{\1a&H00&}い{\r}る
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.87,0:23:06.17,EDjp2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}明日の出会いさえ気づかずにい{\1a&H00&}る{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.06,0:23:12.05,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k25}季{\k50}節{\k25}{\k20}た{\k20}ち{\k20}の{\k20}{\k50}中{\k30}で{\k100}{\k80}輝{\k50}い{\k50}て{\k25}い{\k25}る{\k80}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.26,0:23:07.56,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}季{\r}節たちの中で輝いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.51,0:23:07.81,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季{\1a&H00&}節{\r}たちの中で輝いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.26,0:23:08.56,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節{\1a&H00&}た{\r}ちの中で輝いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.46,0:23:08.76,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節た{\1a&H00&}ち{\r}の中で輝いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.66,0:23:08.96,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たち{\1a&H00&}の{\r}中で輝いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.06,0:23:09.36,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの{\1a&H00&}中{\r}で輝いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.56,0:23:09.86,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの中{\1a&H00&}で{\r}輝いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.86,0:23:11.16,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの中で{\1a&H00&}輝{\r}いているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.66,0:23:11.96,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの中で輝{\1a&H00&}い{\r}ているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.16,0:23:12.46,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの中で輝い{\1a&H00&}て{\r}いるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.66,0:23:12.96,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの中で輝いて{\1a&H00&}い{\r}るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.91,0:23:13.21,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの中で輝いてい{\1a&H00&}る{\r}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.16,0:23:13.46,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}季節たちの中で輝いている{\1a&H00&}よ{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.20,0:23:23.37,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k20}世{\k110}界{\k80}中{\k20}に{\k20}は{\k90}ど{\k20}ん{\k40}な{\k80}想{\k20}い{\k100}も{\k50}{\k120}叶{\k30}う{\k80}日{\k60}が{\k55}く{\k60}る
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.40,0:23:14.70,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}世{\r}界中にはどんな想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.60,0:23:14.90,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世{\1a&H00&}界{\r}中にはどんな想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.70,0:23:16.00,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界{\1a&H00&}中{\r}にはどんな想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.50,0:23:16.80,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中{\1a&H00&}に{\r}はどんな想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.70,0:23:17.00,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中に{\1a&H00&}は{\r}どんな想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.90,0:23:17.20,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中には{\1a&H00&}ど{\r}んな想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.80,0:23:18.10,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはど{\1a&H00&}ん{\r}な想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.00,0:23:18.30,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどん{\1a&H00&}な{\r}想いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.40,0:23:18.70,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな{\1a&H00&}想{\r}いも叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.20,0:23:19.50,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想{\1a&H00&}い{\r}も叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.40,0:23:19.70,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想い{\1a&H00&}も{\r}叶う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.90,0:23:21.20,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想いも{\1a&H00&}叶{\r}う日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.10,0:23:22.40,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想いも叶{\1a&H00&}う{\r}日がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.40,0:23:22.70,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想いも叶う{\1a&H00&}日{\r}がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.20,0:23:23.50,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想いも叶う日{\1a&H00&}が{\r}くる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.80,0:23:24.10,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想いも叶う日が{\1a&H00&}く{\r}る
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.35,0:23:24.65,EDjp3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}世界中にはどんな想いも叶う日がく{\1a&H00&}る{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.69,0:23:33.28,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k140}ずっ{\k20}と{\k130}旅{\k20}を{\k25}{\k20}し{\k20}て{\k120}ゆ{\k30}く{\k90}僕{\k30}ら{\k60}に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.89,0:23:28.19,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}ずっ{\r}と旅をしてゆく僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.29,0:23:29.59,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっ{\1a&H00&}と{\r}旅をしてゆく僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.49,0:23:29.79,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと{\1a&H00&}旅{\r}をしてゆく僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.79,0:23:31.09,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅{\1a&H00&}を{\r}してゆく僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.26,0:23:31.56,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅を{\1a&H00&}し{\r}てゆく僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.46,0:23:31.76,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅をし{\1a&H00&}て{\r}ゆく僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.66,0:23:31.96,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅をして{\1a&H00&}ゆ{\r}く僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.86,0:23:33.16,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅をしてゆ{\1a&H00&}く{\r}僕らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.16,0:23:33.46,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅をしてゆく{\1a&H00&}僕{\r}らに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.06,0:23:34.36,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅をしてゆく僕{\1a&H00&}ら{\r}に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.36,0:23:34.66,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}ずっと旅をしてゆく僕ら{\1a&H00&}に{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.26,0:23:40.75,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(20,385)}{\k20}{\k140}小{\k20}さ{\k80}な{\k60}精{\k50}た{\k50}ち{\k60}{\k60}舞{\k20}い{\k60}降{\k20}り{\k100}る
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.46,0:23:35.76,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}{\1a&H00&}小{\r}さな精たち舞い降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.86,0:23:37.16,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小{\1a&H00&}さ{\r}な精たち舞い降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.06,0:23:37.36,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さ{\1a&H00&}な{\r}精たち舞い降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.86,0:23:38.16,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな{\1a&H00&}精{\r}たち舞い降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.46,0:23:38.76,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな精{\1a&H00&}た{\r}ち舞い降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.96,0:23:39.26,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな精た{\1a&H00&}ち{\r}舞い降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.06,0:23:40.36,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな精たち{\1a&H00&}舞{\r}い降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.66,0:23:40.96,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな精たち舞{\1a&H00&}い{\r}降りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.86,0:23:41.16,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな精たち舞い{\1a&H00&}降{\r}りる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.46,0:23:41.76,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな精たち舞い降{\1a&H00&}り{\r}る
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.66,0:23:41.96,EDjp4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\move(20,385,850,470,0,2300)}小さな精たち舞い降り{\1a&H00&}る{\r}
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓EDCN↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.66,0:22:18.40,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}在風中奔跑著  光影在眼前舞動
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.79,0:22:25.92,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}日夜的積澱匯成了奇跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.22,0:22:33.31,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}在通向遠方的歸途中  仰望所見的彩雲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.48,0:22:41.72,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}比幼時的自己奔跑得更快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.93,0:22:51.14,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}{\1c&H9B4B36&}如同一心期待冰雪消融的孩子那樣飛奔著
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.96,0:22:57.07,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}{\1c&H9B4B36&}閃亮的水珠輕快地在眼前躍動
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.47,0:23:04.57,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}{\1c&H9B4B36&}一直未被察覺的明天的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.06,0:23:12.05,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}{\1c&HA87A55&}在那季節更迭中閃爍著光輝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.20,0:23:23.37,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}{\1c&HA87A55&}世上所有的願望都終會迎來實現的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.69,0:23:33.28,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}{\1c&H3D65B7&}在不斷前行的旅途中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.26,0:23:40.75,EDchn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(20,10)}{\1c&H3D65B7&}小小的精靈們降落到了我們的面前


