Okay! This is episode 11 of the spin-off...
Collaboration #11
Let's Play with
All the Footage Up to Now
Already?
But the one thing we feared most has happened.
Huh?
The thing we feared most?
This time...
No one's schedules matched up!
What?!
Even that "What?!" was recorded
separately for each person.
That's a pain!
Tsunekawa-san, the mixer, did a good job!
Then there won't be an ad-lib part this time?
They couldn't record that with
all of us separately, I guess.
But who wants to watch 20-something
minutes of scripted stuff?
W-Well, Aoi-senpai,
that's the norm for most anime!
True, when I think of the
relaxed and informal atmosphere
that freedom has given us, I worry a little.
On top of that, we're approaching the end,
so the animation production is out of breath,
another cause for concern.
That's true.
I wonder if there's a game
we can play reusing as much
previous footage as possible,
even if we record separately.
So it would ease the burden
on animation production,
but retain that atmosphere of freedom
even if recorded separately...
I'm so lost!
Rin-chan!
Then why don't we add a new
element to the previous footage
and add new voice work to it?
You mean re-dub it?
I've had to record separately a lot for this show,
and it was fun imagining all of your reactions
while trying out different
acting styles in my recording.
Yeah! That has been fun!
Though it was a tight schedule!
All right! Then let's try adding
nuances to previous footage
to make a new collaborative dubbing!
Yeah!
How's it coming, Tomomi-chan?
Okay, I set it so it displays randomly.
Who receives what directions
will all depend on luck.
All right, everyone!
The anime footage will be
on the right screen.
A random "nuance" telling you how to
act it out will be on the left screen,
so follow what it says, okay?
Okay!
Then let's start with episode 1!
"Nuance Dubbing Theater" will now begin!
Here are the members of
Apprentice Goddess Puru-Purun Charm,
whom we're fortunate
enough to collaborate with.
Looking forward to working with you.
Tesaguri Club
>> Trying to act cute to the point of cunning
Apprentice Goddesses
>> While sobbing
Puru-Purun Charm is kind of unique
Tesaguri Club
>> Trying to act cute to the point of cunning
Apprentice Goddesses
>> While sobbing
in that, even though it isn't set to have
an anime adaptation yet, some of
the cast has already been chosen.
And they're all popular voice actors who have
their own regular radio programs, too.
Things sure are different when you
have the support of a big publisher!
Are you sure you're allowed
to say things like that?
But it's a bit daunting being allowed
to collaborate with such a proper work.
But, Koharun, it means we're
helping Charm-san with their
long-sought goal of becoming an anime.
We get the opportunity to do a one-cour
spin-off in a fresh environment.
We're perfect collaboration partners, aren't we?
You're the type that doesn't shy away
from all the grown-up talk, huh?
So how are we collaborating, again?
We've never had an anime adaptation before!
I don't know what we're supposed to do!
I never thought we'd have such a unique start!
Well, since it's a collaboration,
why don't we all do something
together each episode?
All of us?
People with light-colored hair
>> Heavy metal-like shouting
Dark hair
>> Like an old woman without her dentures
People with light-colored hair
>> Heavy metal-like shouting
Dark hair
>> Like an old woman without her dentures
The Apprentice Goddesses!
They are five girls guided
by the five basic elements
to maintain harmony throughout the countless
parallel worlds existing within the same dimension!
All right, shall we begin the regular
Apprentice Goddess briefing?
We shall!
Um, there's one person who's not here yet!
Hey, what is that?
Whoa, it's huge!
Come on!
I don't think it's safe to get close.
Zdravstvujte!
What language is that?!
There was a one-frame comic in the
Puru-Purun Charm manga where you could
put in whatever dialogue you want.
How about we have fun with this?
Agreed!
Then let's all think of a new
one-frame slice-of-life manga!
My new one-frame slice-of-life manga!
"Now that I look more closely,
she has four accessory nipples!"
Cow!
I was thinking that, too!
Seriously?
"How much is it?"
Yuck!
We're trying to get on friendly terms with
the Puru-Purun Charm people now...
Let's not talk about paying money
to touch their boobs and stuff.
There are four accessory nipples,
so it might be
Puru-puru-puru-puru-puru-purun Charm!
And there might be more
buttons underneath, so...
That's true!
Puru-puru-puru-puru-puru-puru-
puru-puru-puru-purun Charm!
People whose names have two hiragana characters
>> With wrong intonation here and there
Three hiragana characters
>> Totally sexily
What's your short-term goal, Hina-chan?
People whose names have two hiragana characters
>> With wrong intonation here and there
Three hiragana characters
>> Totally sexily
Let's see...
I have a lot of homework at the moment,
so I feel like I need to do that.
I see.
What's your short-term goal, Rin-chan?
I guess convincing Hina-chan
to let me copy her homework.
That's nothing to laugh about!
How about you, Kanon-chan?
I'm perfect other than being short,
so if I grow taller, I might as well be a goddess.
I'm tall.
I do gymnastics, so I don't
want to grow any taller.
If anything, I wish I were
your height, Kanon-chan.
I think we're about the same height, Yui-san.
That's right! You want to be me, right?
She didn't say she wanted
to be you, Kanon-chan.
Um...
What?!
Nothing.
Koharun, you seemed envious earlier when
you were looking at Hiina-senpai's chest.
No, I wasn't particularly envious,
but I wish I could experience
being as big as Hiina-senpai once!
But the person voicing her...
What?
People whose names have two hiragana characters
>> Someone with no rhythm
Three hiragana characters
>> With your mouth hanging open
Hey, Grandmob, what kind of anime
is Tesagure! Bukatsumono?
People whose names have two hiragana characters
>> Someone with no rhythm
Three hiragana characters
>> With your mouth hanging open
First, watch this!
I welcome all of your attacking tackles.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on!
I call it a "hugby."
That sounds too hot!
They're all rather fruity guys,
so they go after each other for hugs.
Oh, what a handsome guy.
If they're lucky, they might
catch a different kind of ball.
Two balls! Two balls!
Grab hard!
We do silly stuff like this all the time...
But we have a good reason for it.
There's no single thing that we have to do or be.
So why don't you join us to look for
whatever it is that suits you?
If you accept yourself,
other people will accept you, too.
We'll make a place for you
in this place right here.
It's more important who you spend time with
than what you spend time doing.
There's no need to hold back.
Let's grow together!
Grandmob, I think I understand a little
more about Tesagure! Bukatsumono now!
They still have a long way to go,
but I hope we can grow along with them.
First-years
>> Read all kanji wrong
Second-years
>> Whistling dialogue
Third-years
>> As if you're falling down a hole
Okay! Then let's go the opposite way and
try coming up with a "new interview style"!
First-years
>> Read all kanji wrong
Second-years
>> Whistling dialogue
Third-years
>> As if you're falling down a hole
Yuikoromo-san's "new interview style"!
Come and get me.
Rin-san! Um, you're the MC, right?
Are you aware of that?
Aware...
Where did that question come from?
I mean, there are five of us here!
That's quite a lot!
I'm asking if you, as the one who
holds us together, should be like that!
Should I give a real answer?
Put pressure back on her!
I see.
Hurry up and put pressure back on me!
I feel bad already!
I don't really know!
First-years
>> Rap style
Second-years
>> Whistling dialogue
Third-years
>> Apologetically, while crying
Okay, the first theme is... uh....
First-years
>> Rap style
Second-years
>> Whistling dialogue
Third-years
>> Apologetically, while crying
Girls who are popular with boys!
Got it!
Then here I go!
A girl who acts cute!
Big boobs!
Wow, you suck so bad!
I just can't do this!
Man, Hiina!
It hit you in the crotch!
It's almost like the ball
was aiming at my crotch!
Okay, here I go!
Is attentive!
Runs like a girl!
Um...
And it hit my crotch!
I can't stand it! Enough already!
Her! We're aiming for her!
She's in charge of the crotches!
What does someone in charge of crotches do?
If you wear pajamas to bed
>> Talk like Mobumi
If you wear sweats to bed
>> Talk like Mobusaemon
Okay, Koharun's "new school song."
If you wear pajamas to bed
>> Talk like Mobumi
If you wear sweats to bed
>> Talk like Mobusaemon
It's got cute choreography.
"Boom-chaka-chaka"?
What kind of choreography goes
with a "boom-chaka-chaka" melody?
Huh, what kind?
Three, four...
Boom-chaka-chaka, boom-chaka-chaka,
boom-chaka-chaka...
That's not cute at all!
Standing bowlegged...
Boom-chaka-chaka...
That's awful!
You're bowlegged!
Radio calisthenics?!
Boom-chaka-chaka, boom-chaka-chaka...
Kind of like idols...
Don't make light of idols!
Oh, that's right!
Her real job! Her real job!
You little!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
If you'd go into a beef bowl shop alone
>> Talk like you're bothered by
something stuck between your molars
If you wouldn't
>> Get every emotional beat wrong
"While in a hypnotic state,
If you'd go into a beef bowl shop alone
>> Talk like you're bothered by
something stuck between your molars
If you wouldn't
>> Get every emotional beat wrong
the students will take a spiritual
field trip through history,
from the birth of the Earth to the present,
and will become..."
I can't read the kanji.
Kanon-chan! What's it say?
I'm sorry. Mio-senpai is dumb.
How is this...
"Will become omniscient."
Omniscient?
Oh, okay.
"They will take a spiritual
field trip through history,
from the birth of the Earth to the present...
and will become..." omnipotent?
Omniscient!
Omniscient? "And will awaken feeling radiant."
How many people understood that?
It feels like we made it through!
More than her actual idea,
too much focus went into
the process of reading it.
Kanon-chan, is that how you talk
to someone you've just met?
I'm sorry.
If you know where Fukui Prefecture is
>> Like a painter who loves rice balls
If you don't know
>> Talking with cellophane over your mouth
If you know where Fukui Prefecture is
>> Like a painter who loves rice balls
If you don't know
>> Talking with cellophane over your mouth
Hiina's "new haunted house."
Some of the ghosts provide
on-stage accompaniment.
Accompaniment?
What's that like?
When a ghost is about to come out, the MC says,
"Here's our next ghost! Take it away!"
Then it goes, chan-chaka-chan-chaka-chan!
"Thank you!"
I don't think it's "chan-chaka-chan."
"Please remember me."
He sounds friendly.
And suddenly, Okiku-san starts counting plates...
"What the heck are you doing?"
Hiina's really into this.
This is unusual!
She seems like she's having fun today!
It's such an unusual sight,
I almost can't even look at her!
This is the first time Hiina...
I feel a little embarrassed somehow!
Yeah!
"What the heck are you doing?"
Don't delve into that part! Get into my idea!
Everyone loves it.
How do you feel?
Chan-chaka-chan-chaka!
"What the heck are you doing?"
I know I'm gonna remember this and
laugh before I go to bed tonight.
If you pronounce it "a-vo-cado"
>> Pinch your nose and say "pyon"
at the end of every sentence
If you pronounce it "a-va-cado"
>> Give a needlessly breathy performance
I'd like to hear Aoi-san's idea.
If you pronounce it "a-vo-cado"
>> Pinch your nose and say "pyon"
at the end of every sentence
If you pronounce it "a-va-cado"
>> Give a needlessly breathy performance
Okay, Aoi-san's "new dentist."
Um, the dentist's greeting is "Tooth," pyon!
"Tooth! What seems to be
the problem today, pyon?"
"Okay, I'll see you next time.
Tooth!" Like that, pyon.
He says "tooth" to everything, pyon.
Oh, my, pyon!
What a smug face. She looks so smug.
That was...
That was an out-of-character laugh for me.
That could actually be pretty funny.
That was a pretty high-level gag.
Then...
Rin-chan, ready to fight?
Tooth, pyon.
I'll fight. Okay, I'll give you my "new dentist."
Okay, I'll make a comeback!
Um, the drill... is a multiplication drill!
O-Oh, pyon!
Right. See, it's a multiplication drill,
where the dentist says,
"I'm going to drill your tooth with this,"
and then the patient
Drill
has to solve the problems first!
What do you think, Aoi-san, pyon?
Totally boring, pyon!
That's really cutting, pyon.
That's not good!
Words can be a lethal weapon.
The Tesaguri Club gags are too advanced!
I touched a nerve, didn't I?
There's no way I could've beaten "tooth!"
"Tooth" was just too good.
If you've ever fallen asleep during class
and hit your head on the desk
>> The malice residing in your left hand
occasionally goes out of control
If you haven't
>> In a virtuous tone
We're just heading down now.
If you've ever fallen asleep during class
and hit your head on the desk
>> The malice residing in your left hand
occasionally goes out of control
If you haven't
>> In a virtuous tone
It's okay. There's nothing to be scared of.
The girlfriend's moving away!
It's totally safe! Look!
What's wrong? Are you gonna vomit?
No, no! Just stay back! Keep away!
What?! What's wrong?! Are you okay?!
You're dirty, so stay away!
Huh? Huh?
I hate this, I hate this, I hate this!
Hiina-chan, huh?!
Don't! Don't!
Are you okay?!
Don't! Knock it off!
Should I give you a boob rub?
The worst.
Just because this is a locked room...
You're the worst.
Locked room love!
If you've ever written an embarrassing poem
>> Like a middle-aged man committing sexual harassment
If you haven't
>> Voice recorded on a radio cassette recorder
Okay, Kanon-chan's "new ferris wheel."
If you've ever written an embarrassing poem
>> Like a middle-aged man committing sexual harassment
If you haven't
>> Voice recorded on a radio cassette recorder
It's members only.
You can't ride without an introduction.
What do you mean?
A ferris wheel that you need to
know a member to be able to ride?
Right.
You can't ride the ferris wheel
without an introduction from someone
who's already been on it.
I see.
You didn't understand what she
meant by "without an introduction"?
I thought it had something to do
with a guy from the Edo period...
Edo period?
Oh, boy!
If you've accidentally called your teacher "Mom" before
>> Spin in front of the mic
If you haven't
>> Talk like a fairy
Flutter, flutter, flutter!
If you've accidentally called your teacher "Mom" before
>> Spin in front of the mic
If you haven't
>> Talk like a fairy
This is the Tosei Private
High School girls' dormitory.
Lurking here is an actual yuri girl who has been
attacking unwilling girls every night.
Flutter, flutter!
It's like draft beer. When you say,
"I'll start with whatever's on tap."
"I'll go with Kanon-chan for now."
Koharu-san next to me.
What is it?
Like she didn't want anyone around her to see.
Regarding this activity,
I'll make this clear now.
I'm a normal student.
They can't tell a fortune right now, right?
Right, like, if you were guessing the yuri,
maybe you should say it...
I just said that, but if I were a Yuriwolf,
I wouldn't say it because it'd
make people suspect me.
Then I don't think Aoi-san is the one.
I really love men!
Do you really like guys?
If you've accidentally called your teacher "Mom" before
>> As if you're hyper in the middle of the night
If you haven't
>> From outside the booth
If it's not right now, we can't win.
If you've accidentally called your teacher "Mom" before
>> As if you're hyper in the middle of the night
If you haven't
>> From outside the booth
If one of the two was in the kendo club,
they can't protect anyone.
I'll trust you.
I read a fortune...
How many times have I said that I liked guys?!
Go ahead! Read me!
I can't get a reading on her.
What is suspicious?
I don't even know anymore.
Everyone here looks like a normal girl,
but there's a Yuriwolf among us?
I'm going to vote to banish Koharun.
That's awful!
I like hot guys!
Is this the end?
Or will the Yuriwolf dine again when night falls?
It's true that my character likes
both men and women, but...
The person most likely to be a Yuriwolf is...
Yua-san!
At this rate, all of us will
fall prey to the Yuriwolf!
I have to do something!
People who watched this broadcast in real time
>> Think of this as an incredibly important audition
People who saw it afterwards
>> As if tteokbokki has been stuffed down the back of your shirt
People who honestly almost never watch it
>> Voice recorded on a radio cassette recorder
I'm the fortune-teller!
People who watched this broadcast in real time
>> Think of this as an incredibly important audition
People who saw it afterwards
>> As if tteokbokki has been stuffed down the back of your shirt
People who honestly almost never watch it
>> Voice recorded on a radio cassette recorder
There're two fortune-tellers?
One!
You're totally lying!
No, no, no!
Huh?
This is the person who will be banished
per the result of the trial.
I like... boys!
Tesagure!
Yuri
Tesagure! Tesagure!
I wonder how long that friendship will last!
Yua-san! Yua-san!
Time is up.
Everyone, please choose
one person to banish.
I... like boys!
That was delicious!
Wait! What is this?
I'll break it down.
The Yuriwolves were Aoi and Koharun!
Yay!
TesaPurun
>>Imitating "Hego"
Tomomi-san!
TesaPurun
>> Imitating "Hego"
Yes?
Comrade Tomomi-san.
First, what do you mean by "comrade"?
Um, by "comrade," I meant we
share the same objective.
I see.
You know what "objective" means?
"Objective" is... the moment
when two hearts overlap.
Please stop.
And I embarrassed you!
Is Tomomi-san okay?
But "comrade" is a little hard to understand.
Do you know what "objective" means?
It's like, you know...
Like what?
Will. Consciousness.
Consciousness?!
I see.
Enthusiasm! Energy! Consciousness!
If you don't have consciousness, you're done!
That's important!
If you don't have consciousness,
your eyes would roll back in your head.
No! They can't roll back!
Your eyes...
TesaPurun
>> The favorite way you've done it from all of these
"So to summarize, in a dirty sort of way...
First bonito caught."
TesaPurun
>> The favorite way you've done it from all of these
What is that?!
You can't say that!
That just doesn't sound right!
I don't know what it means!
I used it because
I don't know what it means.
My stomach... My stomach hurts...
That's hilarious!
"So to summarize" is funny.
It tells you something was leading up to it.
There's this long explanation, then...
"So to summarize, in a dirty sort of way...
first bonito caught."
That's terrible, though!
I have no idea what's going on!
All right! I think we all did great!
TesaPurun
I-Is it okay to broadcast this?
This is like an "official" MAD movie.
And so, next week is the
last episode of the spin-off!
It'll totally be the Tesaguri grand prix!
Preview
Sonota
You can't even come together
as one to act? Laughable!
If our hearts can't work as
one at a time like this,
then I have no right to
play 18 characters!
I'll put you out of your
misery once and for all!
Grandmob!
Senile fool!
I've been waiting for you to say that!
Grandmob has a bomb strapped to her back!
What?!
Thank you for everything.
Grandmob!
Collaboration #12
Let's Play with a Totally Tesaguri Grand Prix