Did we get that again?
Collaboration #10
Let's Play with Beauty Salons
and Comic Haiku
Kanon-chan, what's wrong?
My bangs were cut too short...
Ah. So they were.
Um... I know how you feel, but cheer up.
I'll do everything in my power to make
that beauty salon go out of business!
I know how you feel, but calm down!
Is it really worth getting so down about?
Of course it is! A girl's hair is her life!
I really don't think it's anything to worry about.
In fact, I think you look cuter this way.
Really? How so?
You look younger with short bangs!
Or I should say "even younger"?
What's the point of making her
even more depressed?
What's this? Going for a
new look, Comrade Kanon?
I guess...
I think it suits you well. It's cute!
I don't... need any more of that.
You seem fed up with something.
I see... It's true that
girls are creatures who spout "Cute!" reflexively,
even about things that aren't cute at all.
But I sincerely think you are cute, Comrade.
Thanks...
People are reacting to your haircut.
That's something, anyway.
It's sad when nobody notices.
I get my hair trimmed pretty frequently.
But since it's always long,
nobody ever notices.
I'm the same way.
In the first place, my hair grows fast.
I wonder if I have a dirty mind?
Don't ask me that.
Did you know? They say if you have
a dirty mind, your hair grows faster!
I've heard that before!
Then Yua-senpai must cut her hair every day.
Hey, hey, hey! I do not!
Then in those weeks between the end of our
first year and the beginning of our second,
Aoi must have been focusing on dirty thoughts.
Kopochin!
Two balls!
All right, today, we'd like to think of a
"new beauty salon" with these members!
Okay!
Okay.
Okay, I'll go.
Go, go.
All right. Um, my "new beauty salon."
The hairdresser has a short temper,
and he gets angry really easily.
As he's snipping, he snaps.
Tomomi-san laughed!
As he's snipping, he snaps!
That's so stupid!
I don't really understand
Tomomi-san's sense of humor.
But I'm happy! Tomomi-san laughed!
You sort of... caught me by surprise.
To be honest, it was funny.
Yay!
To be honest?
Isn't anyone going to try to spoil this mood?
Someone from that field can do it.
Yeah, over there. One from Yui-san's field.
Me? You singled me out, huh?
Yui-san's "new beauty salon."
As they're shampooing your hair,
they ask right in your ear, "This feel good
for ya?" and "This feel good for ya?
Why do they speak with a provincial accent?
Okay, which is better? "Does this feel good?"
Or "This feel good for ya?"
I like "This feel good for ya" better!
"This feel good for ya"!
"This feel good for ya?"
I like "This feel good for ya"!
So that is better? In the end?
Okay, next...
I'll go.
Okay, Tomomi-san's "new beauty salon."
Your hairstyle is decided by a slot machine.
There's a slot machine at the entrance,
and when you pull the lever,
the machine chooses your cut for
your bangs, your sides, and the back.
Mohawk             Sideburns
Semi-short         Pigtails
Crew Cut           Shaved Sideburns
Bar code
Front      Sides      Back
"Bowl cut" and "shaved off" are in there, too.
But depending on the combination...
Well, you could end up with a new hairstyle.
Like totally shaved in the back...
But leaving the sides, and long in the front.
That's possible.
Oh, like *****?
Maybe that's how he decided on his hairstyle.
By slot machine?
He's a gambler, huh?
Isn't that crazy?
It's like testing your luck.
Yeah. when you're ready to turn over a new leaf,
instead of buying a fortune...
Instead of buying a fortune,
you get this shaved.
Right.
Tomomi-san gets her sides shaved,
and her bangs are...
What's happening with my hair?
In the end, you'd be bald...
Knock it off.
Sorry, but I just thought "gross" to myself.
Thinking of Tomomi-san like that...
Don't imagine someone bald and laugh!
Sorry.
Hiina-san!
Sorry Rin-chan said that.
Okay, let's continue.
Okay, I'll go.
All right, Hiina-san's "new beauty salon."
The stylist only talks about his son,
who recently became a comedian.
The famous stylist talks about his
comedian son the entire time,
but the son isn't very successful.
He tells you all about how
he asks people if he's funny and hopes they'll say yes, even if it's a lie,
but when he was told his son had no chance,
tears came to his eyes.
He only talks about things that
are awkward to respond to.
Yeah. That's all he talks about.
But the father is a famous stylist, right?
Yes, he is really popular.
Then the father could support his son...
That's true.
Except there's an older son, too.
It'd be hard, then.
Yeah, the living expenses...
So the two brothers don't get along.
They don't.
The father is cut in the middle,
but keeps on cutting hair.
If the father is a famous stylist...
Wait a second.
You got that, didn't you?
Um, the father is cut in the middle...
Not "caught" in the middle, right?
Yeah, not "caught"!
She even did a gesture.
I didn't catch that.
Yeah.
I think I liked Rin-san's gag better.
Okay. Maybe I'll go.
Bring it!
My "new hair salon."
The hair iron is one of those machines
that makes hot sandwiches.
She laughed...
She laughed at her own joke.
That was totally an invitation
for everyone to laugh.
She looked so smug!
No, you know those machines that
make hot sandwiches, right?
You use that as a hair iron, too,
and kill two birds with one stone.
And when you use it, you can smell butter!
It smells delicious!
Wow!
You must be happy, huh, Rin-chan?
Good for you.
Rin-chan, you must be happy.
Good for you!
Yua-san, what is that?
I pretended to think it was funny!
Does she laugh at things easily?
Shut up!
She does.
My image is that she'll laugh at anything.
Like at the cigarette shop...
What about the cigarette shop?
What's this about?
Tomomi-san, finish what you say.
When I was little,
the lady at the register at the
cigarette shop was like that.
Cigarettes
She would listen to anything.
Whatever you said, she'd laugh?
Anything you said, she'd say, "Oh, how funny."
Okay, anyone want to ruin this mood?
Why do you say that after everything?
Why do you want to destroy everything we do?
Nothing's coming out of it.
Things were so peaceful!
Okay!
All right, Yua-san's "new beauty salon."
They strip you naked to give you a shampoo.
They don't get naked, but they strip us naked?
We're stripped naked.
I wouldn't want them to be naked, either!
They don't have a hair-washing chair.
Yeah. So they take you to
a place like a shower room.
Then they take off all your
clothes and give you a shampoo.
So of course the hair stylist gets naked, too.
Censored
But they do cover your face with a cloth.
Look, are you...
Is there a point to that?
Are you aware you're saying something pretty risqué?
It's okay to say that?
What are they supposed to do about the visual?
Show a picture with mosaics all over it?
Yes, please. Please add mosaics.
That's bad!
It's okay. They can hide it with steam.
Yeah, hide everything with steam.
I can't say much in detail,
but that has a "soap"-like feel to it.
A cloth would cover your face...
That's a totally different kind of shop.
Let's cover a little more than the face.
In the first place, the face
doesn't need a cloth.
Yeah, you don't. No cloth. Not for the face.
Let's cover up the Devil's Triangle.
That's new, right?
That's new.
Well, it certainly is new, but...
Yua, are you okay with that character?
Well, dirty jokes are all I have left.
Okay, tell us all of them.
Really? Okay, me!
All right.
Okay.
All right, my "new beauty salon."
When they wash your hair,
you have to sit on a delivery bed.
Your ideas are so terrible.
Wait...
They say, "This way,"
and lead you past the chairs to a delivery bed.
Your bottom half has nothing
to do with washing your hair,
but they wash it while you're
in an embarrassing pose.
Awful!
Is this okay?
Now people are going to search
"Nishi Asuka delivery bed."
No way!
People will make photos of
you on one if you say that.
Yeah, shopped photos.
Don't come crying to us.
Don't say "shopped photos"!
I'd want them to make it with Yua.
This is your character?!
Poor Yua!
You're terrible!
Are you begging them to do it?
You "want" them to?
Terrible!
Chicks
Looks like we start with chicks.
Chicks!
Chicks?
How cute!
I wanna pet them!
Here. Something's been born.
So cute!
Cute!
It's the beginning of a new life.
It's going "peep peep."
It has that newborn smell. Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
Eww!
It pooped on me!
Poop? Is it on you? On your hand?
Poop, yes!
It fell!
Wait a second...
Ah, me too! It pooped! It pooped on me!
Poop... It pooped... It pooped...
Why? Stop trying to fly high!
Ow! That's not food!
I'm not food!
Ow!
Chicks are cute.
Sorry.
Yes, thank you. Thank you.
Are you okay? Hey...
Don't, don't, don't!
She's...
Poop? Poop?
It pooped on me.
It pooped on my hand.
Your hand... Your hand...
It's on you. There's poop on you.
Yeah, it's starting to smell now.
It smells like ponies.
Yeah.
Pretty icky smell.
What's its name?
It's Aoi! Aoi!
Th-Thank you.
Aoi!
Not you! Not you.
Not you!
Its name is Aoi?
Aoi!
It's true. Her name is Aoi.
Not you!
There are two Aois?
Aoi-senpai, let's feed Aoi-chan.
One-two...
Aoi!
There she is.
Here she comes.
You want this, right? Huh?
Wow!
She chomped it up.
Her teeth are weird!
Aoi?
Hey!
Give it to her. Give it to her.
Give it to her.
Poor Aoi!
Her mouth...
Her mouth is flapping...
You're such a mean girl.
I kinda feel like training her.
Is she mad?
Look, she's mad.
See? She's mad.
Aoi, I'm sorry. Sorry... I'm sorry!
"Come on, stop bullying me!"
"'Where do you want to go?'
My daughter always says the zoo."
"Better than field guides..."
"Bird droppings are the seeds of future forests."
Animal Welfare Week                                          Animal Welfare Week
9/20-26                                                                  9/20-26
"Where do you                                                     You mean to
want to go?"                                                        look at animals,
My daughter always                                            but they're looking
says the zoo.                                                        at you.
Look at that one. "You mean to look at
animals, but they're looking at you."
They're looking at you!
What does that mean?
All right, let's try thinking of a "new zoo slogan."
But Yua-senpai, isn't it hard to
come up with things like that?
Hiina came up with an easy game
of writing 5-7-5 syllable poems.
Reliable!
Our guests are Kanon-chan and Hina-chan.
We're glad to be here.
Please go easy on us.
I'll explain the rules.
There are three piles, for the first line,
the second line, and the third line.
For the first line, you'll randomly
choose one card from the pile.
First
One person will be in charge
of the second line.
Second
That person will look at the
second line pile and choose a card
that seems like it would be funny
following the first one.
For the third line,
Third
the remaining five people are in charge.
They'll choose one funny card as the third line
from among the cards they've been dealt,
and read them one at a time.
Okay, let's give it a try.
There are a lot of cards.
We can look at our own cards, right?
Right.
What the heck?
There are all kinds of lines...
Awful!
Okay, I'll reveal the first line.
Okay.
One, two... Flip.
Riding on horseback
"Riding on horseback."
I see.
Makes sense. Animals.
I got it! Okay...
"Happy and yet embarrassed."
Happy and yet
embarrassed
Oh, no!
No!
It's some kind of...
This already sounds like something bad!
But this is all there is.
I'll go with this.
This is all I can do.
All right, um, Kanon-chan.
Here I go.
"Riding on horseback, happy and yet
embarrassed... dripping, soaking wet."
Dripping, soaking wet
Huh? Is she starting to think like us?
Huh?
No, she's higher than we are.
No, no, no!
What's soaking wet?
You're terrible!
You're scared of horses...
Uh-huh.
You're so happy, embarrassed, and scared...
Wet with tears?
...you pee.
That?!
Pee?
So your seat is soaking wet.
Soaking wet?
Where you get so scared, you wet yourself.
And that's the last line.
I see.
So the horse ends up soaking wet.
I guess it would, yeah.
It has a warm back.
Thank you. Thank you.
No, that's just weird!
Okay, next... Hina-chan.
Okay.
"Riding on horseback, happy and yet
embarrassed... overcome with love."
Overcome with love
Oh!
Oh, that's nice.
What does it mean?
Please explain.
Well, given what it follows,
it might sound weird,
but it's someone riding on a horse
to see the person that he loves.
Oh, that kind!
A prince on a white horse.
It's the story of a prince on a white horse.
I see.
Yeah.
I was imagining something really strange.
I figured!
You figured!
But that's not entirely wrong, is it?
I guess there's a double meaning.
Oh, good!
I see.
I think there are various meanings.
"Double meaning" is cool. I'm gonna use that.
Yeah.
Okay, next.
Me.
Koharun.
Mine is beautiful.
Um, "Riding on horseback, happy and yet
embarrassed... Eat napolitan!"
Eat napolitan
Wait, sorry, that's too abstract.
I don't get it.
How is that beautiful?
I don't know if it's beautiful.
There must have been a better one!
I thought this one had the best ring to it...
Oh, you just went with the sound?
The sound. I went with the feeling.
It did sound really beautiful.
Napolitan...
Napolitan.
It has no meaning.
You're a little embarrassed,
but you're eating napolitan while riding a horse.
I don't get it.
You'd get ketchup all over your face.
But I do admit that it has a beautiful ring to it.
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
Okay.
What should I do? I don't have many good ones.
Okay, next.
Me.
Hiina.
"Riding on horseback, happy and yet
embarrassed... Boi-oi-oi-oi-oing!"
Boi-oi-oi-oi-oing!
That's terrible!
Awful!
And it doesn't fit the structure, either!
What does that mean?
And it's got an exclamation point.
Yeah. "Boi-oi-oi-oi-oing!"
That doesn't fit.
Terrible!
Right?
But it's got energy...
True.
Yeah!
With the exclamation point.
It gives you a sense of the horse's motion.
Not bad.
So the horse is going "boi-oi-oi-oi-oing"?
I see.
I was thinking of clothes coming off.
Boi-oi-oi-oi-oing!
The bottoms, too?
Both, yeah.
Both? It's a double meaning!
It is a double meaning!
That's useful!
Cool!
That's a convenient expression.
That really is useful.
Okay, next.
For the last one, I'm going to be vague.
Vague?
I'm going to be vague. Here I go.
What'll it be?
"Riding on horseback, happy and yet
embarrassed... and the mood is right."
And the mood is right
Vague.
I see.
Why do these all sound kind of lewd?
Because your mind is full of lewdness.
It's still filling up.
It's still filling up?
The "bottom line" has a
different meaning now.
Yeah.
Who said you could pun on the "last line"?!
The "bottom line"
has a deep meaning here.
Okay, let's move on.
Okay.
I'll reveal the first line.
Indian elephant
"Indian elephant."
That's kind of...
Elephant?
Elephant...
"Indian elephant." The second line is...
"Parboiled terribly quickly."
What's "parboiled"?
Parboiling is when you have hot water, um...
You pass something through hot water.
Right.
Like when you're making shabu-shabu.
Right, right.
So you shabu-shabu it...
Right.
Sheesh...
I don't have anything.
I'll go.
"Indian elephant, parboiled terribly
quickly... You stupid dumbass."
You stupid dumbass
That rolls off the tongue!
What happened?!
"Dumbass"?
The Indian elephant is mad.
The instant it gets scalded,
it says, "Dumbass!"
We hit on something!
"What the hell are you doing?"
The last part is a nice zinger.
True.
The Indian elephant would be like,
"What the hell are you doing?"
That fits together neatly.
"Parboiled... You dumbass!"
He kinda cuts you off.
That's funny!
Okay, now...
Right.
Here's a zookeeper
"Here's a zookeeper."
What should I do?
"Parboiled terribly quickly."
"Here's a zookeeper,
totally without a clue..." Something.
Totally
without a clue
I've got nothing.
I don't have any funny ones.
Neither do I.
Me, neither.
Hina-chan.
Okay.
"Here's a zookeeper, totally without
a clue.... Now a bus tour guide."
Now a bus tour guide
Do your job!
He's leaving the zoo for that, huh?
You're a zookeeper!
Why a bus tour guide?
What are you doing?
Well, bus tour guides really stand out.
You never know. He may be a
bus tour guide for Safari Park.
True. That would be okay.
Somewhere along the way...
He likes to stand out.
Right.
He can do anything.
I see.
Okay, next. Koharun.
Okay. I have no idea what this means, but...
"Here's a zookeeper, totally without
a clue, for 30 long years."
For 30 long years
I get it!
The meaning totally gets across!
That's really good!
That's a really good one!
Somebody tell him sooner than
that! He's already a veteran!
He became a veteran without
ever having a clue!
Poor guy!
That's a long time!
That is long!
He's been clueless for a long time.
That's so long!
I feel bad for him.
A little.
I bet the animals hate him, too.
Yeah, I bet they do!
"He always feeds us at the wrong time!"
"You don't have to wash me there!"
"Not right now!"
That's what they think about him.
Okay, we're out of cards,
so let's do a second round.
Okay.
For the second round,
I'll be in charge of the middle line.
Cool!
Okay.
Starting with the first line.
So to summarize...
Flip!
"So to summarize..."
Isn't that kind of difficult?
This is about my only choice.
"So to summarize..."
"In a dirty sort of way."
In a dirty sort of way
"In a dirty sort of way"?
"So to summarize, in a dirty sort of way..."
Nothing else fits with "So to summarize."
Me!
Go ahead.
"So to summarize, in a dirty sort
of way... let's perk up the town."
Welcome to Sex Town
Two Girl Hunter
Afternoon Delight
Let's perk up
the town
Perk it up how?
I don't wanna go to that town!
They're suffering from depopulation,
so to perk up the town,
they decide to go with a sex theme.
It's all over for Japan.
It's over.
Yeah.
That won't help the town.
In a dirty sort of way...
There's a card that I don't understand,
so I think I'll use it here.
Okay. Then Koharun.
"So to summarize, in a dirty sort of way...
First bonito caught."
First bonito caught
You can't say that!
What is that?!
That's bad!
That just doesn't sound right!
No, wait!
I don't know what it means!
I used it because
I don't know what it means.
My stomach... My stomach hurts...
That's bad in every way!
Every part of it is bad!
First bonito caught...
That's hilarious!
"So to summarize" is funny.
It's a great prelude.
"So to summarize, in a dirty sort of way...
first bonito caught."
But that's terrible!
Preview
Sonota
Mobu...
It looks like I may finally have some fun.
King Mobuko, please!
Take down Mobustopheles!
Mobu...
Jeez! What's happening?!
Start moving from your right leg!
From the left leg is common sense!
Jump and kick!
Who are you people?
All of these Mobukos are
on different wavelengths.
Even though they've
all got the same face.
We're all supposed to be a family here!
See you next week!
Collaboration #11
Let's Play with All the Footage Up to Now