[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2016-07-31 16:06:14
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 	機動戦士ガンダムUC RE:0096
Original Script: shinjico@popgo
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
ScaledBorderAndShadow: Yes
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,FZLanTingHei-R-GBK,76,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H46000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,20,1
Style: note1,@FZLanTingHei-R-GBK,52,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H1E000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,95,100,2,-90.00,1,2,0,7,90,90,45,1
Style: note2,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,74,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H020F0F0F,&H001C1C1C,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,20,1
Style: note3,Arial,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H020F0F0F,&H00F3F3F3,0,0,0,0,92,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,20,1
Style: note4,FZFangSong-Z02,54,&H00FAFAFA,&H00000000,&H021F1F1F,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: note5,@FZFangSong-Z02,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H1E0F0F0F,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,85,100,2,-90.00,1,2,0,7,50,50,20,1
Style: title1,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,84,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H960F0F0F,&H00202020,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,2,2,80,80,30,1
Style: staff,FZZhunYuan-M02,48,&H00EBEBEB,&H00000000,&H28000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,2,8,75,75,30,1
Style: EDCN2,FZSong III-Z05,54,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H3C000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,95,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,80,80,10,1
Style: OPCN1,FZSong III-Z05,52,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H32000000,&H820F0F0F,-1,0,0,0,95,100,2,0.00,1,1,2,2,80,80,10,1
Style: INCN1,@FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,52,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H500C0C0C,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,92,100,5,-90.00,1,2,0,7,90,90,40,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//----------------------------STAF----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.76,0:23:40.76,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(960,30)\fad(700,700)}字幕制作：晶晶电脑  SHINJICO
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.84,0:23:45.84,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(960,30)\fad(700,700)}漫游字幕组\N{\fsp0\fnArial\fs32\b0}http://bbs.popgo.org/
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//----------------------------AVAN----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.82,0:00:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过拉·凯拉姆舰长布莱德策划的作战
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.86,0:00:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,葛兰雪号从玛莎·卡迈因手中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.90,0:00:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救出了密涅瓦和玛莉妲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.25,0:00:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却在返回宇宙的中途发生引擎故障
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.49,0:00:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危急时刻 独角兽高达被未知的光芒包裹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.71,0:00:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功化险为夷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.74,0:00:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但此时出现在他们面前的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.72,0:00:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是联邦军派来的雷比尔将军号舰队
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.15,0:00:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追踪拉普拉斯之盒而来的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.70,0:00:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「黑袖章」的弗卢·伏龙特尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.70,0:00:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,击退了联邦军舰队
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.82,0:00:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们总算可以聊聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.29,0:00:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盒子的钥匙 巴纳吉·林克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.45,0:00:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏匿了盒子最终坐标的巴纳吉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.98,0:00:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与密涅瓦再次相会后终于下定了决心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.52,0:00:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡帝亚斯·毕斯特不顾这些
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要将拉普拉斯之盒公之于众
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.67,0:00:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也愿意相信
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.65,0:00:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人的善意
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//----------------------------OPEN----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.06,0:01:10.70,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}Do you feel alone ?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.86,0:01:13.44,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}Can you hear me now ?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.85,0:01:19.10,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}Your mind is so far away still on earth
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.54,0:01:22.29,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}Many times you are hurting yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.42,0:01:25.04,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}You can't be just a life on the shelf
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.15,0:01:27.83,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}It's only you that can fly this new unicorn
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.94,0:01:29.89,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}Into the sky
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.23,0:01:35.80,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}And it's every time, you hurt yourself with knives
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.94,0:01:41.51,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}And I'm calling, calling out your name again
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.56,0:01:46.59,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}If you're holding, holding onto fear I knew
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.71,0:01:52.55,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}The blind can open, let light shine through
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.62,0:01:53.67,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}And I say
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.80,0:01:59.19,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}Why we can't stop all this sacrifice ?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.28,0:02:04.76,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}I know that all the lies became the stone in your heart
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.86,0:02:10.36,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}I wonder how long you gonna survive
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.48,0:02:15.26,OPCN1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}We didn't see all it's meaning
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//----------------------------TXTA----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.27,0:02:21.28,title1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(900,0)\be1\pos(960,1055)}机动战士高达UC 独角兽 RE：0096
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.99,0:02:32.52,title1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\\pos(90,60)\fad(600,600)\fs90\be1}Episode 16：SIDE共荣圈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.03,0:02:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说葛兰雪号沉了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.11,0:02:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.77,0:02:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代替吉尔博坐上驾驶席
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.99,0:02:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才刚把舵给捏热乎了…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.90,0:02:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她嘴上不情愿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.54,0:02:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对葛兰雪也挺有感情的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.39,0:02:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想几年前刚把她从垃圾堆里拾来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.46,0:02:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在比真正的亲人…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.27,0:03:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上联邦的船之前
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.47,0:03:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本打算找机会占领这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.41,0:03:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这些都不重要了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.19,0:03:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.26,0:03:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你能活着…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.79,0:03:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.58,0:04:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锚甲板上收纳的机体必须确认已经冷却
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.63,0:04:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡本舰搭载机体
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.81,0:04:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一律按规定进行日常维护
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.43,0:04:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这船内装还挺新
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.47,0:04:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说重新改装过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.66,0:04:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 竟然把机动战士搁在地板上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.41,0:04:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是被重力夺走灵魂的人的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.74,0:04:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后勤指挥所呼叫锚甲板
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.41,0:04:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于向新吉翁机动战士配给舰内电源
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.73,0:04:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已获得舰长批准
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.23,0:04:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,务必就近选站点配给
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.83,0:04:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵活应对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.80,0:04:50.94,note1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头部损伤太严重了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.03,0:04:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮游炮全部报销
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.74,0:04:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追加部件也没剩什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.24,0:04:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本属于手无寸铁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.64,0:05:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独角兽高达那边我倒有个主意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.58,0:05:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从工业七号到现在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.97,0:05:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路积累的数据都在上面
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.53,0:05:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对它进行解析 再来个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.51,0:05:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 巴纳吉？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.62,0:05:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.13,0:05:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.56,0:05:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把独角兽改强 也不知道跟谁打
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.72,0:05:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓也先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.66,0:05:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米寇特小姐怎么样了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.20,0:05:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这里还没见过她
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.24,0:05:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 吉普尼先生派她去动力室工作了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.97,0:05:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她打那以后越来越偏激
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.08,0:05:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓也呢 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.32,0:05:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嘛…嗯 还好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.82,0:05:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.55,0:05:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉普拉斯盒子的坐标
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.17,0:05:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经知道了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.69,0:05:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总不能永远藏下去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.96,0:05:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑袖章那群家伙 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.37,0:06:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在看起来还算安分…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.83,0:06:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舰桥 动力室发生异常
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.82,0:06:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不… 紧急事态！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.63,0:06:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老子一步也不会挪！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.99,0:06:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死也不挪！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.64,0:06:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.89,0:06:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,施德轮机长他…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.43,0:06:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利亚姆大副 我受够了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.87,0:06:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就叫这帮家伙滚出船上！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.87,0:06:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不记得这船什么时候归新吉翁了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.07,0:06:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮机长…！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.71,0:06:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.60,0:06:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.56,0:06:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大副你对这种情况不可能没有想法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.43,0:06:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷比尔将军号没打算给我们留活路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.77,0:06:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在只有…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.07,0:06:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就让新吉翁为所欲为吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.06,0:06:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人的敌人就是自己人 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.47,0:06:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想跟部下说这种狗屁道理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.31,0:06:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们大摇大摆在拟·阿伽玛上走动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.34,0:06:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说要在轮机房常驻士兵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.20,0:07:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了死去的战友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.57,0:07:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决不能允许这种情况继续
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.01,0:07:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新吉翁给我滚出这艘船
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.34,0:07:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 对
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.55,0:07:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快滚 快滚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.69,0:07:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.07,0:07:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想干架为什么不知会一声
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.60,0:07:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,康罗伊少校
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.87,0:07:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 ECOAS来得正好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.30,0:07:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们队长和队员不都死在他们手里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.93,0:07:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心情可以理解
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.70,0:07:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我们拒绝撤离 你打算怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.22,0:07:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来硬的也要把你们赶出这里！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.55,0:07:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装成保护我们的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.25,0:07:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打下一堆联邦的机动战士
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.71,0:07:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们保护的是盒子的钥匙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.37,0:07:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你们的死活无关
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.71,0:07:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是你们救了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.83,0:07:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一点上非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.51,0:07:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是从感情上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.57,0:07:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是无法接受你们这些杀死战友的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.60,0:07:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事上大家彼此彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.10,0:08:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安杰洛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.69,0:08:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勿轻率行事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.76,0:08:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若有失礼之处 我深表歉意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.02,0:08:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在面临共同的生存挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.70,0:08:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请暂时息怒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.99,0:08:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上地球 到底是干什么去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.90,0:08:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况越来越糟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.02,0:08:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「只有你能完成的重要任务」就是这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.91,0:08:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咳咳 舰长向全员讲话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.29,0:08:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望各位冷静听下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.28,0:08:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如各位所知
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.13,0:08:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被卷入了一场 围绕拉普拉斯之盒的争端
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.78,0:08:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常遗憾地 沦为了地球联邦军追捕的对象
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.29,0:08:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条联合阵线
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.82,0:09:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有助于我们摆脱眼下的复杂局面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.20,0:09:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不二之选
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.47,0:09:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是逆来顺受
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.20,0:09:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新吉翁军的士兵们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.06,0:09:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也并不打算进驻本舰
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.79,0:09:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了生存 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.17,0:09:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有与他们共进退
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.16,0:09:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,望诸位切忌轻举妄动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.94,0:09:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.35,0:09:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听见没？
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//----------------------------TXTB----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.22,0:09:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢您的配合
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.92,0:09:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说归说 别指望我跟新吉翁联手 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.61,0:09:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕被自己人打成筛子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.33,0:09:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,况且如果因为盒子落入你们手里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.01,0:09:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把地球圈搞得鸡犬不宁 那天理不容
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.00,0:09:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此 想保全这艘船别无选择
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.61,0:10:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以葛兰雪为诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.57,0:10:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把拉·凯拉姆引往了月神2
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.04,0:10:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便他们调头追来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.06,0:10:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰面时我们已达目的地
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.86,0:10:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目的地…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.31,0:10:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗礁宇域的正中央吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.59,0:10:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这片因鲁姆战役而闻名的暗礁宇域
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.72,0:10:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为追溯人类战争史
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.88,0:10:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传达获得盒子的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.40,0:10:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被设定为最后一站
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.93,0:10:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是合情合理
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.55,0:10:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少废话 你们不是有独角兽的资料吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.41,0:10:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何必问我们准确坐标
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.56,0:10:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得到了暗礁宇域的情报
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.48,0:10:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但未知详情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.39,0:10:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.49,0:10:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是独角兽从中阻挠吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.47,0:10:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了巴纳吉这个驾驶者
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.34,0:10:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它开始发挥原始规格中没有的性能
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.94,0:11:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如 让我们先考虑如何得到拉普拉斯之盒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.11,0:11:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盒子会成为你们的免死金牌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.64,0:11:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴纳吉也该明白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.63,0:11:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟早…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.34,0:11:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别光说我们 你想要盒子干什么用？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.48,0:11:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,号称夏亚再临
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.04,0:11:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能单纯为了复兴吉翁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.04,0:11:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今 不如说来听听
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.65,0:11:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.73,0:11:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们开诚布公吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.15,0:11:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗卢·伏龙特尔上校
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.94,0:11:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出你的真心话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.37,0:11:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.28,0:12:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不介意吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.38,0:12:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.79,0:12:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们太空移民想得到的是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.60,0:12:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独立自治权
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.99,0:12:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联邦绝不会允许
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.56,0:12:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们明白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.03,0:12:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,允许就意味着主从关系从此逆转
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.98,0:12:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理由显而易见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.13,0:12:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维持地球圈生活所需的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.35,0:12:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能源 粮食和经济活动
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.42,0:12:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依赖七大SIDE和月球运转
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.58,0:12:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球这颗星球本身
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.96,0:12:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已无法养活20亿地球居民
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相反 太空移民
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.70,0:12:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有地球仍可自给自足
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.08,0:12:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉翁·戴肯错就错在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.78,0:13:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有利用这点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.39,0:13:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他是一位优秀的思想家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.90,0:13:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但并非政治家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.28,0:13:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扎比家歪曲吉翁理念
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.41,0:13:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发动的独立战争也好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.38,0:13:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先后两次新吉翁战争也罢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.84,0:13:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道理相同
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.48,0:13:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一天不把联邦排除在意识之外
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.89,0:13:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一天不能战而胜之
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.87,0:13:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有联合月球与七大SIDE
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.85,0:13:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔除中央杂苗 培育经济环线
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.25,0:13:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建立SIDE共荣圈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.47,0:13:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想法不错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.70,0:13:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各SIDE缔结经济协定
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.39,0:13:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把地球孤立的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.02,0:13:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球很快会沦为
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.07,0:13:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有任何经济价值的穷乡僻壤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.73,0:13:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联邦政府自然也难以为继
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.36,0:13:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能统筹此事的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.78,0:13:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有吉翁共和国
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.11,0:13:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它虽是联邦傀儡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.20,0:13:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但拥有如假包换的自治权
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.80,0:14:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是 根据协定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.14,0:14:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四年之后自治权将被收回
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.44,0:14:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共和国一旦重返SIDE3体制
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.23,0:14:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去地方自治体以上的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.78,0:14:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SIDE共荣圈亦成泡影
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.25,0:14:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这时
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.24,0:14:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕斯特财团主动前来联系
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.76,0:14:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望转让拉普拉斯之盒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.01,0:14:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.09,0:14:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不相信卡帝亚斯·毕斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.67,0:14:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事先获知了我们的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.77,0:14:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单从时间上看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.12,0:14:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共和国如果解体
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.68,0:14:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联邦失去外敌 内部必然僵化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.99,0:14:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他或许不愿看到那样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.44,0:14:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而联邦欲借共和国解体根绝吉翁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.24,0:14:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这又是众所周知的事实
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.95,0:14:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以有了独角兽高达
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.26,0:14:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这台新人类神话的终结者
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.13,0:14:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上校希望利用盒子赢取时间…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.84,0:14:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,震慑联邦 拖延共和国解体的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.08,0:15:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为建立SIDE共荣圈营造条件
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.73,0:15:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.32,0:15:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦知道了 不过如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.38,0:15:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建立SIDE共荣圈使联邦边缘化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.90,0:15:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对待顽固不化的保守者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.21,0:15:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是调和 而是将其放逐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.29,0:15:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与吉翁·戴肯改变人类的梦想相去甚远
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.67,0:15:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至比起夏亚把地球化作废土
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.17,0:15:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逼迫全人类进入宇宙的疯狂举动
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.59,0:15:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都显得缺少热情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.49,0:15:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的只满足于此吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.40,0:15:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SIDE共荣圈实现之日
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.77,0:15:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球居民必会对地球进行二次开发
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.99,0:15:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了自力更生维持经济
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.90,0:15:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公元时代的景象又将重现
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.66,0:15:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被迫在贫困中成长的新一代人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.88,0:15:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千方百计寻找机会向太空移民实施报复
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.37,0:16:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像当年 吉翁发动一年战争那样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.04,0:16:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有调和也没有革新
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.82,0:16:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是强者与弱者的不断更迭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.48,0:16:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个率先站出来的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.23,0:16:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然是为了这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.62,0:16:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主殿下的志向值得钦佩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.60,0:16:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有孰好孰坏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.88,0:16:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是人世间
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.77,0:16:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,容器不思考
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.47,0:16:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它只遵从民众灌输的共同意志
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.45,0:16:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了全人类的兴亡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.13,0:16:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得好像事不关己一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.93,0:16:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明在说自己的将来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.55,0:16:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的话里 却充满事不关己的冷漠
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.75,0:16:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包裹独角兽高达的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.83,0:16:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那么温暖…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.91,0:17:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像汇聚了所有人的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.91,0:17:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类既然有那样的可能性…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.81,0:17:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我目睹过同样的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.69,0:17:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加巨大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.90,0:17:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神框体作为媒介
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.06,0:17:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把全人类的潜意识汇集一处
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.26,0:17:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转换成物理能量
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.80,0:17:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形成了足以推走小行星阿克西斯的精神力场
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.12,0:17:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿克西斯冲击…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.12,0:17:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 即使目睹了那种可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.41,0:17:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类还是没有改变
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.70,0:17:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维持现状的惰性 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.50,0:17:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不惜一切埋葬可能
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.22,0:17:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.21,0:17:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只有在现实中
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.38,0:17:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸索和平与稳定
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.50,0:17:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要明白所谓的可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.00,0:17:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意味着新旧碰撞 是一剂猛药
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.60,0:18:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所熟知的夏亚·阿兹纳布尔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.42,0:18:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来真的已经死了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.79,0:18:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工业七号上的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.63,0:18:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卫星建造者
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.41,0:18:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墨瓦腊尼加
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.80,0:18:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里就是拉普拉斯系统标示的最终坐标
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.12,0:18:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个少年难堪重负
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.32,0:18:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想得到你的确认 巴纳吉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.67,0:18:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我回一次雷乌露拉号
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.06,0:18:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦船长陪我走一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.25,0:18:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就拜托了 安杰洛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.24,0:18:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.68,0:19:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阻止盒子落入新吉翁掌控
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.00,0:19:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一点上 毕斯特财团和联邦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.46,0:19:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始终是利害一致的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.85,0:19:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对那种威胁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.75,0:19:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保盒子的安全 已不是绝对条件
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.24,0:19:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是报丧女妖原属强化人专用…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.20,0:19:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴纳吉能做到的 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.33,0:19:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也能
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.28,0:19:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…还有一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.84,0:19:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.45,0:19:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望救出被黑袖章带走的强化人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.29,0:20:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,璞露12
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.13,0:20:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理由嘛…任凭你想了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.27,0:20:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过别忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.15,0:20:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我力排众议 举荐少尉担任报丧女妖的机师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.65,0:20:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是因为看重你 不会凡事都通报姑妈他们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.73,0:20:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦报丧女妖也无法摧毁独角兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.57,0:20:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕斯特财团只能使用最终手段
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.73,0:20:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时 一切都无法挽回
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.17,0:20:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信少尉也不愿看到那样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.65,0:20:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我不得不杀了你同父异母的弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.28,0:20:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样也不介意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.23,0:20:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经血流成河了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.17,0:20:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那次是 事故…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.01,0:20:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.26,0:20:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的家族 毕斯特家内部
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.83,0:20:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血亲之间的杀戮从未停息
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.72,0:20:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑妈玛莎她
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.97,0:20:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之所以变得如此偏执
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.42,0:20:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为她父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.78,0:20:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是我们的祖父
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.16,0:21:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被曾祖父赛亚姆·毕斯特所杀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.20,0:21:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「报复男性理论支配的世界」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.39,0:21:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为男人或许不该接受这种论调…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.74,0:21:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.77,0:21:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是到了该大扫除的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.37,0:21:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们造出独角兽和报丧女妖这样的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.11,0:21:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许离毁灭已经只有一步之遥了吧…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//----------------------------EDEN----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.01,0:22:14.61,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Behind your mask
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.64,0:22:20.26,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}You smile, smile me with the greed and the frantic eyes
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.72,0:22:23.93,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}I hate it, but I can't deny it
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.00,0:22:27.21,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}I don't wanna be like you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.87,0:22:30.58,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}The feud between us escalates
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.66,0:22:35.33,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}deeper into tons of tragic wages
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.62,0:22:38.96,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Can't stand it, but I never fight it
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.03,0:22:41.58,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Though I haven't proofed enough
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.13,0:22:46.00,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Hypnotized by your charismata
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.04,0:22:49.08,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}None realized, you won't be true
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.58,0:22:53.52,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}But I know you are right if I were on your side
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.65,0:22:55.20,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}So confused...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.55,0:22:58.59,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}God, what a judgement !
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.63,0:23:00.43,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Is my punishment ?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.48,0:23:04.36,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Can't I escape from my sole bloody fate ?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.42,0:23:05.98,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Where is my fragment ?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.07,0:23:07.92,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Lost is the moment
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.98,0:23:11.41,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Need to look back what we'd done with
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.48,0:23:12.71,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}They are still crying
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.08,0:23:16.42,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Who can hold back this war of slaughter ?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.47,0:23:18.78,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Ain't no one gotta refuse
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.85,0:23:20.56,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}It doesn't really matter
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.70,0:23:24.40,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Betray myself to save the others' soul
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.50,0:23:27.22,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}Although I wanna get out of here
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.47,0:23:31.12,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}We will keep rolling
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.17,0:23:33.58,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)\blur2}to replay the One-way Freedom
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//----------------------------NEXT----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.25,0:23:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 机动战士高达独角兽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.49,0:23:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夺还！拟·阿伽马
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.04,0:23:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你体内的新人类将觉醒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
