[Script Info]
Title:To Aru Majutsu no Index II 09 gb
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H28000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,DFGBrushRD-W7,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FF860B,&H00FF0000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,1,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正卡通简体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FF860B,&H00A85400,&H00930000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,2,7,10,10,10,134
Style: edcn,方正粗倩_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64800040,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: edjp,DFPSoGei-W7,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H64800040,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,华文中宋,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H14000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: netitle,方正行楷_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//-----------------------OP-------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.24,0:00:46.33,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}指で弾くコイン見つめた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.45,0:00:54.05,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}表ならＧＯ、裏はstay。まず答えを聞かせて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.67,0:01:01.93,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}「どうか教えてくれませんか？」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.01,0:01:09.90,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}天使は見定める　笑顔のまま
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.11,0:01:17.69,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}迷え！その手を引く者などいない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.74,0:01:22.91,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}神が下す　その答えは不幸だった
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.95,0:01:28.28,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}そう　それこそ神からの贈り物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.29,0:01:35.59,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}乗りこえたら見えてくるさ　だから今すぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.75,0:01:38.13,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}No buts!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.24,0:00:46.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}注视着  从指间弹出的硬币
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.45,0:00:54.05,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}正面就走  反面就留  先把答案给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.67,0:01:01.93,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}「恳请告诉我吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.01,0:01:09.90,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}天使却以看透一切的微笑面对着我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.11,0:01:17.69,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}迷失吧  没人能够指引你的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.74,0:01:22.91,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}神灵宣布的答案  是如此不幸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.95,0:01:28.28,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是的  这就是神所赐予的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.29,0:01:35.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}只要撑过去就肯定能看到  所以趁现在马上
Comment: 0,0:00:00.02,0:00:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//-----------------------ED-------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.06,0:22:02.37,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}絡まった運命も変えて行けるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.67,0:22:08.97,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}総てはこの手の中に在る！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.85,0:22:25.64,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}誰にも負けない能力が身体に無いなら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.85,0:22:25.64,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(341,360)\fs10}チカラ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.85,0:22:25.64,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(405,360)\fs10}ココ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.96,0:22:31.33,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}幻想なんて壊してしまえばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.96,0:22:31.33,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(220,360)\fs10}イマジン
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.60,0:22:35.05,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}張り巡る回路再生
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.60,0:22:35.05,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(372,360)\fs10}システム
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.60,0:22:35.05,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(425,360)\fs10}バックアップ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.05,0:22:37.09,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}強制入力はO.K
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.05,0:22:37.09,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(345,360)\fs10}インストール
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.19,0:22:42.65,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}神さえも知り得ない  領域が開く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.19,0:22:42.65,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(425,360)\fs10}フィールド
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.12,0:22:48.50,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}10万の記憶も 一瞬の奇跡さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.12,0:22:48.50,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(300,360)\fs10}データ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.12,0:22:48.50,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(438,360)\fs10}ミラクル
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.65,0:22:54.14,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}推測不可能な“生きてる形”だから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.37,0:22:57.03,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}In a Magic∞world
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.05,0:22:59.41,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}exciting time or space
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.43,0:23:00.81,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}there's no limit!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:06.40,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}誰かを守れる能力がほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:06.40,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\pos(375,360)\fs10}チカラ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.66,0:23:13.94,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}絡まった運命も変えて行けるから
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.30,0:23:20.82,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}総てはこの手の中に在る！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.06,0:22:02.37,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}纠缠不清的命运也可以改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.67,0:22:08.97,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一切尽在这双手之中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.85,0:22:25.64,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}倘若那绝不会输的能力不在体内
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.96,0:22:31.33,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}幻想什么的就破坏掉算了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.60,0:22:36.94,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}布下的备份系统已经安装完成
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.19,0:22:42.65,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}连神明也无法知晓的领域  在此敞开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.12,0:22:48.50,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}10万的记忆  一瞬间的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.65,0:22:54.14,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}都是无法推测的「生命的形态」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:06.40,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}想得到守护他人的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.66,0:23:13.94,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}纠缠不清的命运也可以改变
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.30,0:23:20.82,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一切尽在这双手之中
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------TITLE----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.59,0:01:55.44,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(568,300)}{\fad(600,800)}追迹封锁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.59,0:01:55.44,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(568,274)}{\fad(600,600)\fs17}Route Disturb
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------TEXT----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.45,0:00:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园都市正沉浸在大霸星祭的喧嚣中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.06,0:00:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而在背后
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.24,0:00:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一场针对能将圣人一击必杀的灵装——刺突杭剑的交易正要展开
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.24,0:00:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(462,358)\fs21}Stab Sword
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.52,0:00:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送货人的名字是——欧丽安娜·汤姆森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.56,0:00:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偶然接触到了与描述极为相似的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.59,0:02:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.06,0:02:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这里现在正在追查欧丽安娜可能当做交易地点的地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.58,0:02:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土御门  我在和某个人握手的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.06,0:02:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻想杀手好像把什么破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.06,0:02:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(270,360)\fs21}Imagine Breaker
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.04,0:02:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么  我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.58,0:02:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人看起来有点不太像是学生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.21,0:02:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人有没有拿着什么大型的行李
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.12,0:02:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  拿着一块像看板一样的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.94,0:02:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上  你现在在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.60,0:02:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正在跟着那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.13,0:02:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把我的GPS代码发给你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.06,0:02:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那边自己查吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.55,0:02:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被发觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.33,0:03:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哪个  阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.75,0:03:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个穿着工作服的金发女人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.17,0:03:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个人是专家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.76,0:03:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说听说他们在街上没法出手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.78,0:03:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我还是想得太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.50,0:03:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得跟目前为止的行动模式不同喵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.90,0:03:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她改变想法了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.72,0:03:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴士整备场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.56,0:03:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是自律巴士的整备场
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.85,0:03:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.94,0:03:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快趴下  阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.64,0:03:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你出场的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.47,0:03:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.88,0:04:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是完美的团队合作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.54,0:04:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够这样彼此分担工作  真是便于行动
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.51,0:04:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小子…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.25,0:04:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我说你快去完成自己的任务
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.58,0:04:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我说给我慢着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.58,0:04:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史提尔  你在这里贴符文卡片然后待机喵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.19,0:04:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去抓送货人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.18,0:04:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.79,0:04:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  阿上你怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.03,0:04:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你待在这里比较安全
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.05,0:04:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.19,0:04:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得你留下来会比较安全
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.55,0:04:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是指你  而是指我的安全
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.01,0:04:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是用来争取时间的诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.16,0:04:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一一对付的话会让对方逃走的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.34,0:05:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使你这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.30,0:05:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.12,0:05:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.64,0:05:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  拜托了是指…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.30,0:05:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「追迹封锁」  欧丽安娜·汤姆森是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.30,0:05:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(233,360)\fs21}Route Disturb
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.49,0:06:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.43,0:06:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.34,0:06:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.53,0:06:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我才是要道歉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.62,0:06:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个术式是「理派四阵」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.07,0:06:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用这个术式就能搜索到欧丽安娜的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.51,0:06:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是使用魔术不是很危险吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.32,0:06:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要请人帮忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.58,0:06:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺着风  但非透过空气而于此地传达意志
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.58,0:06:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(194,360)\fs21}I I T I A W
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.58,0:06:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(388,360)\fs21}H   A   I   I   C   T   T   P   I   O   A
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.62,0:07:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「顺着风  但非透过空气而于此地传达意志」  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.62,0:07:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(164,360)\fs21}I I T I A W
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.62,0:07:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(362,360)\fs21}H   A   I   I   C   T   T   P   I   O   A
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.98,0:07:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史提尔！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.17,0:07:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.38,0:07:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去拍一下史提尔的身子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.54,0:07:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的…是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.81,0:07:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是某种防止逆探知的术式吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.29,0:07:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  没有那种术式的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.25,0:07:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕设置了对史提尔个人的魔力有反应的自动迎击术式
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.04,0:07:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.51,0:07:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说有这东西在  史提尔就没法对欧丽安娜用魔术了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.72,0:07:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  设下了麻烦的玩意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.62,0:08:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能凭一己之力就能将生命力的探索  解析…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.69,0:08:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆算  应用  迎击等一并达成
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.51,0:08:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是人称「追迹封锁」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.51,0:08:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(414,360)\fs21}Route Disturb
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.80,0:08:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追迹封锁？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.80,0:08:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(344,360)\fs21}Route Disturb
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.27,0:08:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧丽安娜·汤姆森的外号啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.48,0:08:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是总觉得这没人情味的作法  好像在哪里见过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.48,0:08:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不会吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.05,0:08:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算她是欧丽安娜  也应该不可能有那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.80,0:08:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  史提尔  我和你的想法一致
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.01,0:08:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.38,0:08:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.89,0:08:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙就不是魔术师了  而是魔导师了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.29,0:08:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是怎么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.77,0:08:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么玩意儿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.49,0:08:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要塞进有关魔术的相关知识
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.34,0:08:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些知识就能不经由术者的意志  作为单独魔法阵启动
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.05,0:08:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是魔道书的原典
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.86,0:08:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  根据情况制作魔道书那也太…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.94,0:08:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是原典  也应该只是草书吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.45,0:08:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有原典的效果  不久就会毁坏的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.09,0:09:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是「速记原典」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.09,0:09:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(373,360)\fs21}Short Hand
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.89,0:09:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么究竟该怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.43,0:09:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先要把自动迎击术式破坏掉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.00,0:09:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让史提尔可以再次使用魔术
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.83,0:09:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要是在破坏的过程中  目标跑到探索范围以外了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.63,0:09:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是她有逃出去的自信的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.03,0:09:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得她还会特意搞一个迎击术式吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.60,0:09:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史提尔  什么魔术都好  随便用一个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.62,0:09:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「占术圆阵」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.47,0:09:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是还没有任何人的魔力通过的未使用魔法阵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.46,0:09:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它能对迎击魔术的魔力有所反应而起动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.92,0:09:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆算魔力源头的方向和距离
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.76,0:09:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么接下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.14,0:09:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  土御门
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.96,0:09:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用这个的话  史提尔就要再一次…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.90,0:09:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.50,0:09:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说过这样的话了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.46,0:09:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不能找出「速记原典」的地点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.46,0:09:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(384,360)\fs21}Short Hand
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.74,0:09:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要不停地试下去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.10,0:09:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.26,0:09:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.19,0:10:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像忘了一件事  我来好好告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.39,0:10:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是场性命攸关的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.92,0:10:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国家或世界可能因其结果而倾覆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.27,0:10:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就这么办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.66,0:10:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.78,0:10:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装熟人  上条当麻
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.06,0:10:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这样就能解决一切问题  那就没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.25,0:10:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相对的  无论发生什么都要找到迎击术式的所在地
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.47,0:10:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.66,0:10:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保茵蒂克丝在学园都市里的生活  这就是你的条件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.38,0:10:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上条当麻  我对你现在在这个地方很有意见
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.11,0:10:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不在那个孩子身边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.72,0:10:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是因为这个让那个孩子不开心了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.15,0:10:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就全部是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.20,0:11:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得换好衣服  想让当麻瞧瞧的说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.04,0:11:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就随便跑到其它地方去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.39,0:11:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小修女  不要这么沮丧嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.43,0:11:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小上条肯定有什么难言之隐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.91,0:11:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上条当麻那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.96,0:11:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微没注意  人就不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.49,0:11:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.84,0:11:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.43,0:11:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小吹寄
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.05,0:11:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在大庭广众下干些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.69,0:11:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是轻微的精神错乱的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.77,0:11:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就使用辣椒粉等刺激物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.06,0:11:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把思考转移到表层…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.24,0:11:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.61,0:11:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.90,0:11:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没事  小吹寄
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.67,0:11:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.36,0:11:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当麻他…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.31,0:11:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当麻他到底去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.96,0:12:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.24,0:12:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,占术圆阵有反应了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.83,0:12:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  阿上  你有地图喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.37,0:12:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  手机上有GPS地图啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.98,0:12:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我自己来…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.66,0:12:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土御门！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.06,0:12:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么能那么冷淡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.27,0:12:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为史提尔是为了谁受的伤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.06,0:12:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.48,0:12:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是专业的魔术师
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.70,0:12:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该有做好应付术式攻击的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.87,0:12:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土御门…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.12,0:12:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.50,0:12:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,占术圆阵能对散发在空中的术式的魔力产生反应
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.26,0:12:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从而找出距离与方向
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.98,0:12:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么方便的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.40,0:12:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能不用魔力就能发动得起来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.14,0:12:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我能够更好地使用魔术
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.22,0:12:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史提尔也不至于变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.95,0:12:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我承认  所以随你怎么怨恨我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.58,0:12:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我一定会把速记原典找出来破坏掉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.58,0:12:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(367,360)\fs21}Short Hand
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.08,0:13:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再把欧丽安娜抓住
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.46,0:13:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一定会亲手粉碎这次刺突杭剑的交易
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.46,0:13:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(437,360)\fs21}Stab Sword
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.42,0:13:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上  给我地图
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.61,0:13:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道西北三百零二米处都有些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.98,0:13:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速记原典一定在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.98,0:13:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(297,360)\fs21}Short Hand
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.17,0:13:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.35,0:13:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是初中？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.36,0:13:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs21\fad(100,100)}离初中丢球比赛开始还有十分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.93,0:13:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是赛场啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.58,0:13:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开始已经没多少时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.29,0:13:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看客和摄像机都已经到了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.21,0:13:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不能悄无声息地行动了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.97,0:13:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么办啊  也不能就这样放着不管吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.53,0:13:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能假装成选手混进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.89,0:13:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当真想这么干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.43,0:13:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是高中生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.25,0:13:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混进初中生里面也太强人所…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.24,0:13:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.61,0:13:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那招迎击术式
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.33,0:13:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有向其他人攻击的危险
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.21,0:14:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道什么是世界上最简单的魔术仪式吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.22,0:14:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是触摸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.26,0:14:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是不懂魔术的普通人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.32,0:14:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过触摸  也有发动迎击术式的可能
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.11,0:14:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.09,0:14:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有作为魔术师的防御力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.47,0:14:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会非常危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.94,0:14:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.24,0:14:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在出现受害者之前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.58,0:14:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要把迎击术式解决掉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.58,0:14:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.62,0:14:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.04,0:14:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.48,0:14:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.41,0:14:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们接下来要比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.62,0:14:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这副打扮出场果然是不行的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.35,0:14:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,况且还有录像
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.48,0:14:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是服了你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.16,0:14:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有能换的运动服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.18,0:14:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  是有的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.45,0:14:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在活动室里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.31,0:14:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.35,0:14:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那快点去换衣服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.73,0:15:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是规定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.19,0:15:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我确认一下ID吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.74,0:15:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土御…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.29,0:15:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.35,0:15:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我按…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.21,0:15:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.20,0:15:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能把手擦干净再按啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.77,0:15:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.89,0:15:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.70,0:15:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中途参加可是不允许的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.55,0:15:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.59,0:15:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.27,0:15:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这身打扮混进比赛有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.33,0:15:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.26,0:15:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正常情况保健室里是有能换的衣服的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.95,0:15:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来的比赛是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.60,0:15:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南川中学选拔出来的两百人对阵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.84,0:15:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常盘台中学选拔出来的二十人的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.18,0:15:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢球比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.52,0:15:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们身上散发出失败的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.78,0:16:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭死了臭死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.94,0:16:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.01,0:16:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那里干什么啊  嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.92,0:16:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？  常盘台中学？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.69,0:16:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里有很多很可怕的能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.22,0:16:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.23,0:16:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  要注意流弹哦  阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.10,0:16:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这里布置有速记原典
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.10,0:16:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(427,360)\fs21}Short Hand
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.14,0:16:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.98,0:16:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是那些篮子很可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.62,0:16:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该有从外面借来的篮子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.05,0:16:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在搬进这里之前就能够进行术式设置
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.06,0:16:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会对球篮进行逐一调查
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.13,0:16:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于阿上你  在找到速记原典后就是你的工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.13,0:16:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(358,360)\fs21}Short Hand
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.66,0:16:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各就各位
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.30,0:16:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预备
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.52,0:16:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.60,0:16:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别退缩  要冲进去了阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.26,0:17:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土御门
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.72,0:17:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这根  阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.40,0:17:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去下一根
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.51,0:17:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上  这根也不对
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.34,0:17:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.90,0:17:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上  踩到我的背上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.27,0:17:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.44,0:18:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.67,0:18:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么想让我…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.47,0:18:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承担惩罚游戏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.93,0:18:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.41,0:18:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你遇到危险的话就没意义了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.43,0:18:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御坂！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.63,0:18:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着御坂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.27,0:18:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.01,0:18:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了御坂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.61,0:18:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理由待会我会详细说明
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.53,0:18:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以快点离开那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.20,0:18:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？  你突然说些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.63,0:18:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  为什么你会在这种地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.79,0:19:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我详细解释一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.61,0:19:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.40,0:19:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御坂  什么也别说快到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.83,0:19:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.47,0:19:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是傻子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.34,0:19:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便没有你救我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.31,0:19:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.16,0:19:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  你要对我说些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.64,0:19:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说了待会儿再说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.37,0:19:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.10,0:19:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想你受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.15,0:19:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是笨蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.19,0:19:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种程度的比赛里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.01,0:19:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不着这么担心我的安危…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.07,0:19:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  别突然说那么奇怪的事情吓唬别人好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.58,0:19:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.50,0:20:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说话  不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.88,0:20:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.96,0:20:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.99,0:20:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.96,0:20:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么难受吗  御坂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.03,0:20:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是发烧…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.67,0:20:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事也没有啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.99,0:20:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土御门
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.30,0:20:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的球篮…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.49,0:20:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.84,0:20:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上条当麻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.41,0:20:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里干些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.62,0:20:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才还慌慌张张地跑了  怎么又会在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.28,0:20:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.26,0:20:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛重新开始
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.64,0:20:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹寄！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.82,0:20:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.04,0:20:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.89,0:20:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去拍一下吹寄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.09,0:20:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是魔术师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.69,0:20:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去身体会受不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.66,0:21:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹寄  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.15,0:21:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹寄
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.16,0:21:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.62,0:21:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧丽安娜·汤姆森
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.77,0:21:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这是你的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.00,0:21:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不但让无辜的人卷进来还丝毫没有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.50,0:21:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那可笑的幻想
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.57,0:21:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由我这只手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.06,0:21:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉碎到瓦砾无存
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.50,0:23:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹寄倒下了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.85,0:23:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史提尔  还有土御门
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.07,0:23:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这场争端的原因是刺突杭剑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.07,0:23:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(462,360)\fs21}Stab Sword
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.10,0:23:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就一定要毁掉它
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.63,0:23:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一集  速记原典
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.63,0:23:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(389,360)\fs21}Short Hand
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.33,0:23:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科学与魔术交织之时  故事便拉开序幕


