Jinwoo, you've changed a lot.
Yet, I remain the same.
So much has happened to me.
Everyone benefits differently
from their experiences.
That's true.
As a hunter, I seem to be too timid.
Although I've tried to overcome it,
it's too hard.
Logically, I should be taking part
in A-rank or B-rank,
or at least C-rank missions.
Yet, I've always chosen D-rank
or E-rank ones.
That's why I got to know you.
Looking back, it seems like
I was always treating you.
Honestly, when you kept
getting injured at the beginning,
I found you a bit annoying.
But Jinwoo, you have always survived.
Your eyes are brimming with life,
and I'll never forget them.
We agreed to have a meal together, right?
Here. Take it back.
Are you…
Actually, I've decided to retire.
I plan to go back to my hometown.
If you happen to come nearby,
please let me know.
I'll take you out to enjoy the view.
We'll have a meal together then.
Okay.
I don't think you at E-rank
can defeat Kang Taeshik at B-rank.
I don't want to suspect again
that you had a second awakening.
But I still want to tell you,
if you want to live longer,
be more careful.
What do you mean?
In the annihilation incident
of Hwang Dongsuk's team,
the only survivors were you
and a D-rank hunter.
Hwang Dongsuk's brother,
Hunter Hwang Dongsoo,
may have already set his sights on you.
S-rank Hunter Hwang Dongsoo
has set his sights on me?
Yes.
What happened in the dungeon
isn't important.
The fact is Hwang Dongsuk died
and you came back alive.
He is an S-rank hunter.
The law cannot restrain him.
The existence of S-rank hunters is
both a miracle and a disaster.
The monster that even monsters fear
will very likely come after you.
That's it.
If possible,
I think you'd better leave
this country with your family.
I have another reason to become stronger.
I must become stronger.
Only then can I survive.
Um…
Jinho.
Why are these people here?
Them?
Isn't that obvious?
They are members of our team.
Those hunters who are unable
to work for some reason
and those living in poverty
are my priority targets.
The injured and drunkards.
That's more convenient for us.
We need at least eight members
to enter a C-rank gate.
Hey, why is there a kid?
Awakened minors can also participate.
It's not illegal.
Hey.
You're being quite rude.
I am a real hunter.
But you're a high-schooler, right?
Were you ever on a raid mission?
Er… I haven't.
Are you an E-rank hunter?
So what?
Never mind.
You're just waiting outside anyway.
Only Jinho and I will enter the dungeon.
Um… Is it really just you two going in?
We get three million
just by waiting outside?
Yes.
Three million for one raid mission.
You get money
without having to fight, isn't it nice?
But this must be kept secret.
If I find out you didn't,
you'll be charged ten times
the reward as per the contract.
The stealth rune stone I got
after defeating Kang Taeshik.
I'll try it now.
Good. Looks like I've learned it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's with that kit?
This is an enhanced armor set
made in Italy.
After all, only the two of us
are going into the dungeon.
I have to make some preparations.
Take my advice and get it off.
Yes.
Jinwoo.
Can you pull me up?
Let's set off then.
I'm starting to feel a bit nervous.
You haven't taken
that thing off your head.
At least let me wear a helmet.
All right.
Let's go.
Yes.
They're really going in by themselves.
Will they be okay?
We've already warned them.
We've already got the money,
so just leave them alone.
A D-rank hunter and an E-rank hunter
want to tackle a C-rank raid mission?
Two greenhorns.
It's not as easy as they think.
Did Song-Yi skip class?
How long has it been?
About an hour.
Even a regular team
would take more than two hours.
It won't be that…
You managed to escape?
Lucky for you.
No. They didn't escape.
The gate is closing.
No way.
Did they defeat the boss?
Where's the next gate?
It takes an hour to get there.
Understood, let's go.
Everyone, we are leaving.
We have three places to go today.
You can earn nine million in just one day.
Don't you want to go?
These two…
Who are they?
Jinwoo, I'm all done.
Understood.
I'll take care of it.
I'm heading out.
You're going to work today too?
Yeah, can you lock the door?
He even has such a skill.
He seems to have gotten even stronger.
Skill, Stealth.
Although the process of obtaining this
was unpleasant, this skill is very useful.
Using Stealth in fights is very efficient.
The skill level of Dash has increased?
New skills.
Advanced Dagger Wielding and Fatal Strike.
Great skills too.
You've worked hard, Jinwoo.
I'm almost done collecting.
You take a rest first.
Thanks.
I have more interesting skills now.
But no matter which skill,
it's limited by its duration,
which means I don't have enough mana.
It seems I also need
to increase my intelligence.
All right.
It's going well, but should I head
straight to the Demon's Castle?
No.
My current strength should be
above B-rank and below A-rank.
Am I capable of challenging that dungeon?
"The player has reached
the required level."
"A job-change quest"?
Please take a look at this,
Chief Ahn.
What's up, Kichul?
This is the bidding document
for a C-rank gate.
One hundred fifty million?!
Someone spent 150 million
to conquer a C-rank gate?
Yes.
There has been a raid team
that bid double the market price
for every C-rank gate lately.
Their Captain is… "Yoo Jinho"?
I've never heard of this person.
He is the second son
of Yoojin Construction's chairman.
Yoojin Construction?
He might cause his company to lose money.
Even if it's a rich kid having fun,
he's gone too far.
"Sung Jinwoo, E-rank"?
Yes.
Their members are also
put together temporarily.
I have no idea what they're trying to do.
No.
The name Sung Jinwoo also appeared
in the double dungeon incident.
There's something fishy.
There definitely is.
-Hey, wait.
-I won.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
No, it's okay.
You came back earlier than expected.
Collecting mana crystals
took longer than I thought.
All right, let's go.
You must be tired too.
Do you want me to drive?
I'm getting restless from boredom.
At least let me do something.
I see.
What?
-Nothing.
-We agreed for you to wait outside.
You don't need to do anything more.
What? Hunter Sung Jinwoo
is a second awakener?
Yes, that's right.
Do you have any proof?
Hunter Sung has had three major incidents,
yet he came out alive every time.
The first was the double dungeon incident.
The second was the annihilation incident
of the Hwang Dongsuk's team.
The third was the incident
of prisoners being killed
by the Surveillance Team hunter.
Nearly all participants
in these events died.
Yet he survived.
If he's not a second awakener,
there's no way to explain this.
That… is true.
By the way, Chief Ahn, where are we going?
Where else?
To scout for new talent.
What's this?
It's like they're having a picnic.
Mister,
this area is currently off-limits.
Ah, sorry about that.
I was just curious because it looked like
hunters were gathering here.
That's a gate, right?
Are you sure it's okay to stand so close?
Please don't treat me like a child.
I am a hunter too.
Eh? Then…
Are you also with this team?
Yes.
But…
Hunter Sung…
He went in without the rest of the team.
If I'm not mistaken,
he must be a rare strong one.
No, a super strong one.
I see.
I apologize for disturbing you.
Please be careful.
Eh? Are we leaving, Chief?
The captain is coming out.
Everyone, prepare to leave.
Do you have any tasks
scheduled for tomorrow?
I'm busy tomorrow.
Should we take a day off?
Ah… tomorrow?
I do have a gate reserved.
Should I cancel it?
Don't cancel if you've reserved it.
That'd be a waste of money.
I can keep it for two days.
Then keep it for now.
I understand.
Thank you for waiting.
All right, let's head to the next one.
That dream again?
The day is approaching.
Well, thank you, everyone.
Excuse me for intruding, Hunter Sung.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ahn Sangmin from White Tiger Guild's
second management division.
May we have a chat with you?
I believe I don't need
to elaborate further.
Our White Tiger Guild
is one of the best in the country.
So we are always looking
for outstanding talents.
Let me get straight to the point.
We can offer you twice as much money
as Yoojin Construction can offer,
if you join our White Tiger Guild.
If you have any conditions,
I will do my best to satisfy them.
How's that?
For someone who was
an E-rank hunter not long ago,
this must be a chance you can't refuse.
I will make you say yes.
How much is the market value
of White Tiger Guild's building?
What?
Well… it's probably worth
around 50 billion.
So, do you plan to give me
the entire building?
I don't quite understand.
Thirty billion?!
Did you hear that?
The terms offered to me
by Yoojin Construction is a building
with a market value of 30 billion.
You said you would pay me double.
I thought you were going to give me
that 50-billion building.
If you don't believe me,
I can prove it here.
But…
Such a large amount
is beyond my authority.
I need to discuss it with my superiors.
Then this is the end of the topic.
Was I too hasty?
I should have investigated the terms
offered by Yoojin Construction first.
Right, by the way,
how did you know about me?
Have you been
secretly investigating me?
Huh? Where is he?
Th-This is…a Stealth skill.
So he is a second awakener
with a Stealth skill.
No wonder Yoojin Construction
offered him such a large sum.
I-I apologize for investigating you
without permission.
But I meant no malice.
Don't look back.
Because someone is
monopolizing the dungeons,
it prevents us from training
our newcomers.
According to company regulations,
they can't be deployed without training.
To negotiate the deal regarding gates,
we found you when we investigated
the person who was buying up dungeons.
Besides you, how many others
know about me?
Just me and one of my subordinates.
I don't want anyone to know about me.
If rumors about me spread,
you will be the first person I suspect.
I have an obligation
to report to the guild.
But I don't want to die.
I will also keep my subordinate silent.
Thank you.
It seems our monopoly of C-rank gates
has caused you some trouble.
I apologize, but this situation
will continue for a while.
That's going to be difficult.
In that case, we will be unable
to train newcomers.
Then, would you like
to make a deal with me?
A deal?
I can sell you three C-rank gates
we have reserved.
If you don't take it, you can't get access
to a C-rank dungeon for a while.
He is using hunger marketing
to lure me in.
But…
I understand.
How much are they?
Three hundred million for each.
Th-Three hundred million?!
The mana crystals and magic gems
in a C-rank dungeon
are worth at most 200 million.
I hope the price can be lowered
to 200 million--
Okay.
Deal.
Then…
You will give us three gates, right?
Yes, three C-rank gates.
Six hundred million in total.
Then it's settled.
Please transfer the money
into this account today.
And another thing, I have a gift for you.
Can you close your eyes
and open your mouth?
Don't worry. I won't hurt you.
Really? My wound has healed!
Goodbye.
Since you have shown me these abilities,
can I take it that
I have earned your trust?
On the condition that you keep my secret.
Chief.
How did it go?
Hey, Kichul.
He might be stronger than we imagine.
Jinwoo, I've received the money.
Six hundred million
has been transferred to me.
How did you sell the gates we
planned to cancel for such a high price?
Who did you sell them to?
That's a trade secret.
What?
There are still C-rank gates left
in our area?
Yes, Yoojin Construction only bid
on those three gates.
Current bidding prices
are all below 70 million.
We've been tricked.
Not only did I fail to poach him,
I even got tricked.
What a disgrace.
Is this how the strong are?
A message.
Who sent it?
This is Sung Jinwoo.
With this, we're even.
I'll forget the fact that you spied on me.
I see. He tricked me.
I admit defeat this time.
He is not to be underestimated.
Was it from Hunter Sung?
Yes.
Although he tricked me this time,
I managed to get his phone number.
I'll compromise this time.
A job-change quest…
How exciting.